FROM:MR. JAMES NGOLA. CONFIDENTIAL TEL: 233-27-587908. E-MAIL: (james_ngola2002@maktoob.com). URGENT BUSINESS ASSISTANCE AND PARTNERSHIP. DEAR FRIEND, I AM ( DR.) JAMES NGOLA, THE PERSONAL ASSISTANCE TO THE LATE CONGOLESE (PRESIDENT LAURENT KABILA) WHO WAS ASSASSINATED BY HIS BODY GUARD ON 16TH JAN. 2001. THE INCIDENT OCCURRED IN OUR PRESENCE WHILE WE WERE HOLDING MEETING WITH HIS EXCELLENCY OVER THE FINANCIAL RETURNS FROM THE DIAMOND SALES IN THE AREAS CONTROLLED BY (D.R.C.) DEMOCRATIC REPUBLIC OF CONGO FORCES AND THEIR FOREIGN ALLIES ANGOLA AND ZIMBABWE, HAVING RECEIVED THE PREVIOUS DAY (USD$100M) ONE HUNDRED MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS, CASH IN THREE DIPLOMATIC BOXES ROUTED THROUGH ZIMBABWE. MY PURPOSE OF WRITING YOU THIS LETTER IS TO SOLICIT FOR YOUR ASSISTANCE AS TO BE A COVER TO THE FUND AND ALSO COLLABORATION IN MOVING THE SAID FUND INTO YOUR BANK ACCOUNT THE SUM OF (USD$25M) TWENTY FIVE MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS ONLY, WHICH I DEPOSITED WITH A SECURITY COMPANY IN GHANA, IN A DIPLOMATIC BOX AS GOLDS WORTH (USD$25M) TWENTY FIVE MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS ONLY FOR SAFE KEEPING IN A SECURITY VAULT FOR ANY FURTHER INVESTMENT PERHAPS IN YOUR COUNTRY. YOU WERE INTRODUCED TO ME BY A RELIABLE FRIEND OF MINE WHO IS A TRAVELLER,AND ALSO A MEMBER OF CHAMBER OF COMMERCE AS A RELIABLE AND TRUSTWORTHY PERSON WHOM I CAN RELY ON AS FOREIGN PARTNER, EVEN THOUGH THE NATURE OF THE TRANSACTION WAS NOT REVEALED TO HIM FOR SECURITY REASONS. THE (USD$25M) WAS PART OF A PROCEEDS FROM DIAMOND TRADE MEANT FOR THE LATE PRESIDENT LAURENT KABILA WHICH WAS DELIVERED THROUGH ZIMBABWE IN DIPLOMATIC BOXES. THE BOXES WERE KEPT UNDER MY CUSTODY BEFORE THE SAD EVENT THAT TOOK THE LIFE OF (MR. PRESIDENT).THE CONFUSION THAT ENSUED AFTER THE ASSASSINATION AND THE SPORADIC SHOOTING AMONG THE FACTIONS, I HAVE TO RUN AWAY FROM THE COUNTRY FOR MY DEAR LIFE AS I AM NOT A SOLDIER BUT A CIVIL SERVANT I CROSSED RIVER CONGO TO OTHER SIDE OF CONGO LIBREVILLE FROM THERE I MOVED TO THE THIRD COUNTRY GHANA WHERE I AM PRESENTLY TAKING REFUGE. AS A MATTER OF FACT, WHAT I URGENTLY NEEDED FROM YOU IS YOUR ASSISTANCE IN MOVING THIS MONEY INTO YOUR ACCOUNT IN YOUR COUNTRY FOR INVESTMENT WITHOUT RAISING EYEBROW. FOR YOUR ASSISTANCE I WILL GIVE YOU 20% OF THE TOTAL SUM AS YOUR OWN SHARE WHEN THE MONEY GETS TO YOUR ACCOUNT, WHILE 75% WILL BE FOR ME, OF WHICH WITH YOUR KIND ADVICE I HOPE TO INVEST IN PROFITABLE VENTURE IN YOUR COUNTRY IN OTHER TO SETTLE DOWN FOR MEANINGFUL LIFE, AS I AM TIRED OF LIVING IN A WAR ENVIRONMENT. THE REMAINING 5% WILL BE USED TO OFFSET ANY COST INCURRED IN THE CAUSE OF MOVING THE MONEY TO YOUR ACCOUNT. IF THE PROPOSAL IS ACCEPTABLE TO YOU PLEASE CONTACT ME IMMEDIATELY THROUGH THE ABOVE TELEPHONE AND E-MAIL, TO ENABLE ME ARRANGE FACE TO FACE MEETING WITH YOU IN GHANA FOR THE CLEARANCE OF THE FUNDS BEFORE TRANSFRING IT TO YOUR BANK ACCOUNT AS SEEING IS BELIEVING. FINALLY, IT IS IMPORTANT ALSO THAT I LET YOU UNDERSTAND THAT THERE IS NO RISK INVOLVED WHATSOEVER AS THE MONEY HAD NO RECORD IN KINSHASA FOR IT WAS MEANT FOR THE PERSONAL USE OF (MR. PRESIDEND ) BEFORE THE NEFARIOUS INCIDENT OCCURRED, AND ALSO I HAVE ALL THE NECESSARY DOCUMENTS AS REGARDS TO THE FUNDS INCLUDING THE (CERTIFICATE OF DEPOSIT), AS I AM THE DEPOSITOR OF THE CONSIGNMENT. LOOKING FORWARD TO YOUR URGENT RESPONSE. YOUR SINCERELY, MR. JAMES NGOLA.

FROM HIS ROYAL MAJESTY (HRM) CROWN RULER OF ELEME KINGDOM CHIEF DANIEL ELEME, PHD, EZE 1 OF ELEME.E-MAIL ADDRESS:obong_715@epatra.com ATTENTION:PRESIDENT,CEO Sir/ Madam. This letter might surprise you because we have met neither in person nor by correspondence. But I believe it is one day that you got to know somebody either in physical or through correspondence. I got your contact through discreet inquiry from the chambers of commerce and industry of your country on the net, you and your organization were revealed as being quite astute in private entrepreneurship, one has no doubt in your ability to handle a financialbusiness transaction. However, I am the first son of His Royal majesty,Obong.D. Eleme , and the traditional Ruler of Eleme Province in the oil producing area of River State of Nigeria. I am making this contact to you in respect of US$60,000,000.00 (Sixty Million United State Dollars), which I inherited, from my latefather. This money was accumulated from royalties paid to my father as compensation by the oil firms located in our area as a result of oil presence on our land, which hamper agriculture, which is our major source oflivelihood. Unfortunately my father died from protracted diabetes.But before his death he called my attention and informed me that he lodged some funds on a two boxes with a security firm with an open beneficiary status. The lodgment security code number was also revealed to me, he then advised me to look for a reliable business partner abroad, that will assist me in investing the money in a lucrative business as a result of economic instability in Nigeria. So this is the main reason why I am contacting you for us to move this money from the security firm to any Country of your choice for investment purpose. So I will like you to be the ultimate beneficiary, so that the funds can be moved in your name and particulars to any Country of your choice where it will be claimed and invested. Hence my father have had intimated the security firm personnel that the beneficiary of the box is his foreign partner whose particulars will be forwarded to the firm when due. But I will guide you Accordingly. As soon as the funds reach, I will then come over to meet you in person, so that we can discuss physically on investment potentials. Based on this assistance my Family and I have unanimously decided to give you 30% of the total money, 5% for Charity home, 10% for expenses, which may arise during this transaction, Fax and phone bills inclusive. The balance of 55% you will invest andmanaged for my Family. I hereby guarantee you that this is not government money, it is not drug money and it is not money from arms deal. Though you have to maintain high degree of confidentiality on this matter. I will give more details about the proceedings of this transaction as soon as I receive your favorable reply. Please reply to my Email Address:obong_715@epatra.com I hope this will be the beginning of a prosperous relationship between my family and your family. Nevertheless if you are for any reason not interested, kindly inform me immediately so that I will look foranother contact. I am waiting for your quick response. Yours faithfully, Prince Obong Eleme

ATTENTION: PRESIDENT/MANAGING DIRECTOR Dear Sir/Madam, Request for Urgent Business Relationship We are Top Officials of the Federal Government of Nigeria Contract Review Panel who are interested in importation of goods into our country and investing abroad with funds which are presently trapped in Nigeria. In order to commence this business we solicit your assistance, knowledge and expertise to enable us recieve the said trapped funds abroad, for the subsequent purchase and inventory of the goods to be Imported and the investment abroad. The source of this fund is as follows: During the previous military regimes in our country, government officials set up companies and awarded themselves contracts which were grossly over-invoiced in various ministries. The new civilian government now setup a contract review panel which i and my colleagues are members and we have identified a lot of inflated sum, due to our position as civil servants and members of this panel, we cannot aquire this money in our names. I have therefore, been delegated as a matter of trust by my colleagues of the panel to look for an oversea partner into whose account the sum of us$31,000 000,00 (thirty-one million united states dollars) will be Paid by telegraphic transfer. Hence we are writting you this letter. We have agreed to share the money thus: 1. 70% for us (the officials) 2. 20% for the foreign patner(you) 3. 10% to be used in settling taxation and local and Foreign expenses. It is this 70% that we wish to commence the importation business and the investment abroad. Please note that this transaction is 100% safe and we hope that the funds can arrive your account in latest ten(10) banking days from the date of reciept of the following information.A suitable company name and bank account(company or personel) into which the funds can be paid. The above information will enable us write letters of claim and job description respectively. This way we will use your company's name to apply for payments and re-award the contract to your company name. We are looking foward to doing business with you and solicit your confidentiality in this transaction. Please acknowledge reciept of this letter using this e-mail address. davidkuta2002@yahoo.com I await your urgent response. NOTE: ALL CORRESPONDENCE SHOULD BE CONFIDENTIAL. Best Regards, David Kuta

CHALLENGE SECURITIES LTD. LAGOS, NIGERIA ATTENTION:MADAM/SIR I am MR.USMAN ABACHA , the Director of Operations CHALLENGE SECURITIES LTD,LAGOS NIGERIA. Here in NIGERIA Our firm is a security company of high repute with years of outstanding service to the people of Africa. I have resolved to contact you through this medium based on business proposal that will be of mutual benefit to both of us. I got your particulars through a consultant company base on my research for a trustworthy and established person that understands investment ethic for entering into a life time profitable joint partnership investment and also co-operation with confidence and trust that you will keep the contents secret and divulged to any third party. To be explicit and straight to the point. Some time early 1997, a reputable client of ours deposited a consignment in our company's vault for safe keeping. And since then our client has failed to come forward to claim his consignment, which has accumulated a considerable amount of money in demurrage. Consequently, in our bide to contact this client to redeem the demurrage which his consignment had accumulated we discovered that our client was the former president of the Federal Republic of Zaire, who died of illness after he was de-throwed in the same year the consignment was entrusted into our care. Since the death of our client President Mobutou Seseseko, none of his benefactors has come forward to claim the consignment with us, which means that non of his relatives or aids had any knowledge of this consignment. Hence out of curiosity I decided to secretly open the two boxes that our client deposited in our vault. And to my surprise I discovered that the two boxes that were registered as treasurer by our client actually contained a considerable amount of money in United States Dollars amounting to about US$30 million Dollar. Since this development I have been nursing plans secretly. I also found out from enquiries and the foreign media that our late client siphoned a lot of money from his country while he was in office as head of state. It is my conviction that the consignment in our vault was part of the money that our client siphoned and now that he is dead there is no race to this money in our care. I am now soliciting your noble assistance to assist me in transferring this money out of nigeria to your country for immediate investment with your assistance. I have also decided that you will generously be entitled to 30% of the total amount. Upon my receipt of your reply confirming your willingness to assist me of this transaction, I will immediately arrange and transfer all the rights of ownership of this consignment to your name to facilitate your easy clearance and transfer of the complete funds to your country. you have nothing to worry about, as I will be there to assist you in anyway necessary with all proper documentation. This transaction is 100% risk free. Please maintain absolute confidentiality on this matter. Thanks. Yours faithfully. MR. USMAN ABDUL

FROM: MR TEMI JOHNSON DEMOCRATIC REPUBLIC OF CONGO. TEL:44 7775770781 EMAIL:temijohnson@rediffmail.com Dear Sir, SEEKING YOUR IMMEDIATE ASSISTANCE. Please Permit me to make your acquaintance in so informal a manner. This is necessitated by my urgent need to reach a dependable and trust wordy foreign partner. This request may seem strange and unsolicited but I will crave your indulgence and pray that you view it seriously. My name is MR TEMI JOHNSON of the Democratic Republic of Congo and One of the close aides to the former President of the Democratic Republic of Congo LAURENT KABILA of blessed memory, may his soul rest in peace. Due to the military campaign of LAURENT KABILA to force out the rebels in my country, I and some of my colleagues were instructed by Late President Kabila to go abroad to purchase arms and ammunition worth of Twenty Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars only (US$20,500,000.00) to fight the rebel group. But when President Kabila was killed in a bloody shoot-out by one of his aide a day before we were schedule to travel out of Congo, We immediately decided to divert the fund into a private security company here in Congo for safe keeping. The security of the said amount is presently being threatened here following the arrest and seizure of properties of Col. Rasheidi Karesava (One of the aides to Laurent Kabila) a tribesman, and some other Military Personnel from our same tribe, by the new President of the Democratic Republic of Congo, the son of late President Laurent Kabila, Joseph Kabila. In view of this, we need a reliable and trustworthy foreign partner who can assist us to move this money out of my country as the beneficiary. WE have sufficient ''CONTACTS'' to move the fund under Diplomatic Cover to a security company in the europe in your name. This is to ensure that the Diplomatic Baggage is marked ''CONFIDENTIAL'' and it will not pass through normal custom/airport screening and clearance. Our inability to move this money out of Congo all This while lies on our lack of trust on our supposed good friends (western countries) who suddenly became hostile to those of us who worked with the late President Kabila, immediately after his son took office. Though we have neither seen nor met each other, the information We gathered from an associate who has worked in your country has encouraged and convinced us that with your sincere assistance, this transaction will be properly handled with modesty and honesty to a huge success within two weeks. The said money is a state fund and therefore requires a total confidentiality. Thus, if you are willing to assist us move this fund out of Congo, you can contact me through my email address above with your telephone, fax number and personal information to enable us discuss the modalities and what will be your share (percentage) for assisting us. I must use this opportunity and medium to implore You to exercise the utmost indulgence to keep this Matter extraordinarily confidential, Whatever your Decision, while I await your prompt response. Thank you and GodBless. Best Regards MR TEMI JOHNSON

FROM THE DESK OF DR.SAM JORDAN THE MANAGER Headquarter, First Bank of Nigeria Plc. Lagos, Nigeria. Alternative E-mail: sam01jordan@yahoo.com Sir, Compliment of the day and how is life general with you? Of course it is my humble wish to solicit and crave your indulgence to make this project request for a joint business transaction which I hope will not come to you as a surprise, hence I plead for your pardon. I am Dr.Sam Jordan, the Manager of headquarter First Bank of Nigeria Plc. Lagos. I have an urgent and confidentialbusiness proposal for you. On June 6, 1998, an Italian oil consultant/contractor with via National Petroleum cooperation (NNPC) Mr. Paul Bush made a numbered time (fixed) deposit for twelve calenderer month valued at US$43.7,000.00 in my branch. On maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarded address but got no reply after months we send a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employee (Nigeria national petroleum Corporation) that Mr. Paul Bush died from an automobile accident. On further investigation, it was clear that he died without making a will. All attempts by the Australian to trace his next of kin were fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr. Paul Bush did not declare any next of kin or relations in all his official documents including his deposit document in my bank. The total sum US$43.7,000,000.00 is still in my bank as dormant acct. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Nigerian banking law, after five years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Nigerian Government. If the account owner is certified death and nobody comes forward to claim it. This is the situation , and my proposal is that I am looking for a foreigner who will stand in as the beneficiary/next of kin. This is simple. All you have to do is to immediately send me the details of a bank account anywhere in the world for me to arrange the proper money transfer document. The money will then be transferred into the account for us to share in the ration of 60% for me 30% for you while the remaining 10% will be set aside for expenses incurred with here and there. There is no risk involved. I am using my position and connection in the bank here to do all the document work for the transaction. We shall employ the services of an attorney to draft the will and obtain all necessary documents and letter of administration in your fovour for the transfer. This transaction is risk free guaranteed. If you are interested, please reply immediately confidentiality and be rest assured that this transaction could be most profitable for both of us. Please do not expose this deal if you are not interested because if you do, it will take me out of seat.Please expenses is involve in this business,phone/fax number,and your bank particulars. I am awaiting your urgent reply. Best regards, Dr.Sam Jordan.

FROM: COL. MICHAEL BUNDU. DEMOCRATIC REPUBLIC OF CONGO. Tel No: Your country Intl. access code + 8821652098236 email : mikebundu@rediffmail.com Dear Sir/Madam SEEKING YOUR IMMEDIATE ASSISTANCE. Please permit me to make your acquaintance in so informal a manner. This is necessitated by my urgent need to reach a dependable and trust worthy foreign partner. This request may seem strange and unsolicited but I crave your indulgence and pray that you view it seriously. My name is COL. MICHAEL BUNDU of the Democratic Republic of Congo and one of the close aides to the former President of the Democratic Republic of Congo LAURENT KABILA of blessed memory, may his soul rest in peace. Due to the military campaign of LAURENT KABILA to force out the rebels in my country, I and some of my colleagues were instructed by Late President Kabila to go abroad to purchase arms and ammunition worth of Twenty Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars only (US$20,500,000.00) to fight the rebel group. We were then given this money privately by the then President, LAURENT KABILA, without the knowledge of other Cabinet Members. But when President Kabila was killed in a bloody shoot-out by one of his bodyguards a day before we were schedule to travel out of Congo, We immediately decided to put the funds into a private security company here in Congo for safe keeping. The security of the said amount is presently being threatened here following the arrest and seizure of properties of Col. Rasheidi Karesava (One of the aides to Laurent Kabila) a tribesman, and some other Military Personnel from our same tribe, by the new President of the Democratic Republic of Congo, the son of late President Laurent Kabila, Joseph Kabila. In view of this, we need a reliable and trustworthy foreign partner who can assist us to move this money out of my country as the beneficiary. WE have sufficient ''CONTACTS'' here to move the fund under Diplomatic Cover to a security company in Europe in your name. This is to ensure that the Diplomatic Baggage is marked ''CONFIDENTIAL'' and it will not pass through normal custom/airport screening and clearance. Our inability to move this money out of Congo all this while stems from our lack of trust of our supposed good friends (western countries) who suddenly became hostile to those of us who worked with the late President Kabila, immediately after his son took office. Though we have neither seen nor met each other, the information We gathered from an associate who has worked in your country has encouraged and convinced us that with your sincere assistance, this transaction will be properly handled with modesty and honesty to a huge success within two weeks. The said money is a state fund and therefore requires a total confidentiality. We would please need you to stand on our behalf as the beneficiary of this fund in Europe. This is because we are under restricted movement and watch and hence we want to be very careful in order not to lose this fund which we have worked so hard for. Thus, if you are willing to assist us to move this fund out of Congo, you can contact me through my email addresses, Tel/Fax nos. above with your telephone, fax number and personal information to enable us discuss the modalities and what will be your share (percentage) for assisting us. Please note that There are no RISKS involved in this Deal as everyone's Security is Guaranteed if we follow the required guidelines. I will hence furnish you with further details of this Deal as soon as I am assured of your Sincere interest to assist us. I must use this opportunity and medium to implore you to exercise the utmost indulgence to keep this matter extraordinarily confidential, Whatever your decision, while I await your prompt response. Thank you and God Bless. Best Regards COL. MICHAEL BUNDU(RTD). mikebundu@rediffmail.com N\B. When you are calling my line, you dial your country Intl. access code, then you dial directly, do not include my country code i.e. (243). Just dial your country Intl. access code + 88216 52098236. You can also contact me through the above email addresses.

Dear Sir, A Very Good day to you I am Mrs Mariam Abacha. I got your contact from a close Associate of mine who works with the Nigerian Chamber of Commerce and Industry who visited your country for an International Trade Fair upon my quest for a trusted and reliable foreign businessman or company. He however gave me the assurance that you can be trusted to handle a transaction of this magnitude. Following the sudden death of my husband General Sani Abacha the late Former Head of State of Nigeria in 1998, I have been thrown into a state of utter confusion, frustration and hopelessness by the present civilian administration, I have been subjected to physical and psychological torture by the security agents in the country. As a widow that is so traumatized, I have lost confidence with anybody within the country. You must have heard over the media reports and the internet on the recovery of various huge sums of money deposited by my husband in different security firms abroad, some companies willingly give up their secrets and disclosed our money confidently lodged there or many outright blackmail. In fact the total sum discovered by the Government so far is in the tune of $700. Million dollars. And they are not relenting to make me poor for life. I will give you more information as to this regard as soon as you reply. I repose great confidence in you hence my approach to you due to security network placed on my day to day affairs I cannot afford to visit the embassy so that is why I decided to contact you and I hope you will not betray my confidence in you. I have deposited the sum of US$35 million dollars with a security firm abroad whose name is withheld for now until we open communication. I shall be grateful if you could receive this fund into your account for safekeeping. This arrangement is known to you and my family lawyer who shall deal directly with you as I am still under house arrest. I am seriously considering to settle down abroad as soon as this fund get into your account so that I can start all over again if only you wish, but if it is possible, just help me in diverting this funds into your bank account which will accrue you 20% of this fund. Please honesty is the watchword in this transaction. And should you accept my terms, kindly send me an email signifying your interest to my email box as this is only safe for me now so that we can commence communication immediately. And upon receipt of your message of interest, I shall give you a more detailed picture of things. In case you don't accept please do not let me out to the security as I am giving you this information in total trust and confidence.NO RISK IS INVOLVED AS IAM STILL IN CONTROL OF MY HUSBANDS AFFAIRS. I will greatly appreciate if you accept my proposal in good faith. Please expedite action. Prefer all further correspondence be sent via presidentwifeng@indiatimes.com but please copy this email:profadams@ usa.com sincerely yours Hajia Mariam Abacha. for certain comfirmations. Please logg into this internet sites www.swissmoney.net/briefs.htm and www.thisdayonline.com.ng click on archive, then click on 2001, click on march 10th,

FROM: JAMES NGOLA. CONFIDENTIAL TEL: 233-27-587908. E-MAIL:(james_ngola2002@maktoob.com) DEAR RESPECTFUL, I BEG TO SOLICIT FOR YOUR URGENT AND MAXIMUM ASSISTANCE THIS MAIL, I KNOW THIS MAIL MAY EMBARRASS YOU OR SURPRISE YOU BY EMBARRASSMENT, I MEAN COMING FROM SOMEBODY YOU NEVER KNOW OR MET BEFORE, EVEN COMING FROM A COUNTRY PERHAPS YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW (GHANA) NOTED FOR DISHONEST AND FRUADULET PRACTICES. WELL, THIS IS NOT ONE OF THOSE SCAM LETTERS FROM (GHANA OR OTHER AFRICAN COUNTRIES, BUT FROM A FAMILY OF WHO ARE IN DISTRESS AND REQUIRE YOUR ASSISTANCE.LET ME START BY INTRODUCING MYSELF PROPERLY TO YOU. LET ME ATART BY INTRODUCING MYSELF PROPERLY TO YOU, I AM MR. JAMES NGOLA, THE FIRST SON OF BRIDGR. GEN. THEOPHILUS NGOLA (LATE). FORMER CHIEF OF DEFENCE STAFF: NATIONAL REPUBLIC OF LIBERIA. BRIEFLY: MY FATHER, BRIDG. GEN. T. NGOLA BEFORE HIS DEATH DIVERTED THIS FUND (US$25M) TWENTY FIVE MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS. MEANT FOR PURCHASE OF AMMUNATION FOR MY COUNTRY "LIBERIA" DURING THE PERIOD OF THEETHNIC CIVIL WAR BETWEEN MY COUNTRY AND GUINEA REPUBLIC. AND NOW, THE WAR IS OVER BY THE INTERVENTION OF "ECOMOG"FORCES. FOUR MONTHS AFTER THE WAR ENDED, THE RADIO NATIONAL OF LIBERIA WENT ON AIR, ON A WILD BROADCAST, UNCINGAN UNSUCCESSFUL "COUPD'TAT" IN MY COUNTRY, ATTEPTED TO OVERTROW THE PRESENT GOVERNMENT IN MY COUNTRY HEADED BY "PRESIDENT CHARLES TAYLOR". THIS BROADCAST CONTINUED TO ANNOUNCE THE NAMES OF THOSE IN CONNECTION WITH THE ATTEMPT. BUT UNKNOWINGLY TO ME, MY FATHER WAS INCLUDED AMOUNG THESE GROUP OF MEN ARRESTED IN CONNECTION WITH THIS PLOT AS THE "MASTERMINDER" AND THE "FINANCIER" OF THIS UNDEMOCRATIC ACT. ALTHOUGH HE WAS EXECUTED ALONG SIDE WITH OTHERS. (MAY THEIR SOULS REST IN PERFECT PEACE) TWO WEEKS AFTER THEIR EXECUTION THE GOVERNMENT OF LIBERIA STIL WENT FURTHER TO PASS JURGEMENT TO CONFISTICATE MY FATHER'S ASSETS AND ALSO TO FREEZE HIS ACCOUNTS. SO WHEN THIS NEWS REACHED ME, I HURRIEDLY GATHERED SOME VALUABLES IN OUR FAMILY VILLA AND ESCAPED TO (ACCRA), CAPITAL OF GHANA FOR SAFETY, WHILE MY MOTHER AND MY BROTHERS, SISTERS ARE NOW IN COTE D'IVOIRE AS REFUGEES. THIS FILE, WHICH CONTAINING DOCUMENTS OF A CONSIGNMENT (1 METALIC TRUNK BOX) DEPOSITED BY MY LATE FATHER IN ONE OF THE PRIVATE SECURITY COMPANIES, WAS AMOUNG THE VALUBLE THINGS I ESCAPED WITH TO GHANA. HONESTLY SPEAKING, IN THIS"BOX" IS THE SUM OF THIS FUND (US$25 M.) TWENTY FIVE MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS ONLY DIVERTED BY MY LATE FATHER. HE REGISTERED THIS CONSIGNMENT (BOX) WITH SECURITY COMPANY AS TO CONTAIN (AFRICA ARTS WORK), BUT THERE IS A CLAUSE IN THE DEPOSIT AGREEMENT WITH THE COMPANY THAT SAYS ONLY HIS FOREIGN PARTNER WILL BE ALLOWED TO COLLECT THE CONSIGNMENT ON HIS BEHALF HENCE HE NEVER WANTED TO BE TRACED WITH THE AMOUNT AS A POPULAR PERSON. IT IS ON THIS NOTE THAT I AM CONTACTING YOU TO FAITHFULLY AND CONFIDENTIALY ASSIST ME TO "FRONT" AS MY LATE FATHER FOREIGN BUSINESS PARTNER IN ORDER TO NECCESITATE AND FACILITATE THE CLAIM OF THIS CONSIGNMENT FROM THE SECURITY COMPANY. AND THE FUND ALSO BE TRANSFERED INTO YOUR PRIVATE FOREIGN BANK ACCOUNT FOR INVESTMENT PERHAPS IN YOUR COUNTRY FOR I CANNOT INVEST HERE DUE TO ITS NEARNESS. ONCE AGAIN, I AM PRESENTLY LIVING IN GHANA ALSO AS A REFUGEE TOO (ASYLUM SEEKER) FOR THE SAKE OF MY LIFE. BE INFORMED, THAT THE FINANCIAL LAW OF GHANA DOES NOT ALLOW A REFUGEE TO OPERATE AN ACCOUNT NOR INCORPORATE A COMPANY. WITH THIS, COUPLED WITH THE WAY IN WHICH THE MONEY WAS ACQUIRED, AND I DON'T WANT ANYBODY TO KNOW ABOUT THIS DEVELOPMENT THAT IS WHY I DECIDED NOT TO INVEST IN ANYWHERE IN AFRICA OR LIBERIA NOR EVEN GHANA WHERE I AM CURRENTLY RESIDING AS A REFUGEE AND THAT IS WHY I'M SOLICITING FOR YOUR SUPPORT. IF YOU AGREE TO ASSIST US, I WILL COMPENSATE YOU WITH 15% OF THE TOTAL FUND AFTER THIS CONSIGNMENT IS CLEARED AND THE MONEY TRANSFERED INTO YOUR BANK ACCOUNT. MOST IMPORTANT: PROMISE ME TO KEEP THIS TRANSACTION CONFIDETIAL & SECRET BECAUSE THIS FUND IS THE ONLY HOPE OF MY FAMILY. FINALLY, CONSIDER THIS PROPOSAL AND GET BACK TO ME WITH THE E-MAIL ABOVE OR YOU CAN ALSO CALL ME ON THIS NUMBER: 233-27-587908, FOR MORE DETAILS ABOUT THE TRANSACTION AND THE ARRENGMENT ON THE MODALITIES, TO ENSURE QUICK AND SMOOTH TRANSACTION. FURTHER DETAILS WILL BE FORWARDED TO YOU UPON RECEIPT OF YOUR RESPONSE. THANKS AND WISHING THE BEST COOPERATION IN FUTURE. MR. JAMES NGOLA. NB: THIS TRANSACTION IS 100% RISK-FREE AND YOUR SECURITY IS QUITE GAURANTEED. YOUR CONFIDENCE & TRUST IS OUR WATCHWORD AS WE ARE TO WORK TOGETHER TO THE REALIZATION OF THIS OBJECTIVE. I HEREBY INFORMING THAT I HAVE ALL THE NECESSARY DOCUMENTS AS REGARDS TO THIS CONSIGNMENT, SO BE REST ASSURED. WAITING FOR YOUR QUICK RESPONSE. THANK YOU. AND BEWARE OF IMPERSONATORS.

FROM:MRS. M SESE-SEKO DEAR FRIEND, I AM MRS. SESE-SEKO WIDOW OF LATE PRESIDENT MOBUTU SESE-SEKO OF ZAIRE? NOW KNOWN AS DEMOCRATIC REPUBLIC OF CONGO (DRC). I AM MOVED TO WRITE YOU THIS LETTER, THIS WAS IN CONFIDENCE CONSIDERING MY PRESENT CIRCUMSTANCE AND SITUATION. I ESCAPED ALONG WITH MY HUSBAND AND TWO OF OUR SONS KONGOLO AND NZANGA OUT OF DEMOCRATIC REPUBLIC OF CONGO (DRC) TO ABIDJAN, COTE D'IVOIRE WHERE MY FAMILY AND I SETTLED, WHILE WE LATER MOVED TO SETTLED IN MORROCO WHERE MY HUSBAND LATER DIED OF CANCER DISEASE. HOWEVER DUE TO THIS SITUATION WE DECIDED TO CHANGED MOST OF MY HUSBAND'S BILLIONS OF DOLLARS DEPOSITED IN SWISS BANK AND OTHER COUNTRIES INTO OTHER FORMS OF MONEY CODED FOR SAFE PURPOSE BECAUSE THE NEW HEAD OF STATE OF (DR) MR LAURENT KABILA HAS MADE ARRANGEMENT WITH THE SWISS GOVERNMENT AND OTHER EUROPEAN COUNTRIES TO FREEZE ALL MY LATE HUSBAND'S TREASURES DEPOSITED IN SOME EUROPEAN COUNTRIES. HENCE MY CHILDREN AND I DECIDED LAYING LOW IN AFRICA TO STUDY THE SITUATION TILL WHEN THINGS GETS BETTER, LIKE NOW THAT PRESIDENT KABILA IS DEAD AND THE SON TAKING OVER (JOSEPH KABILA). ONE OF MY LATE HUSBAND'S CHATEAUX IN SOUTHERN FRANCE WAS CONFISCATED BY THE FRENCH GOVERNMENT, AND AS SUCH I HAD TO CHANGE MY IDENTITY SO THAT MY INVESTMENT WILL NOT BE TRACED AND CONFISCATED. I HAVE DEPOSITED THE SUM OF EIHGTEEN MLLION UNITED STATE DOLLARS(US$18,000,000,00.) WITH A SECURITY COMPANY , FOR SAFEKEEPING. THE FUNDS ARE SECURITY CODED TO PREVENT THEM FROM KNOWING THE CONTENT. WHAT I WANT YOU TO DO IS TO INDICATE YOUR INTEREST THAT YOU WILL ASSIST US BY RECEIVING THE MONEY ON OUR BEHALF.ACKNOWLEDGE THIS MESSAGE, SO THAT I CAN INTRODUCE YOU TO MY SON (KONGOLO) WHO HAS THE OUT MODALITIES FOR THE CLAIM OF THE SAID FUNDS. I WANT YOU TO ASSIST IN INVESTING THIS MONEY, BUT I WILL NOT WANT MY IDENTITY REVEALED. I WILL ALSO WANT TO BUY PROPERTIES AND STOCK IN MULTI-NATIONAL COMPANIES AND TO ENGAGE IN OTHER SAFE AND NON-SPECULATIVE INVESTMENTS. MAY I AT THIS POINT EMPHASISE THE HIGH LEVEL OF CONFIDENTIALITY, WHICH THIS BUSINESS DEMANDS, AND HOPE YOU WILL NOT BETRAY THE TRUST AND CONFIDENCE, WHICH I REPOSE IN YOU. IN CONCLUSION, IF YOU WANT TO ASSIST US , MY SON SHALL PUT YOU IN THE PICTURE OF THE BUSINESS, TELL YOU WHERE THE FUNDS ARE CURRENTLY BEING MAINTAINED AND ALSO DISCUSS OTHER MODALITIES INCLUDING REMUNERATION FOR YOUR SERVICES. FOR THIS REASON KINDLY FURNISH US YOUR CONTACT INFORMATION, THAT IS YOUR PERSONAL TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBER FOR CONFIDENTIAL PURPOSE AND ACKNOWLEDGE RECEIPT OF THIS MAIL USING THE ABOVE EMAIL ADDRESS. BEST REGARDS, MRS M. SESE SEKO

ATTN:President/Ceo Business Proposal, > > DEAR SIR, > > I am the manager of bills and exchange at the > foreignremittance > department of the ECOBANK Nigeria. I am writing this > letter to ask > foryour support and co-operation to carry out this > business > opportunity in my department. > We discovered an unclaimed sum of US$ 25.5 million > (Twenty-five > million five hundredthousand United States Dollar > only) in an account > that belongs to one of our customers who died a long > with his entire > family in November 1997 in plane crash in > Nigeria.Since we got > information about his death we have been expecting his > next of kin > tocome over and claim his money because we cannot > release the money > unless somebodyapplied for it as the next of kin or > relation to the > deceased as indicated in ourbanking guidelines. > > Rightaway,neither the family member nor the > relationhas appeared to > claim this money, at this discovery another official > and I in > thedepartment now decide to do business with you as > the next of kin > or relation of thedeceased for safety and sequent > disbursement since > nobody is coming for it and wedon't want this money to > go into the > bank treasure as an unclaimed debt. The bankinglaw and > guidelines of > the ECOBANK Nigeria stipulates that if such money > remained > unclaimedfor a period of four (5) years it will be > transferred into > the ECOBANK treasury asunclaimed fund. The need for a > foreigner as > next of kin in this business is occasionedby the fact > that the > customer was a foreigner and cannot stand as his next > of kinor heir. > > We agreed that 25% of the money will be for youas the > foreign > partner, thereafter my colleague and I will visit your > country > fordisbursement according to the percentage indicated. > Therefore to > enable the immediatetransfer of the fund to you as > indicated.You must > apply to the bank as relation ornext of kin of the > decreased, > indicating your bank account number and location > wherein the money > will be remitted. Upon receipt of response, I will > send to you by > fax the Application Form. As soon as you receive this > letter you > should contact me immediatelyand indicate your direct > and > confidential telephone and fax number for effective > communication.Trusting to hear from you immediately. > Yours faithfully, > MD.OBINA OKORO. ------------------------------------------------------------ http://Game.37.com/ <--- Free Games http://newJoke.com/ <--- J O K E S ! ! ! --------------------------------------------------------------------- Express yourself with a super cool email address from BigMailBox.com. Hundreds of choices. It's free! http://www.bigmailbox.com ---------------------------------------------------------------------

TRANSFER OF USD$22MILLION INTO YOUR ACCOUNT} ATTENTION: President\CEO. I, on behalf of my other colleagues from different organs of Federal Government of Nigeria (FGN) owned parastatals decided to solicit your assistance as regards transfer of the above-mentioned amount into your bank account. This fund accrued from over invoicing of various contract awarded in my parastatal to certain Foreign Contractors sometimes ago. We, as holders of sensitive position in our various parastatals, were mandated by the Federal Government to Scrutinise all payments made to certain foreign Contractors and we discovered that some of the contracts they executed were grossly over-invoiced either by omission or commission. In the process the sum of US$27M (Twenty Seven Million US Dollars only) was found lying in the parastatal suspense account after the foreign contractors had been paid their rightful dues for executing the said contracts. We all agreed that this over-invoiced amount be transferred (for our own use) into a bank account provided by a foreign partner, because we are government workers and the Code of Conduct does not allow us to operate foreign accounts. However, we have succeeded in transferring some of this money precisely US$5.0M (Five Million US Dollars only) into a foreign account in MOROCCO (North Africa), but the provider of the account in MOROCCO is up to some mischief and refuses to comply to the earlier mutual agreement by insisting that the total amount be paid into his nominated bank account before disbursement will take effect. If for a meagre sum of US$5.0M (Five Million US Dollars only) we are not compensated, is it when the balance of US$22M (Twenty-two Million US Dollars)is transferred that we will be sure of our full compensation? Of course, this abuse of trust and inhumanity calls for sober reflection and search for absolute trust. Thus we are seeking your unwavering assistance that the remaining amount of US$22M can be speedily processed and fully remitted into your nominated bank account. On successful remittance of the fund into your account, you will be compensated with 30% of the amount for your assistance and services. So far, much have been said and due to our sensitive positions, we cannot afford a slip in this transaction neither can we give out identity as regards our respective offices, but whereby cordial relationship is established, smooth operations commences, you will be furnished with details of all you deserves to know. I am at your disposition to entertain any question from you with respect to this transaction, so contact me immediately through my e:mail for further information on the requirements and procedure for this transaction. Please, treat with the strictest confidentiality and utmost urgency. Yours faithfully, MR FRED OBI.

ATTN:MANAGING DIRECTOR I am writing this proposal hoping that you would be of assistance in this business of mutual benefit. My name is Mr.David Agu an auditor at one of the Federal Ministries in lagos-Nigeria. During our last audit exercise,some amount of money totalling $16.5Million was discovered and traced to be owned by one late Engineer Muller Robert, a foreigner who died in a plane crash. The source of this fund was further traced to be a contract payment made to him but has remained unclaimed till now.Since his death, nobody has shown up to claim this fund and this attracted my curiosity. I therefore made a research and found out that he did not leave any next of kin in his confidential document with the ministry that he executed the contract for. A panel setup by the Federal Government on recovery of funds expects that this fund should be unquestionably claimed by any of his available foreign next of kin or alternatively the fund should be donated for arms and ammunition at a military war college here in Nigeria. Fervent valuable efforts were made by the Panel to get in touch with any of the family or relatives but all have proved to no avail. It is because of the perceived possibility of not going to be able to locate any next of kin ( he had no wife and children) that the panel under the influence of our chairman, Rtd Major General Usman Bello, that arrangement is being made for the fund to be declared UNCLAIMABLED and then be donated to the Trust Fund for arms and ammunition which will further enhance the perpetration of war in Africa and the third world in general. To forestall this move, my colleagues and I have taken it upon ourselves to source for a foreign partner who could assist in claimimg this fund for further transfer abroad. I have been given the sole mandate to source for a partner as soon as possible to that effect.All documents and proof to enable you get this fund have been carefully worked out and I am assuring you a 100% risk free involvement. Your share would be 30% of the total amount if you agree to assist while 10% would be set aside to offset all expenses in course of the transfer and the rest would be for us for investment purposes in your country. If this proposal is OK by you, and you do wish to take the advantage of the trust we hope to bestow on you and your company, then kindly reach me immediately via Fax:234-1-7597019 furnishing me with your most confidential telephone and fax numbers and exclusive email so that I can forward to you the relevant details of the transaction. I expect your urgent response. Regards, David. Fax:234-1-7597019 E-mail:david_agu-gov@excite.com

Dr John Ejime Office of the Financial Controller Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation Falamo Ikoyi Lagos-Nigeria. Tel/ Fax: 234 1 7592865. REQUEST FOR URGENT BUSINESS TRANSACTION. Dear Sir, I am Dr.John Ejime,the financial controller of the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation Headquarters Lagos. I am writing you on behalf of my colleagues in the corporation and have been assign to seek for the assistance of a reliable foreign company through which we can transfer the sum of Thirty Five Million United States Dollars Only (US$35,000,000). This fund is deposited in the Corporation Treasury account with the Apex Bank. ORIGIN OF THE FUND: This sum arose from the deliberated over-invoicing of a contract awarded by my ministry Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation to foreign firm in the twinlight days of the last military regime. This contract has been completely executed and commissioned and the contractor that handled this contract has collected his full and final payment thus leaving behind the above stated amount which represent the over invoiced sum. We have been safeguarding this money for conducive time for it's transfer out of the country for our personal use. However, the code of employment does not allow us (civil servant) to own and operate foreign account and because the contract was handled by a foreign firm and the payment made in dollars, we now need a foreign partner that will present himself as the sub-contractor so that the fund will be transfer into your company's or personal account. Your address was made available to us by a very good friend who work with the Nigeria export promotion council and he assured us of your company's viability and capability in business transaction. This assurance gave us the courage to link you up in this particular transaction and I hope it will be of mutual benefit to all of us. Note that the nature of your business is not particularly relevant to the success of the transaction. All we require is your willingness to present yourself as the subcontractor by providing your bank information so that the fund will be transferred into your account. SHARING RATIO: For your assistance in this business , your share will be 30% of the total fund. I and my colleagues will take 60% while we set aside 10% for any expenses that may incurred in the course of this transaction. If you are willing to assist us in this business. Send the following information. 1. Name of your bank and address 2. Your account number/beneficiaryâs name. 3. Your private telephone and fax number for easy communication. This information will enable us put an application for payment approval to the concerned Ministries and final to the Senate Committee on Contract Payment and it is going to last for fourteen working days starting from the day we receive the above information. All modalities for the take off of this transaction have been worked out and further action will commence immediately we hear from you. I am waiting for your reply by fax on this fax number :234-1-7592865 as stated above. Yours faithfully. Dr.John Ejime.

AFEX BANK OF AFRICA MOHAMMED BELLO (Ph.D) Director/Coordinator Forex & Computer Operations Department Tel/Fax: 234-9-2726223 Sir, Accept my apologies for writing to you in this mode for it might be of inconvenience to you but due to my quest for an honest and reliable international assistance concerning a business here in my country Nigeria I have no other option than to go this length. I need the effectiveness of your professionalism in accomplishing this very business. I am DR. MOHAMMED BELLO Director/coordinator Forex and computer operations department of the Afex Bank of Africa PLC. I am writing this letter to ask your support and cooperation to carry out this business opportunity in my department. We discovered an abandoned sum of $42.500,000.00 (forty two million, Five hundred thousand United States Dollars) in an account that belongs to one of our customer in Afex Bank of Nigeria, Late Monsieur. Ives Laurent (a French citizen and an Engineer executing major Federal contract with governments of West African sub region). He died with a fellow business associate in a ghastly auto crash last October and his remains have since been incarcerated. Since his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and put claims as the next of kin and beneficiary to the resources in Monsieur. Ives Laurent account, for it is against the ethics and norms of the finance institution to claim such resources without a beneficiary unless proclaimed by the government. The federal government of Nigeria has given directives to finance institutions to declare adamant accounts that has stayed more than 8months in their custody as they intend to use it to pay off her military peace keeping force (ECOMOG) who fought in War ravaged African countries precisely and as the case may be, Late Monsieur. Ives Laurent account fell into this category thus the necessity for contacting you for I am determined to move this fund out as the rigorous and rash economic decision and policies has really turned we government workers to mere civil laborers. I have worked for almost a decade and half and I have nothing to show as reaps and rewards of my hard earned labor. As I need a next of kin/beneficiary and financial assistance to re-claim this resources for I cannot take on this project alone. My attorney and I have propose a commission of 25% out of the total resources for your kind assistance and five 5% has been mapped out to be reimbursed to both parties as sundry expenses incurred in the course of this business. To commence this transaction, I require you to immediately indicate your interest by a return correspondence to this fax number 234-9-2726223 and enclose your private contact telephone number, fax number, full name & address, and your designated bank coordinates to enable us file a letter of claim to the appropriate departments for necessary approvals before the transfer could be made. Note also that this business must be kept strictly confidential because of its nature and can be finalized within a short time depending on the level of your commitment/swiftness. I look forward to receiving your prompt response. Best regards, MOHAMMED BELLO (Ph.D)

CORDINATOR, DEBT RECOVERY AND RECONCILIATION UNIT OFFICE OF THE ASSISTANT TO THE AUDITOR GENERAL AMALGAMATED BANKS OF SOUTH AFRICA (ABSA) 14TH FLOOR EMBASSY BUILDING CNR SMITH ALIWAL STREET, P.O. BOX 1596 ALBERTON BRANCH DURBAN 4000 SOUTH AFRICA. EMAIL ga_m@epatra.com dear, I humbly wish to seek your assistance in a matter that is very important and needs utmost trust and confidence. I am MR Gabriel Mukanabe THE ASSISTANT TO THE AUDITOR GENERAL AMALGAMATED BANKS OF SOUTH AFRICA (ABSA) and a close confidant of one of the South-African most powerful family. The wife of former top Government official, a Gold magnet {OriginalOwner of GRUGGER GOLD CO.}, i.e. late Dr BAMUNGA SANGO MBEKI, former Junior Minister of Mines and Power , Republic ofSouth-Africa.Unfortunately, he died of heart attack soon after handing over because the new Government wanted to probe his activitieswhile in office for financial misappropriations. Presently, all their foreign and local count was frozen and their assets confiscated. The wife, who is now on her sick bed helplessly since her husbands death with her only son to look after, wishes to move out of South-Africa the sum of USD$75 million . She wishes to invest the a for mentioned sum on real estate property/viable inves! tments overseas. For obvious reasons, my client does not want to place this fund with established financial institution with the family name forsecurity reasons. It is her desire that the deal be handled as quietly as possible without possibility of any leakage to the public or Government. She has therefore empowered me to find and negotiate for a reliable and trustworthy foreigner who can assist us by using his/her name in moving the money to a foreign safe account and who can assist to invest the fund properly for the family. If you agree to act as a fund manager for my client and the family, I shall release the sum of $75 USD[seventy five million united states dollars] to you if you meet my requirements.The money is available safe with a private security company coded and lodged in with a fictitious name. Upon a favorable response from you, I shall let you know the steps involve. Your commission shall be down payment of 25% of the total sum, and annual 10% of the after ta! x returns on investment for the first 5 years. Thereafter, the terms shall be re-negotiated. If you are capable and willing to participate in this transaction contact me through ga_m@epatra.com IF FOR ANY REASON YOU ARE NOT DISPOSED AT MOMENT TO UNDERTAKE THIS DEAL,LET ME KNOW ON TIME SO AS TO MAKE ALTERNATIVE ARRANGEMENT.BECAUSE I WILL NOT CONACT ANOTHER PERSON UNTILL I HEAR FROM YOU. Yours faithfully, MR Gabriel Mukanabe ______________________________________________________ Get Paid... With Your Free Email at http://www.zwallet.com/index.html?user=ga_mm1

MR & MRS PETER WILLIAMS EMAIL: panmentat@rediffmail.com panmentat@phantomemail.com KINDEST ATTENTION, PLEASE PERMIT ME TO MAKE YOUR ACQUAINTANCE IN SO INFORMAL A MANNER. THIS IS NECESSITATED BY MY URGENT NEED TO REACH A DEPENDABLE AND TRUSTWORTHY FOREIGN PARTNER. THIS REQUEST MAY SEEM STRANGE AND UNSOLICITED BUT I CRAVE YOUR INDULGENCE AND PRAY THAT YOU TAKE MY REQUEST VERY SERIOUS. I AM MR PETER WILLIAMS, A REKNOWNED BUSINESSMAN IN ONE OF THE REBEL-HELD TOWNS, BOUAKE (ONE OF THE WAR ZONES IN IVORY COAST) I RECEIVED INFORMATION FROM A RELIABLE SOURCE WHO DESCRIBED YOUR COUNTRY AS BEING ECONOMICALLY CONDUCIVE FOR INVESTMENT AND HER PEOPLE AS TRANSPARENT AND TRUSTWORTHY TO ENGAGING BUSINESS WHICH MADE ME TO WRITE YOU. AS YOU MAY WANT TO KNOW AND TO MAKE YOU LESS CURIOUS,I GOT YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS FROM AN INTERNET SITE THAT PORTRAYED YOU (YOUR ESTABLISHMENT) IN GOOD LIGHT. ON THE 17TH OF SEPTEMBER 2002. THE REBEL LEADERS, UNTIL THEN WERE LOYAL SOLDIERS TO THE GOVERNMENT OF PRESIDENT LAURENT GBAGBO CONTACTED ME IN MY OFFICE WITH THE BUSINESS OF IMPORTATION OF ARMOURIES. WITHOUT THE PREMONITION OF WAR, I ACCEPTED THE JOB. THE SOLDIERS PAID ME THE SUM OF TWENTY MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS (US$ 20.5) ON THE SPOT AND TOLD ME TO EXPEDITE ACTION. SINCE I AM NOT INTO IMPORTATION OF ARMUNITIONS AND BECAUSE OF THE URGENCY, I IMMEDIATELY STARTED MAKING SEVERAL CONTACTS WITH BUSINESSMEN ACROSS THE GLOBE. TWO DAYS LATER, HEAVY FIGHTING BROKE UP IN CENTRAL BAOUKE AND KORHOGO, EVERYWHERE WAS IN DISSARRAY AND I LOST EVERYTHING THAT TOOK ME SO MANY YEARS TO ACQUIRE. I HAVE NO OPTION THAN TO DO AWAY WITH THE US$20.5M. MY WIFE AND I QUICKLY MADE AN ARRANGEMENT WITH A RED CROSS RELIEF WORKER WHO USED HIS OFFICIAL VAN TO MOVE THIS MONEY TO ABIDJAN, ALTHOUGH HE DID NOT KNOW THE REAL CONTENT OF THE BOX. PRESENTLY, THIS FUND HAS BEEN DEPOSITED WITH A SAFE RELIABLE SECURITY COMPANY IN ABIDJAN WHERE I AM HIDING FROM THE REBEL WHO DECLEARED ME WANTED. I DO NOT WANT TO INVEST THIS MONEY IN ABIDJAN DUE TO UNFAVORABLE ECONOMIC CLIMATE. AS A RESULT, I KEPT THE MONEY IN A CUSTOM BONDED WAREHOUSE WITH THE SECURITY COMPANY. SO THAT I CAN NOT LAY MY HANDS ON IT UNTIL IT GETS TO YOUR COUNTRY, WHERE I WILL COMMENCE INVESTMENT. THE ONLY ASSISTANCE WE NEED FROM YOU WHICH I BELIEVE YOU WOULD DO FOR US ARE THE FOLLOWING: 1. MAKE IMMEDIATE ARRANGEMENT TO TAKE THE DELIVERY OF THE CRATE (FUND) AT THEIR EUROPE OR AMERICAN COMMISSION AGENTS. 2. ASSURANCE FROM YOU THAT YOU WILL NOT SIT ON OUR SHARE WHEN THIS FUND GETS TO YOUR COUNTRY. MY WIFE AND I AGREED THAT YOU SHALL BE ENTITLED TO 20% OF THE TOTAL AMOUNT WHILE THE PRINCIPAL SUM WILL BE INVESTED IN A VIABLE BUSINESS VENTURE WITH YOUR ADVICE. MOST IMPORTANTLY, I WILL LIKE TO BUY A PERSONAL HOUSE WHERE MY WIFE, MY TWO SONS AND I WILL RESIDE. UPON CONFIRMATION OF YOUR INTEREST TO HELP US AS OUR FOREIGN PARTNER TO CLAIM THE CRATE FROM THE SECURITY COMPANY ON OUR BEHALF AT ANY OF THEIR COMMISSION AGENT CLOSER TO YOU, I SHALL FURNISH YOU WITH THE DETAILS OF THE MOVEMENT OF THE CONSIGNMENT TO BE SCHEDULED IN YOUR FAVOUR BY THE SECURITY COMPANY PREPARE AN AIRWAY BILL AND TAG THE CONSIGNMENT IN YOUR FAVOUR. YOUR PRIVATE FAX AND TELEPHONE NUMBERS ARE NEEDED TO ENHANCE THE SPEEDY CONCLUSION OF THIS TRANSACTION (OUR ONLY HOPE IN LIFE NOW) URGENTLY. KINDLY TREAT AS URGENT AND CONTACT ME IMMEDIATELY THROUGH THE ABOVE E-MAIL ADDRESS {PANMENTAT@REDIFFMAIL.COM OR PANMENTAT@PHANTOMEMAIL.COM}. I HAVE NOT ACQUIRED A NEW PHONE AS I LOST ALL MY PROPERTIES IN BOAUKE YOURS FAITHFULLY, MR PETER WILLIAMS

STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL PLEASE IDRIS ADAMU NNPC, IKOYI Lagos- Nigeria email: idris_adamu@africamail.com Fax: 234-1-4401017 4/12/2003 Attention: The President/Chairman PROPOSAL FOR TRANSFER OF TWENTY MILLION, FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND US DOLLARS (US$20.5M) TO YOUR ACCOUNT. Your contact address got to me via export promotions council, your reliability and trustworthiness in business transaction was the main conviction that compelled me to solicit for your support in this deal. I am the Financial Controller of the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation (NNPC) Lagos, Nigeria and Secretary to the Contract Award Committee of my Ministry. In collaboration with my colleagues, we have agreed to transfer out of the Country through Central Bank of Nigeria (CBN) some amount and we will later reinvest it abroad after the success of this transaction. The amount involved is Twenty Million, Five Hundred Thousand US Dollars (US$20,500,000.00). This is as a result of over inflated amount of a contract. The contract has been already executed and the original contractor had collected his full and final payment. In as much as this contract was awarded to a Foreign Contractor and the payment in dollars, we now need a Foreign firm that will present itself as the contractor for this amount of Twenty Million, Five Hundred Thousand US Dollars (US$20,500,000.00) and then the fund will be transferred into your account. Since we do not want to use the original contractor in applying for the payment, because the Contractor is not aware of this over-invoiced sum. Therefore, I as the Financial Controller was told to write you by my colleagues and see the success of the remittance immediately, you will however, be required to furnish us with these necessary informations. 1. Your personal phone and fax number for easy communication 2. Name and Address of your Bank, Phone, Fax and Telex numbers 3. Your Account number where this money will be lodged into and the Beneficiary's name. It could be personal or corporate. These information will enable us put APPLICATION OF CLAIM for the release of this money from concerned Government Agencies and it will last for ten working days. For your assistance we have agreed that the fund will be shared as follows: You as the Account Owner 20%, Miscellaneous Expenses 5%, Officials Involved 75% Now, we assure you that all arrangements have been concluded for the success of this transaction, so if you are interested, reply us STRICTLY THROUGH this e-mail or Alternatively through the above contact. Yours faithfully, IDRIS ADAMU.

Attn: The President, Dear Sir, My mail may come to you as a surprise, but sincerely this is a proposal for a business deal that will benefit both of us. I am contacting you after a frantic search for a person who will be trustworthy and capable of handling a business of this dimension. My name is Mr. Jonathan Mokoena, the Under-Secretary in charge of Intergration at the Specialized Technical Committee of the African Union (AU), formerly Organization of Afriacn Unity (OAU). You may be aware of the transformation of the OAU to AU, and the mandate to build a new united Africa modelled on the pattern of European Union (EU). For this therefore, the various African leaders recently inaugurated the New Patnership for African Development (NEPAD). NEPAD is to streamline Africa towards achieving a common market, defence force, currency, foreign policy, judiciary etc. For the above, the various African countries have made whosoever contributions in hundreds of million dollars. We have equally received grants/aids from the EU, USA and other international governments and agencies. These moneies in all have ran into millions of dollars. As the officer in charge of receiving and managing these funds and executing the projects for which they are ment for, I have received all the money expected. I have also prepared my account which I have submitted to the AU High Command, and it has been approved by the AU Secratary-General, Dr. Amara Essy. However, in some of the money received, some of the donor countries and international bodies remitted to us amounts in excess of what they pledged. The AU before now, has written to all of them to acknowledge the receipt of the monies from them. The money in excess and which I have kept out with only me having knowledge of it, is in the tune of Thirty-Five Million United States Dollars (US$35,000,000.00). As it is now, this money belongs to me, as neither the AU nor any of the donor countries/international agencies has declared their money missing. I am therefore contacting you to assist me with the movement and safe-keeping of this fund. As a public officer in my category, I cannot openly put this money into any bank here in Addis Ababa, Ethiopia, the AU headquarters where I am now, or in any other part of Africa, as an account holder. This will surely raise eyebrows and expose me. I have therefore concealed this amount of US$35M in four metal trunk boxes, and declared them as artefacts belonging to a foreigner. I deposited the boxes with a Security Company based in Spain which has an affliate offices in Ghana, Cot d'Ivoire and South Africa. These cities are safe havens for this kind of transaction. This transaction will however be hitch-free. So, I would therefore want you to be in Banjul, The Gambia for the clearing and claiming of this fund. I will furnish you with information/documents on how you will stand as the beneficiary of the boxes. I have decided to give to you 40% of the total amount involved. Please I will want you to contact me on this e-mail address or the alternative: (joe_mokoena@fastermail.com). Also, you have to assure me of the secrecy and confidentiality in this transaction. Thanks in anticipation of your valued co-operation. Mr. Jonathan Mokoena. joe_mokoena@fastermail.com

HIGHLY CONFIDENTIAL FROM: Prince Tunde O Adisaraki MOBILE:234-90-509398 MOBILE:234-80-33254029 FAX:234-92726808 Greetings, This letter might surprise you because we have not met neither in person nor by correspondence. But I believe it is one day that you get to know somebody either in physical or through correspondence. I got your contact through some discreet inquiry from the chamber of commerce and industry, you and your organization were revealed as being quite astute in private entrepreneurship, one has no doubt in your ability to handle a financial business transaction. However,I am the first son of his Royal Majesty, Iginawari Nweke Adisaraki III and the traditional ruler of Eleme Province in the oil area of Rivers State of Nigeria. I am making this contact to you in respect of US 28,000,000.00 (Twenty eight million United States Dollars) which I inherited from my late father. This money was accumulated from royalties paid to my father as compensation by the oil firms located in our area as a result of oil presence on our land which hamper agriculture which is our major source of livelihood. Unfortunately my father died from protracted diabetes. But before his he called my attention and informed me that he lodged some funds on a two boxes with a security firm with an open beneficiary status. The lodgment Security Code Number was also revealed to me, he then advised me to look for a reliable business partner abroad, who will assist me in investing the money in a lucrative business as a result of economic instability in Nigeria. So this is the main reason why I am contacting you for us to move this money from the security firm to any country of your choice for investment purposes. So I will like you to be the ultimate beneficiary, so that the funds can be moved in your name and particulars to any country of your choice where it will be claimed and invested. Hence my father have had intimated the security firm personnel that the beneficiary of the Box is his foreign partner whose particulars will be forwarded to the firm when due. But I will guide you accordingly. As soon as the fund reaches, I will then come over to meet you in person, so that we can discuss physically on Investment entials.Based on this instance I and my family have unanimously decided to give you 20% of the total money and annual 5% of the after tax returns on investment for the first three years. Thereafter, the term shall be varied. 2% for charity homes and 3% for expenses, which may arise during the transaction, fax and phone bills inclusive. The balance of 70% you will invest and manage for my family. I hereby guarantee you that this is not government money, it is not drug money and it is not money from arms deal. Though you have to maintain high degree of confidentiality on this matter. I will give you all proof of deposit and existence of money once urged and fully satisfied with you capability and honesty. I hope this will be the beginning of a prosperous relationship between my family and your family. Nevertheless if you are for any reason not interest, kindly inform me immediately so that I will look for another contact. I required also your private phone and fax numbers for easy communication.I am waiting for your quick response through my private phone or fax Number. I am waiting for your quick response. Yours faithfully, Prince Tunde Olusola Adisaraki (For the Family)

NAME:DR. OLUSEGUN SMITH dr.olusegun.smith@caramail.com REQUEST FOR ASSISTANCE: _STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL I AM DR. OLUSEGUN SMITH, THE CHAIRMAN OF CONTRACT AWARD AND REVIEW COMMITTEE SET UP BY THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT OF NIGERIA UNDER THE NEW CIVILIAN DISPENSATION TO AWARD NEW CONTRACTS AND REVIEW EXISTING ONES. I CAME TO KNOW OF YOU IN MY SEARCH FOR A RELIABLE AND REPUTABLE PERSON TO HANDLE A VERY CONFIDENTIAL TRANSACTION, WHICH INVOLVES THE TRANSFER OF A HUGE SUM OF MONEY TO A FOREIGN ACCOUNT. THERE WERE SERIES OF CONTRACTS EXECUTED BY A CONSORTIUM OF MULTI-NATIONALS IN THE OIL INDUSTRY IN FAVOUR OF N.N.P.C. THE ORIGINAL VALUE OF THESE CONTRACTS WERE DELIBRATELY OVER INVOICED TO THE SUM OF USD$25,000,000.00 (TWENTY FIVE MILLION UNITED STATE DOLLARS). THIS AMOUNT HAS NOW BEEN APPROVED AND IS NOW READY TO BE TRANSFERED BEING THAT THE COMPANIES THAT ACTUALLY EXECUTED THESE CONTRACTS HAVE BEEN FULLY PAID AND THE PROJECTS OFFICIALLY COMMISSIONED. CONSEQUENTLY, MY COLLEAGUES AND I ARE WILLING TO TRANSFER THE TOTAL AMOUNT TO YOUR ACCOUNT FOR SUBSEQUENT DISBURSEMENT, SINCE WE AS CIVIL SERVANTS ARE PROHIBITED BY THE CODE OF CONDUCT BUREAU (CIVIL SERVICE LAW) FROM OPERATING AND/OR OPENING FOREIGN ACCOUNTS IN OUR NAMES. NEEDLESS TO SAY, THE TRUST REPOSED ON YOU AT THIS JUNCTURE IS ENORMOUS, IN RETURN, WE HAVE AGREED TO OFFER YOU 30% OF THE TRANSFERED SUM, WHILE 10% SHALL BE SET ASIDE FOR INCIDENTAL EXPENSES (INTERNAL AND EXTERNAL) BETWEEN BOTH PARTIES IN THE COURSE OF THE TRANSACTION YOU WILL BE MANDATED TO REMIT THE BALANCE TO OTHER ACCOUNTS IN DUE COURSE. MODALITIES HAVE BEEN WORKED OUT AT THE HIGHEST LEVEL OF THE MINISTRY OF FINANCE AND THE CENTRAL BANK OF NIGERIA FOR THE IMMEDIATE TRANSFER OF THE FUNDS WITHIN 10 WORKING DAYS SUBJECT TO YOUR SATISFACTION OF THE ABOVE STATED TERMS. OUR ASSURANCE IS THAT YOUR ROLE IS RISK FREE.TO ACCORD THIS TRANSACTION THE LEGALITY IT DESERVES AND FOR MUTUAL SECURITY OF THE FUNDS THE WHOLE APPROVAL PROCEDURES WILL OFFICIALLY AND LEGALLY PROCESSED WITH YOUR NAME OR THE NAME OF ANY COMPANY YOU MAY NOMINATE AS THE BONEFIDE BENEFICIARY. ONCE MORE I WANT YOU TO UNDERSTAND THAT HAVING PUT IN OVER TWENTY FIVE YEARS IN THE CIVIL SERVICE OF MY COUNTRY, I AM AVERSE TO HAVING MY IMAGE AND CAREER DENTED. THIS MATTER SHOULD THEREFORE BE TREATED WITH UTMOST SECRECY AND URGENCY IT DESERVES.AND I WILL LIKE YOU TO SEND ME YOUR MAIL TO MY PRAIVTE BOX dr.olusegun.smith@caramail.com I WANT TO ASSURE YOU THAT THIS BUSINESS PROPOSAL IS 100% RISK FREE AS WE HAVE DONE OUR HOME WORK PROPERLY I QUITE BELIEVE THAT YOU WILL PROTECT OUR INTEREST BY TAKING THIS DEAL STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL, AS WE ARE STILL IN GOVERNMENT SERVICE, WHICH WE INTEND TO RETIRE FROM.KINDLY EXPEDITE ACTION AS WE ARE BEHIND SCHEDULE TO ENABLE US INCLUDE THIS TRANSFER IN THE SECOND BATCH WHICH WOULD CONSTITUTE THE FIRST QUARTER PAYMENTS FOR THE 2003 FINANCIAL YEAR. THANKS AND GOD BLESS. DR.OLUSEGUN SMITH NB: BUT IF YOU KNOW YOU ARE INTERESTED LET ME KNOW. LIST YOUR PHONE & FAX NUMBERS SO WE MAY COMMUNICATE WITH YOU. THIS IS IMPORTANT AS WE WOULD HAVE TO TALK ABOUT THE MODALITIES OF THE TRANSACTION. WAITING TO HEAR FROM YOU. ------------------------------------------------- This mail sent through MailService.MS -> http://www.MailService.ms

CONFIDENTIAL/COOPERATION IT IS MY GREAT PLEASURE IN WRITING YOU THIS LETTER ON BEHALF OF MY COLLEAGUES AND MYSELF. YOUR PARTICULARS WERE GIVEN TO ME BY A MEMBER OF THE NIGERIAN EXPORT PROMOTION COUNCIL (NEPC) WHO WAS AT THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT DELEGATION TO YOUR COUNTRY DURING A TRADE EXHIBITION. I HAVE DECIDED TO SEEK A CONFIDENTIAL COOPERATION WITH YOU IN THE EXECUTION OF THE DEAL DESCRIBED HERE FOR THE BENEFIT OF ALL PARTIES INVOLVED AND HOPE THAT YOU WILL KEEP IT AS TOP SECRET BECAUSE OF THE NATURE OF THE BUSINESS AND THE PERSONALITIES INVOLVED. WITHIN THE MINISTRY OF POWER AND STEEL WHERE I WORK AS A DIRECTOR PROJECT IMPLEMENTATION AND WITH THE COOPERATION OF FOUR OTHER TOP OFFICIALS, WE HAVE IN OUR POSSESSION AS OVERDUE PAYMENT BILLS TOTALLING $85,000 000:00m USD (EIGHTY FIVE MILLION UNITED STATE DOLLARS) WHICH WE WANT TO TRANSFER ABROAD WITH THE ASSISTANCE AND COOPERATION OF A TRUSTED FOREIGN FIRM OR INDIVIDUAL WHO WILL RECEIVE THE SAID FUND ON OUR BEHALF INTO ANY ACCOUNT PROVIDED TO RECEIVE SUCH FUNDS. WE ARE HANDICAPPED IN THIS DEAL BECAUSE THE CIVIL SERVICE CODE OF CONDUCT DOES NOT ALLOW PUBLIC SERVANTS LIKE US TO OPERATE OFFSHORE ACCOUNT, HENCE YOUR IMPORTANCE IN THE WHOLE TRANSACTION. THE SAID AMOUNT WHICH WE HAVE GOTTEN APPROVAL TO REMIT BY TELEGRAPHIC TRANSFER (T.T.) TO FOREIGN BANK ACCOUNT YOU WILL PROVIDE BY FILING IN AN APPLICATION THROUGH MY MINISTRY FOR THE TRANSFER OF RIGHT AND PRIVILEGES TO YOU. SINCE THE PRESENT NEW CIVILIAN GOVERNMENT OF MY COUNTRY IS DETERMINED TO PAY EVERY FOREIGN CONTRACTOR ALL DEBTS OWED SO AS TO MAINTAIN GOOD RELATIONSHIP WITH FOREIGN GOVERNMENT AND NON-GOVERNMENT FINANCIAL AGENCIES, WE HAVE DECIDED TO INCLUDE OUR BILL FOR APPROVALS WITH THE COOPERATION OF SOME OFFICIALS FROM ALL THE GOVERNMENT MINISTRY WHICH WILL BE INVOLVED IN THE PAYMENT PROCESS. WE ARE SEEKING YOUR ASSISTANCE IN PROVIDING A VITAL ACCOUNT INTO WHICH WE CAN REMIT THIS MONEY BY ACTING AS OUR MAIN PARTNER AND TRUSTEE OR ACTING AS THE ORIGINAL CONTRACTOR. THIS WE CAN DO BY SWAPPING OF ACCOUNT AND CHANGING OF BENEFICIARY AND OTHER FORMS OF DOCUMENTATION UPON APPLICATION FOR CLAIM TO REFLECT THE PAYMENT AND APPROVALS TO BE SECURED ON BEHALF OF YOU. I HAVE THE AUTHORITY OF MY PARTNERS INVOLVED TO PROPOSE THAT, SHOULD YOU BE WILLING TO ASSIST US IN THE TRANSACTION, YOUR SHARE OF THE SUM WILL BE 20% OF THE TOTAL SUM, 70% FOR US AND 10% FOR TAXATION AND MISCELLANEOUS EXPENSES. THE BUSINESS IS 100% SAFE ON YOUR PART, BUT YOU HAVE TO KEEP IT CONFIDENTIAL. DO NOT INFORM YOUR BANKER YET UNLESS INSTRUCTED BY US. ALSO, YOUR AREA OF SPECIALIZATION IS NOT A HIDERANCE TO THE SUCCESSFUL EXECUTION OF THIS TRANSACTION. I HAVE REPOSED MY CONFIDENCE IN YOU AND HOPE THAT YOU WILL NOT DISAPPOINT ME. PLEASE SEND REPLY TO ME TO INDICATE YOUR WILLINGNESS IN ASSISTING US SO THAT I WILL DIRECT YOU ON WHAT NEXT TO DO.INCLUDE YOUR DIRECT TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBERS IF YOU ARE RESPONDING. THANKS FOR YOUR ANTICIPATED ASSISTANCE. YOURS SINCERELY, MR.TUNDE BALOGUN

From: MR. NDIDI OKOCHA Accountant: Union Bank of Nigeria Idumota Branch, Lagos-Nigeria Email:georgebest@37.com Dear Friend, Let me start by first introducing myself properly to you. I am MR. NDIDI OKOCHA the Accountant with the Union Bank of Nigeria Idumota Branch Lagos. I came to know of you in my private search for a reliable and reputable person to handle the confidential transaction, which involves the transfer of a huge sum of money to a foreign account requiring maximum confidence. A foreigner,Mr. Barry Kelly an oil Merchant/Contractor with the Federal Government of Nigeria, until his death in ADC airline that crash on her way to Port-Harcourt 1996 banked with us at Union Bank Plc, Lagos, and had a closing balance as at the end of March 2000 worthUS$11.5M Eleven Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) which the Bank now expects a next of kin to claim as beneficiary. Valuable efforts are being made by Union Bank of Nigeria to get in touch with any of the late Mr. Barry Kelly family or relatives but there has been no success. It is because of the perceived possibility of not being able to locate the late Mr. Barry Kelly next of kin (he had no known wife nor children that isknown to us). The management under the influence of our Chairman and members of the Board of Directors, retired Major General Umaru Shelling, that arrangement has been made for the funds to be declared "UNCLAIMABLE" and subsequently be donated In order to avert this negative development, I now seek your permission to have you stand as the next-of-kin to late Mr. Barry Kelly so that the funds You will be presented as the next of kin with all documentary proof and the funds would be released and paid into your account as the beneficiary's next-of-kin. All documents and proves to enable you get this fund will be carefully worked out. We have secured from the probate an order of mandamus All efforts to locate any of the deceased beneficiaries and proved abortive Moreso, i am assuring you of a 100% risk free involvement. Your share stays while the rest would be for me and my colleagues for investment purposes in your Country. I have decided that the funds be shared thus, after it has been transferred into your account in a matter of one week: 1. 30% of the money will go to you for acting as the beneficiary of the fund. 2. 5% will be set aside for reimbursement to both parties for any incidental expenses that may be incurred in the course of the transfer. 3. 65% to us the originator of the transaction. kindly get to me immediately on my email:georgebest@37.com Please furnish me with your most confidential telephone and fax No. and your bank coordinates so that I can use these information to apply for the release and subsequent transfer of the funds in your favour. Thanks for your anticipated co-operation. Yours faithfully, MR. NDIDI OKOCHA Accountant Union Bank of Nigeria Idumota Branch Lagos-Nigeria

FROM: BARRISTER Graham Douglas OKOBI & ASSOCIATES LAGOS - NIGERIA REPLY VIA THIS ADDRESS ONLY: graham_d01@go.com DEAR PARTNER, MAY THE BLESSINGS OF THE MOST HIGH BE UPON YOU! PLEASE AS YOU READ KINDLY OPEN THE WEBSITE FOR THISDAY NEWSPAPEROF MONDAY 18TH.MARCH 2002, VOL 8,NO.2521 FRONT PAGE AND THAT OF MONDAY MAY 20TH., 2002.VOL 8, NO. 2584 AND TUESDAY SEPTEMBER 24TH., 2002 INCLUDING ALL NEWSPAPER ABOUT THE TRUE STATE OF THINGS FOR FURTHER DETAILS AT(WWW.THISDAYONLINE.COM ) SO THAT YOU KNOW HOW URGENT IT IS. COMPLIMENTS OF THE SEASON. GRACE AND PEACE AND LOVEFROM THIS PART OF THE ATLANTIC TO YOU. I HOPE MY LETTER DOESNOT CAUSE YOU TOO MUCH EMBARRASSMENT AS I WRITE TO YOU IN GOOD FAITH. PLEASE EXCUSE MY INTRUSION INTO YOUR PRIVATE LIFE INTO YOUR PRIVATE LIFE. I AM BARRISTER Graham_Douglas, I REPRESENT MRS MARIAM ABACHA,WIFE OF THE LATE GEN. SANI ABACHA, WHO WAS THE FORMER MILITARY HEAD OF STATE IN NIGERIA. HE DIED IN 1998. SINCE HIS DEATH, THE FAMILY HAS BEEN LOOSING A LOT OF MONEY DUE TO VINDICTIVE GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS WHO ARE BENT ON DEALING WITH THE FAMILY. BASED ON THIS THEREFORE, THE FAMILY! HAS ASKED ME TO SEEK FOR A FOREIGN PARTNER WHO CAN WORK WITH US AS TO MOVE OUT THE TOTAL SUM OF US$75,000,000.00 ( SEVENTYFIVE MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS ), PRESENTLY IN THEIR POSSESSION. THIS MONEY WAS OF COURSE, ACQUIRED BY THE LATE PRESIDENT AND IS NOW KEPT SECRETLY BY THE FAMILY. THE SWISS GOVERNMENT HAS ALREADY FROZEN ALL THE ACCOUNTS OF THE FAMILY IN SWITZERLAND, AND SOME OTHER OUNTRIES WOULD SOON FOLLOW TO DO THE SAME. THIS BID BY SOME GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS TO DEAL WITH THIS FAMILY HAS MADE IT NECESSARY THAT WE SEEK YOUR ASSISITANCE IN RECEIVING THIS MONEY AND IN INVESTING IT ON BEHALF OF THE FAMILY. THIS MUST BE A JOINT VENTURE TRANSACTION AND WE MUST ALL WORK TOGETHER. SINCE THIS MONEY IS STILL CASH,EXTRA SECURITY MEASURES HAVE BEEN TAKEN TO PROTECT IT FROM THEFT OR SEIZURE. I HAVE PERSONALLY WORKED OUT ALL MODALITIES FOR THE PEACEFUL CONCLUSION OF THIS TRANSACTION. THE TRANSACTION DEFINITELY WOULD BE HANDLED IN PHASES AND THE FIRST PHASE WILL INVOLVE THE MOVING OF US$30,000,000.00( THIRTY MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS ). MY CLIENTS ARE WILLING TO GIVE YOU A REASONABLE PERCENTAGE OF THIS MONEY AS SOON AS THE TRANSACTION IS CONCLUDED. I WILL, HOWEVER, BASED ON THE GROUNDS THAT YOU ARE WILLING TO WORK WITH US AND ALSO ALL CONTENTIOUS ISSUES DISCUSSED BEFORE THE COMMENCEMENT OF THIS TRANSACTION. YOU MAY ALSO DISCUSS YOUR PERCENTAGE BEFORE WE START TO WORK. AS SOON AS I HEAR FROM YOU, I WILL GIVE YOU ALL NECESSARY DETAILS AS TO HOW WE INTEND TO CARRY OUT THE WHOLE TRANSACTION. PLEASE, DO NOT ENTERTAIN ANY FEARS,AS ALL NECESSARY MODALITIES ARE IN PLACE, AND I ASSURE YOU OF ALL SUCCESS AND SAFETY IN THIS TRANSACTION. PLEASE, THIS TRANSACTION REQUIRES ABSOLUTE CONFIDENTIALITY AND YOU WOULD BE EXPECTED TO TREAT IT AS SUCH. IF YOU ARE INTERESTED IN ASSISTING MY CLIENT PLEASE SEND THE FOLLOWING DETAILS TO ME: 1.FULL NAMES/CONTACT ADDRESS 2.TEL/FAX NUMBERS PLEASE, YOU WILL ALSO IGNORE THIS LETTER AND RESPECT OUR TRUST IN YOU BY NOT EXPOSING THIS TRANSACTION, EVEN IF YOU ARE NOT INTERESTED. I LOOK FORWARD TO WORKING WITH YOU. YOURS FAITHFULLY. BARRISTER Graham Douglas

ATTN: SIR/MADAM I understand that this letter will be of great surprise to you ,Especially as itcomes from a stranger .I am Prince.Dennis Melange Savimbi from the republic ofAngola.I got your contact from the internet while i was searching for a foreignerwho can help me in this case. On the 22nd of february 2002, the rebel leader JONAS SAVIMBI my dad was killed.butbefore his death,he told me secretly that he deposited some money for us in case heis killed,we should flee for our lives.the money he said was supposed to be forammunitions.he told me that he divided the money for ammunitions and gave some ofthe money to the head of Armed and Ammunition Procurement Division , and sent themon a mission to NIGERIA with the sum of (US$30Million United State Dollars) toenable them stay there and negotiate with any of the Europe or America country asregards the buying and shipment of arms and ammunition into my country . The moneywas conveyed to NIGERIA through diplomatic means and the other part ($25M) wasdeposited at a Security Company in Nigeria by my father, while they were negotiatingthe arms deal.THE MONEY HE SAID WAS DEPOSITED IN MY NAME. During the begining part of last year ,we heard my father was dead and so,i remebered that my dad talked about some money he kept for us in the security vaultin Nigeria.i also remembered that he said we should immediately flee for our saftyto anywhere that is safe.so,i decided that the money must be cleared and used forsomething that will make us ok in life. my mum had resolved to end the war in my country.She needed oversea medical attention for her heart disease and as a result,she wanted us to get out of thecountry for the sake of our safety. So , we thus agreed to look for a God fearing person oversea who can assist us inclaiming these fund and deposit it into his or her personal/company account. So,Weare soliciting for your assistance on this matter ;as this stands to be the onlyhope for the future survival of the Family cause we cannot travel out of the countrybecause things are not yet settled. Presently we are seeking assylum in Nigeria,since it became necessary for us to live my country completly for securityreasons and the money is here in Nigeria in a security company ; fortunately enoughthis company we believe is closer to us and so,we will instruct them to airship itto netherland where they have diplomatic immunities for fear of discovery we willdiscuss with the company as regards the money in their Nigerian Office, but for thefact that we have not got any contact from out side Africa for now we are unable togive the instructions. This is the more reason why we are contacting you. Here inNigeria ;we have limited right to invest this fund ; considering the means in whichthe money was acquired, and Nigeria been a African Nation ,Hence we took this decision .In antipation of your assistance we have agreed to give: 30% of the totalsum to you,10% mapped out to cover any expenses that may be incuried in course ofthe transaction, 60% for me and my family. We wish to invest this fund in yourcountry ,this transaction is 100% risk free as we have concluded all necessaryarrangments before contacting you. We expect your favourable response, indicate your private Telephone and Fax numbersfor easy comunication. Upon comfirming your readiness to assist we shall get all necessarydocument including the certificate of Deposit made in your name as it was merelydeposited by my father as family valuables. Thanks For your Co-operation, We expect to here from you . Yours Faithfully, Prince DENNIS MALANGE SAVIMBI. --------------------------------------------------- WWW.COM - Where The Web Begins! http://www.www.com/

TOP BUSINESS PROPOSAL

ATTN: PRESIDENT/C E O,

I am Engineer.Chris Adamu,Chairman Senate Committee on Contracts Review and foreign payments In My Country Nigeria. Presently There is available the sum of US$18.500,000 (Eighteen Million Five hundred Thousand United States Dollars} which members of this committee wish to transfer into your account, to be used for our re-election This year 2003 general elections in Nigeria. SOURCE OF FUND. This amount was realized from inflated or over-invoiced aspect of contracts executed by some foreign firms in 1999 when Nigeria hosted the world youth soccer Championship.ln the course of our duty we observed this sum un-paid claims.lt is one of them that we intend to lodge into your bank account for our mutual benefit. REMUNERATION. We have unanimously agreed that you will be entitled to 30% of the total sum, while 10% Is set aside to offset expenses incurred during the transaction. INVESTMENT. You will be required to place 60% of the! total sum into any high yield investment facility in your country, for an initial duration of 10 months. During the 2003 elections, you will return 30% to us, but this time as a foreign loan for our election purposes. The accrued interest and the remaining 30% is what you will re-invest in the same process for a period of 4years. OPERATIONAL MODALITIES. We shall present you as one of the contractors awaiting payment for over-due contract payment for job executed for the Federal Republic of Nigeria in 1999.Application for claims, processing of approvals will be undertaken by my committee in conjunction with some highly placed officials, to ensure that fund is wired into your nominated bank account.

REQUIREMENTS. Your company details, banking details, as well as your confidential tell and fax numbers should be sent to me immediately to indicate your interest.

CONCLUSION. You do not stand any risk at all for being parts of this project, and your present line of business or profession is no hindrance. Honestly, our re-election in 2003 will be determined by this transaction and your ability to partner with us in all sincerity will enhance its success. Note: That this transaction is expected to last between 7-14 days from the day we received the information I am waiting for your reply via e-mail. Thanks for your co-operation and understanding while your urgent response is expected.

Best Regards, Engr.Chris Adamu.(SENETOR)

Note: Please reply a copy to chr_adamu@excite.com

Do you Yahoo!? Yahoo! Mail Plus - Powerful. Affordable. Sign up now

FROM THE DESK OF DR. BELLO MUSA N N P C. ATTN, MUTUAL BUSINESS RELATIONSHIP-STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL I am Dr. BELLO MUSA.The chief accountant of The Nigeria National Petroleum Corporation (NNPC) and I head five man tender board in charge of contract award and payments approvals.I came to know of you in my search for a reliable person to handle a very confidential transaction which involves the transfer of a huge sum of money to a foreign account. There were series of contracts executed by aconsortion of multinationals in the oil industry in favour of Nigeria National Petroleum Corporation (NNPC) among which were for the following:-1. The expansion of the pipelines network within for a crude down stream products distribution and subsequent evacuation:- $8, Billion United States Dollars.2. Contract for the turn around maintenance (TAM) of the various refineries in the country $115 million Uited States Dollars. 3. The construction of storage tanks for petrolwum products (depots) $190 Million United States Dollars. The original value of these contracts were delebrately over invoiced in the sum U$69,000.00 (sixty nine Million United States Dollars Only) which has now been approved and is now ready to be transferred, being that the companies that actually executed these contracts have been fully paid the projests officially commissioned.It does not matter whether or not your comapny does contracts project of that nature described here, the assumption is that your company won the major contract and sub-contracted it out to other companies. Consequently, my colleaques and I are willing to transfer the total amount to your account for subsequent disbursement, since we as civil servants are prohibited by the code of conduct bureau (civil service laws) from opening and or operating foreign accounts in our names. Needless to say, the trust imposed on you at this junction enormous. In return, we have agreed to offer you 20% of the transferred sum, while 5% shall be set aside for incidental expenses (internal and external) between the parties in the course of the transaction, and the remaining 75% is for us,The Nigerian officials. Modalities have been worked out at the highest level of the ministry of finance and the central bank of Nigeria for the immediate transfer of the fund within 14 working days subject to your satisfaction of the above stated terms.Our assurance is that your role is risk free, I accord this transaction the legality it deserves and for mutual security of the fund, the whole approval procedures will be officially and legally processed with the name of any company you may nominate as the bonafide beneficiary of the above mentioned amount. Therefore, when the business is successfully concluded we shall through our same connections withdraw all documents used from all the concerned government ministries for 100% security risk free.Once more, I want you to understand that having put in over 19 years in the civil service of my country, I am very careful to have my image and career deemed. Please contact me immediately through E-mail whether you are or not interested in this deal, if you are not, it will enable us scout for another foreign partner to carry out this deal but where you are interested send the required documents.One blank letter head, one invoice sheet and your bank particulars through my above address as time is not on our side in the business. Send by Email for security reasons. Thanks as I await in anticipation for your fullest co-operation. Very truly yours, Dr. bello musa

From: Mr. Frank Williams. Gulf Bank Nig,plc. Head Office,Plot 1212, tijian bello Street, Victoria Island.P.M.B 0090, Lagos .www.gulfbank.com Attn: Sir, I know that you must have recieved the first letter I sent to you by post, but if you have not, here comes a follow-upto the letter. First I must seek for your understanding and pray that God will give you the wisdom to understand my problem and be in a position to help as you will be surely blessed as you help. I am Mr. Frank Williams,I am 41 Years old and also the chief accountant with Gulf Bank Nig PLC . I have a transaction which I think will be of mutual benefit to both of us. In my desire for a foreign partner with whom to do this transaction, I stumbled on your contact from a business directory. As the head of accounts department of GBNP, I discovered some amount of money while I was auditing accounts for the 2003 financial year which has been lying there for over 3 years. On further inquiry, I discovered that this money totalling about USD$21.5 Million (twenty-one Million five hundred thousand United States Dollars) including accumulated interest belonged to one MR Michael Osterkamp ,a Germany Nationale who lived here and died intestate with no beneficiary.This man died through a plane crash of ADC airlines in 1998. I have Successfully secured the money and with the assistance of my colleague,the money has been moved out of my bank and deposited in a finances company. It was packed in three(2)metal trunk boxes as photographic materials.I would need your particulars to enable me prepare documents which will authenticate that the Consignment belongs to you as the next of kin to MR Michael Osterkamp and to enable you claim the money. I want to be assured of a safe account where the money will be deposited pending my arrival.This transaction is absolutely risk free with no illegal complications,I have made all necessary arrangements for a successful transaction. Before this money is entrusted into your care, there must be an agreement that will be reached between us stating that: 1.BOTH PARTIES WILL NOT FOR ANY REASON CHEAT EACH OTHER. 2.BOTH PARTIES WILL WORK TOGETHER TO SEE THIS TRANSACTION THROUGH. 3.A HIGH DEGREE OF TRUST AND CONFIDENTIALITY WILL BE APPLIED FOR THE SAKE OF OUR WORK. 4.I AND MY PARTNER WILL STRONGLY BE BY YOUR SIDE AS YOU CLAIM THIS FUND AND I AND MY PARTNER WILL ARRAGE AN ATTORNEY(LAWYER)WHO WILL WORK ON YOUR BEHALF TO GET THE NECESSARY PAPERS NEEDED FOR A SMOOTH TRANSACTION. 5.YOU WILL NOT DISAPPEAR WITH OUR FUND AFTER YOU HAVECLAIMED IT. 6.DISBURSEMENT RATIO WILL BE 70 FOR ME AND MY COLLEAGUE,15 FOR YOU, 5% WILL BE DONATED TO CHARITY,WHILE 10% WILL TAKE CARE OF OUR MUTUALEXPENCES. There is need for you to respond to this offer immediately as the government of my country have concluded plans to apply the money into arms procurement to project wars and unrest in African continent.I must let you know that a high degree of trust is required and also we will like to use our own share to go into any lucrative business with your help/assistance. Awaiting your urgent response now. Yours Faithfully Mr. Frank Williams. _______________________________________________________________________________________________________ Obtén gratis tu cuenta de correo en StarMedia Email. ¡Regístrate hoy mismo!. http://www.starmedia.com/email

CENTRAL BANK OF NIGERIA FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPT. TINUBU SQUARE, LAGOS NIGERIA EMAIL-Lawrencesmith@caramail.com 25TH OF January 2003 ATTN: PRESIDENT/CEO STRICTLY PRIVATE BUSINESS PROPOSAL I am Mr. Lawrence Smith. A, the bills and exchange Director at the Foreign Remittance Department of the Central Bank of Nigeria. I am writing you this letter to ask for your support and cooperation to carrying this business opportunity in my department. We discovered abandoned the sum of US$37,400,000.00 (Thirty seven million four hundred thousand unitedstates dollars) in an account that belong to one of our foreign customers,an American late Engr.ben daniel (Junior) an oil merchant with the federal government of Nigeria who died along with his entire family of a wife and two children in Kenya Airbus (A310-300) flight KQ430 in November2000. Since we heard of his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and put claims for his money as the heir, because we cannotrelease the fund from his account unless someone applies for claims asthe next of kin to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines. Unfortunately, neither their family member nor distant relative has appeared to claim the said fund. Upon this discovery, I and other officialsin my department have agreed to make business with you release the total amount into your account as the heir of the fund since no one came for it or discovered either maintained account with our bank, other wisethe fund will be returned to the bank treasury as unclaimed fund. We have agreed that our ratio of sharing will be as stated thus: 30%for you as foreign partner and 70% for us the officials in my department. Upon the successful completion of this transfer, my colleague and I will come to your country and mind our share. It is from our 60% we intend to import computer accessories into my country as way of recycling thefund. To commence this transaction we require you to immediately indicateyour interest by calling me or sending me a fax immediately on the aboveTelefax # and enclose your private contact Telephone #, Fax #, full nameand address and your designated banking co- ordinates to enable us fileletter of claim to the appropriate department for necessary approvalsbefore the transfer can be made. Note also, this transaction must be kept strictly confidential becauseof its nature. NB: Please remember to give me your Phone and Fax No Mr. Lawrence Smith. A ------------------------------------------ Faites un voeu et puis Voila ! www.voila.fr

DEAR SIR/MADAM, THIS LETTER MAY COME TO YOU AS A SURPRISE DUE TO THE FACT THAT WE HAVE NOT YET MET. THE MESSAGE COULD BE STRANGE BUT REAL IF YOU PAY SOME ATTENTION TO IT. I COULD HAVE NOTIFIED YOU ABOUT IT AT LEAST FOR THE SAKE OF YOUR INTEGRITY. PLEASE ACCEPT MY SINCERE APOLOGIES. IN BRINGING THIS MESSAGE OF GOODWILL TO YOU, I HAVE TO SAY THAT I HAVE NO INTENTIONS OF CAUSING YOU ANY PAINS. I AM MS. PETER SAVIMBI, DAUGHTER OF THE LATE REBEL LEADER JONAS SAVIMBI OF ANGOLA WHO WAS KILLED ON THE 22ND OF FEBUARY 2002 . MY LATE FATHER, JONAS SAVIMBI WAS ABLE TO DEPOSIT A LARGE SUM OF MONEY IN DIFFERENT BANKS IN EUROPE AND THE MOVEMENT OF HIS FAMILY MEMBERS (INCLUDING ME) IS RESTRICTED. WE ARE FORBIDDEN TO EITHER TRAVEL ABROAD OR OUT OF OUR LOCALITIES. PRESENTLY, THE SUM OF US$8,500,000.00 EIGHT MILLION, FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND DOLLARS MY FATHER TRANSFERRED TO NETHERLANDS IS SAFE AND IS WITH A SECURITY FIRM. I AM THEREFORE SOLICITING YOUR HELP TO HAVE THIS MONEY TRANSFERRED INTO YOUR ACCOUNT BEFORE MY GOVERNMENT GET WIND OF THIS FUND. YOU MAY KNOW THAT MY FATHER WAS A REBEL LEADER IN ANGOLA BEFORE HIS DEATH AND MY REASON FOR DOING THIS IS BECAUSE IT WILL BE DIFFICULT FOR THE ANGOLAN GOVERNMENT TO TRACE MY FATHER'S MONEY TO AN INDIVIDUAL'S ACCOUNT, ESPECIALLY WHEN SUCH AN INDIVIDUAL HAS NO RELATIONSHIP WITH MY FATHER THEREBY KEEPING THAT MONEY FOR MY FAMILY USE. AT PRESENT THE MONEY AS I SAID IS KEPT IN A SECURITY COMPANY IN THE NETHERLAND. I AM CURRENTLY AND TEMPORARILY LIVING IN ANGOLA WITH MY HUSBAND. MY BROTHER HAS A REFUGEE STATUS IN THE NETHERLANDS. MOREOVER, THE POLITICAL CLIMATE IN ANGOLA AT THE MOMENT IS SO SENSITIVE AND UNSTABLE SO IT WILL BE BETTER WE DO THIS TRANSACTION NOW. WITH THIS PASSWORD AND INFORMATION I WILL SEND YOU, AND THE CHANGE OF OWNERSHIP THAT I WILL SEND TO THE SECURITY FIRM, YOU WILL BE ABLE TO REPRESENT US IN THE NETHERLANDS TO CLAIM THIS CONSIGNMENT FROM THE SECURITY FIRM. WHEN YOU ARE READY, I WILL GIVE YOU THE INFORMATION NEEDED BEFORE YOU CAN GET ACCESS TO THE FUND, YOU WILL THEN PROCEED TO NETHERLANDS WHERE YOU WILL SIGN THE FINAL RELEASE DOCUMENTS OF THE US$8,500,000.00 EIGHT, MILLION, FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND DOLLARS. I WILL GIVE YOU FURTHER DETAILS WHEN I GET YOUR RESPONSE TO THIS LETTER ASSURING US THAT YOU WILL BE ABLE TO REPRESENT US IN THE NETHERLANDS ANDTHAT WILL MAKE THIS TRANSACTION CONFIDENTIAL. IT IS VERY IMPORTANT THAT YOU GIVE ME YOUR PHONE AND FAX NUMBERS WHILE THIS IS KEPT CONFIDENTIAL. YOU CAN CONTACT ME WITH MY E-MAILADDRESS,peter_savimbi20@phantomemail.com YOURS SINCERELY, PETER SAVIMBI

UNION BANK OF NIGERIA PLC # 145 BANK RAOD VICTORIA ISLAND LAGOS NIGERIA. ATTN: Dear PLS REPLY TO MY PRAVATE BOX suleman775@mailsurf.com URGENT BUSINESS PROPOSAL First, I must solicit your confidence in this transaction this is byvirtue of its nature as being utterly confidencial andtop secret. Though I know that a transaction of this magnitudewill make any one apprehensive and woried, but I am assuring you that all will be well at the end of the day. We have decided to contact you due to the urgency of this transaction, as we have been reliably informed of your discreetness and ability of this nature by Chief Omole. Let me start by introducing myself properly to you. I am Barrister BELLO MAN SULE officer with the union Bank of Nigeria Plc, Lagos. I came to know you through Chief Omole who assured me that you are Reliable and Reputable Person to handle this Confidential Transaction, which involves the transfer of Huge sum of Money to a Foreign Account requiring Maximum confidence. THE PROPOSITION: A Foreigner an American, Late Engr. John Creek (Snr) an oil Merchant with The Federal Government of Nigeria, until his death months ago in Kenya Air Bus (A310 - 300) Flight KQ430, Banked with us at Union Bank of Nigeria Plc, Lagos and had a closing balance as at the end of September, 2000 worth Us$30,000.000.00 (Thirty Million United State Dollars), the bank now expects next of kin as beneficiary. Valuable effforts are being made by the Union Bank of Nigeria to get in touch with any of the Creek's Family or Relatives but to no success. It is because of the perceived possibility of not being able to locate any of Late Engr. John Creek (Snr.)'s next of kin (He had no wife or childrenthat is know to us). The Management underthe influence of our Chairman and Members of the Board of Directors, that arrangement has been made for thefund to be decleared "Unclaimed" and ubsequentlly be donated to the trust fund for arms ammunition to further enhance the course of War in Africa and the World in General. In order to avert this negative development, some of my trusted colleagues and I now seek your permission to have stand as next of kin to the late Engr. John Creek (Snr.) so that the fund US$30 Milion will be released and paid into your Account as the beneficiary next of kin. All documents and proves to enable you get this fund wilcarefully worked out. We have secure from the probate an order of Mandamus to locate any of deceased beneficiaries, and more so we are assuring you that this business is 100% Rick Free involvement. Your share stays while the rest be for myself and my colleagues for investment purpose, According to agreement within both parties. As soon as we receive an acknowledgement of recipt of this mail message the procedure for the transfer of this fund will be made known to you. PLS REPLY TO MY PRAVATE BOX suleman775@mailsurf.com I await your timely response. BELLO MAN SULE ------------------------------------------------- HKNETMAIL.COM Free WEB MAIL Service by HKNET

DEAR, I AM THE DIRECTOR OF BILLS AND EXCHANGE AT THE FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPARTMENT OF OUR BANK HERE IN ABIDJAN COTE D’IVOIRE. IN MY DEPARTMENT WE DISCOVERED AN ABANDONED SUM OF US$12.500,000.00 (TWELEVE. FIVE MILLION USD ONLY) IN AN ACCOUNT THAT BELONGS TO ONE OF OUR FOREIGN CUSTOMERS WHO DIED ALONG WITH HIS ENTIRE FAMILY IN NOVEMBER 1999 IN A PLANE CRASH. SINCE WE GOT INFORMATION ABOUT HIS DEATH, WE HAVE BEEN EXPECTING HIS NEXT OF KIN TO COME OVER AND CLAIM HIS MONEY BECAUSE WE CANNOT RELEASE IT UNLESS SOMEBODY APPLIES FOR IT AS NEXT OF KIN OR RELATION TO THE DECEASED AS INDICATED IN OUR BANKING GUIDELINES. UNFORTUNATELY WE LEARNT THAT ALL HIS SUPPOSED NEXT OF KIN OR RELATIONS DIED ALONG WITH HIM AT THE PLANE CRASH LEAVING NOBODY BEHIND FOR THE CLAIM. IT IS THEREFORE UPON THIS DISCOVERY THAT I AND ONE OF THE OFFICIALS IN THE DEPARTMENT NOW DECIDED TO MAKE BUSINESS WITH YOU AND RELEASE THE MONEY TO YOU AS THE NEXT OF KIN OR RELATIONS OF THE DECEASED FOR SAFETY AND SUBSEQUENT DISBURSEMENT SINCE NOBODY IS COMING FOR IT AND WE DON’T WANT THIS MONEY TO GO DISBURSEMENT ACCOUNT AS UNCLAIMED BILL. THE BANKING LAW AND GUIDELINES HERE STIPULATED THAT IF SUCH MONEY REMAINED UNCLAIMED AFTER FOUR YEARS THE MONEY WILL BE TRANSFERRED INTO FEDERAL GOVERNMENT ACCOUNT AS UNCLAIMED FUND. THE REQUEST OF A FOREIGNER AS NEXT OF KIN IN THIS BUSINESS IS OCCASIONED BY THE FACT THAT THE CUSTOMERS WAS A FOREIGNER AND AN IVORIEN CANNOT STAND AS NEXT OF KIN TO A FOREIGNER. WE AGREE THAT 15% OF THIS MONEY WILL BE FOR YOU AS FOREIGN PARTNER AND 5% FOR EXPENSES INCURRED DURING THE COURSE OF REMITTANCE. THEREAFTER TO THE PERCENTAGES INDICATED. THEREFORE TO ENABLE THE IMMEDIATE TRANSFER OF THE FUND TO YOU AS ARRANGED. YOU MUST APPLY FIRST TO THE BANK AS A RELATION OR NEXT OF KIN OF THE DECEASED INDICATING YOUR BANK ACCOUNT NUMBER AND LOCATION WHERE IN THE MONEY WILL BE REMITTED . UPON RECEIPT OF YOUR REPLY I WILL SEND TO YOU THE TEXT OF THE APPLICATION. AS SOON AS YOU RECEIVE THIS LETTER, YOU SHOULD CONTACT ME IMMEDIATELY AND INDICATE YOUR DIRECT AND CONFIDENTIAL TELEPHONE/FAX NUMBERS FOR THE EFFECTIVE COMMUNICATION REQUIRED. TRUSTING TO HEAR FROM YOU IMMEDIATELY ON TELEPHONE NUMBER 0022507822694. YOURS FAITHFULLY, F. LAMINE DIRECTOR, FOREIGN OPERATIONS _________________________________________________________ Gagne une PS2 ! Envoie un SMS avec le code PS au 61166 (0,35€ Hors coût du SMS)

Dear, Naturally, this letter will come to you as a surprise since we have not met, permit me however, I am Mr. Lawrence Abba, a Zimbabwean Farmer. I am contacting you as the need to for me to have a foreign partner in your country has become necessary due to my plans to relocate and establish a private company in that region, as the present political instability in my country Zimbabwe, does not encourage financial investment as the environment is not conducive for investment and most of all security is not insured, just as reported by international media. I got your contacts through personal research and out of desperation I decided to reach you through this medium. I will give you more information as regards to this as soon as you reply and I repose great confidence in you hence my approach due to security network place on us and I hope you will not let me out to security personal. This problem started when the Zimbabwean government under the leadership of President Robert Mugabe announced a degree on May 31st 2000 to seize more than 849 white-owned farms. So far, more than 1,400 white owned farms have been invaded and confiscated, as well as claiming the properties of the farmers. Consequently, most of my colleagues and our properties were seized again putting us to total confusion, frustration and hopelessness by the administration of President Mugabe in my country and we where subjected to psychological torture by the security agents in the country. Some of my friends are still under detention, although arrangements are being made for their release, now I have no confidence with anybody within my country. During these periods, as reported by some international media including the CNN, so many white farmers were killed, the government is not stopping at this, as just recently the government have asked all white-farmers to give up their farms to black farmers or risk going to prison. Having lived in this country Zimbabwe for so many years, I have no other country to go to, nor can I trace any of my distant relatives. Therefore, I decided to contact you, for your assistance, so that I can establish a company in your country and relocate there. Also, I must re-iterate the importance of having a citizen of your country to front as the owner of the enterprise, due to the fact that I am a foreigner. For this purpose, I have put in a security deposit all monies from the sale of my farm and farming equipments (including tractors etc) which amounted to US$6.5Million, I had to move the money out of the country through a very secret arranged channel in a very unconventional method by my friend an official at the "Security Minting & Printing Company" of my country. Presently, the money is in an Oversea Country, under the custody of a private security firm whose name is withheld for now until we open communication. I will upon receiving your consent prepare every document to enable you receive this money on my behalf, pending my arrival to meet with you in your country so that we can both make further arrangements with regards to establishing the company. As a partner you will be entitled to 20% stake in whichever company that you both decide to establish when I arrive your country. I am waiting urgently for your response and please treat with utmost confidentiality. Best Regards Lawrence Abba.

From: Mr Benard Gelicah Sankoh. benardsankoh@rome.com Dear, I am well confident of your capability to assist me in a transaction for mutual benefit of both parties, ie(me and you) I am also believing that you will not expose or betray the trust and confidence I am about to establish with you. I have decided to contact you with greatest delight and personal respect. I am Mr Benard Gelicah Sankoh Son to FODAY SANKOH who was arrested by the ECOMAOG PEACE KEEPING FORCE months ago in my country Sierra Leone. Few days before the arrest of my father, he confided in me and ordered me to go to his underground safe and move out immediately, with a Deposit Agreement and Cash Receipt he made with a security Company where he deposited One Iron Box containing USD$22 million dollars cash (TWENTY TWO MILLION DOLLARS). This money was made from the sell of Gold and Diamond by my father and he have already decided to use this money for future investment of the family. Thereafter, I contacted the security company and notify them with the two documents and confirmed the deposit of the box by my father. Meanwhile, my father have instructed me to look for a trusted foreigner who can assist me to move out this money immediately for investment . Based on this, I solicited for your assistance to transfer this fund into your Account, but I will demand for the following requirement: (1) Could you provide for me a safe Bank Account where this fund will be transferred to in your country or another nearby country where taxation will not take great toll on the money? (2) Could you be able to assist me to obtain my travelling papers after this transfer to enable me come over to meet you in your country for the investment of this money? (3) Could you be able to introduce me to a profitable business venture that would not require much technical expertise in your country where part of this fund will be invested? Please, all these requirements are urgently needed as it will enable me to establish a stronger business relationship with you hence I will like you to be the general overseer of the investment thereafter. I am a Christian and I will please, want you to handle this transaction based on the trust I have established on you. For your assistance in this transaction, I have decided to offer you 15% percent commission of the total amount at the end of this business. The security of this business is very important to me and as such, I would like you to keep this business very confidential. Upon the receipt of your mail I shall expect your urgent reply. Thank you and God bless you Mr Benard Gelicah Sankoh. -- __________________________________________________________ Sign-up for your own FREE Personalized E-mail at Mail.com http://www.mail.com/?sr=signup

Good day, It is my humble pleasure to write this letter irrespective of the fact that you do not know me. However, I came to know of you in my private search for a reliable and trustworthy person that can handle a confidential transaction of this nature in respect of this, I got your contact through an uprooted search on the internet. Though I know that a transaction of this magnitude will make any one apprehensive and worried, but I am assuring you that all will be well at the end of the day I am Stevens Bangura, son of late Mr John Bangura of Sierra Leone who was killed by the Sierra Leone's rebel forces on the 24th of December,1999 in my country Sierra Leone. When he was still alive, he deposited one trunk box containing the sum of USD$30 million dollars in cash (Ten Million dollars). with a private security and safe deposit company here in Abidjan Cote d´Ivoire. This money was made from the sell of Gold and Diamond by my mother and she have already decided to use this money for future investment of the family. Recently, I rushed down to Abidjan after being able to locate where my late father kept the depository Agreement made between himself and the security company. I have confirmed from the security company that the consignment is in their custody, when I demanded for the release of the consignment to me in my capacity of being the son of Mr Bangura, the depositor of the consignment, I was told that in the absence of my father, the only person that can demand for the release of the consignment is my late father´s foreign partner on whose behalf the consignment was deposited. Meanwhile, my father have instructed me that in the case of his death, that I should look for a trusted foreigner who can assist me to move out this money from Côte d´Ivoire immediately for investment . Based on this , I solicit for your assistance to transfer this fund into your Account, but I will demand for the following requirement: (1) Could you provide for me a safe Bank Account where this fund will be transferred to in your country after retrieving the box containing the money from the custody of the security company. (2) Could you be able to introduce me to a profitable business venture that would not require much technical expertise in your country where part of this fund will be invested? I am a Christian and I will please, want you to handle this transaction based on the trust I have established on you. For your assistance in this transaction, I have decided to compensate you with 10 percent of the total amount at the end of this business. The security of this business is very important to me and as such, I would like you to keep this business very confidential. I shall expect an early response from you. Thank you and God bless. Yours sincerely, Stevens Bangura _________________________________________________________ Gagne une PS2 ! Envoie un SMS avec le code PS au 61166 (0,35€ Hors coût du SMS)

Dear webmaster , Union Bank Of Nig. Plc Union House Marina Lagos State Nigeria. PRIVATE AND CONFIDENTIAL Dear Sir/madam I sincerely write to seek your co-operation and trust to enable my colleagues and I carry out an urgent business opportunity in my department. I work with the Union Bank of Nigeria PLC; currently I am the senior manager of bills and exchange at the foreign remittance department of my bank. I was the account officer to one Mr. Ali B. Ashraf who died along with his family on the 8th of November 1996 in an ADC Boeing 727 plane crash at Egirin River. All 141 passengers on board were feared dead. He left in his domiciliary account the total sum of Sixty Five Million United States Dollars [$65million] Since the management got the information of his death we have been expecting any of his relation or his next of kin to come up and claim his money. Unfortunately from the day of his death till the time of this letter none of his relation or friends has come up for the claim. The banking and financial law of Union bank of Nigeria Plc stipulates that if such fund remained unclaimed after a period of four years (4) it will be transferred into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill. On this discovery sir, I and a colleague of mine now decided do business with you and release the money to you as the next of kin to Ali B. Ashraf for safety and subsequent disbursement. I will soon proceed for my retirement in the middle of this year, and I personally do not want this fund to be transferred into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill. That is why I wanted the fund to be move out of the bank before I proceed on my retirement from the banking services by june 15th 2003. The need for a foreigner as next of kin in this project is occasioned by the fact that the customer Mr. Ali Ashraf was a foreigner and a Nigerian cannot stand as his next of kin or heir. We have agreed that 15% of the Fund would be for you as foreign partner; thereafter my colleague and I will visit your country for disbursement according to the percentages indicated. To enable the immediate transfer of the fund into your nominated account, you will first apply to the bank as the next of kin of the deceased, indicating your bank account number and location wherein the money will be remitted. Upon receipt of your acknowledgement indicating your interest, I will send to you the text of the application that you will send to the Union Bank authority for an approval to submit your claims. Send your reply through my direct private email address and indicate your direct Fax and telephone numbers for effective communication that this transaction is required. Do not reply through the union bank email address because it will fall at the receptionist's desk and is for public use . Please note that you are not to appear in person, as every thing regarding this project will be strictly on documentations and every banking documents needed for this transaction will be taken care of by my self. Looking forward to urgently hearing from you. Yours Faithfully MR. DONALD ATTAH

PLEASE COME AND HELP Before you read my message for which I am requesting for financial assistance to enrol at American Intercontinental University, I want to enjoin you to surrender your life to Christ. Please repent for the Kingdom of God is at hand. I will be sending you revelation messages a week later. Thanks and God bless. God bless you once again. Amen -------------------------- DEAR SERVANTS OF GOD, I AM CYRIL AKWARANDU, I GAINED ADMISSION INTO AMERICAN INTERCONTINENTAL UNIVERSITY, LONDON BUT I HAVE NO MONEY TO PAY FOR THE TUITION FEE OF £3,670 AND I HAVE NO PERSON TO ASSIST ME. AS A RESULT, MY ADMISSION WAS DEFARRED TO JANUARY 2003. I HAVE BEEN INFORMED BY MY ADMISSION COUNSELLOR, THAT I NEED TO PAY FOR THE FEE IMMEDIATELY IN ORDER TO JOIN THE 2003 SESSION. ANY AMOUNT GOD LAIDS IN YOUR HEART, PLEASE ASSIST AND THE ALMIGHTY WILL REWARD YOU ABUNDANTLY. THIS AMOUNT CAN BE PAID STRAIGHT TO THE SCHOOLS ACCOUNT AS STATED BELOW AND A CONFIRMATION SENT TO ME VIA MY E-MAIL (cyakwarandu@hotmail.com) I HEREBY PLEAD WITH YOU TO COME TO MY AID WITH WHAT THE LORD LAIDS IN YOUR HEART. I NEED TO PAY THE TUITION FEE AND I HAVE NO BODY EXCEPT GOD TO ASSIST IN THIS REGARD. GOD WILL BLESS YOU MORE AND MORE, IF YOU WOULD ALLOW YOURSELF USED TO HELP THE POOR OUT OF THE DUNGEON. GOD BLESS YOU. AMEN. DON'T BE WEARY IN WELL DOING FOR YOUR REWARD IS IN THE KINGDOM OF HEAVEN. The information above can be confirmed from American Intercontinental University, London and below is the Letter of Acceptance to me from the University. Congratulations again on you acceptance. As I mentioned you now need to pay your full fees now so that we can send you your visa letter. To make the payment your sponsor needs to go to his bank and get them to transfer £3,670.00 to our bank account. The bank details are as follows - Bank address: National Westminster Bank Westminster Branch PO BOX 3038 London SW1H 0HN UK Account number: 48 20 22 31. Account name: The American European Corporation Sort code: 56 00 33 Please fax a statement from the bank, showing that this transfer has been made, and including the student name on the fax. The fax number is at the bottom of this message. As I mentioned earlier I will be leaving the University on Monday. Your new admissions officer is going to be Amer Mourad and you can contact him by phone on +44 207 467 5645 or by email on amourad@aiulondon.ac.uk <http://lw15fd.law15.hotmail.msn.com/cgi-bin/compose?curmbox=F000000001&a=9c169e6ac45d169cd524ad16a41b8ffc&mailto=1&to=amourad@aiulondon.ac.uk&msg=MSG1030550435.140&start=375935&len=2328&src=&type=x> Best regards Anna Davison ********************************** Anna Davison Admissions Officer AIU - London 110 Marylebone High Street London W1U 4RY Tel: +44 (0) 207 467 2441 Fax: +44 (0) 207 467 5641 email: adavison@aiulondon.ac.uk <http://lw15fd.law15.hotmail.msn.com/cgi-bin/compose?curmbox=F000000001&a=9c169e6ac45d169cd524ad16a41b8ffc&mailto=1&to=adavison@aiulondon.ac.uk&msg=MSG1030550435.140&start=375935&len=2328&src=&type=x> www.aiulondon.ac.uk

ATTN: Sir/Madam. My name is MR YARO BAMIYI, the eldest son of Rtd General BUBA S.G.BAMIYI, who was the estwhile Minister of the Federal Capital territory Abuja in thelate General Sani Abachas Regime of 1993-1998.I am contacting you in a benevolent spirit; utmost confidence and trust to enable us provide a solution to a money transfer of $25M that is presently putting my entire family into great disarray. You may be quite surprised at my sudden contact to you but do not despair, I got your contact from a business site on the internet and following the information I gathered about you, I was convinced that you could be of assistance to me. So,I decided to contact you at once due to the urgency required for us to immediately transfer the said funds out of the country. During the time my father was in the government with the late General Sani Abacha as the head of state,they were both involved in several deals that yielded Billions of Dollars. The prominent amongst the deals was monies that emanated from funds set aside for the importation of Arms and Ammunitions to boost the Nigerian Defense, funds set to embark on an oversea ampaign to counter the United States action to put a stop to the self succession bid of the Abacha government to retain power, and monies set aside to rehabilitate the ailing Nigerian Petroleum Refineries and the National Electric Power Authority which supplies Electricity to the entire nation. If you are conversant with world news, you would understand better. During this period my father was able to make some good money for himself and kept in his private bank accounts. The then head of state General Sani Abacha transferred his share of the money through a Lebanese businessman, Chagoury and a Jewish businessman, Mark Rissar to bank accounts overseas. Unfortunately, all the secrets were revealed by the investigation agencies set up by the successive governments and most of the Abacha?s loots were traced and repatriated fromthe various accounts to the Federal Government Treasury. Out of the money my father made, he left the sum of N50 Million (Fifty Million Naira) in the CBN escrow account for further transfer into a foreign account and a sum of $25M (TWENTY-FIVE Million Dollars) was kept in a Private security firm here in Nigeria. Through the confessions made by the Abacha?s Family, the N50 Million was recovered by the investigating agency from the CBN escrow account. But were unable to discover the $25M, which he kept in the vaults. The reason is because no names were used to lodge in the funds.Instead, he used PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION NUMBERS (PIN) and declared the contents as Bearer Bonds and Treasury Bills. Also the firm issued him with a certificate of deposit of the consignments. Note thatI have these information in my custody. Right now, my father has been arrested and detained for interrogation. As the eldest son of my Father, I believe that I owe the entire family an obligation to ensure that the $25M is successfully transferred abroad for investment purposes. With the present situation, I cannot do it all by myself. It is based on this that I am making this contact with you. I have done a thorough homework and fine-tuned the best wayto create you as the beneficiary to the funds and effect the transfer accordingly. Is rest assured that the modalities I have resolved to finalize the entire project guarantees our safety and the successful transfer of the funds. So, you will be absolutely right when you say that this project is risk free and viable. If you are capable and willing to assist,contact me at once via email for more details. Believe me, there is no one else we can trust gain.All my fathers friends have deserted us after exploiting us on the pretence of trying to help my father. As it is said, "it is at the time of problems that you know your true friends". So long as you keep everything to yourself, we would definitely have no problems. For your assistance, I am ready to give you as much as 20% of the total funds after transfer and invest a reasonable percentage into any viable business you may suggest. Please, I need your assistance to make this happen and please; do not undermine it because it will also be asource of up liftment to you also. You have absolutely nothing to loose in assisting us instead,you have so much to gain. Awaiting your urgent and positive response. Best Regards MR.YARO BAMIYI. Alternative Email:(yaroroyal@bluemail.ch) OR (yarobamiyi@themail.com)

DR.DOUGLAS NWANKWO. DIRECTOR AND MEMBER OF THE CONTRACT AWARD PANEL WITH THE PIPELINES AND PRODUCTS MARKETING COMPANY (P.P.M.C) A SUBSIDIARY OF THE NIGERIAN NATIONAL PETROLEUM CORPORATION. TEL234-1-7760962 ATTENTION: PRESIDENT/CEO I AM A MEMBER OF THE CONTRACT AWARD PANEL WITH THE PIPELINES AND PRODUCTS MARKETING COMPANY (P.P.M.C) A SUBSIDIARY OF THE NIGERIAN NATIONAL PETROLEUM CORPORATION. OUR DUTIES INCLUDE EVALUATION, VETTING AND APPROVAL FOR PAYMENT OF CONTRACTS AND SERVICES RENDERED FOR THE (P.P.M.C). I HEAD THIS SEVEN MAN PANEL IN CHARGE OF CONTRACT AWARD AND PAYMENT APPROVALS AND CAME TO KNOW OF YOU IN MY SEARCH FOR A RELIABLE AND REPUTABLE PERSON TO HANDLE A VERY CONFIDENTIAL TRANSACTION WHICH INVOLVES THE TRANSFER OF FUNDS TO A FOREIGN ACCOUNT. THERE WERE SERIES OF CONTRACTS EXECUTED BY A CONSORTIUM OF ABB LUMUS, J.G.C CORPORATION OF JAPAN, BOUYGUES OFFSHORE AND A JOINT VENTURE OF SPIEBATIGNOLES AND DRESSER GMBH OF GERMANY IN FAVOUR OF THE (P.P.M.C) AMONG WHICH WERE 1) THE EXPANSION AND MAINTENANCE OF PIPE LINE NETWORK FROM ONE MAIN STATION TO ESCRAVOS DEPOT FOR CRUDE OIL AND DOWNSTREAM PRODUCTS. DISTRIBUTION AND SUBSEQUENT EVACUATION --USD333 Million 2) CONTRACT FOR THE TURN AROUND MAINTENANCE (TAM) OF THE VARIOUS REFINERIES IN THE COUNTRY. 3) THE EXPANSION AND CONSTRUCTION OF NEW STORAGE TANKS FOR PETROLEUM PRODUCTS (DEPOSIT) --USD94 Million. THE ORIGINAL VALUE OF THESE CONTRACTS WERE DELIBERATELY OVER INVOICED TO THE SUM OF THIRTY EIGHT MILLION, SIX HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS (USD38.6 MILLION) WHICH HAS RECENTLY BEEN APPROVED AND NOW READY TO BE TRANSFERRED BEING THAT THE COMPANIES THAT ACTUALLY EXECUTED THE AFOREMENTIONED CONTRACTS HAVE BEEN FULLY PAID AND THE PROJECTS OFFICIALLY COMMISSIONED. CONSEQUENTLY, MY COLLEAGUES AND I ARE WILLING TO TRANSFER THE TOTAL AMOUNT OF USD38.6 MILLION TO YOUR ACCOUNT FOR SUBSEQUENT DISBURSEMENT, SINCE WE AS CIVIL SERVANTS ARE PROHIBITED BY THE CONDUCT BUREAU (CIVIL SERVICE LAWS) FROM OPENING OR OPERATING FOREIGN ACCOUNTS IN OUR NAMES. NEEDLESS TO SAY, THE TRUST REPOSED IN YOU AT THIS JUNCTURE IS ENORMOUS, IN RETURN, WE HAVE AGREED AMONGST OURSELVES TO OFFER YOU 25% OF THE ENTIRE SUM, WHILE 5% SHALL BE SET ASIDE FOR ANY INCIDENTAL EXPENSES THAT WOULD BE INCURRED DURING THE COURSE OF THE TRANSACTION AND WOULD BE SPLIT AFTER THE MONEY IS TRANSFERRED INTO YOUR ACCOUNT WHILE THE REMAINING 7O% WOULD BE FOR MY COLLEAGUES AND I. YOU MUST HOWEVER NOTE THAT THIS TRANSACTION IS SUBJECT TO THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS; OUR CONVICTION OF YOUR TRANSPARENT HONESTY, DILIGENCE AND THAT YOU MUST ACCORD THIS TRANSACTION UTMOST SECRECY AND CONFIDENTIALITY. MODALITIES HAVE BEEN WORKED OUT AT THE HIGHEST LEVELS OF THE FEDERAL MINISTRY OF FINANCE, AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK AND THE PRESIDENTIAL TASK FORCE ON CONTRACT PAYMENT FOR THE IMMEDIATE REMITTANCE OF THE FUND WITHIN 7 WORKING DAYS SUBJECT TO YOUR SATISFACTION OF THE ABOVE STATED TERMS. OUR ASSURANCE IS THAT YOUR ROLE SHALL BE TOTALLY RISK FREE.TO ACCORD THIS TRANSACTION THE LEGALITY IT DESERVES AND MUTUAL SECURITY OF THE FUNDS, THE WHOLE APPROVAL PROCEDURES SHALL BE OFFICIALLY AND LEGALLY PROCESSED WITH YOUR NAME AND COMPANY AS THE LEGAL AND BONAFIDE BENEFICIARY OF THE FUND. ONCE MORE, I WANT YOU TO UNDERSTAND THAT HAVING PUT IN OVER 20 YEARS IN THE CIVIL SERVICE OF MY COUNTRY, I AM VERY MUCH AVERSED TO HAVING MY IMAGE AND CAREER DENTED. THIS MATTER SHOULD BE TREATED WITH UTMOST SECRECY AND URGENCY. KINDLY EXPEDITE ACTION AS WE ARE WELL BEHIND SCHEDULE TO ENABLE US INCLUDE THIS TRANSFER IN THIS QUARTER OF THIS FISCAL YEAR CONTRACTUAL PAYMENTS.PLEASE CONTACT ME BY E-MAILS/TELEPHONE. THE TELEPHONE LINES COULD BE BUSY BUT IF YOU PERSEVERE YOU WOULD GET THROUGH EVENTUALLY. I AWAIT YOUR IMMEDIATE RESPONSE. YOURS FAITHFULLY DR.DOUGLAS NWANKWO

Dear Sir, I Am Mrs. Safinatu Al Mustapha The First Wife Of Major Al Mustapha The Chief Security Officer (Cso)To Major General Sani Abacha Who Diedin Office . Since The Death Of The President, The Present Nigerian Government Of General Olusegun Obasanjo Has Done Virtually Nothing Except To Hunt Down The Family Of The Late President And All Those Associated Withe Him.The Government Has Seized And Frozen All The Assets And Funds Of The Abacha Family And His Associates. You Can Visit The Following Websites For A First Hand Information On This: Http://Allafrica.Com/Stories/200203180074.Html Http://Www.Time.Com/Time/Europe/Magazine/2000/27/Swiss.Html My Husband Has Been In Detention For The Past 3 Years After Forfeiting His Assets To The Government. All His Known Bank Accounts Are Presently Frozen And This Has Made It Very Difficult For Us To Fight His Various Court Cases With The Present Government And Life In General Is Becoming Unbearable For Us. When This Whole Saga Began, My Husband Did Not Take It Serious Thinking That He Will Be In Detention For A While And Then Regain His Freedom But To His Chagrin, He Has Been Held For 3 Years And Now The Funds He Left With Us Has Been Exhausted By Attorney Fees. Although The Government Froze His Accounts And Seized His Properties, But Unknown To Them My Husband Had Some Funds Stashed In Safe Deposit Vault With A Security Company In A Neighboring Country. The Amount Of This Deposit Is Us $60 Million And Was Given To Him By The Late President For Safe Keeping Outside The Country Before His Death. My Detained Husband Has Asked Me To Seek The Assistance/Collaboration Of A Foreigner To Help Me In Securing The Release And Eventual Transfer Of This Money Oversee To Ensure That The Nigerian Government Does Not Seize It Equally. This Is Why I Am Contacting You To Assist Me In The Release And Transfer Of This Money To Your Country For Safe Keeping. Because Of Restriction On My Movement Here, My Husband Has Advice Me To Use The Services Of My Personal Lawyer To Liaise With You On This Transaction To Ensure That I Am Not Cheated In Any Way given Our Present Circumstances. As Compensation For Your Envisaged Role In This Transaction, My Husband Has Asked Me To Offer You Us $6.0 Million As Fees, This Should Be Deducted From The Deposit Upon Withdrawal. Your Envisaged Expenditure In Securing The Release And Transfer Of This Money Is To Be Tabulated For A Refund Upon Transfer. Please Help My Family Out Of Our Present Ordeal By Treating This Transaction With Utmost Secrecy . Please Forward Your Observation Through My Lawyer Who Is Better Placed To Plot The Logistics With You. My lawyer Is Barr. Abdul Mohammed Email Mohammedchambers99@Yahoo.Co.Uk Thanking You In Anticipation Of Your Cooperation. Yours, Mrs. Safinatu Al Mustapha

FROM THE DESK OF MR. MIKE CHUKWU. ZENITH INTERNATIONAL BANK PLC, LAGOS-NIGERIA. EMAIL: mikechukwu32@primposta.com DEAR SIR, STRICTLY A PRIVATE BUSINESS PROPOSAL I AM MIKE CHUKWU , THE MANAGER, BILLS AND EXCHANGE AT THE FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPARTMENT OF THE ZENITH INTERNATIONAL BANK PLC. I AM WRITING THIS LETTER TO ASK FOR YOUR SUPPORT AND COOPERATION TO CARRY OUT THIS BUSINESS OPPORTUNITY IN MY DEPARTMENT. WE DISCOVERED AN ABANDONED SUM OF $15,000,000.00 (FIFTEEN MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS ONLY) IN AN ACCOUNT THAT BELONGS TO ONE OF OUR FOREIGN CUSTOMERS WHO DIED ALONG WITH HIS ENTIRE FAMILY OF A WIFE AND TWO CHILDREN IN NOVEMBER 1997 IN A PLANE CRASH. SINCE WE HEARD OF HIS DEATH, WE HAVE BEEN EXPECTING HIS NEXT-OF-KIN TO COME OVER AND PUT CLAIMS FOR HIS MONEY AS THE HEIR,BECAUSE WE CANNOT RELEASE THE FUND FROM HIS ACCOUNT UNLESS SOMEONE APPLIES FOR CLAIM AS THE NEXT-OF-KIN TO THE DECEASED AS INDICATED IN OUR BANKING GUIDELINES. UNFORTUNATELY, NEITHER THEIR FAMILY MEMBER NOR DISTANT RELATIVE HAS EVER APPEARED TO CLAIM THE SAID FUND. UPON THIS DISCOVERY,I AND OTHER OFFICIALS IN MY DEPARTMENT HAVE AGREED TO MAKE BUSINESS WITH YOU AND RELEASE THE TOTAL AMOUNT INTO YOUR ACCOUNT AS THE HEIR OF THE FUND SINCE NO ONE CAME FOR IT OR DISCOVERED HE MAINTAINED ACCOUNT WITH OUR BANK, OTHERWISE THE FUND WILL BE RETURNED TO THE BANKS TREASURY AS UNCLAIMED FUND. WE HAVE AGREED THAT OUR RATIO OF SHARING WILL BE AS STATED THUS; 30 % FOR YOU AS FOREIGN PARTNER, 60 % FOR US THE OFFICIALS IN MY DEPARTMENT AND 10% FOR THE SETTLEMENT OF ALL LOCAL AND FOREIGN EXPENCES INCURRED BY US AND YOU DURING THE COURSE OF THIS BUSINESS. UPON THE SUCCESSFUL COMPLETION OF THIS TRANSFER, I AND ONE OF MY COLLEAGUES WILL COME TO YOUR COUNTRY AND MIND OUR SHARE. IT IS FROM OUR 60 % WE INTEND TO IMPORT AGRICULTURAL MACHINERIES INTO MY COUNTRY AS A WAY OF RECYCLING THE FUND. TO COMMENCE THIS TRANSACTION, WE REQUIRE YOU TO IMMEDIATELY INDICATE YOUR INTEREST BY A RETURN E-MAIL AND ENCLOSE YOUR PRIVATE CONTACT TELEPHONE NUMBER, FAX NUMBER FULL NAME AND ADDRESS AND YOUR DESIGNATED BANK COORDINATES TO ENABLE US FILE LETTER OF CLAIM TO THE APPROPRIATE DEPARTMENTS FOR NECESSARY APPROVALS BEFORE THE TRANSFER CAN BE MADE. NOTE ALSO, THIS TRANSACTION MUST BE KEPT STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL BECAUSE OF IT'S NATURE. I LOOK FORWARD TO RECEIVING YOUR PROMPT RESPONSE. REGARDS, MR. MIKE CHUKWU ZENITH INTERNATIONAL BANK PLC .

Dear Sir, I am Engr. Ugo Nzego with the Engineering Stores Department of the Federal Ministry of Agriculture and Natural Resources and member of Tenders Board. We have urgent need for a trustworthy foreign contact person with whom we can carry out a successful business deal. Federal Government has voted the sum of US$1.86 Billion for Local Production of food crops. The Government has also considered the impact of the importation of some food items like Rice, Beans, Frozen Chicken and Turkeys and other food stuffs on the Nations Foreign Reserve and have banned the importation of the items that could be produced locally. As a result, the Federal Ministry of Agriculture and Natural Resources has been mandated to import Agricultural Equipments for supply to Local Farmers both at SUBSISTENT AND COMMERCIAL level to encourage them to produce enough food items for local consumption and for export to other African Countries. We have already started awarding new contracts for supply of the equipments to successful bidders. We want you to submit to us immediately your complete company name, address, your name as President or Managing Director / CEO of the company, your banking particulars:- (banks name address, telephone, fax and telex numbers. Your receiving number, swift and routing numbers), with these informations, we can get you properly registered as one of the contractors of FMANR who has already been awarded part of this contract for the sum of US$113.4 Million to supply some of the Agricultural Equipments parts of which we already have in our custody (stores). After receiving the above needed and stated information from you, we will process all the documentation and submit them for immediate approvals and the Federal Government will pay 25% of US$113.4 Million into your nominated bank account in the name of your company as the beneficiary, which is US$28.35M . In no time, the remaining US$85,050,000.00 Million shall be paid as balance payment or we together in agreement as partners will use another foreign firm's name that will carry out the supply of the remaining equipments as a sub-contractor to you in our documentation to receive this balance payment. We shall come to your country immediately this fund is in your account to share the US$28.35 Million. The sharing pattern should be negotiated by both parties concerned. However, be rest assured that no risk is involved or any scandal in the future, for we have done all our homework very well, nobody will be hurt during and after this transaction. It may also please you to know that all the GOODS that cover the 25% payment are on record, only us that are key members of the contract board committee has this knowledge and information. There is the serious need to keep this transaction secret and very confidential. To that effect, I would require your private phone and fax numbers for easy and confidential communication. I await your immediate response to this Proposal. Meanwhile, I look forward to establishing life long business relationship with you. The nature of your company or business does not necessarily have to be Agriculturally related but ownership of a company is a criterium for the project. Please reply immediately through this fax number 234-9-2726567. As soon as I receive your fax, I will call you on phone for detailed discussion. Best regards, Engr. Ugo Nzego.

ATTN: MY DEAR, I KNOW THIS PROPOSAL LETTER MIGHT BE A PLEASANT SUPRISE TO YOU AS WE DON'T KNOW OUR SELVES BEFORE BUT BE SURED IT IS REAL AND A GENUINE BUSINESS. I AM MR. SOLOMON KONATEH,A SIERRA-LEONIAN BORN 30 YEARS AGO,NOW SEEKING ASYLUM IN DAKAR-SENEGAL UNDER (UNHCR) I GOT YOUR CONTACT FROM THE INTERNET AS A CAUSE OF MY SERIOUS SEARCH FOR A RELIABLE AND TRUSTWORTHY PERSON THAT CAN HANDLE SUCH A CONFIDENTIAL TRANSACTION OF THIS NATURE. MY FATHER (LATE) MR. FEDELIX KONATEH THE FORMER DEPUTY MINISTER OF FINANCE UNDER THE EXECUTIVE CIVILIAN PRESIDENT OF SIERRA-LEONE,BUT WAS ASSASINATED BY THE REBELS DURING THE CIVIL WAR AND PROPERTIES DESTROYED,BUT I AND MY AGED MOTHER WITH MY TWO JUNIOR BROTHERS NARROWLY ESCAPED WITH SOME VERY IMPORTANT DOCUMENT OF (US$14.5M) FOURTHEEN POINT FIVE MILLION U.S DOLLARS DEPOSITED BY MY LATE FATHER IN A HIGH SECURITY AND FINANCE COMPANY HERE IN DAKAR AS A FAMILY TREASURE UNDER MY NAME. HOWEVER,WE SADDLED WITH THE PROBLEM OF SECURING A TRUST WORTHY FOREIGN PERSONALITY TO HELP US TRANSFER THIS MONEY PENDING OUR ARRIVAL TO MEET WITH YOU. FURTHERMORE,WE ONLY WANT THIS TO BE DONE THIS WAY BECAUSE YOUR COUNTRY IS POLITICALLY STABLE FOR ANY PROFITABLE INVESTMENT AND WE ALSO WANT TO ADD HERE THAT IF ACCEPTED BY YOU,YOU WILL SERVE AS THE ORIGINAL BENEFICIARY OF THE MONEY. WE FEEL CONFIDENT THEREFORE,TO INTRODUCE THIS OFFER TO YOU. FOR YOUR PARTICIPATION AND ASSISTANCE REGARDING THIS TRANSFER,WE HAVE DECIDED TO GIVE YOU 15 PERCENT OF THE TOTAL AMOUNT AND 5 PERCENT MAPPED OUT FOR ANY MISCELLENEOUS EXPENSES THAT MAY OCCURE DURING THE TRANSFER OF THE MONEY TO YOUR LOCATION. CONCLUSIVELY,THEREFORE,YOU ARE REQUESTED TO FURNISH US BACK IMMEDIATELY YOU RECIEVE THIS REQUEST TO TRANSFER THIS MONEY FROM DAKAR SENEGAL TO YOUR COUNTRY RESIDENT ACCOUNT OR ANY ACCOUNT OF YOUR INTEREST. ON COMMENCEMENT OF THIS TRANSACTION I WANT TO LET YOU UNDERSTAND THAT THE FUTURE OF MYSELF AND FAMILY DEPENDS SOLELY ON THIS MONEY. SO PLEASE KEEP THIS BUSINESS TO YOURSELF ONLY. FINALLY NOTE THAT THIS BUSINESS IS 100% RISK FREE ON YOUR PART AS A RESULT THERE IS NOTHING TO FEAR ABOUT. A COPY OF CERTIFICATE OF DEPOSIT BOND RECIEPT OF THE SECURITY COMPANY AND ALL THE VITAL DOCUMENTS THAT COVERED THE DEPOSITED MONEY WILL BE SENT TO YOU FOR YOUR RECORD PURPOSE AS SOON AS WE HEAR FROM YOU. I AM EAGERLY EXPECTING YOUR URGENT RESPONSE. YOURS FAITHFULLY, SOLOMON KONATEH. __________________________________________________ Do You Yahoo!? Everything you'll ever need on one web page from News and Sport to Email and Music Charts http://uk.my.yahoo.com

From: Mr. Charles Nwodo Universal Trust Bank.website:www.utbplc.com Dear friend, This letter may come to you as a surprise due to the fact that we have not yet met. The message could be strange but real if you pay some attention to it. I could have notified you about it at least for the sake of your integrity. Please accept my sincere apologies. In writing you this message, I have to say that I have no intentions of causing you any embarrassment. I am Mr. Charles Nwodo Manager with Universal Trust Bank Plc. of Nigeria, Island Branch. I managed to get your contact details through the Internet myself. Time is of the importance and I am desperately looking for a person to assist me in this confidential business. A British oil consultant/contractor with the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation, Mr. Claude Brian Best made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit on January 6, 1999, valued at US$2,500,000.00 (Two Million Five Hundred Thousand US Dollars), for twelve (12) calendar months in my branch. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation that Mr. Claude Brian Best died in an automobile accident. On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL and all attempts to trace his next of kin were fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr. Claude Brian Best did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$2,500,000.00 is still sitting in my Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Nigerian Law, at the expiration of 4 (four) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Nigerian Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr. Claude Brian Best so that the fruits of this old man's labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that the attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits that will put you in place as the next of kin. We shall employ the service of two lawyers for drafting and notarization of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/administration in your favor for the transfer. A bank account in any part of the world that you will provide will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 60% for me and 40% for you. There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and my position as the Branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately via the private email address below; charlesnwodo@dr.com. Upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Awaiting your urgent reply via my email address .Thanks and regards. Mr. Charles Nwodo.

Greetings, My Friend, Permit me to introduce first myself then the purpose of this letter. I am Mr PAPA BELLO, Bank Manager of ORIENT BANK OF NIGERIA, Lagos Branch. I have urgent and very confidential business proposition for you and it is carefully explained for your understanding as follows. On June 6 1997, an American oil consultant/contractor with the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation, Mr. Barry Kelly made a numbered time account (Fixed) deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at US$25,000,000.00 (Twenty-five Million United States Dollars) in my branch. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation that Mr. Barry Kelly has since died from an automobile accident. On further investigation, I found out that he did not leave a WILL and all attempts to trace his next of kin were fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr. Barry Kelly did not declare any next of kin in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork. This sum of US$25,000,000.00 is still sitting in the Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will come forward to claim it. According to the Nigerian Law, at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Nigerian Government if nobody applies to claim the funds. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr. Barry Kelly so that the fruits of this old man's labour will not get into the hands of some undeserving and corrupt officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide me immediately with the following; your full names, date and place of birth and complete address with confidential telephone and fax numbers so that the attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits, which will put you in place as the next of kin. We shall employ the services of two attorneys for drafting and notarization of the WILL and obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/administration in your favor for the transfer. A bank account in any part of the world, which you would provide, will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 60% for me and 40% for you. There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and my position as the Branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, Upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand. Please observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Awaiting your urgent reply via e-mail. Thanks and regards, Mr PAPA BELLO.

Re Urgent Assistance Kindly allow me the modesty of introducing myself. I am KEN GREEN KABILA,the son of the former head of state/ president of Congo-Kinshasha (then called Zaire) Mr. Laurent Desire Kabila. I am contacting you in order to ask for your assistance on this confidential Business proposal with full financial benefit for both of us. Before I go into further details please be informed that I am writing without any other person(s) pre-knowledge of my contacting you on this transaction. Therefore I will appreciate same attitude to be maintained all through. I have the sum of USD55Million from a secret sale of Diamond by my father before he was assassinated by one of his body guard (Rashid) on January 16th 2001, which I will like you to receive on my behalf due to security reasons,as my narration below will explain. But before I continue b e well informed that your share in this transaction has been calculated at 15% of the total sum of USD$55M, 5% for expenses and the rest for my family and me. My father as a real African traditionalist was a polygamist thereby having married so many wives, and my mother being the second wife of my father, My step brother Joseph, who is the current president of my country, is the son of the first wife and he does not have any knowledge about this deal. Already president Joseph is using his power to colonize all the money and private property, which my father left behind for the whole family. Now my mother and I are left with nothing in the inheritance of my late father's wealth. Our situation is seriously critical that we need your assistance to help us receive these funds overseas for proper investment. Let me quickly assure you the 100% safe proof of this transaction because the diamond sales are packaged from the onset in a pa ttern that shows no direct trace or linkage with us (Kabi! la family). At present the money is in cash and is secured in a financial institution company as consignment. The consignment will be released within seven (7) days of my being in receipt of your reply via my email address above only for security reasons. I am waiting for your swift and favorable response, and in case you have any question(s), do not hesitate to contact me.my alternative email is ken_kabil40@zwallet.com you can call me mmediately on my private phone number which is :229-988-039. Best Regards, KEN GREEN KABILA.

Good Day, With warm heart I offer my friendship, and greetings, and I hope this mail meets you in good time. However strange or surprising this contact might seem to you as we have not met personally or had any dealings in the past, I humbly ask that you take due consideration of its importance and immense benefit. I duly apologize for infringing on your privacy, if this contact is not acceptable to you, as I make this proposal to you as a person of integrity. First and foremost I wish to introduce myself properly to you. My name is Oliveira Chuli Savimbi, I am a nephew and Personal Assistant to Late Jonas Malheiro Savimbi, leader of UNITA (National Union for the Total Independence of Angola). As led by my instinct, I selected your email address from an internet directory, in my search for a partner, hence this email. I also crave your indulgence to read this carefully, and have a general overview of my situation. My Uncle (Mentor) was killed in a battle with government forces of Angola, led by President Dos Santos, on Friday 22nd February 2002. After his death, Mr. Antonio Dembo who was his second in command, assumed office as leader of UNITA, due to the lack of Charisma my Uncle had carried the party with in Dembo, there was chaos and struggle for leadership. Prominent members like Carlos Morgado lobbied to depose him and assume office as leader to enrich themselves and some of them who saw me as a threat to their ambitions, including Mr.Dembo, planned to kill me. The tension and confusion in UNITA become uncontrollable when Mr. Dembo died 10days after my Uncle's death. As I already lost my mentor in this struggle that has been on for three decades now, not so much of the struggle interested me anymore, as there was no more sense of direction. I then desired a peaceful life, as I no more had interest in conflicts and wars. For this reason, I secretly left Angola and came here (Holla! nd) to seek for political asylum. I am sincerely proposing to you to render me your most needed assistance in respect to safekeeping of some of my Uncle's money that arose from Diamonds sales. This money (US$18.5million), which was already on its way to my Uncle's Swiss Bank account, through the Diplomatic means we use to move money abroad, and was on transit with a private safe deposit security company here in Amsterdam, Holland in February last year when the tragic incident of my Uncle's death occurred. I then instructed the company to secure the consignment containing the money pending on further instructions from me. I have waited all this time now for security reasons, and have now decided to act with your reliable assistance. As a matter of fact, the reason I came to Holland and sought for political asylum here is the safe deposit with the Security Company here in Amsterdam. President Jose Eduardo Dos Santos has lobbied the International Community to freeze my Uncle's assets and accounts abroad, to ground UNITA, and has already done this in Angola. Hence I cannot lodge the funds in my name. Also I did not declare the funds to the government here. I plan to use this money to safeguard my future. It is very essential that you understand that the kind of trust and confidence I want to place in you is extraordinary, and an act of desperation on my part, in order not to lose this money. Also, ensure that this contact with you should be treated with utmost secrecy. Your role in this project, is acting on my behalf to clear the safety deposit containing the money which is deposited in my name, from the Security company, after which, the money will lodged into an account preferably a new account you should open for this transaction. My share of the money will be returned to me when my asylum application in this country is granted, and I have permission to do business and open an account here. For your reliable assistance, I will reward you with 15%($2,775,000) of the money. I have with me, the Certificate of Deposit for the safety deposit, which will be used for claim from the security company, and the release codes of the vaults. Also, everything will be legally processed for transfer of ownership to you, and this transaction should be completed immediately depending on your prompt response. I thank you in advance as I anticipate your assistance in enabling me achieve this goal. Please contact me whether or not you are interested in assisting me. This will enable me scout for another partner in the event of non-interest on your part. To know more about the struggle by UNITA to liberate Angola, click on the links below and read. http://www.the-idler.com/IDLER-02/3-16.html http://news.bbc.co.uk/hi/english/world/africa/newsid_1839000/1839252.stm Sincerely, O.C.Savimbi.

B.P 25 Sarue de Bruno Dantokpa cotonou Republiqe du Benin Dear sir, I got your contact while searching for somebody who will be of immediate assistance to me , then I decided to forward this business proposal to you with hope that it will be of benefit to both of us. I'm Frank Guei Jnr, the first Son of late Gen. Robert Guei the former military ruler of ( cote d' Ivoire/ivory coast,) who was killed on 19/9/2002 with some of his loyalist officers during a cross fire battle between them and government troops in his attempt to seize power through coup de eta in Abidjan on 19/9/2002 . In brief, I have the sum of Twenty Million Seven Hundred Thousand united states dollars(us$20,700,000)only which I want to move out of here with most desperation. This money was deposited by my late father in a security company for the purpose of using it to fine tune his administration in the invent that he succeed in the fail coup attempt. While I was also made the sole beneficiary and next of kin as the first son of my father. So because of the present situation in my country cote d' ivoire , my mother advised me before she was mudered cold bloodedly with 18 of my sibblings to leave the country immediately for security reasons, and also to look for a trust worthy foreign partner who can assist me to transfer the money out of Cotonou-Benin Republic to his private or company's account for investment as the security company had earlier rejected my application for the withdrawal of the money because I am underaged. Sir, I highly need your unreserved assistance both in transferring the money to your country and also investing it in a profitable venture with your kind advice,as I confide in you hoping you will never betray me at last.My guidian and myself have proposed (20%) percent of the total sum of the money for you as your own commission,and (5%) for any expensis that you might incure in the process so that you can give us all necessary assistance and protection we may need in our investment in your Country. Please treat as highly confidential because our future depends on this money. All the vital documents covering the deposit of this fund in a security company are with me here in Cotonou, and will be used to effect change of ownership in your favour for subsequent transfer to any account you may wish us to use abroad. The identity of the finance company where the fund is deposited will be revealed to you as soon as I recieve confirmation from you on your willingness to proceed.Even our family lawyer thatassisted my father when he was depositing the money has been approched on this issue and he promised to give us all the legal backing that might be required in this transfer. Reach me through this mail box to discuss modalities on how to proceed. Looking forward to hearing from you urgently. Best wishes. Frank Guei Jnr.

10 Jasim Street, Ibrahim'Ali, Baghdad, Iraq. Email: falbashar@olumo.net Re: Urgent Assistance Needed By way of introduction I am Eng. Farouk Al-Bashar, I represent my family as the oldest son of the Al-Bashar family, who are the descendants of Ibrahim Al-Bashar Ali from one of the oil rich areas in Iraq. Over the years my family has acquired huge sums of money from royalties for the exploration of oil in our region but over the past 15 years, Saddam Hussein and his gangs of bandits have taken our oils without payments and we can not complain as those who did are all dead. In the wake of the Gulf War of 1990, our family withdrew most moneys that remain in coded bank accounts that Saddam did not find and we hide it in a secret chamber underground, where it remained safe until after the war. At the end of Gulf war, we moved the funds into a private vault of a security company in Baghdad, where it was until we collected it a few days ago on the fear of the eminent war with America. We pray they remove Saddam as he is the cause of much hardship here, but our funds are trapped here and there is no avenue to transfer any amount from Iraq without Saddam knowing. The problem now is how do we transfer the funds totalling US$12.5 Million in cash from here. We are afraid that with the capacity of the bombs America is coming to Baghdad with nowhere would be safe for the money, so we need you to help in securing a private collection agency who would come to Iraq and collect the money and have them moved to the west, where our family is planning to relocate to as life in Iraq is no longer worth living because of Saddam. I have to travel lots of miles each day to send an email hoping someone out there would assist this family, if you can we will give you the details of an agency that can lift the funds from here as given to me by a US Marine. The private collection agency would then collect the fund from here and deliver it to you for safe keep. Hoping the American campaign would be successful, we would then come over to your country for a meeting to share the funds and hopefully start a new life with you as a partner. For your assistance with this project the family is willing to give you 10% of the funds, however if this does not suit you we are open for negotiation. We eagerly await your response so we can inform you of the next line of action. Regards. Eng. Farouk Al- Bashar For the entire Al-Bashar family

DEAR SIR, HOW ARE YOU AND YOUR FAMILY? I HOPE ALL IS WELL. YOU WILL BE SURPRISE TO RECEIVE THIS LETTER BUT WHEN YOU GO THROUGH IT YOU MIGHT NOT BE SURPRISE AGAIN IF THE INFORMATION HAS SOMETHING TO DO WITH YOU. I AM THE CONFIDENTIAL SECRETARY FOR THE INVESTMENT CONTROLLER OF A SOUTH AFRICAN BASED INVESTMENT CORPORATION.MY BOSS/PARTNER INSTRUCTED ME TO CONTACT YOU IN RESPECT OF A CLAIM/DIVIDEND,WHICH MATURED SINCE 2000.THE INVESTOR AFTER COLLECTING THE SAID RETURN OFINVESTMENT FROM OUR FIRM AND DEPOSITED THE CASH WITH A SECURITY COMPANY DIED AFTER ONE WEEK IN A MOTOR ACCIDENT,IN NOVEMBER 2000 AND FROM THE CONTENT OF HIS FILE WITH US,WE NOTICED THAT THERE WAS NO NEXT OF KIN IN HIS DETAILS AS HE PROMISED TO FORWARD THE INFORMATION LATER TO US.BUT THIS HE DID NOT PROVIDE UNTIL HE DIED. WITH FURTHER INVESTIGATION TO TRACE THE ROOT OF THE INVESTOR,THIS MADE THINGS MUCH COMPLEX AS THE INFORMATION WE GOT CONFIRMED THAT HIS WIFE AND ONLY SON DIED IN RUSSIA IN AN AIRCRASH IN THE YEAR 1998. HOWEVER,MY BOSS HAS TAKING IT UPON HIMSELF TO TRACE THE NEXT OF KIN IF POSSIBLE TO CLAIM THE US$255,600,000.00 (TWO HUNDRED AND FIFTY FIVE MILLION SIX THOUSAND UNITED STATE DOLLARS ONLY) WHICH IS THE TOTAL SUM PAYABLE TO THE NEXT OF KIN AS ALL THE LOCAL TAXES HAS ALREADY BEEN DEDUCTED AND THE CASH ALREADY WITHDRAWN FROM THE SOUTH AFRICAN RESERVE BANK AND BOXED. THE INVESTOR HAS DEPOSITED THIS AMOUNT /CASH WITH A SECURITY COMPANY WITHOUT THE COMPANY KNOWING THE CONTENT OF THE BOX FOR SECURITY REASONS BEFORE HIS DEATH. THE CONTAINS WAS DECLEARED TO BE COMPANY TREASURE DOCUMENTS,FILES(PAPER)AND THE CORPORATION HAS PAID THE SECURITY COMPANYUS$20,000,000.00 ON BEHALF OF THE BENEFICIARY AS THE INITIAL DEPOSIT FOR THE SAFE KEEPING OF THE BOX AS THEY HAVE CHARGED US$100.00 PER DAY FOR THE SAFEKEEPING. I AM CONTACTING YOU BECAUSE YOUR LAST NAME AND THAT OF THE INVESTOR IS THE SAME,WHICH MY BOSS SUSPECTED THAT YOU MIGHT BE THE INVESTOR'S RELATION. PLEASE RECONFIRM TO US IMMEDIATELY IF YOU HAVE ANY BROTHER WHO WAS 78YEARS OLD BEFORE HE DIED IN 1998.IF IT IS TRUE,WE WILL ARRANGE FOR YOU TO MAKE THIS CLAIM AS SOON AS POSSILBE.BUT IF NOT WE HAVE NO OTHER OPTION THAN TO PROCESS IT WITH YOUR NAME AND COLLECT THE MONEY TO AVOID THE CASH BEING RETURNED TO THE SOUTH AFRICA GOVERNMENT AS UNTRACABLE/UNCLAIMED DIVIDEND.AS WE CANNOT AFFORD TO WAIT AND SEE SUCH AMOUNT OF MONEY WASTE INTO THE GOVERNMENT POCKET . FOR YOUR INFORMATION ,IF YOU ARE WILLING TO ASSIST IN CLAMING THIS FUNDS ,PLEASE CONTACT ME AS SOON AS POSSIBLE WITHIN THREE MONTHS FROM TODAY.BEFORE THE SOUTH AFRICAN GOVERNMENT TEAMS TO KNOW ABOUT IT. PLEASE DISREGARD MY PROPOSAL TO USE YOUR NAME TO CLAIM IT IF THE INVESTOR IS REALLY YOUR BROTHER.BUT IF NOT WE WILL SHARE THE MONEY ON 50% EACH AFTER THE CASH HAS BEEN PAID TO YOU. NOTE THAT THIS BUSINESS IS 100% LEGAL AND RISK FREE. PLEASE TREAT THIS AS MOST URENT AND CONFIDENTIAL. YOU CAN REACH ME ON MY SATELLITE PHONE NUMBERS /FAX (voice)+873-762874250 (fax))+873-762874252 OR my PRIVATE EMAIL AT BEST REGARDS, DR AKIGA STEPHEN

To: President/Ceo From: James Kabila. INVESTMENT OFFER Dear Sir, In appreciation of your esteemed contact received through a reliable source and the choice of your country I wish to introduce myself, I am Mr.James Kabila the son of the late Democratic Republic of Congo President Laurent Desire Kabila of the blessed memory.I know this letter might come to you as a surprise butI honestly do not intend to surprise you. I write this letter in respect of my intention to invest the sum of US$35M(Thirty Five Million United State Dollars) with you.I inherited this money from my mother. This money was got through the smuggling and sales of Diamond and Timber when my father was the head of state. My mother though not her legal wife used her privilege position to engage in the business of Diamond and Timber since she knows that her survival will depend on how much she can get out of the privilege situation. When my father was assassinated on 16TH Jan. 01 by one of his bodyguards Lt. Rashidi Kasereke through the conspiracy of some top army officers that wanted to topple him. I escaped to Madrid, Spain because of the fear that I might be arrested by my half brother Lt.General Joseph Kabila the present head of state.Actually his mother and my mother are not in the best of relationship because of who among them will be the first lady tussle and this ultimately affected us their children.My mother advised me to leave For Madrid, Spain where these funds were deposited for safe keeping with a Private Security Company here in Spain.On getting to Spain where I have been living since then as a political refugee, I am seeking for a reliable foreigner who can come down to Madrid, Spain for a meeting and to clear the funds in his name as the sole beneficiary of the Consignment as I was afraid of being defraud. Honestly I contacted you because I don't want to invest this money in Madrid Spain due to my status here as a political Refugee. And moreover I wouldn't want to take risk because this money is all that my Mother and I are depending on. My step brother Joseph,who is now the present leader of my country has seized all my father's assets and money. He left us empty handed without knowing about this funds deposited with the Security Company here. That is why I decided that investing this money abroad should be the best investment for me. I will be honored if I can be given the privilege of investing this money with you. I expect you to be trust worthy and kind enough to respond to this distress call to save My Mother and I from a hopeless future. And if you agree, I hereby agree to compensate your sincere and candid effort in this regard with 15% of the total amount of $35million US Dollars. When the money ($35 million) is moved into your discrete account. You will be allowed to draw 15% in your favor, while the remaining 85% will be invested meaning fully for our future if possible in your area of business and different sectors of the Economy in your country which are dividends yielding.Whatever your decision is please reach me immediately,and keep this letter tight secret for the interest of my Family. Best regards, Mr.James Kabila. ___________________________________________________ Yahoo! Messenger - Nueva versión GRATIS Super Webcam, voz, caritas animadas, y más... http://messenger.yahoo.es

DAYO NAPS 234 80 372 20807 Dear Sir, I am Mr. Dayo Naps, an official with one of the APEX banks in Nigeria.My colleagues and I have an urgent and very confidential business proposal for you. On the 6th of June 1998 an American miner, Mr. Travis Myers ran an account with us and his present balance is valued at US$28,500,000.00 (Twenty-Eight Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars Only) in my Bank. We sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally, we discovered from his employers that he died from an automobile accident. On further investigation, we found out from his account file that he never made a will and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless, as he had none. We therefore made further investigations and discovered that Mr. Travis Myers did not declare any next of kin or relations in all his official documents in the bank files. This sum of $28,500,000.00 is still lying in the bank and the principal sum and interest is being rolled over at the end of every year. As it is now, no one will ever come forward to claim this money. According to the Nigeria law, at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Government if unclaimed. Consequently, my proposal is that I would like you to stand in as the next of kin of Mr. Travis Myers. This is simple; all we need is some of your details so that the Attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits which would put you in place as Mr. Myers's next of kin. We shall also employ the services of an accredited Attorney for the drafting and notarisation of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and letters of probate/administration in your favour for the transfer. The money would be shared in the ration of 75% for us and 25% for you. There is no risk at all as the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the Attorney and my position as a manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately via email. Please observe utmost confidentiality and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for us. I shall still require your assistance to invest my own share in your country just incase you can help, otherwise we'll take our share . Awaiting your urgent reply. Mr.Dayo Naps 234 80 372 20807

Dear sir, This business will be of interest to you and your business and involves $30,000,000.00, which emanated from over invoiced contracts executed on behalf of my ministry of minerals and Energy, by foreign contractor. Though the actual contract value has been paid to the original contractor, GUILDER MINING (PTY) SA, now in-liquidation. We have however included our billforthe over invoiced amount of US$30m amongst the present bills that are scheduled for payment in the name of the company in-liquidation. We have also planned the execution of this deal perfectly both in the area of documentation and the changing of beneficiary from the company in liquidation that we had used to apply for payment, to the name, which you will forward to us. I shall supply you with all the relevant documents relating to this transaction as soon as we establish a working relationship. . This transaction is itself risk free and should be concluded within the next ten to fourteen working days if you follow my instructions carefully and we work closely as a team. . Where you are going to come in is this. We are going to effect a change of company name from GUILDER MINING (PTY) SA to your company so as to legalize your company as the bona fide beneficiary of the contract sum. In this regard we will do the incorporation of your company here and reflect your company as having taken over the assets of Guilder Mining (pty). Once we complete this process, your company will now be legally entitled to the US$30m, which the Department of Minerals and Energy owes GUILDER MINING (PTY) SA. We will thereafter use your company's name to apply for the payment of the US$30m into your company's designated account. This application we will process here in my Ministry and the approved Payment Recommendation sent to the Ministry of Finance, whi! ch will authorize the South African Reserve Bank to effect the transfer of the fund to your designated account. For assisting us with a receiving account and a company name, we propose 20% of the contract amount of US$30m for you and 10% for taxes, phone, fax and other incidental expenses that we may incur in the course of the eventual realization of the transaction. Meanwhile, please send me your confidential telephone/fax numbers, to enable us to speak first and know ourselves better. You can also contact me on my confidential sat phone-00+871763427855 fax-00+871763427856. I promise that you will not regret helping us, you have my personal word of honor. My colleagues and I strive for the commitment to operate only on high standards of integrity and honesty. We need the same honesty and commitment to this transaction from you. Thank you for your anticipated cooperation. My Sincere Regards. Dr Pascal Ugoti

Good Day, With warm heart I offer my friendship, and my greetings, and I hope this letter meets you in good time. It will be surprising to you to receive this proposal from me since you do not know me personally. However, I am sincerely seeking your confidence in this transaction, which I propose with my free mind and as a person of integrity. My name is Mr.Mako Okere, the first son of Iko Okere,one of the most popular black farmer from Zimbabwe, murdered in the land dispute in my country. As led by my instict, I decided to contact you through email, after searching for contacts via the internet, as it is the only means I can contact anybody since I am cutting off ties with Zimbabwe for security and safety reasons. However,I apologize if this is not acceptable to you. The purpose of this letter is to seek your most needed assistance in a business venture. Due to the the land and political problems in Zimbabwe, as a result of President Robert Mugabe's introduction of new Land Act Reform wholly affecting the rich white farmers and the few rich black farmers, and his desire to hold on to power for life, my father forsaw the danger that came in Zimbabwe. Before he was murdered, he withdrew all of our business foreign accounts in dollars and sold up our shares in major companies. We then went to Johannesburg, South Africa to deposit the sum of US$14.5 million (Fourteen million, Five Hundred thousand US dollars), in a private security company. This money was deposited with this Private Security company for safety and security reasons, and was to be used for the purchase of land, new machines and chemicals establishment of new farms in Botswana and Swaziland. President Mugabe's support for the violent imbabwean war veterans and some lunatics in the society, led to the murder of my beloved father and other innocent lives. I was continually threatened to abandon my inheritance from my father after he was murdered. I resited for a while, but when the danger became unbearable, and I survived two murder attempts, I fled Zimbabwe to South Africa where I was arrested and detained for eight(8 good month)in jail.I fled south Africa for The Netherlands with the help of the present prison command chief officer in Charge(P.C.C.O) I am currently staying in the Netherlands where I am seeking political asylum. In fact my decision to come here to seek asylum, is because the security company from South Africa, has a branch here, and they have moved the deposit from their office in Johannesburg here. I need to transfer this money to an account and invest part of the money. Since the law of Netherlands prohibits a refugee (asylum seeker) to open any bank account or to be involved in any financial ransaction, this is why I am seeking a genuine and reliable partner, whose account this money can be transferred, ence this proposal to you.You have to understand that this decision taken by me entrusts my future and in your hands, as a result of the safe keeping of this money. If you accept to assist me, all I want you to do for me, is to assist with the arrangements to claim the deposit from the security company from their office here in The Netherlands, as it has now been transfered from Johannesburg, South Afri! ca to their branch here. The company will be legally informed of you representing me. For your assistance, I have two options for you. Firstly you can choose to have 10% of the money for your assistance, and helping me open an account for the money to be deposited here, or you can go into partnership with me for the proper profitable investment of the money in your country. Whichever the option you want, please to notify me in your reply. I have also set aside 1%($145,000,00) of this money for all kinds of expenses that come our way in the process of this transaction, and 4% ($580,000,00) for Charity donation. If you prefer to accept the 10% for assisting with opening an account, then 85%will be left in the account here for me. Please, I want you to maintain the absolute secrecy for the purpose of this transaction.I look forward to your reply and co-operation, and I thank you inadvance as I anticipate your co-operation. Thanks and God bless. Sincerely, Mako Okere

Dear friend, 31-612-696-672 I am Domas k, yankThe son of former minister of finance (Domas Makabo) of the Republic of Sierra-Leone West Africa based on the information I gathered from your chamber of commerce and industry on your credibility, I decide to contact for the assistance. Regarding my zeal toward foreign investment and security for my life and possession, I therefore write to you a break down of this proposal. My father died when a group of rebel soldier led by Sir Foday Sankoh overthrown Government of sierra-Leone forcing the president out of power and killing many members of the cabinet and minister including my own father. When it become apparently obvious that the country no longer safe for the citizens due to the political war and massive killing and destruction of properties, I decided to move to Holland with a treasure containing the sum of US$12.500.000.00(twelve million five hundred thousand united state dollars) through a diplomatic means, this fund is the last tangible money my father left behind before his death. The said amount is presently in Holland (The Netherlands) where I am currently seeking political asylum. While the consignment containing the fund is in the custody of the diplomatic courier company they are not aware of the content as it was deposited as personal effect and artifact. I am seeking for partner who will serve as a the guardian of this fund with whom I could plan the best way to move this money out of Holland for investment which is my main purpose of contacting you. Thus I decided to offer you 20% of the total money for assisting me to actualize this project while 10% of the money has been set aside to offset any incidental expenses that might incurred during the course of this funds and the balance 70%shall be for me and my family which shall be invested in your country. And are will visit you country soonest in order to inquire areas of possible business investment. I shall be sincerely glad if my request is rendered. Thank you God bless you Domas k. yank

Good day, This email message requires your utmost confidentiality. It is with warm heart I am offering you my friendship, and I hope this mail meets you in good time. I know this is a most unusual way to contact you as we have not met personally or had any dealings in the past, but I am humbly asking that you take due consideration of the importance of my proposal and the immense benefit in it for you. Also I duly apologize for infringing on your privacy, if this contact is not acceptable to you, as I make this proposal to you as a person of integrity. First and foremost I wish to introduce myself properly to you. My name is Oliveira Chuli Savimbi, I am a nephew and Personal Assistant to Late Jonas Malheiro Savimbi, leader of UNITA (National Union for the Total Independence of Angola). As led by my instinct, I selected your email address from an internet directory, in my intensive and desperate search for a partner, hence this email to you. I crave your indulgence to read this carefully, in order to have a general overview of my situation. My Uncle was killed in a surprise attack by government troops of Angola, led by President Dos Santos, on Friday 22nd February 2002. After his death, Mr. Antonio Dembo who was his second in command, assumed office as leader of UNITA, due to the lack of the Charisma my Uncle had carried UNITA with in Dembo, there was chaos and struggle for leadership. Prominent members like Carlos Morgado lobbied to depose Dembo and assume leadership in order to enrich themselves and some of them who saw me as a threat to their ambitions, including Mr.Dembo, planned to kill me. The tension and confusion in UNITA become uncontrollable when Mr. Dembo died 10days after my Uncle's death. As I already lost my Uncle who is my mentor in this struggle that has been on for three decades now, not so much of the struggle interested me anymore, as there was no more sense of direction. I then desired a peaceful life, as I no more had interest in the war. For this reason, I secretly left Angola and came her! e (Holland) to seek for political asylum. I am sincerely proposing to you to render me your most needed assistance in respect to safekeeping of some of my Uncle's money that arose from Diamonds sales. This money (US$18.5million), which was already on its way to my Uncle's Swiss Bank account, through the Diplomatic means we use to move money abroad, and was on transit with a Private Security company here in Amsterdam, Holland in February last year when the tragic incident of my Uncle's death occurred. I then instructed the company to secure the safety deposit containing the money pending on further instructions from me. I have waited all this time for security reasons, and have now decided to act with your reliable assistance. As a matter of fact, the reason I came to Holland to seek for political asylum here, is the location of the Security Company here in Amsterdam. Since President Jose Eduardo Dos Santos has lobbied the International Community to freeze my Uncle's assets and accounts abroad, to ground UNITA, and he has already done this in Angola, I cannot lodge the funds in my name any where in the world at the moment. Also I did not declare the funds to the government here on arrival last year. I plan to use this money to safeguard my future. It is very essential that you understand that this kind of trust and confidence I want to place in you is extraordinary, and an act of desperation on my part in order not to lose this money. Please ensure that this contact with you should be treated with utmost secrecy. Your role in this project, is to act on my behalf as a trustee to claim the safety deposit containing the money which is deposited in my name, from the Security company, since I can not participate in any business activity or open a bank account here as a political asylum seeker. After the safety deposit is claimed, the money will lodged into an account preferably a new account you should open for this transaction. My share of the money will be returned to me when my asylum application in this country is granted, and I have permission to do business and open an account here. For your reliable assistance, I will reward you with 15 %($2,775,000) of the money. I have with me, the Certificate of Deposit and the release codes of the vaults for the safety deposit, which is in my name, and will be used for claim from the security company. Also, everything will be legally processed for transfer of ownership to you. This transaction should be completed immediately depending on your prompt response. I thank you in advance as I anticipate your assistance in enabling me achieve this goal. Please contact me on my private email address; olivsav@netscape.net whether or not you are interested in assisting us. This will enable us make alternative plans, in the event of non-interest on your part. To know more about the struggle by UNITA to liberate Angola, visit the links below and read. http://www.the-idler.com/IDLER-02/3-16.html http://news.bbc.co.uk/hi/english/world/africa/newsid_1839000/1839252.stm Sincerely, O.C.Savimbi.

DR. PAUL BABS. Contract award Unit N.N.P.C Ikoyi Lagos Nigeria. Email:paulbabs@zwallet.com cc. oshiorenua@email.com RE: CONFIDENTIAL Dear Sir/Ceo, I am, DR. Paul Babs, a director with the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation Contract award monitoring committee. It is with trust and confidence that I make this urgent and important business proposal to you on behalf of my colleagues . Actually,I would have contacted you by surface mail but for the urgency and the confidentiality this transaction demands hence I decided to contact you via email. My colleagues and I are members of the Contract Award Committee(CAC) of the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation (NNPC). My colleagues have mandated me to look for a trustworthy company into whose account some funds is to be transferred. We are in our possession vital approved documents to remit the sum of Twenty-six Million Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars (US$26,500,000.00)incurred from returns of our OPEC Oil sale which we want to transfer to a reliable safe foreign bank account in your country for our mutual benefits, as we intend to invest into lucrative business venture, in your country with your advice all we require from you is to provide us a safe bank account for the remittance of the fund and also to help source for lucrative long term investment to invest part of this fund. We are willing to offer to you upon negotiation an aggreable percentage of the total sum and profit accruing from investment plans. We are absolutely sure and positive that this arrangement will be of mutual benefit to us, and we crave your indulgence to treat this proposal with utmost trust and seriousness. We will fly over to meet with you, as soon as the money is transferred to your account for the disbursement of the fund and business plans, please note that this fund in question is not an illegal money, as all vital approved papers for the transfer will be sent to you as soon as we receive your banking information such as completed particulars of the bank account where you wish the fund to be transferred. The nature of your company?s business is irrelevant to this transaction, as all arrangements have been concluded for a successful and hitch-free transaction. We have taken measures to ensure that there is no risk involved on both parties; we have estimated that this transaction will be concluded within 14 working days on receipt of your acceptance to this proposal. Most important to send back to me now: Your private telephone, fax numbers: Name and address of your bank: phone and fax numbers: Your name, company name and address: Bank account and particulars. My colleagues and I have had some fruitful discussion with relevant top officials of both the Federal Ministry of Finance (FMF) and Central Bank of Nigeria (CBN) and they have agreed to co-operate in the transfer. An application for funds transfer shall be made at the appropriate ministries in favour of the beneficiary (you or your company). Thereafter, your company shall be officially regarded as having executed the contract for the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation (NNPC) for which payment is being made. This process makes the operation legal according to the laws of the Federal Republic of Nigeria. Please treat this transaction as strictly confidential,as we are civil servants who are not entitled to operate a foreign account. While thanking you for your envisaged co-operation. I await your immediate response through email address or fax. Best Regards, Dr. Paul Babs. P/S . copy your response to both email addresses above.

Dear sir , I am Mrs. Mrs. Grace Abba-Ganna, personal accountant to Late Chief Bola Ige(SAN) the Attorney General of the Federation and Minister of Justice, who wasrecently assassinated at his country home on the 23rd December, 2001 by assassins (May his gentle soul rest in peace) Amen. Before his death,he entrusted a certificate of deposit valued US$10,000,000 (United States Ten Million Dollars), with a security company in Europe.He told me that this money was deposited for him by the Former Military Head of State Rtd. General Ibrahim Babangida to protect his interest not to appear at the Oputa panel for re-conciliation and human rights violation investigation commission headed by Rtd. Justice Chukwudife Oputa. My reason of contacting you is for both of us to join heads and hands together to make claim over the US$10,000,000, as this money was deposited on my favour at the security company as instructed by the late Attorney General, to avoid trace of his name over accepting such gift or offer. His intention before his death was to contact a foreign partner who is trust worthy, capable of handling such huge amount of money and also operate a foreign account where the money will be deposited or paid into waiting for his retirement. The reason is because our country law states that civil servants are not entitled to operate foreign accounts. As it is now, with your full co-operation both of us can make claim over the US$10,000,000, what is expected of you is: (a) Your full name and address (b) Your phone and fax number (c) Your International Passport or Drivers license and your readiness to appear at the security company to sign off the money to your personal account. As soon as I confirm your interest, I will forward to you the certificate of deposit, power of attorney/transfer which will give you legal backing to make claim over the money at the security company. I will also forward to you the contact particulars of the Security Company and letter of agreement between both of us over the security of my fund that will be in your custody. For accepting to help out 30% of the US$10,000,000 will be for you, 60% for me and 10% set aside for re-imbursement of expenses incurred by both parties during the transaction. Awaiting your urgent response. Regards, Mrs. Grace Abba-Ganna alternate email gabbagana@yahoo.com -----------------------------------------------------------------------------------This E-mail was sent through Albawaba E-mail. Get your own at mail.albawaba.com ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------- This E-mail was sent through Albawaba E-mail. Get your own at mail.albawaba.com

Urgent & Confidential: Re: Tranfer of ($12,800.000. USD) twelve million eight hundred thousand united states dollars only. I want to transfer abroad ($12,800.000. USD) twelve million eight thousand united states dollars, from-guaranty trust bank plc, lagos-Nigeria. i want you to help or look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable and fit to provide either an existing account or open or set up new one immediately to receive this floating fund from my bank here in lagos, even an emty account can serve to receive the money, as long as you remain honest to me till the end of this important business transaction. I want to believe you will not let me down now or after the fund transfer to your account. I am aderoju muyiwa the audit/surpervisor, guaranty trust bank , lagos-Nigeria. during the course of auditing i discorvered a floating fund in an account opened since 1993 and also since 1996 nobody has operated this account again. after going through some files in the record, I discorvered that the owner account died without a living [Heir], hence the money has being floating and if i do not remit the money out urgently it will be forfeited to the goverment for nothing. The owner of the account Mr Allan miller,a foreigner and an industrialist,died since 1996 with his wife who is his next of kin,that is why nobody has come to ask for the money, my investigation proved to me as well that the late Allan seaman until his death was the managing director of diamond safari [pty] sa. With the particulars that you will provide, i will change all his banking docs to yours and start the fund transfer process to your account,but first you have to give me your word that you will not let me down like i said before and also agreement signed between us. We will start the first transfer with six million dollars [$6,000.000.] upon succesfull transfer without any disappointment from your side,we shall re-apply for the transfer of the remaining six million eight hundred thousand united states dollards, [$6,800.000.] into your account bringing the total to twelve million eight hundred united states dollars [$12,800.000.]. I am contacting you as a foreigner because this money can only be approved to a foreigner with valid international passport, drivers particulars and with foreign account because the fund is in dollars and the former owner of the account,late Mr Allan seaman is a foreigner. I will like us to sign a binding agreement that will bing us together in these deal, I am revealing this to you with the believe that you will not let me down, You are the first and only person I am contacting as regards this business, so please reply urgenly for me to brief you on the next step to take. You should forward your private telephone and fax numbers and your banking details that will be needed for the transfer of the money.you will have to give me the assurance that this money will be intact pending my arrival physically in your country for sharing/disbursement of the fund which will be 35% for your assistance, 60% will be for us and 5% will be set aside for expenses that will be incured by both parties during the course of the fund transfer to your account. I look forward to your earliest response through my private email address given below aderojumuyiwa@ecplaza.net for security reasons. Best Regard. Aderoju muyiwa

My Dear, I got your contact address through internet browsing in my search for a reliable and trustworthy person who will assist me in a business investment venture in your country I am MRS. CEDIA D. ASTRADA the wife of MR.JOSEPH ASTRADA the former president of Philliphine located in the Southeast Asia. My husband was recently impeached from office by a backed uprising of mass demostration and the senate parliament. The present government has enforced my husband out of office for Manila to avoid demonstration by his supporters. During my husband regime as president of Phillipine I realised millions of dollars from various projects I executed successfully I had plans to > invest this money for future on real estate and industrial production. My husband is not aware of this because I wish to do it secretly now. Before my husband was impeached from office I secretly deposited this money valued at about $30 millon us dollar with a security that deals with transhipment of value googs through a diplomatic courier services to the adhoc offices. The consignment or boxes I declared owned by my foreign business partner. I wish to give you 20% out of the total sum if You will be willing to assist me claim money and invest the money as I assumed you 100% risk free business transaction I am trusting you as a God fearing person that will not sit on my fund when it get into your account but rather assist me in this business venture. This business demands absolute secrecy and confidentiality as such it's my considered opinion that all correspondence shall be via email because my lines are connected to the philliphine telecommunication network services. I will furnish you with more details (documents) when I receive your positive response wishing you a long lasting business relationship. Thanks. MRS LUISA ASTRADA PLS SEND YOUR RESPONSE TO MY PRIVATE EMAIL:luisa_2003@myself.com ___________________________________________________________ Kukamail.com - Free Email for the World! Open your account here: http://www.kukamail.com ___________________________________________________________ SPONSOR MESSAGE: Get Email @YOURFAMILY, @YOURBUSINESS, or @YOURDOMAIN Visit: http://www.entergroup.com today!

Hello, I am sorry for the embarrassment this letter might cause you as we have not had any correspondence before this letter. I got your address through my nephew with Nigerian Military Chamber of Commerce industry and Mining during my research for a reliable and trustworthy partner who l can do business with though l did not disclose the nature of the business l intend to do with whoever he recommend for me. I am DR. MRS MARIAM ABACHA, wife of the late Nigeria Head of State, General Sanni Abacha who died on the 8th of June 1998 while still on active duty. I am contacting you in view of the fact that we will be of great assistance to each other likeness developing a cordial relationship. I currently have within my reach the sum of Twenty - Five Million US Dollars (US$25,000,000.00) cash which l intends to use for investment, like Real Estate Development specifically in your country. This money came as a payback contract deal between my late husband and a Russian Firm on our countries Multi-billion dollars Ajaokuta Steel Plant. The Russian Partners returned my husband's Share of USD$25,000,000.00 after the death of my husband and Lodged in my husband's Security Company of which l am director right now, the new Civilian Government have intensified their probe on my husband? Financial and oil company. In view of these, l acted fast to withdraw the US$25,000,000.00 from the company vault and deposited it in a Security Company. I have since declared the Security Company bankrupt. No record ever existed concerning the money traceable by the government because there is no documentation showing that we received the money from the Russian. Due to the current situation in the country concerning government attitude towards my family, it has become quite impossible for me to make use of this money within. Let me refer you to the front page of this day newspapers of 10th March 2001. You can check it through their website www.thisdayonline.com the present government in Nigeria had frozen and seized all our bank accounts both here in Nigeria and abroad.Thus consent l shall expect you to contact me urgently to enable us discuss in detail about this transaction.Bearing in mind that your assistance is needed to transfer this fund, I proposed a percentage of 30% of the total sum to you for the expected service and assistance, 15% for offsetting minor expenses incurred in the course of this transaction. Your urgent response is highly needed as to stop further contacts. All correspondence must be by the email address mariamabacha200@ecplaza.net I will give you my Tel numbers where you can contact me when I hear from you. I must use this opportunity to implore you to exercise the utmost indulgence to keep this matter extraordinarily confidential whatever your decision while await your prompt response. NB: Because of the security being mounted on the members of my family, l has decided that this transaction exist between you and my nephew Dr. Azeez Bello. Remember to include your private Tel/fax or mobile number for easy communication. Best Regards. DR. (MRS) MARIAM ABACHA

DR.TUNJI OWO Gulf Bank Ltd,Lagos,Nigeria, Private Tel:234-80-2354-6330. E-Mail: tunji_owo@zwallet.com Dear Friend, I am DR.TUNJI OWO.The Manager Gulf Bank, Lagos, Nigeria. I have urgent and-ery confidential business proposition for you. On April 6, 1996, a Foreign Oil consultant/contractor with the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation, Mr.james smith made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for some months, valued at S$22,500,000.00 (Twenty Two Million Five hundred Thousand Dollars only) in my branch. Upon maturity,I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month,we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers,the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation that Mr. james smith on 1 February 1997 died in a plane crash on air senegal on aircraft Name Hawker Siddeley HS-748. This crash happened in Tambacoumba, Senegal, Africa and the registration number of the aircraft is 6AV-AEO, and since his untimely death the funds has been dormant in his account with my Bank without any claim of the fund On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL, and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr. james smith did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$22,500,000.00 has carefully been moved out of my bank to a security company for safe-keeping.No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Nigerian Law,at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Nigerian Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as an Foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to the late mr.james smith as to claim the money I deposited with the security company in two trunk boxes though the security company does not know the contents of the boxes as I tagged them to be photographic materials for export. am writing you because as a public servant, we can not operate a foreign account or have an account that is more than $1m.I want to present you as the owner of the boxes in the security company so you can be able to claim them with the help of my attorney.All these are to make sure that the fruits of this old man's labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. This is simple.I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that the Attorney will prepare the necessary documents which will put you in place as the owner of the boxes. The money will be moved out for us to share in the ratio of 70% for me and 25% for you and 5% will take care of all expenses.There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the Attorney and this will guarantee the successful execution of this transaction. if you are interested, please reply immediately via my email address/phone upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please observe with utmost confidentiality, and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. REGARDS. DR.TUNJI OWO.

From:Muhammed Abacha I wish to introduce myself to you and the reason for my reaching out to you. I am Muhammed Abacha the the son of the late military head of state General Sani Abacha who died mysteriously on the 8th of June 1998. Following the death of my father Gen. Sani Abacha,elections were successfully held in the country and a civilian administration was sworn into power with the assistance of the American Government under the leadership of President Clinton. With the advent of the new democratic administration, a decision was taken by the new president of Nigeria, Olusegun Obasanjo to probe and ultimately prosecute all past military officers and their cohorts that served in very strategic capacities in the last military regime of my father.I was among those singled out to to be punished after a makeshift trial,for the supposed deeds of my dad,ever since I have been in detention(the past 3 years). On monday the 24 September 2002,I was released,on the condition that I will release the rest of my fathers money in my care,to the tune of $I.5b,which I agreed. Now I have been released but kept under severe house arrest,I had amassed monies running into hundreds of millions of dollars stashed in various private foreign accounts around the world,most of wish have been frozen. Presently, I am confined under house arrest after my recent release from detention and I am now constrained into seeking for this assistance today because I cannot afford to let this goverment know that I still have funds stashed away. Shortly, before my detention I hurriedly deposited the sum of USD35.5 m illion with a security deposit firm for safekeeping,hence my seeking your assistance to receive this fund. I have since had this amount stashed away in a private security company in Europe. I cannot send this money to any of my Bank Account abroad or open a new account for reasons mentioned earlier. I hereby seek your assistance in moving and securing this money in your account abroad. I will adequately compensate you with 15% of the total sum for your assistance and co-operation with me to move this fund to your account for safe keeping where I can easily utilise it. The present administration has beamed their search light on any body remotely related to me and my family and you strongly know for certain that I am under surveillance and I cannot operate any of my bank accounts any more, due to their being frozen. I intend to safeguard and invest this amount of money abroad, but with a reliable foreign business partner so that we can invest the funds in doing business in your country. That is why I am soliciting your assistance and cooperation as regards this business.Arrangements are being concluded with the Security Company which has branches in Europe to receive the money in cash. I cannot tell the full story of my predicament on this letter. However you can get more information by checking the following web; links. http://allafrica.com/stories/200010230279.html http://:allafrica.com/stories/200012070247.html http://www.lagos-online.com/fg_details_loot_from_abacha.htm Please note that I have a relocation plans for me and my family immediately you have cleared and received this funds in your account. Please indicate your willingness to assist me by sending to me the following information, your private phone and fax numbers so that I can contact you and commence the transaction in earnest. I am waiting to hear from you very soon. Please for total confidentiality reply to orionventures@dmailman.com Best regards, Muhammed Abacha 234 8033205913 ___________________________________________________ GO.com Mail Get Your Free, Private E-mail at http://mail.go.com

Barrister.james oni E-mail:jamesoni2002@rediffmail.com Dear Friend It is obvious that this proposal will come to you as a suprise. This is because we have not met before but i am inspired to sending you this email by the huge fund transfer opportunity that will be of mutual benefit to the two of us.However, I am Barrister james oni,the Personal Attorney to the late Engr.Brian Loyd Smith a national of Isle ofMan in UK, who used to work with Shell Petroleum Development Company(SPDC) in Nigeria. On the 21st of April 1996, my client,his wife And their three children were involved in a car accident along Sagamu/Lagos Express Road. Unfortunately they all lost their lives in the event of the accident, Since then I have made several enquiries to several Embassies to locate any of my clients extended relatives, this has also proved successful. After these several unsuccessful attempts, I decided to trace his relatives over the Internet to locate any member of his family but of no avail, hence I contacted you. I contacted you to assist in repartrating the money and property left behind by my client,I can easily convince the bank with my legal practice that you are the only surviving relation of my client. Otherwise the Estate he left behind will be confiscated or declared unserviceable by the bank where this huge deposits were lodged. Particularly, the Bank where the deceased had an account valued at about $5million U.S dollars( five Million United State of America dollars). Conseqently,The bank issued me a notice to provide the next of kin or have the account confiscated within the next ten official working days. since i have been unsuccesfull in locating the the relatives for over several years now.I seek your consent to present you as the next of kin of the deceased,so that the proceeds of this account valued at $5million U.S dollars can be paid to your account and then you and me can share the money. I have all necessary legal documents that can be used to back up any claim we may make. All I require is your honest cooperation to enable us see this deal through. I guarantee that this will be executed undera legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law.Please get in touch with me by my email:jamesoni2002@rediffmail.com to enable usdiscuss further. Yours Faithfully, Barrister james oni. N.B. Please indicate your telephone and fax numbers for easy communication in this mutual transaction. Please forward your reply to: jamesoni2002@rediffmail.com. ___________________________________________________ GO.com Mail Get Your Free, Private E-mail at http://mail.go.com

Ahmed martins. D Union Bank Plc. Lagos – Nigeria. I am the manager of bill and exchange Foreign Operations Department of Union Bank of Nigeria. I am writing following an impressive information about you through one of my friend who runs a consultancy firm. He assured of your capability and reliability, although I did not tell him the details of the business I want to do with you. In my department we discovered an abandoned sum of $11.5million dollars (Eleven million five hundred thousand United States Dollars) in an account that belongs to one of our foreign customers who died along side his entire family on 2002 E.A.S plane crash. Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his relation to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless somebody applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines. Unfortunately we learnt that all his immediate family members died along with him at the plane crash leaving nobody with the knowledge of this fund behind for the claim since the account is his private account. It is therefore upon this discovery that I and two other officials in this department now decided to make business with you and release the money to you as the next of kin to the deceased for safety keeping and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we don’t want this money to go back into Federal Government account as unclaimed bill. The banking law and guidelines here stipulates that such money remained after Seven years the money will be transferred into banking treasury as unclaimed funds and will further be handed over to government. The request of a foreigner as next of kin in this business is occasioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and a Nigerian cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner. We agreed that 35% of this money will be for you as foreign partner, while the balance will be for my colleagues and I. I will visit your country for the disbursement according to the percentages indicated above once this money gets into your account. Please be honest to me. Therefore to enable the immediate transfer of the funds to you as arranged, you must apply first to my bank as next of kin of the deceased. Upon receipt of your response I will send to you a text of the application with the name of the deceased and his country and other information about him. Note this transaction is confidential and risk free. As soon as you receive this mail you should contact me through my e-mail address or alternative email address ahmedmartins10@juno.com Best regards AHMED MARTINS. D

Dear Sir, You may be surprised to receive this letter from me since you do not know me personally. I am Gabriel Kali, the first son of Gadik kali, one of the most popular black farmers in Zimbabwe who was murdered in the land dispute in my country. I got your contact through network online hence decided to write you. Before the death of my father, he had taken me to Johannesburg to deposit the sum of US15.5 million (FIFTEEN MILLION, FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS), in one of the private security company, as he foresaw the looming danger in Zimbabwe this money was deposited in a box as gem stones to avoid much demurrage from security company. This amount was meant for the purchase of new machines and chemicals for the Farms and establishment of new farms in Swaziland. This land problem came when Zimbabwean President Mr. Robert Mugabe introduced a new Land Act Reform wholly affecting the rich white farmers and some few black farmers, and this resulted to the killing and mob! action by Zimbabwean war veterans and some lunatics in the society. In fact a lot of people were killed because of this Land reform Act for which my father was one of the victims. It is against this background that, my family and I fled Zimbabwe for fear of our lives and are currently staying in the Nigeria where we are seeking political asylum and however have decided to transfer my father's money to a more reliable foreign account. Since the law of this country prohibits a refugee (asylum seeker) to open any bank account or to be involved in any financial transaction throughout the territorial zone. As the eldest son of my father, I am saddled with the responsibility of seeking a genuine foreign account where this money could be transferred without the knowledge of my government who are bent on taking everything we have got. The South African government seems to be playing along with them. I am faced with the dilemma of moving this amount of money out of this country for! fear of going through the same experience in future, both countries h ave similar political history. I am seeking for a partner who I have to entrust my future and that of my family in his hands. If you accept to assist me and my family, all I want you to do for me, is to make an arrangements with the security company to clear the consignment (funds) from their affiliate office here as I have already given directives for the consignment to be brought to the Netherlands from South Africa. But before then all modalities will have to be put in place like change of ownership to the consignment and more importantly this money I intend to use for investment. I have two options for you. Firstly you can choose to have certain percentage of the money for nominating your account for this transaction. Or you can go into partnership with me for the proper profitable investment of the money in your country. Whichever the option you want, feel free to notify me. I have also mapped out 5% of this money for all kinds of expenses incurred in the process of thi! s transaction. If you do not prefer a partnership I am willing to give you 15% of the money while the remaining 80% will be for my investment in your country. Contact me with the above E-mail address while I implore you to maintain the absolute secrecy required in this transaction. Thanks, GOD BLESS YOU Yours Faithfully, GABRIEL KALI.

From: Mr.Kola Awosika NIGERIAN NATIONAL PETROLEUM CORPORATION( N.N.P.C) PLOT 775, MCPHERSON CLOSE, VICTORIA ISLAND, LAGOS, NIGERIA. Tel:234-802-3230248 DEAR SIR, I AM MR.KOLA AWOSIKA AN ACCOUNTANT IN THE NIGERIAN NATIONAL PETROLEUM CORPORATION (N.N.P.C.).I HEAD A SEVEN-MAN TENDERS BOARD IN CHARGE OF CONTRACT AWARDS AND PAYMENT APPROVALS.I CAME TO KNOW OF YOU IN MY SEARCH FOR A RELIABLE AND REPUTABLE PERSON TO HANDLE A VERY CONFIDENTIAL TRANSACTION WHICH INVOLVES THE TRANSFER OF A HUGE SUM OF MONEY TO A FOREIGN ACCOUNT. THERE WERE SERIES OF CONTRACTS EXECUTED BY A CONSORTIUM OF MULTI- NATIONALS IN THE OIL INDUSTRY IN FAVOUR OF N.N.P.C. THE ORIGINAL VALUE OF THIS CONTRACTS WERE DELIBERATELY OVER INVOICED TO THE SUM OF USD$35,000,000.00 (THIRTY FIVE MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS). THIS AMOUNT HAS NOW BEEN APPROVED AND IS NOW READY TO BE TRANSFERRED, BEING THAT THE COMPANIES THAT ACTUALLY EXECUTED THESE CONTRACTS HAVE BEEN FULLY PAID AND THE PROJECTS OFFICIALLY COMMISSIONED. CONSEQUENTLY,MY COLLEAGUES AND I ARE WILLING TO TRANSFER THE TOTAL AMOUNT TO YOUR ACCOUNT FOR SUBSEQUENT DISBURSEMENT, SINCE WE CIVIL SERVANTS ARE PROHIBITED BY THE CODE OF CONDUCT BUREAU (CIVIL SERVICE LAW) FROM OPERATING AND/OR OPENING FOREIGN ACCOUNTS IN OUR NAMES. NEEDLESS TO SAY,THE TRUST REPOSED ON YOU AT THIS JUNCTURE IS ENORMOUS. IN RETURN,WE HAVE AGREED TO OFFER YOU 25% OF THE TRANSFERRED SUM, WHILE 10% SHALL BE SET ASIDE FOR INCIDENTAL EXPENSES (INTERNAL AND EXTERNAL) BETWEEN PARTIES IN THE COURSE OF THE TRANSACTION.YOU WILL BEMANDATED TO REMIT THE BALANCE TO OTHER ACCOUNTS IN DUE COURSE. MODALITIES HAVE BEEN WORKED OUT AT THE HIGHEST LEVEL OF THE MINISTRY OF FINANCE AND THE CENTRAL BANK OF NIGERIA (C.B.N.) FOR THE IMMEDIATE TRANSFER OF THE FUNDS WITHIN 13 WORKING DAYS SUBJECT TO YOUR SATISFACTION OF THE ABOVE STATED TERMS. OUR ASSURANCE IS THAT YOUR ROLE IS RISK FREE. TO ACCORD THIS TRANSACTION THE LEGALITY IT DESERVES AND FOR MUTUAL SECURITY OF THE FUNDS THE WHOLE APPROVAL PROCEDURES WILL BE OFFICIALLY AND LEGALLY PROCESSED WITH YOUR NAME OR THE NAME OF ANY COMPANY YOU MAY NOMINATE AS THE BONAFIDE BENEFICIARY. ONCE MORE,I WANT YOU TO UNDERSTAND THAT HAVING PUT IN OVER TEN YEARS IN THE CIVIL SERVICE OF MY COUNTRY,I AM AVERSE TO HAVING MY IMAGE AND CAREER DENTED.THIS MATTER SHOULD THEREFORE BE TREATED WITH THE UTMOST SECRECY AND URGENCY IT DESERVES. KINDLY EXPEDITE ACTION AS WE ARE BEHIND SCHEDULE TO ENABLE US INCLUDE THIS TRANSFER IN THE FIRST BATCH WHICH WOULD CONSTITUTE THE SECOND QUARTER PAYMENTS FOR THE 2003 FINANCIAL YEAR. CONTACT ME THROUGH E-MAIL ADDRESSES BELOW AS SOON AS POSSIBLE OR CALL ME IMMEDIATELY ON THIS TELEPHONE NUMBER:234-802-3230248 . YOURS SINCERELY, Mr.Kola Awosika awosika@caramail.com

DEAR SIR, I AM FORCED BY PREVAILING CIRCUMSTANCES TO WRITE YOU AND MAKE THIS PROPOSAL AT THE EXPENSE OF MY BEING EXPOSED;BUT I AM ENCOURAGED BECAUSE OF YOUR COUNTRY'S NON SUPPORT OF THE BRITISH/AMERICAN AGGRESSION AGAINST MY COUNTRY AND PEOPLE. I AM MR. SAAD ABDULRHMAN ALLI FROM AL-HUSSEINIA CITY IN IRAQ AND A SENIOR MEMBER OF THE BATH PARTY IN IRAQ. I AM PRESENTLY TAKING REFUGE SOMEWHERE INSIDE SYRIA. I NEED YOUR HELP AND COOPERATION TO SECURE SOME FORTUNE DEPOSITED SOMEWHERE IN EUROPE BY US FOR SENIOR IRAQI OFFICIALS BEFORE THE WAR IN MY COUNTRY AND I WILL DISCLOSE THE LOCATION OF THIS MONEY TO YOU AS WE PROGRESS. AFTER THE FIRST GULF WAR IN 1991, AMERICA BEGAN TO FREEZE ALL THE PERSONAL BANK ACCOUNTS OF SENIOR IRAQI OFFICIALS AND OUR LEADERS QUICKLY WITHDREW THEIR MONEY FROM WESTERN BANKS AND HAVE THEM CHANNELLED INTO SOUTH AMERICAN INVESTMENTS. HOWEVER MY DIRECT BOSS WAS UNCOMFORTABLE WITH THE SOUTH AMERICAN INVESTMENTS AND HE DECIDED TO HAVE HIS FORTUNE SECURED IN CASH IN SAFEDEPOSIT HOUSES IN EUROPE WHICH WERE LATTER USED TO BUY UP PAINTINGS, DIAMONDS AND GOLD BARS FOR HIM. PRESENTLY, WE HAVE A TOTAL SUM OF $15 MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS($15,000,000.00) IN A SAFE DEPOSIT HOUSE IN EUROPE AND I AM SEEKING YOUR COOPERATION AND ASSISTANCE TO WITHDRAW THIS MONEY FROM THE SAFEDEPOSIT HOUSE URGENTLY AND HIDE IT FOR US UNTIL THINGS SETTLE DOWN IN OUR COUNTRY IRAQ. IF YOU AGREE TO BE PART OF THIS PROJECT, WE WILL GIVE YOU 30% OF THE TOTAL AMOUNT AS YOUR REWARD FOR THIS ASSISTANCE AND FOR KEEPING EVERYTHING TOP SECRET. I AM CONFIDENT THAT YOU WILL NOT EXPOSE ME TO THE BRITISH AND AMERICAN INVADERS BECAUSE YOUR COUNTRY AND COUNTRYMEN CAMPAIGNED AGAINST THE INVASSION OF OUR COUNTRY AND WE CONSIDER YOU OUR FRIENDS AND SYMPATHISERS. IT WILL BE YOUR ABSOLUTE RESPONSIBILITY TO HADLE THE WITHDRAWAL OF THIS MONEY OUT OF THE DEPOSIT HOUSE AND TO SCURE OUR SHARE OF IT FOR US UNTIL WE ARE FREE TO COME OUT OF OUR HIDING TO MEET YOU AND COLLECT OUR SHARE FROM YOU AND WE HOPE TO COUNT ON YOU IN THIS HOUR OF ABSOLUTE NEED. FURTHER DETAILS WILL BE MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU UPON YOUR CONFIRMATION OF THE ACCEPTANCE OF THIS OFFER AND THE PROOF OF YOUR SERIOUSNESS. MEANWHILE YOU CAN REACH ME THROUGH THIS EMAIL ADDRESSES AND SATELLITE PHONE NUMBER. EMAIL: husseinalli@zwallet.com EMAIL: husseinalli44@zwallet.com SATELLITE NUMBER: 00 88 216 4711 9220. I LOOK FORWARD TO YOUR PROMPT REPLY AND UNDERSTANDING WHILE HOPING FOR YOUR UNDERSTANDING OF MY TIME CONSTRAINTS. THANKS, I REMAIN, MR. SAAD ABDULRHMAN ALLI.

ATTN: I am interested in your partnership in a business transaction. This business proposal I wish to intimate you of will be of mutual benefit to the both of us and it?s success is entirely based on mutual trust, cooperation and a high level of confidentiality. I am representing the board of the contract award and monitoring committe of the Zambian Ministry of Mining and Resources. I am seeking your assistance to enable me transfer the sum of US$30,500,000.00 (Thirty Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) into your private/company account. The fund came up as a result of a contract awarded and executed for and on behalf of my Ministry. The contract was supposed to be awarded to two foreign contractors to the tune of US$180,000,000.00 (One hundred and Eighty Million United States Dollars). But in the course of negotiation, the contract was awarded to a Bulgarian contractor at the cost of US$149,500,000.00 (One hundred and Forty-nine Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) to our advantage unknown to the contractor. This contract has been satisfactorily executed and inspected as the Bulgarian firm is presently securing payment from my Ministry, where our Board is in-charge of all foreign contract payment approval. As a civil servant still in active government service, I am forbidden by law to operate an account outside the shores of Zambia. Hence this message to you seeking your assistance so as to enable me present your private/company account details as a beneficiary of contractual claims alongside that of the Bulgarian contractor, to enable me transfer the difference of US$30,500,000.00 (Thirty Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) into your provided account. On actualisation, the fund will be disbursed as stated below. 1. 20% of the fund will be for you as beneficiary 2. 80% of the fund will be for Us. All logistics are in place and all modalities worked out for a smooth actualisation of the transaction within the next few working days of commencement. For further details as to the workability of this transaction, please reach me as soon as possible for further clarification. Please, call me on receipt of this mail on TEL: +31 612 932 685 Thank you and God bless as I await your urgent response. Yours Sincerely, Mr. JOHNSON ABBAS

FROM: THE DESK OF MR.DELE MARTINS UNION BANK OF NIGERIA PLC LAGOS NIGERIA BIG, STRONG, RELIABLE. DEAR SIR, I KNOW THIS PROPOSAL WILL COME TO YOU AS A SURPRISE EXPECIALLY WHEN YOU DO NOT KNOW THE WRITER, CONDSIDERING, THE HUGE SUM OF MONEY INVOLVED WHICH COULD MAKE ANY APPREHENSIVE. LET ME START BY INTRODUCING MYSELF TO YOU, I AM MR.DELE MARTINSDIRECTOR CREDIT CONTROL, UNION BANK OF NIGERIA PLC. LAGOS. I SAW YOUR CONTACT DURING MY PRIVATE SEARCH AT THE INFORMATION CENTRE HERE IN NIGERIA CHAMBER OF COMMENCE AND INDUSTRY AND I WANT TO BELIEVE THAT YOU WILL BE VERY HONEST, COMMITTED AND CAPABLE OF ASSISTING IN THIS BUSINESS VENTURE. FIRSTLY, LET ME EXPLAIN THE SOURCE OF THIS FUNDS AND WHAT YOU ARE EXPECTED TO DO. A FORIGNER LATE ENGINEER THEOPHILUS BAKER, AN OIL MERCHANT/CONTRACTOR WITH THE GOVERNMENT OF NIGERIA, UNTIL HIS DEATH, OVER A YEAR AGO, WAS A VICTIM OFA KENYA AIRWAYS: BUS (A310-300) FLIGHT KQ430 PLANE CRASH. THE DECEASED, ENGNIEER THEOPILIUS BAKER, BANKED WITH US AND HAS A CLOSING BALANCE AS A JULY 2000 WORTH $4.5M (FOUR MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOSAND USD). WHICH MY BANK, NOW EXPECTES A NEXT-OF-KIN TO CLAIM AS THE BENEFICIARY OF THE FUNDS, EFFORTS HAS BEEN MADE BY UNION BANK OF NIGERIA TO GET IN TOUCH WITH THE BAKER'S FAMILY OR RELATIVE BUT TO NO SUCCESS. BASED ON THE PERCEIVED POSSIBILITY OF NOT BEING ABLE TO LOCATE ENGNIEER THEOPILUS'S NEXT-OF-KIN, THE MANAGEMENT UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF OUR CHAIRMAN AND THE BOARD OF DIRECTORS ARE MAKING ARRANGEMENTS FOR THE FUNDS TO BE DECLARED UNCLAIMED AND CHANNELED TO AN UNKNOWN ACCOUNT. IT IS BASED ON THIS THAT WE HAVE CONTACTED YOU TO STAND AS THE NEXT-OF-KIN OF LATE ENGR. THEOPILUS BAKER SO THAT THE FUNDS, WILL BE RELEASED AND PAID INTO YOUR ACCOUNT AS THE BENEFICIARY AND THE NEXT-OF-KIN TO THE DECEASED. ALL DOCUMENTS, AND PROOF TO ENABLE YOU GET THE FUNDS HAVE BEEN CAREFULLY WORKED OUT AS WE HAVE SECURED FROM THE DIFFERENT OFFICES CONCERNED FOR THE SMOOTH TRANSFER OF THE FUND TO YOUR NOMINATED ACCOUNT.IT HAS BEEN AGREED THAT THE OWNER OF THE ACCOUNT WILL BE COMPENSATED WITH 20% OF THE REMITTED FUNDS, WHILE WE KEEP 75% AND 5% WILL BE SET ASIDE TO OFFSET EXPENSES AND PAY THE NECESSARY TAXES. IF THIS PROPOSAL SATISFIES YOU, PLEASE REACH US ONLY BY MAIL , FOR MORE INFORMATION. YOURS FAITHFULLY, MR.DELE MARTINS. NB: FOR CONFIDENTIAL REASON AND SECURITY PURPOSE,WE WILL BE COMMUNICATING THRUOGH EMAIL FOR NOW.

FROM THE DESK OF DR. HAJIA MARIAM S. ABACHA ATTN, I am Hajia Mariam Abacha the wife of the formal head of state the Fedral Republic of Nigeran Late General Sani Abacha. Following the sudden death of my husband General Sani Abacha the late former head of state of Nigeria in August 1998, I have been thrown into a state of utter confusion, frustration and hopelessness by the present civilian administration, I have been subjected to physical and psychological torture by the security agents in the country. I have lost confidence with anybody within the country.You must have heard over the media reports and the internet on the recovery of various huge sums of money deposited by my husband in different security firms abroad, some companies willingly give up their secrets and disclosed our money confidently lodged there or many out right blackmail.In fact the total sum discovered by the Government so far is in the tune of $700. Million dollars. And they are not relenting to make me poor for life. I got your contacts through my personal research,and out of desperation decided to reach you.I will give you more information as to this regard as soon as you reply.I repose great confidence in you hence my approach to you due to security network placed on my day affairs I cannot afford to visit the embassy so that is why I decided to contact you and I hope you will not betray my confidence in you. I have deposited the sum of 48.3 million dollars with a security firm abroad whose name is with held for now until we open communication. I shall be grateful if you could receive this fund into your account for safe keeping. This arrangement is known to you and my son Mustapha Abacha alone who have just been relised by the Federal Government,so my son will deal directly with you as security is up my whole being. I am seriously considering to settle down abroad in a friendly atmosphere like yours as soon as this fund get into your account so that I can start all over again if only you wish, but if it is impossible,just help me indiverting this fund into your account which will accrue you 30% of this fund.Please honesty is the watch word in this transaction. I will give you a more detailed picture of things. In case you dont accept please do not let me out to the security as I am giving you this information in total trust and confidence I will greatly appreciate if you accept my proposal in good faith.Please expedite action. Sincerely yours Hajia Mariam Abacha N.B I would like you to send me your Phone/fax numbers so that my son will call you for more details. __________________________________ Do you Yahoo!? The New Yahoo! Search - Faster. Easier. Bingo. http://search.yahoo.com

SOLICITING FOR A BUSINESS VENTURE AND PARTNESHIP. DEAR SIR, I AM THE SON OF THE LATE PRESIDENT OF THE FEDERAL REPUBLIC OF ZAIRE, PRESIDENT MOBUTU SESE SEKO,(NOW REPUBLIC OF CONGO UNDER THE LEADERSHIP OF THE SON OF MR. LAURENT KABILA) I PRESUME YOU ARE AWARE THERE IS A FINANCIAL DISPUTE BETWEEN MY FAMILY (THE MOBUTU’S) AND THE PRESENT CIVILIAN GOVERNMENT. THIS IS BASED ON WHAT THEY BELIEVE AS BAD AND CORRUPTS GOVERNANCE ON MY LATE FATHER’S PART. MAY HIS SOUL REST IN PEACE. PRESENTLY, WE CANNOT DO BUSINESS HERE IN HOLLAND AND MANY OTHER COUNTRIES OF THE WORLD BECAUSE OF THE NEW FRIENDLY RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN THE PRESENT GOVERNMENT AND THE WESTERN WORLD AS YOU MIGHT HAVE HEARD HOW A LOT OF MY FATHER’S BANK ACCOUNT IN SWITZERLAND NORTH AMERICAN HAVE SINCE BEEN FROZEN. FOLLOWING THE ABOVE MENTION REASONS, I AM SOLICITING FOR YOUR HUMBLE AND CONFIDENTIAL ASSISTANCE TO TAKE CUSTODY OF TEN MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS (US$10.5) AND (5KG OF DIAMOND) ALSO TO FRONT FOR ME IN THE AREAS OF BUSINESS YOU DESIRE PROFITABLE. THIS SUM OF US$10.5M AND DIAMOND HAS SECRETLY BEEN DEPOSITED INTO A CONFIDENTIAL SECURITY COMPANY, WHERE IT CAN EASILY BEEN WITHDRAWN OR PAID TO A RECOMMENDED BENEFICIARY. THIS FUNDS WILL BE RELEASED TO YOU BY THE SECURITY COMPANY BASED ON MY RECOMMENDATIONS ON THAT NOTE, YOU WILL BE PRESENTED AS MY PARTNER WHO WILL BE FRONTING FOR ME AND MY FAMILY IN ANY SUBSEQUENT VENTURES. TO SHOW MY PREPAREDNESS AND THE APPRECIATION TO CONDUCT THIS BUSINESS WITH YOU I SHALL GIVE YOU 20% OF THE FUNDS AND 20% COMMISSION ON ANY PROFIT REALIZABLE IN THE PROCESS OF INVESTMENT OF THIS FUNDS FOR YOUR ROLE IN THIS BUSINESS,WE ARE WILLING TO MAKE AVAILABLE 5% FOR ANY EVENTUAL EXPENSE THAT MAY OCCUR IN THE PROCESS OF THIS TRANSACTION. PLEASE, I NEED YOUR ENTIRE SUPPORT AND CO-OPERATION FOR THE SUCCESS OF THIS BUSINESS VENTURES, YOUR UTMOST CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECRECY IS HIGHLY REQUIRED, DUE TO MY FAMILY PRESENT PREDICAMENT. I SINCERELY WILL APPRECIATE YOUR ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AS SOON AS POSSIBLE. YOU CAN MAIL ME ON THIS E-MAIL:nzangamobutu@myself.com Best regards, MR. NZANGA MOBUTU.

Dear Sir / Madam I am Mr.Chuks Anthony,an account officer with Stanbic Bank of South Africa. I have an urgent and confidential business proposition for you. On June 6, 1997, an American Mining Consultant/Contractor with the South African Mining Corporation, Mr. Ken Power made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve (12) calendar months, valued at US$28,320,000.00 (Twenty-Eight Million Three Hundred and Twenty Thousand Dollars) in my branch. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the South African Mining Corporation that Mr. Ken Power died from an automobile accident. On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr. Ken Power did not declare any next of kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paper work in my Bank. This sum of $28,000,000.00 USD is still sitting in my Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to South African Law, at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the South African Government if nobody applies to claim the funds. Consequently, my proposal is that I would like you to stand in as the next of kin to Mr. Ken Power so that the fruits of this old man's labour will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that the Attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits which will put you in place as the next of kin. We shall employ the service of an Accredited Attorney for drafting and notarization of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and letter of Probate/Administration in your favour for the transfer. A bank Account in any part of the world which you will provide will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your Account for us to share in the ration of 60% for me and 40% for you. There is no risk at all as the paper work for this transaction will be done by the Attorney and my position as the Branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately email. Upon your response,I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documentsthat will help you understand the transaction. Please observe utmost confidentiality, and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Awaiting your urgent reply. Mr. Chuks Anthony

Dear sir/madam, Assalamalekum Before I introduce myself, I wish to inform you that this letter is not a hoax mail and I urge you to treat it serious. I am Dr. Muhammad Khalil Hasan, a banker with the Mashreq Bank Plc Dubai, UAE. I am the Accounts officer late Mr. Robert Chapman the African Area Director of SIL International, who unfortunately died in the crash of Kenya Airways Flight 431 in Abidjan, Ivory Coast, January 30 2000. You will read more stories about the crash on visiting this website, news.airwise.com/airlines/archive/2000/kenya2000.html and also in this website, where Chapman's company talked about his death in the Kenya crash. You shall as well find the pictures of Chapman and his wife there. Mr. Chapman was from Hamilton, Ontario Canada. Since the death of Chapman, I as his accounts officer in the bank, have made several enquiries to locate his only surviving relation, without any success. I came across your name and contact, on the course of my personal searching for Chapman's relations, so I decided to contact you for this project. I am contacting you to assist in repatriating and securing the wealth left behind in a fixed deposit account by Robert, before they get confiscated or declared unserviceable by my bank. The board of my bank, has issued a notice that after 2 months from now and no next of kin shown up for the claim, the funds will be confiscated and declared unserviceable. Since I and my team have been unsuccessful in locating Robert's relatives for sometime now, I seek your consent to present you as the Next of Kin of the deceased since you are a foreigner, so that the proceed of this deposit valued at $USD7.5 Million Dollars can be released to you. The bank will release the funds to any foreigner who has all related information/documents to the bank account. I am in charge of this matter in my bank, because I am his accounts officer. Your application will be directed to my department for verification and approval. Everything is under my control. I shall provide you all the information and copy of the certificate of deposit issued to Robert when he deposited the funds. I shall also involve a good attorney who shall represent you in all the appropriate offices for the claim. Please, find in the attachment my work ID Card. This is just to proof to you that my proposal is genuine. I also have all necessary information we need for the claim and once the money is transferred to you, I shall destroy all the documents used for the claim and leave no traces. After everything, you shall have 40% of the total sum,while 60% for me. All requires is your honest cooperation to enable us see this business successful. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. Robert was a very good man and it is not wise to allow his hard earned wealth to be stolen by the greedy directors of my bank. Further details awaits your response by email. PLEASE, TREAT THIS PROPOSAL AS TOP SECRET. Please, confirm the receipt of my Id Card in the attachment, as it was difficult to attach. Best Regards Muhammad Khalil Hasan. Mashreq Bank Dubai.

Greetings, First, I must solicit your confidence in this transaction, this is by virtue of its nature as being utterly CONFIDENTIAL and TOP SECRET. Though I know that a transaction of this magnitude will make any one apprehensive and worried, but I am assuring you that all will be well at the end of the day. We have decided to contact you due to the urgency of this transaction, as we have been reliably informed of your discreteness and ability in transactions of this nature. Let me start by first introducing myself properly to you. I am Mr.Hamzat Sulaiman, a director with the Union Bank of Nigeria Plc. Lagos. I came to know of you in my private search for a reliable and reputable person to handle this confidential transaction which involves the transfer of a huge sum of money to a foreign account requiring maximum confidence. THE PROPOSITION: A foreigner, Late Engineer Johnson Creek, an Oil Merchant/Contractor with the Federal Government of Nigeria, until his death four years ago in a ghastly air crash, banked with us here at Union Bank of Nigeria Plc. Lagos,and had a closing balance of US$18.5M (Eighteen Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) which the bank now unquestionably expects it to be claimed by any available foreign next-of-kin of he Late beneficiary or alternatively be donated to a discredited trust fund for arms and ammunition at a military war college here in Nigeria. Fervent valuable efforts are being made by the Union Bank to get in touch with any of the Creek family or relatives but proved to no avail. It is because of the perceived possibility of not being able to locate any of Late Engr. Johnson Creeks next-of-kin (he had no wife and children) that the management under the influence of our chairman and member of the board of directors, Retired Major General Kalu Uke Kalu, that an arrangement be made for the funds to be declared UNCLAIMABLE and subsequently be donated to the Trust Fund for Arms and Ammunition to further enhance the course of war in Africa and the world in general. In order to avert this negative development, my trusted colleagues and I now seek your permission to have you stand as a next-of-kin to Late Engr. Johnson Creek so that the funds US$18.5M would be released and paid into your bank account as the beneficiary next-of-kin. All documents and proves to enable you get this fund will be carefully worked out and more so we are assuring you of a 100% risk free involvement.Your share stays while the rest would be for myself and my colleagues for investment purposes in your country. We have agreed that, the funds will be shared thus, after it has been transferred into your account; 1. 30% of the money will go to you for acting as the beneficiary of the funds. 2. 10% will be set aside for reimbursement to both parties for any incidental expenses that may be incurred in the course of the transaction. 3. 60% to us the originators of the transaction. If this proposal is OK to you and you do not wish to take undue advantage of the trust, we hope to bestow on you and your company, then kindly get back to me immediately via my private Email for security reasons: Furnish me with your most confidential telephone, fax number and exclusive bank particulars so that I can use these information to apply for the release and subsequent transfer of the funds in your favour. Thank you in advance for your anticipated co-operation. Yours faithfully, Mr.Hamzat Sulaiman Email:hamzatsulaiman@unionintbanks.com IF THIS EMAIL COMES IN ERROR PLEASE DELETE.

SWEETIE AMINAT USMAN E.MAIL:ami44000@netzero.net TEL:234-8034540228 Dear Sir,/Madam I am LADY SWEETIE AMINA USMAN, Bank Manager of Zenith International Bank of Nigeria,Adeola Odeku Branch,Lagos . I have urgent and very confidential business proposition for you. On June 6, 1999, an American Oil consultant/contractor with the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation, Mr. Barry Kelly made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at US$35,000,000.00 (Thirty- five Million Dollars) in my branch. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation that Mr. Barry Kelly died from an automobile accident. On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL, and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr. Barry Kelly did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$35,000,000.00 is still sitting in my Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Nigerian Law, at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Nigerian Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foriegner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr. Barry Kelly so that the fruits of this old man's labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that the Attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits which will put you in place as the next of kin. We shall employ the service of an Attorney for drafting and notarization of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/administration in your favor for the transfer. We would need you as a Foreigner acting as the next of kin and sole benefactor to the inheritance of Mr. Barry Kelly to travel and claim this money in a SECURITY COMPANY based in Europe or sub-regional African country which is used by my bank as an offshore clearing house to the bank.The money will be paid to you for us to share in the ratio of 60% for me and 40% for you. There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the Attorney and my position as the Branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately via the private email address below. Upon your response,I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Please furnish me with your telephone and fax numbers for easier and faster communication. Awaiting your urgent reply via my email:ami44000@netzero.net Thanks and regards, SWEETIE AMINA USMAN ________________________________________________________________ The best thing to hit the internet in years - NetZero HiSpeed! Surf the web up to FIVE TIMES FASTER! Only $14.95/ month -visit www.netzero.com to sign up today!

>From : L.T. J.N. KAMPALA 08 BP 313 Abidjan 08 E-mail: kampala09@zwallet.com TEL 00225 07 59 70 57 ATTN SIR: I got your contact from the International Economic / Business Directory in Cote d'Ivoire. I consider your company extremely capable in handling this mutual business transaction I wish to undertake with you. As a result of my zeal towards foreign investment and also security for my life and possession, I therefore wish to give an insight of my purpose of contacting you. I was the personal confidant to the ousted military head of state of Sierra Leone (MAJOR JOHNNY KOROMAH). However, when the ECOMOG peace keeping force struck, his excellence was forced to run into Liberia on exile while some of his aides left for some other neighbouring countries. While these events took place, I decided to move to Côte d?Ivoire with my family and a total sum of thirty million US dollars (US$30,000,000) which was the part of cash under my control within the presidential mansion when I was in change of securities. On getting to Abidjan, I immediately deposited the fund in a bank in Abidjan the economic capital of Cote D'Ivoire. Consequently, I sincerely implore you as a partner to arrange an avenue which this money could be transferred to you for investment purposes and in order to actualise this investment proposal. You are implored to assist in the following. 1)You are required to provide a safe foreign bank accounts into which the money could be transferred. 2)You shall serve as a general overseer and guardian of this fund and all the investments thereafter. 3)And you shall benefit 20% of the total sum for your efforts and absolute assistance in ensuring that this fund is successfully transferred into your accounts and as well as 5% of every monthly profit out of all investments. Having stated the above clearly, I expect your soonest response through this mail number kampala09@zwallet.com Please also endeavour to treat this business transaction as highly confidential. Yours truly, L.T. J.N. KAMPALA ______________________________________________________ Get Paid... With Your Free Email at http://www.zwallet.com/index.html?user=kampala09

DEAR PARTNER, I GUESS THIS LETTER MAY COME TO YOU AS SURPRISE SINCE I HAD NO PREVIOUS CORRESPONDENCE WITH YOU. I AM THE CHAIRMAN TENDER BOARD OF INDEPENDENT NATIONAL ELECTORAL COMMISSION (INEC). I GOT YOUR CONTACT IN THE COURSE OF MY SEARCH FOR A RELIABLE PERSON WITH WHOM TO HANDLE A VERY CONFIDENTIAL TRANSACTION INVOLVING THE TRANSFER OF THE SUM OF $30,000,000.00 D0LLARS (THIRTY MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS) INTO YOUR PRIVATE ACCOUNT FOR SAFE KEEPING THE ABOVE FUND IN QUESTION IS NOT CONNECTED WITH ARMS, DRUGS OR MONEY LAUNDERING. IT IS THE PRODUCT OF AN OVER INVOICE ON CONTRACT AWARDED IN 1999 BY INEC TO A FOREIGN COMPANY FOR THE SUPPLY OF ELECTORAL MATERIALS THAT WAS USED FOR CONDUCTING 1999 ELECTION. THE CONTRACT HAS LONG BEEN EXECUTED AND PAYMENT OF THE ACTUAL CONTRACT AMOUNT HAS BEEN PAID TO THE FOREIGN CONTRACTOR LEAVING THE BALANCE OF US$30MILLION DOLLARS IN A DORMANT ACCOUNT, WHICH MY COLLEAGUES AND I NOW WANT TO TRANSFER OUT OF NIGERIA INTO A RELIABLE FOREIGN ACCOUNT FOR OUR PERSONAL USE. AS CIVIL SERVANTS WE DO NOT HAVE THE NECESSARY FOREIGN ACCOUNT MACHINERY TO SUCCESSFULLY HANDLE THIS TRANSACTION THEREFORE IT BECOMES NECESSARY TO SOURCE FOR A FOREIGN COMPANY OR AN INDIVIDUAL WITH THE CAPABILITY TO ACT AS THE ORIGINAL BENEFICIARY OR THE CONTRACTOR. MY DEAR, IT IS A GOOD THING THE PRESIDENT HAS ENDORSED THE RESOLUTION PASSED BY THE SENATE THAT ALL FOREIGN CONTRACTORS OWED BY THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT OF NIGERIA SHOULD BE PAID. WE WILL SEIZE THIS GOOD OPPORTUNITY TO SUPPORT YOU AS ONE OF THE BENEFICIARIES TO BE PAID. IF YOU ARE INTERESTED IN THE PROPOSAL KINDLY GET BACK TO ME BY SENDING ME YOUR LETTER OF ACCEPTANCE ALONG WITH YOUR DIRECT TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBERS, BUT IF YOU CANNOT FOR ANY REASON TO HANDLE THIS TRANSACTION I SHOULD BE GRATEFUL, IF YOU CAN INTRODUCE IT TO A RELIABLE AND TRUST WORTHY PERSON IN WHICH IN ANY CASE YOUR INTEREST WILL BE PROPERLY TAKEN CARE OF. MEANWHILE, MY COLLEAGUES AND I HAVE DECIDED TO SHARE THE MONEY IN THE FOLLOWING RATIO: 60% FOR MY COLLEAGUES AND I, THEN 30% FOR YOU THE ACCOUNT OWNER AND 10% FOR ALL LOCAL AND INTERNATIONAL EXPENSES THAT MAY ARISE IN THE COURSE OF THIS TRANSACTION. FURTHER DETAILS ABOUT THIS TRANSACTION WILL BE DISCUSSED IN THE SUBSEQUENT CORRESPONDENCE. THIS TRANSACTION IS STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL BUT 100% RISK FREE. NOTE ALSO THAT THE PARTICULAR NATURE OF YOUR BUSINESS IS IRRELEVANT TO THIS TRANSACTION AND THIS TRANSACTION IS EXPECTED TO BE CONCLUDED WITHIN 21 WORKING DAYS SINCE ALL LOCAL CONTACTS AND ARRANGEMENTS HAVE BEEN PROPERLY PERFECTED FOR A SMOOTH AND SUCCESSFUL CONCLUSION OF THISTRANSACTION. CONTACT ME VIA EMAIL WITH YOUR CONTACT TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBERS, SO THAT I CAN CALL YOU FOR A DISCUSSION. THANK YOU AS I AWAIT YOUR RESPONSE. YOURS FAITHFULLY, FREDRICK MBONU

Dear SIR/MADAM, I am Mr. John Coleman and my sister is Miss Rose Coleman, we are the children of late Chief Paul Coleman from Sierra Leone. I am writing you in absolute confidence primarily to seek your assistance to transfer our cash of twenty one Million Dollars ($21,000.000.00) now in the custody of a private Security trust firm in Europe the money is in trunk boxes deposited and declared as family valuables by my late father as a matter of fact the company does not know the content as money, although my father made them to under stand that the boxes belongs to his foreign partner. Source of the money: My late father Chief Paul Coleman , a native of Mende District in the Northerh province of Sierra Leone, was the General Manager of Sierra Leone Mining co-operation (S.L.M.C.) Freetown . According to my father, this money was the income accrued from Mining Co-operation's over draft and minor sales. Before the peak of the civil war between the rebels forces of Major Paul Koroma and the combined forces of ECOMOG peace keeping operation that almost destroyed my country, following the forceful removal from power of the civilian elected President Ahmed Tejan Kabbah by the rebels. My father had already made arrangement for his family thats talking about my mother, my little sister and myself to be evacuated to HOLLAND NETHERLAND, with the CERTIFICATE OF DEPOSIT he made with a security firm in Europe through the aid of U.N evacuation team. During the war in my country, and following the indiscriminate looting of Public and Government properties by the rebel forces, the Sierra Leone mining coop. Was one of the target looted and it was destroyed. My father including other top Government functionaries were attaked and killed by the rebels in November 2000 because of his relationship with the civilian Government of Ahmed Tejan Kabbah. As a result of my father's death , and with the news of my uncle's involvement in the air crash in Januaryit dashed our hope of survival. The untimely deaths caused my mother's heart failure and other related complications of which she later died in the hospital after we must have spent a lot of money on her early this year . Now my 18 years old sister and myself are alone in this strange country suffering without any care or help. Without any relation,we are nowlike refugees and orphans. Our only hope now is in you and the boxes deposited in the Security Firm To this effect, I humbly solicit your assistance in the followings ways. 1. to assist me claim this boxes from the security Firm as our beneficiary 2. to transfer this money (USD$21M) in your name to your country 3. to make a good arrangement for a joint business investment on our behalf in your country and you, our Adviser/ Manager For your assistance, I have agreed with my younger sister that 15% of the total amount will be for your effort and another 5 % to cover all the expenses that may incur during the business transaction, Last, I urge you to keep this transaction strictly confidential as no one knows our where about. Please as you show your willingness, Forward to us your full name, address and Tel/ Fax numbers, to me via my private email address as indicated bellow,(rosecolemen@netscape.net) this is for security reasons as i will only be accessing my private email earnestly awaiting your response. Thanks. May God bless you as you assist us. Mr. JOHN COLEMAN.

Date: Tue, 13 May 2003 10:32:09 -0700 (PDT) Nkomo Oil Services . Director:Aron Nkomo Our Ref:private Present Direct Tel: 31645570750 Direct Fax: 31645570751 World Tel: +873-76-3432240 World Fax: +873-76-3432241 South Africa: +27-833654452 Joshua Nkomo Avenue, Bulawayo, Zimbabwe. Date:08-06-2003 Urgent! Attention: Do not be surprised about this letter to you as I got your contact through a financial consultant of mine in Europe. My name is Gooday Nkomo the last born of late Joshua Nkomo the former Vice President of Zimbabwe and Former President of Zimbabwe African People's Union (ZAPU). However, I was studying in a boarding high school when I had to forcefully return for my father's burial. After the burial, my father's lawyer notified the family about his Will in their chamber. While going through the will, I discovered that my father used his position as the Former Vice President to acquire and make a deposition of US$ 23 M {Twenty-three Million United States dollars} in a special Security Company in South Africa. I immediately had to travel to South Africa where a financial Expert advised me on the best way to safe guard and realize usefully this funds without any problems from the South African authorities. This was to involve a foreigner, who will come down here to South Africa, open a non-resident Bank account where the money will be deposited for onward transfer to any nominated account overseas as foreigners are highly respected. This is why I am making this contact with you now though I am in Amsterdam arranging for the best possible way to ensure the delivery of the consignment to Europe here. You are to come down to Amsterdam and assist me in getting the money out to your beautiful country where I and my family can make further investment of the money and where I can live a better life and have a better education as this is my life long dream. Here in Amsterdam, my refugee status has eliminated any chances of my owning an account. Please, do contact me with my Tel No: +873-76 3432240 or Fax No: +873 76 3432241 or Amsterdam Tel:+31indicating your interest and capability for more details. You are entitled to 25% of the total amount for assisting me; I have mapped out 3% for immediate re-imbursement for expenses upon your arrival here, while the rest will be for me, and my family members, which I would like to invest in your country under your close supervision and direction. Note: The content of the consignment is US$ 23 million cash money, but the Security Company does not know the actual content of the consignment because it was deposited by my father with a declaration that the content is precious metals and diamond valued at US$ 23 M, and this was done with diplomatic immunity and for security reason, at the time, my father was still in government in my country Zimbabwe. This transaction is basically risk-free for you; therefore, reach me, preferably with the above stated phone or fax number to ensure the security of this transaction. Note that it is because of the confidential nature of this transaction that I am giving you these contact info. which you can use to reach me anywhere I am in the world: Tel: +873-76-3432240 Fax: +873-76-3432241 Private E-mail:goodnkomo@hotmail.com Awaiting your immediate, urgent contact! Yours Faithfully, GOODAY NKOMO Director;NKOMO OIL SERVICE. _________________________________________________________________ Protect your PC - get McAfee.com VirusScan Online http://clinic.mcafee.com/clinic/ibuy/campaign.asp?cid=3963

Union Bank of Nigeria. UBN. Plc. UBN. House Apapa. Lagos-Nigeria E-mail: hammzaidiris @yahoo.co.uk Attn: President/CEO REQUEST FOR YOUR COOPERATION I am hamza idiris, the head of accounts department in the Union Bank of Nigeria (UBN Plc), Lagos. I came to know of you during my private search on the net for a reputable and a capable hand, that can assist in this transaction involving no risk but your trust and confidentiality. There was this Engineer, Engr. Kelvin Michael, an oil merchant/contractor with the Federal Govt. of Nigeria, who died in a fatal motor accident three years ago.This man before his death was having a closing balance of $8.5m(eight million five hundred thousand dollars.)with our bank, UBN Plc. And our effort to get in touch with Mr Kelvin's family or his next of kin proved abortive. Now we have gotten a new Managing Director who is not aware of this money, and we the few management staff that are aware of the development doesn't want him to know, to avoid this money been declared "Unclaimed" and subsequently be donated to a Charitable Organization. To avoid this negative development, my colleagues and I have decided to seek your cooperation to have you stand as the next of kin to Late Engr. Kelvin Michael so that the said fund (US$8.5m) would be released and paid into your account overseas as the next of kin. All documents and proof that will enable you claim this fund without stress will be forwarded to you. Moreso, I want to inform you that we have unanimously agreed to offer you 20% of the sum for the assistance and role you are going to play in this transaction, 5% have also been arranged to take care of any eventual expenses. If this proposal interest you, and assure us that you will not take undue advantage of the trust we hope to bestow on you, please kindly reach me through my e-mail address. Expecting a positive response from you, thanks and bye for now. Regards, HAMMZA IDIRIS. ______________________________________________________ Get Paid... With Your Free Email at http://www.zwallet.com/index.html?user=hammzaidiris

PRICE WILLIAMS Richards&asociates Chambers 150 Airport Road, Lagos Nigeria email:princewilliamson@portugalmail.com CONFIDENTIAL AND EXCLUSIVE BUSINESS NEGOTIATION PROPOSAL. TRANSFER OF $15 MILLION UNCLAIMED FUNDS I am PRINCE WILLIAMS, an attorney . I was the personal attorney to MR HAMADA KASUMOTO(hereinafter refered as my client) from KOBE, JAPAN , who was a consultant with Shell-Development Company . On the 21st of April 2001, MR HAMADA was involved in a fatal road accident and died on the spot with his wife and two kids. Since then I have made several enquiries to the EMBASSY to locate any of my client's relatives or next of kin, this has also proved unsuccessful. I was appointed his trustee and sole admnistrator of his estate which includes his Bank Account. I am contacting you to assist in repatriating the money and property left behind by my client before it is confiscated or declared unserviceable by the bank where this deposit was lodged. Particularly the finance company where he has a Bank account deposit with credit balance $15 million dollars ( Fifteen million dollars ) have issued me a notice to provide the next of kin. I seek your consent to present you as the next of kin so that the proceeds of this account valued at $15 million dollars can be paid to you and then we can share the money. 50% to me and they Bank officers who will assist to accomplish it successfully while 45% to you. Then the balance of 5% will be reserved for incidental expences. I have all necessary legal documents that can be used to back up this transaction. All I require is your honest cooperation to enable us see this deal through. I am very sure with your trust and asistance, we will successfully and legally transfer this money to you before the Bank Management take any decision about it. As an experience lawyer, I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law as we have also arranged to immediately close the account immediately after the transfer. Please get in touch with me through my email as stated below and send to me your telephone and fax numbers to enable us discuss further about this transaction. I hereby attach the CERTIFICATE OF APPOINTMENT as his trustee and sole administrator of his estate and also the current statement of his already dormant Bank Account with Union Bank Finance securities which my client operated before the unfortunate incident with a fixed deposit Balance of $15M. Also attached is a form for next of kin for you to fill carefully and append your signature then return by email attachment or fax. Please contact me immediately through my email: princewilliamson@portugalmail.com Note however, that your nature of business,sex or country of origin will not be a hindrance to the transfering of this money. Best regards, and peace be with you. Please if you want clarification or my personal photograph and international passport and driving licence, I will be happy to provide it provided you will not betray my trust and confidence in you and that you will provide yours too. PRINCE WILLIAMS email contact:princewilliamson@portugalmail.com --

Dear Good Friend, REQUEST FOR URGENT ASSISTANCE. This business proposal to you is strictly confidential, with due respect. Sorry at this perceived confusion or stress you may have receiving this letter from me, Since we have not known ourselves or met previously. Despite that, I am constrained to write you this letter because of the urgency it requires.As amatter of fact, I got your contact through the internet and decided to write you immediately believing you will be of a great assistance to my kids and me. My decision to consult you for a partnership business of mutual benefit is indeed personal.Iam not in doubt that you can be trusted in financial related matters of this magnitude. I am Mrs.cecilia aku, the widow of the former nigeria youth and sports minister late mark Ishaya Aku who died in a plane crash on the 4th of april,2002 My kids and I are trapped in an obnoxious custom And traditional rites of my late husband's family. We have suffered maltreatment and untold hardship in the hands of my late husbands family, simple because Iam not from the same tribe with my late husband.His brothers have taken all that I suffered with my husband to acquire including treasure, houses and his bank accounts closed by them. I wanted to escape to the United States of America [USA} with my children on exile, but again they conspired and stole my international passport and other traveling document to further frustrate me. Thank God, a week ago, I received Key Text Code (KTC} from an offshore payment center[OPC]in overseas via our family lawyer that my late husband deposited the sum of U.S $15.7 Million[Fifteen Million Seven Hundred Thousand United States Dollars] in cash with this company,hence my late husband's brothers would not allow me to have any telephone contact with anybody. It has therefore, become very necessary and urgent to contact someone, a foreigner like you who can travel to the offshore payment center on our behalf to help me receive/secure these funds and to help invest it on our behalf as well, while we find a way of getting out to meet with you in your country. These funds are kept on a CODE with the Security Company to avoid detection, seizure or diversion. I have had several discussions with with our family lawyer who has express willingness to help me with the necessary documents for the claim of the funds from the security company should I get an honest,competent and capable foreigner who will not cheat my kids and me or even sit on the funds after claiming it, to stand on our behalf to claim the funds. This is why I have contacted you to help save my children and I from this obnoxious tax levelled on us by my late husbund's brothers by claiming these funds and investing it on our behalf. But, you would need to give me sufficient assurance that if you help me, you would not divert the funds. My children and I have resolved to give you 20% of the total sum. This is all my children and I have got to live on. Please, I have reposed my confidence and trust in you and hope you will not disappoint me. I will forward you the contact of our family lawyer for you to get in touch with him immediately hence he will be the one to deal with you on the transaction to avoid suspicion from my late husband's brothers. I look forward to your urgent response. THANKS AND God bless. Mrs.cecilia aku

FROM: Mr  JOSEPH  ZODWAZD

TEL:27:73-149-6172

FAX: 27: 72-381-8254

E-MAIL: joseph_zodwazd@yahoo.com

DEAR CEO/DIRECTOR, I know that this business proposal will come to you as a surprise since we don’t know each other before but that doesn't mean that you will not be of a great help to me,but first let me introduce myself, I am MR. JOSEPH ZODWAZD, the CHIEF AUDITOR OF AMALGAMATED BANKS OF SOUTH AFRICA (ABSA). There is an account opened in this bank in 1983 and since 1991 nobody has operated on this account again but all this came to light after an internal auditing that I conducted by going through some old files in the records, I discovered that if I do not remit this money out immediately it would be forfeited for no reason.The owner of this account is MR SMITH B. ANDREAS, a foreigner, and a miner at Kruger gold co, a geologist by profession and he died since 1990. No other person knows about this account or any thing concerning it, the account has no other beneficiary and my investigation proved to ! me as well that this company does not know anything about this account and the amount involved is (US$26M) TWENTY SIX MILLION UNITED STATE DOLLARS. I  am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money can not be approved to a local bank here, but can only be approved to any foreign account because the money is in US Dollars and the former owner of the account was MR SMITH B. ANDREAS. We will sign an agreement, but I assure you that it is real and a genuine business. Please reply urgently so that I will inform you the next step to take immediately. Send also your private telephone number and a fax number including the full details of the account to be used for the deposit. I want us to meet face to face or sign a binding agreement together so that we can receive this money into a foreign account or any account of our choice where the fund will be safe. And I will fly to your country for withdrawal, sharing and other investments.

I am contacting you because of the need to involve a foreign account and  a foreign beneficiary. I need your full co-operation to make this work fine. I have a correct information of this account, which I will give to you later, if you are able and willing to handle such an amount of money in strict confidence and trust according to my instructions and advice for our mutual benefit because this opportunity will never come again in my life. I need a trustworthy person in this business because I don’t want to make a mistake, I need your strong assurance and trust. With my position now in the office I can transfer this money to any foreign reliable account, which you can provide with assurance that this money will be intact pending my physical arrival in your country for sharing. I will destroy all documents of transaction immediately we receive this money leaving no trace to any place.

You can also come to discuss with me face to face after which I will make this remittance in your presence and two of us will fly to your country at least two days ahead of the money going into the account. I will use my position and influence to effect the legal approvals and onward transfer of this money to your account with appropriate clearance forms of the ministries and foreign exchange departments. At the conclusion of this business, you will be given 30% of the total amount 60% will be for me, and meanwhile 10% will be for expenses both parties might have incurred during the process of transferring. I look forward to your earliest reply.

If my proposal is acceptable to you and you are willing to help me, please let me know so that you will enable me to  transfer the fund without any further delay or If there is anything beyond your understanding your welcome to e-mail or fax me on the number written above, because time is of essence.

I will hang-on until I hear from you soon.

Yours Faithfully, MR. JOSEPH  ZODWAZD

Do you Yahoo!? Yahoo! News - Today's headlines

From:FRANK BELLO, ATTN:PLEASE, permit me to inform you of my desire of going into business relationship with you . I am FRANK BELLO JR, The first son of late Mr and Mrs Usman Bello. My father was a very wealthy GOLD and COCOA mernchant in congo republic. He was poisoned to death by his business associate on one of their business outings. When my mother died on the 21ST october 1994 , My father took me and my brother so special because we were motherless. Before the death of my father on the 29th November 2000 in a private hospital here in NIGERIA,He sincerely called me on his bed side and told me that he had a sum of 55.600,000 US DOLLARS (FIFTY FIVE MILLION SIX HUNDRED THOUSAND USA DOLLARS)kept in a security company in SOUTH AFRICA. He also said that the security company does not know the content of the safe Box.He also used my name to Deposit the money as his first Son for next of kin. He also explained to me that it was because of this wealth that he was poisoned by his business assocaites, That I should seek for a foreign partner in a country of my choice where I will transfer this money and use it for investment purposes, I want you to assist me in clearing this fund into your account overseas as a beneficiary of the fund, and also use it for an investment purpose, such as real estate management. My intrested areas of investment are; REAL ESTATE,HOTELS, PETROLEUM INDUSTRY. I am honourablyseeking for your assistance in the following ways. (1)To assist me to clear this fund from the security company and transfer to your account successfully. (2)To serve as the guardian of this fund since I am a Boy of (26)yrs . (3) To make arrangement for me to come over to your country to further my Education and to secure a residential permit in your country. Moreover, I am willing to offer you 25% of the total sum as compensation for your effort /input after the successful transfer of this fund to your nominated account.Furthermore, you can indicate your option towards assisting me as I believe that this transaction would be concluded within 14 days,from the day you signify interest to assist me. Awaiting to hear from you soonest. please you can also reply this email to my alternate email address fbellojr10@zwallet.com Thanks and God bless you for your anticipated coperation . Best Regards, FRANK BELLO JR

DEAR SIR, ( I SEEK YOUR ATTENTION TO SHIFT THE TOTAL SUM OF US$60MILLION INTO YOUR PRIVATE ACCOUNT FOR INVESTEMENT PURPOSE) WE WOULD LIKE TO DEVELOP BUSINESS RELATIONS WITH YOU BY ESTABLISHING A TRUST AGREEMENT WHEREBY YOU SHALL HOLD, MANAGE INVEST AND DISTRIBUTE ALL ASSESTS RECEIVED FROM US IN TRUST AND THE PROCEEDS THEREFROM, UNDER THE TERMS OF THE TRUST AGREEMENT. I AM AN ATTORNEY & CONSULTANT TO AN INFLUENTIAL POLITICIAN, CURRENTLY A FEDERAL MINISTER IN THE FEDERAL REPUBLIC OF NIGERIA WHO HAS BEEN ABLE TO USE HIS DIPLOMATIC STATUS TO MOVE THE SUM OF US$60MILLION OVERSEAS (NAME OF COUNTRY WITH HELD UNTIL YOU ARE READY TO DO BUSINESS) AND PRESENTLY DEPOSITED IN A PRIVATE SECURITY COMPANY FOR SAFE KEEPING. THESE BOXES OF MONEY WERE AIRFEIGHTED AS ARTIFACTS AND PHOTOGRAPHIC MATERIALS. MY CLIENT, BECAUSE OF HIS PRESENT STATUS IN GOVERNMENT CANNOT BE PHYSICALLY INVOLVE IN THE MANAGEMENT OF THE MONEY, HENCE HE DO THIS BY WAY OF PROXY AND FIDUCIARY AGENT IN ORDER TO AVOID ANY PROBE BY THE PRESENT DEMOCRATIC GOVERNMENT OF NIGERIA. I AM REQUESTING YOUR ASSISTANCE AS MY COLLEAGUE AND LEARNED FRIEND TO HELP SECURE INVESTMENT OUTLETS WHEREBY THIS FUNDS ARE INVESTED IN GOVERNMENT TREASURY BILLS AND BONDS AND IN SECURE FIRST MORTGAGES SUPPORTED BY YOUR COUNTRIES REAL ESTATE AND OTHER ATTRACTIVE INVESTMENT PROGRAMS AVAILABLE. MANAGE THE COMPLETE PROCESS & ESCORT OUR FIDUCIARY AGENT THROUGH THE VARIOUS PROCEDURES. IF THE ABOVE IS WORKABLE FOR YOU & YOUR ASSOCIATE, I WOULD BE GLAD TO FORWARD OUR STANDARD DISCRETIONARY ASSET MANAGEMENT AGREEMENT FOR YOU TO LOOK AND MAKE ANY NECESSARY AMENDMENT. IF ANY, THIS AGREEMENT WE HOPE WILL HELP TO ASSURE THE SAFETY OF THE FUNDS AND CONSOLIDATE THE RELATIONSHIP.PRIOR TO HANDING OVER THE FUNDS TO YOU & YOUR ASSOCIATES, WE HOPE TO ARRANGE FOR A PRELIMINARY MEETING WITH YOU ON A NEUTRAL GROUND WHERE THE ORIGINAL OF THE AGREEMENT WILL BE SIGNED BY YOU & OUR FIDUCIARY AGENT/ MYSELF. TO ENSURE THE SUCCESS OF THIS TRANSACTION AND GUARANTEE THIS UNIQUE RELATIONSHIP, KINDLY TREAT AS CONFIDENTIALITY. SEND YOUR PRIVATE TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBERS TO ENABLE US TALK ON ONE ON ONE BASIS.I AWAIT YOUR URGENT RESPONSE.PLEASE , YOU CAN ALSO GET BACK TO ME WITH THIS EMAIL BOX. E-MAIL ADDRESS: basseyowo200@hknetmail.com BEST REGARDS. BARR. BASSEY OWO.

Dear , I know this letter will come to you as surprise. I managed to get your contact line from the Cote Divoire Chamber of Commerce, hence I did not waste time to contact you on a business proposal. Firstly, I deem is important to introduce myself. I am MRS SARA KABILA the third WIFE of late Democratic Republic of Congo President Luarent Kabila, who was assassinated on Tuesday 16th Jan . 2001, by his bodyguard. After the death of my husband, I and my son williams Kabila were not well treated in the family. His first wife(Madam Maman Kabila and her son(Joseph Kabila)who succeeds my late husband as the next President of Democratic Republic of Congo dominated my entire husband assets and property. Fortunately for me, on the day of the incident, I was in my husband&#146;s private house at LUMUBASHI, Firstly I wept over his assassination and then I thought of my future. I then started searching for important documents and valuables, because I know that my husband used to exchange minerals to buy arms from foreign companies. Eventualy I ran into one of these important documents. As God has planned for me, it happened that my husband deposited a Diplomatic Box in my name with a security and Finance Company in Abidjan Cote Divoire. I could not believe when I picked up the document Referred to here as the &#147;DEED OF LODGE&#148; My late husband secured (US$12million) TWELVE MILLION UNITED STATE DOLLARS, which was acquired from the sales of minerals. On discovering this document I came to Abidjan Cote Divoire where I am presently residing with my only son williams. Right now I want you to assist me to transfer this money into your account in your country, where I will invest it in any lucrative business as you may advice me. For your assistance I will offer you 25% of the total amount and 10% will be set aside for expenses we may incure in the process of this transaction. Should this letter receive your honor please do not hesitate to contact me or my son, and try to maintain the confidentialty of this transaction. I'm waiting anxiously to hear your favourable reply. NB: Please furnish me with your private number for easy communication. Please note that this Transaction is 100% risk free and you should up hold the secrecy involved. Best regards, MRS SARA LAURENT KABILA.

Dear, Please I am Mr Makathy Adams, the only son of late chief Adams Williams from Sierra Leone. I got your contact from the Ecowas Infomation Center in Cote d'Ivoire. My sources of your contact gave me the courage and confidence to rely on you. I am writing you in absolute confidence primarily to seek your assistance to transfer our cash of twenty one million eight hundred dollars ($21,800,000) now in the custody of a BANK here in Abidjan to your private account pending our arrival to your country. SOURCE OF THE MONEY My late father, chief Adams Williams, a native of mende district in the Northern province of Sierra Leone, was the general Manager of Sierra Leone mining co-operation (S.L.M.C.) Freetown. According to my father. This money was the income accrued from mining co-operation's over draft and minor sales. Before the peak of the civil war between the rebels forces of major Paul Koroma and the combined forces of ECOMOG peace keeping operation that almost destroyed my country, following the forceful removal from power ofthe Civilian Elected President Ahmed Tejan Kabbah by the rebels. My father had already made arrangement for his family, my mother, my little sister and myself to be evacuated to Abidjan, Cote d'Ivoire with our personal effects and the box containing team. My father deposited the fund for the safe custody until after the war when he will join us. During the war in my country, and following the indiscriminate looting of public and Government properties by the rebel forces, the sierra Leone mining coop. Was one of the targets looted and destroyed. My father including other top Government functionaries Were attacked and killed by the rebels in November 1999 because of his relationship with the civilian Government of Ahmed Tejan Kabbah. As a result of my father death, and with the news of my uncles involvement in air crash in January, dashed our hope of survival. The untimely deaths caused my mothers heart failure and other related complications of which she later died in the hospital After we must have spent a lot of money on her. Now my 16-year-old sister and myself are alone in this strange country suffering without any care or help.Without any relation, we are now like refugees and orphans. Our only hope now is in fund our father deposited in the BANK. To this effect, I humbly solicit your assistance in the followings ways. -To assist me claim this fund from the BANK asco-beneficiary. -To transfer this money in your name to your country. -To make a good arrangement for a joint business investment on our behalf in your country and you, thecaretaker. -To secure a college for my little sister and my self in your country to further our education. -And to make arrangement for our travel with you toyour country after you have transferred this fund. Most importantly. The whole documents issued after deposit in my custody. For your assistance, I beg to concede 15 % of this money to you for your efforts assistance . Best regards Makathy Adams

STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL My Dear Friend, I am highly compelled upon strict recommendation, to write you this very urgent and confidential letter.I do hope my letter will not embarrass you since I had no previous correspondence with you.I hope this mail will not come to you as a surprise. I am sending this proposal with due sense of humanity, responsibility and with few awareness that you will give it a sympathetic attention. I regret to the inconvenience it may cause you base on the condition that we have not met before. I wish to use this opportunity to introduce myself to you, I am Mrs Mary Iddo Sankoh,the wiife of the former minister of Diamond Mining Corporation in my country Sierra Leone in West Africa,My husband had a bullet shot by the rebels on his way travelling to Lusia a city after Freetown the capital along with my daughter, My daughter died on the spot while the U N peace keeping force rescued my Husband, he was taken to hospital for medical treatment which he later died about three months now. Fortunately, My Husband has Ten million and Five hundred thousand United States Dollars(US$10.5 million) cash, which he intended to use for investment purposes overseas. This money is kept with private security company in Europe since two years ago. It is only my son and myself that know where the money is kept and has the documents for it. Due to the current situation in the country concerning government’s vendettas towards my family, we seek your assistance to transfer the ownership of this fund to you so that you can asisst us to claim it and used for the purpose of investment as intended by my husband. My family is currently being probed by this present government for alleged involvement in misappropriation of public funds during his regime. Towards this effect, an embargo restricting my family members from traveling or carrying out financial transactions without their express permission is in force. Right now, my son and myself have concluded plans and decided to take immediate claim of this fund so that we can use it to better our lives and alliviate our present suffering hence this contact. However, I have an arrangement on how you can help us to recieve this money after receiving some assurances from you. The money personally belongs to my husband and he intended that it still be used for investment. No record ever existed concerning this money, neither is the money traceable by the government because there is no documentation concerning the funds in the Federal Treasury. Bearing in mind that your assistance is needed to transfer this fund, we propose a commission of 20%(Twenty Percent) of the total sum to you for the expected services and assistance. While 5% is mapped out for miscellaneous expenses. On your positive consent, I shall expect you to contact me urgently to enable us discuss about this.Your urgent response is highly needed. I must use this opportunity to implore you to exercise utmost indulgence to keep this matter extraordinarily confidential, while I await your prompt response. Best regards, MRS. MARY IDDO SANKOH/ABDUL SANKOH

Mr. Daniel Abass. Direct Tel:234-803-3049003. PRIVATE AND CONFIDENTIAL RE: TRANSFER OF US$50.5Million Dollars. Dear Friend, My name is Mr. Daniel Abass, an Accountant with the Ajaokuta Steel Company Ltd (ASCL). I am the chiarman of a committee set up by the Govrnment to investigate contracts awarded by this company for the past seven years, vetting and making payments on behalf of Ajaokuta Steel Company Ltd (ASCL). SUBJECT: After due consideration, we have fully agreed to privately invest extensively in your country. I am intending to resign from Government services to private business with someother officials of my parastatal as partners. I have specifically been mandated by my partners to arrange with you for terms of trade and possible transfer of the funds needed for the investment into your company’s account or personal account. This funds were incurred from an over invoiced contract awarded to a Russian firm during the regime of Late Gen. Sani Abacha. The original value of these contracts were purposely over estimated by us the Tenders Board Committee to the tune of US$50.5M(Fifty million,Five hundred Thousand Uinted States Dollars only). Now that the firm has received their payment fully, we want to transfer the over invoiced sum to your company’s account and privately invest in any profitable form of business. The US$50.5M has since been approved for Payment/remittance among other payments that have been made. This money is now floating in an escrow account of one the top commercial banks in the country as redundant funds waiting to be claimed. Because of our civil service code of conduct which prohibits all Civil Servants owning a company or operating a foreign account, I Therefore, solicit your help to remit this funds into your company’s OR PERSONAL account pending when we come over for the sharing. To enable us process and remit this fund into your bank account successfully within 10 banking days from the day of your response, we need the following information from you by a return E-MAIL. (1).YOUR COMPANY NAME AND ADDRESS (2)YOUR PRIVATE AND CONFIDENTIAL TEL/FAX NUMBERS AND ADDRESS. Note that as soon as we receive this information, it will be forwarded to the appropriate quarters for final processing and approvals. With this modality, it makes it possible for your company to act as a subsidiary of the original firm; and when satisfied by the agency, your bank account will be credited via Telegraphic Transfer by the Telegraphic Transfer Department of the commercial bank within 48 hours.This transfer is 100% risk-free having done all the underground works locally for the smooth transfer of the fund into your bank account within the shortest period. I advice that you should keep this business a top secret and rest all correspondences to E-mail and phone only because I am occupying a sensitive position in the government circle and also this is once in a life time opportunity which I do not wish to loose. We have jointly agreed to reward you with 20% of the total sum for your honest assistance and co-operation while 75% will be for my colleagues and I. And the remaining 5% will be mapped out for settling all expenses (local and foreign) incurred in the course of this transaction. Indicate your interest urgently by e-mail while you can always reach me at anytime of the day on my directy telephone number: 234-803-3049003 as soon as you get this mail. Best Regards Mr. Daniel Abass. Direct Tel:234-803-3049003.

Good Day, You may be surprise to receive this email since you do not know me. I am the son of the late president of Democratic Republic Of Zaire, President Mobutu Sese Seko, ( now The Republic of Congo, under the leadership of the son of Mr. Laurent Kabila). I presume you are aware there is a financial dispute between my family ( THEMOBUTUS ) and the present civilian Government. This is based on what they believe as bad and corrupt governance on my late father's part. May his soul rest in perfect peace. As you might have heard how a lot of my father's bank account in Switzerland and North America have been frozen. Following the above named reasons, I am soliciting for your humble and confidential assistance to take custody of THIRTY Million United States Dollars ( US$30,000,000.00 ), also to front for me in the areas of business you desire profitable. These funds have secretly been deposited into a confidential Security Company, where it can easily be withdrawn or paid to a recommended beneficiary. The funds will be released to you by the Security Company, based on my recommendations, on that note, you will be presented as my partner who will be fronting for me and my family in any subsequent ventures. Myself and my mother have decided to give 20% to you if you are able to help us claim this consignment. We have also decided to give you any money spent on phone calls or traveling expenses in the course of this transaction at the end of the transaction. Please, I need your entire support and co-operation for the success of this transaction, your utmost confidentiality and secrecy is highly required, due to my family's present predicament. I sincerely will appreciate your willingness to assist us as soon as possible. I am presently in the refugee camp here in the Netherlands under the united nations refugee camp in Netherlands and I can be reached on phone number +31-655-904-604 or E-mail me at basher200@latinmail.com for more information on how we can proceed in this transaction. Please indicate your interest by sending your telephone and fax number or call me up at anytime. I sincerely will appreciate your acknowledgement as soon as possible. Warmest regards, Basher Mobutu Sese-Seko.

FROM THE DESK OF DR.DAN BELLO FEDERAL MINISTRY OF PETROLUEM RESOURCES(F.M.P.R) LAGOS NIGERIA. ATTN:SIR, REQUEST FOR ASSISTANCE-STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL I am DR.DAN BELLO, an accountant in the Ministry of petroleum Resources (MPR) and a member of a three-man Tender Board in charge of contract review and payment approvals. I came to know of you in my search for a reliable person to handle a very confidential transaction that involves the transfer of a huge sum of money to a foreign account. It may sound strange but exercise patience and read on. There were series of contracts executed by a consortium Multinational in the Oil industry in favor of Ministry of Petroleum Resources among which were: 1. The extension of pipeline network within Nigeria for crude oil, Down stream products distribution and subsequent evacuation- US$ 195 Million. 2. Contract for the Turn Around Maintenance (TAM) of the various refineries in the country~ US$ 152Million. 3. The construction of storage tanks for petroleum products (Depots) US$240 Million. The original values of this contract were deliberately over invoiced to the sum of US $35.5million American Dollars which has now been approved and is now ready to be transferred being that the companies that actually executed these contracts has been fully paid and project officially commissioned. consequently, my colleagues and I are willing to transfer the total amount to your account for subsequent disbursement since we are Civil Servant and are prohibited by the Code of Conduct Bureau (Civil Servant Laws) from opening operating foreign account in our names. Needless to say, the trust posed on you at this juncture is enormous. In return, we have agreed to offer you 30% of the transferred sum while 10% shall be set aside for accidental expenses (Internal & External) between the parties in the course of the transfer. We will mandate you to draw up an investment plan for us of which you will control since we cannot bring our shares back to Nigeria. We are very interested in investing in real estate in your country. You must however note that this transaction is subjected to the following termsand conditions: 1. Our conviction of your transparent honesty anddiligence. 2. That you would treat this transaction with utmost secrecy and confidentiality because of thecircumstances we now find ourselves. 3. That the funds would be transferred to an account over which you have absolute control. Modalities have been worked out at the highest level of the presidency at the Central Bank of Nigeria for the immediate transfer of the funds within 14 working days, subject to your satisfaction of the above stated terms. Our assurance is that your role is 100% risk free. To accord this transaction, the legality it deserves and for mutual security of the parties involved and the funds, the whole approval procedures will be officially and legally processed with your name or the name of your company you may nominate as the bonafide beneficiary. Also, be informed that our main reason of contacting you is for the obvious reason that we will want to invest these funds in the real estate. It is our believe that you can be ofimmense help in this regards. Kindly expedite action so as to enable us include this transaction into this batch as payment to foreign contractors is usually carried out on quarterlybasis. Please, contact me as soon as possible on my private e-mail address: Best regards, DR.DAN BELLO _________________________________________________________________ Tired of spam? Get advanced junk mail protection with MSN 8. http://join.msn.com/?page=features/junkmail

Dear Friend, I am delighted to write this letter, hoping you will understand my predicament and answer back without hesitation since I am convince you must be an honest and God fearing fellow who will help save my life and my only son,hence our country has been frustrating us since the death of my husband. I am MRS M. MBEki, the wife of the late DR.MARTIN MBEKI,the former Chief Excutive and Group Director of PACIFIC BANK OF SOUTH AFRICA. I am in possession of $6,500,000.00 (SIX MILLION,FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND U.S DOLLARS)which I want to invest in your country. For your clarification and understanding, this money in a security company, which I deposited as a family effect since 6th of Febuary 2000 after the death of my husband, is not an ill gotten wealth rather it was generated by my late husband from over twenty years of his Banking Service and business relationship. On your acceptance to render this assistance to me,I will contact my son to instruct the Clearing House to effect a change of ownership of this fund in your name as the bonafide owner/my next of kin to enable you retrieve the fund on behalf of me and my family to your country to make good arrangement for any profitble joint business investment pending my arrival with my son to your country after you have transferred this fund. Bear in mind that this transaction demands absolute confidentiality because properties, assets and bank accounts bearing the MBEKI'S family name, are being ordered to be confiscated by the newly elected civilian President of South Africa. hence I will not want to be exposed for security reasons. I am only revealing this to you with believing in God that you will not let me and my only son down now or in future if this money gets to you because this is the only hope of our future survival since our bread winner is no more. For your knowledge, 1 % of this total amount has been set aside for all the expenses you might incure during the process of securing this fund. Example: TELEPHONE BILLS, HOTEL BILLS, FLIGHT BILLS,and other miscellenous expenses. Try and negotiate for some profitable blue chip investment opportunities which is risky free which I think we can invest with part of this money when it is transferred.Personally I am interested in estate management and hotel business,please contact my son (SODINDO M MBEKI) who was lucky to escape from South Africa to Lome-Togo with the Certificate of the claim Deposit, where he is now staying as a refugee on his email address (sodindo@uboot.com) for detailed procedure. Thanks for your anticipated co-operation. Yours sincerely, MRS M MBEKI. mbeki2@uboot.com NB: FOR CONFIDENTIAL REASONS,OUR COMMUNICATION SHOULD ONLY BE TRANSACTED THROUGH ELECTRONIC MAIL BECAUSE I'M NOT IN GOOD POSITION TO RECEIVE TELEPHONE CALLS FOR SECURITY OF THE FUND.

Mr.Kola Daniel E-mail:kolad05@hknetmail.com No 16 Kingsway Rd, Ikoyi,Lagos. Web Fax:+1-775-320-0047 REQUEST FOR ASSISTANCE - STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL I am Mr.Kola Daniel an Accountant in the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation (NNPC) and I head a seven-man tenders committee in charge of Foreign/Expatriate Contract Awards Review and Payment Approvals (CRPAC). I came to know of your name and address in my search for a reliable and low-key person to handle a very confidential transaction based on unflinching trust as we have not met before. This transaction involves the transfer of huge sum of foreign exchange (the United States Dollars) to a foreign account. There were a series of contracts executed by a Consortium of Multinationals in the oil industry in favour of NNPC among which are: (1) The expansion and rehabilitation of the ageing pipeline network within Nigeria for crude oil and downstream products distribution and evacuation - US$9 Billion; (2) Contracts for the Turn Around Maintenance (TAM) of the four epileptic refineries in the country; (3) The construction of more storage tanks and maintenance and servicing of old ones for Petroleum Products Storage (Depots) - US$90 Million; (4) The construction of Escravos Gas Poduction Offshore facility. The original value of these contracts was deliberately over-invoiced in the sum of USD Eighteen Million,Five Hundred Thousand ($18,500,000.00) by this committee (CRPAC) during the awards of the various contract. This sum ($18,500,000.00) has now been approved for payment by this committee (CRPAC)and is now ready to be transfered by the Central Bank of Nigeria to the account of any individual and or company which the CRPAC presents as the beneficiary, since the company that actually executed these contracts has been fully paid their fund and the projects have been officialy commissioned. Consequently, my colleagues and I are willing to transfer the total amount to your account for subsequent disbursement on our behalf, since we as civil servants and we are also serving in a sensitive foreign payment approval committee (CRPAC) are prohibited by the Code of Conduct Bureau (Civil Service Laws) from opening or operating foreign account and or dealing in foreign exchange in our names. Needless to say! , the trust reposed on you at this juncture is enormous. In return, we have agreed to offer you 25% of the transferred sum, while 10% shall be set aside for incidental expenses (internal and external) accrued between the parties in the course of the transaction. You must however note that this transaction is subject to the following terms and conditions: a) Our conviction of your transparent honesty and diligence; b) That you would treat this transaction with utmost secrecy and confidentiality; c) That you have an unflincing trust in us, and our ability to complete all official processes with your co-operation; (d) That the funds would be transfered to an ordinary account which you have total control over. Modalities have been worked out at the highest levels of the relevant government departments involved and the Central Bank of Nigeria for the immediate transfer of funds within 14 working days subject to your satisfaction of the above stated terms. Our assurance is that your role is risk-free. To accord this transaction the legality it deserves and for mutual security of the fund, the whole approvalprocedures will be officially and legally processed with your name or the name of any company you may nominate as the bonafide beneficiary, as in an ideal situation.It is imperative that you bear in mind that having put in 19 years in the service of the government, I am averse to having my image and career dented. This matter should therefore be treated with utmost secrecy and urgency. Kindly expedite action by contacting me on my e-mail address, indicating your interest in this transaction. For swift response to your reply,kindly indicate your fax and telephone numbers clearly so that I can explain further, especially by fax. I am urgently waiting your reply as payment to foreign contractors is usually made on quarterly basis. Yours faithfully, Mr.Kola Daniel.

Good Day , l am Dr.Titi Okonkwo., Civil Servant in the Ministry of Health. l know this proposal will come to you as asurprise because we have not met before either physically or through correspondence. I got your contact from our chamber of commerce here in Nigeria and have no doubt in your ability to handle this proposal involving huge sum of money. My father Chief Isama Okonkwo (Now Late) was the Royal Head of my community, ELEME (an oil rich town) in Nigeria. My community produces 5.8% of the total crude oil production in Nigeria and 0.5% of the Dollar value of each barrel is paid to my father as royalty by the Federal Government. My father was also the Chairman of ISAMA Special Oil Trust Fund. In his position as the Royal head and Chairman of the Oil Trust Fund, he made some money which he left for me as the only heir to inherit. The money is Eighteen Million, Five Hundred Thousand US Dollars(US$18.5). This Money originated from the accumulated royalties between 1976-1998 . Due to poor banking system in Nigeria and political instability as a result of past Military rules (1985-1999) , he deposited this Money in a Strong Room/"VAULTS" with an open beneficiary in a security company pending when he would finish arrangement to transfer it abroad . He was planning this when he died late last year of Heart Attack. Just before my father died he called my attention to the money and charged me to look for a foreigner who would assist me in the transfer/investment of the funds abroad. So l would be very grateful if you could accept to help me achieve this great objective. I promise to give you 15% of the total funds transferred to your vital bank account as compensation for your assistance. Five percent (5%)has been set aside to take care of all expenses we may incure during the transaction. To indicate your interest, contact me urgently and confidentially for more information and the roles you will play in this business. All the legal Documents concerning this Money will be sent to you as soon as we agreed together. Please I will appreciate that you send your telephone/fax numbers to enable me contact you immediately for discussions. May the almighty God bless you. Yours faithfully, Dr.Titi Okonkwo You can reach me with my private email address: " titiokonkwo@post.cz

ATTENTION I am Executive Accountant with the south Africa Department of Mining and Natural Resources (DMNR)South Africa and my department is directly in charge of contract award and payment of contractors. In the course of carrying out my duties as contract award/payment director I negotiated the award of a project to a Swedish firm for US$15 Million and already my government has allocated the amount of US$25 Million for this particular project. Having used my position to manipulate the extra US$10 M [ten million US Dollars] to my favour , I am soliciting a reliable but obscure individual to assist me as I will be handicap without a foreign partner given the fact that as a serving civil servant in my country we are not allowed to operate foreign accounts. My government is presently paying foreign contractors through their payment outlet abroad "Foreign Payment Board" in London-UK and if we move fast your particulars can be drafted as one of the contractors to be paid for onward release of the US$10Million to you/your company via FPB. I am soliciting that I facilitate the transfer of this money into your provided account so that I can travel to meet with you after the transaction to discuss my personal investment plans in your country. Note clearly that this transaction has been well planned having followed all the required official contract award/ payment procedures. Please, You have to give me your total co-operation and follow my advice /instructions and you should consider this transaction as already successful & concluded. Upon your reply I plan to register your company as a contractor with my Department here in South Africa. for this I would require you to provide me with your company name, address as well as your phone and fax numbers. Note clearly that as top Government officials in South Africa, occupying very sensitive top Government position we receive little salaries compared to our positions hence I must do this in order to leave a legacy for my family. I urge you to consider this proposal sincerely and reply back to me providing the requested information to proceed with the workability of the transaction. Best Wishes. Mark David(Engr)

From:DR. FEMI JOHNSON, Credit Officer First bank Of Nigeria PLC. Madam/Sir, First, I'm soliciting your utmost confidenciality in this Transaction. I am DR.FEMI JOHNSON, credit officer with First Bank of Nigeria PLC, Lagos. I came to you in my private search for a reliable person to handle this confidential transaction, which involves huge sum of money to your country. The Proposition: A foreigner an American, late Engr. John creek (SNR) who died on 30th of January 2000 in Kenya airways plane crash, while returning to his country from a business trip. He Banked with us at First Bank of Nigeria plc Lagos and had a closing balance worth US$35,Million, having heard of the tragic incident involving Engr. John creek (SNR) the bank now expects a next of kin as beneficiary. Valuable efforts have been made by First Bank to get in touch with any of his family's but I personally found out that he until his death neither had wife nor children that is known to us. The only name of next of kin given to ! us by late John Creek unfortunately was with him in the same flight that crashed, and this is unknown to the bank. I'm taking this advantage in order to bettermy life and that of my family, I now decided to seek your permission to have you stand as next of kin to late Engr.John Creek, so that the fund (US$35M)will be released in to your account as the next of kin. All documents and proves to enable you get this fund will be carefully worked out, by the lawyer that I will employ to work with me down here on your behalf. I am assuring you that this transaction and its procedures is 100% legal and risk free involvement. Your share stays while the rest will be for myself. The sharing of the fund between the two of us will be as follows: 20% of the tatal sum will go to you for your effort and commitment to the sucess of this transaction. 75% will be for us here. While 5% as been set aside for expenses incured in due process of this transaction As s! oon as I receive an acknowledge of the receipt of this message in Acce ptance, I will immediate! ly! start up with the process. If this proposal is acceptable by you, kindly get to me . I want you to also furnish me with your private telephone/fax or preferably your mobile numbers and I will have to apply for the release and subsequent Transfer of the fund in your favor. Thank you in advance for your anticipated cooperation. Yours faithfully, DR. FEMI JOHNSON (Credit Officer, First bank Of Nigeria PLC) Please upon your response include your private telephone and fax for further and oral communication. You can also reach me on my private number: +234-802-3504437

Please reply to savimbicar1@fizgigs.com Dear friend My proposal to you will be very surprising as we have not had any personal contact. However I sincerely seek your confidence in this transaction which I propose to you as a person of transparency and caliber Let me first start by introducing myself properly to you My name is Carlos Savimbi cousin and Personal Assistant of Jonas Malheiro Savimbi the leader UNITA (National Union for the Total independence of Angola) I got your email address from network directory I apologize if I infringed on your privacy. You may know that my Uncle was recently killed in a battle with the government troops of Angola led by President Dos Santos on friday 22nd February 2002 Now Mr Antonio Dembo who was my Uncle's second in command has assumed office as leader of UNITA In spite of this UNITA is like a herd of cattle without shepherd Prominent members like Carlos Morgado are still lobbying to oust him and assume office as leader to enrich themselves and some of them who see me as a threat to their ambitions including Mr Dembo are planning to kill me For more information check www.angola.org However I am a young man who has ambitions and I am not in any way interested in wars this is why I secretly left Angola I am sincerely seeking for your urgent help in respect to safekeeping of some of my Uncle's money that arose from Diamonds sales This money US$20 million was already on its way to my Uncle's Swiss Bank account It was on transit with a safe deposit company in Europe when the tragic incident of my Uncle's death occurred. As a matter of fact this is the reason I chose to come and seek political asylum. It is very clear with the way things are now that President Dos Santos will lobby the International Community to freeze my Uncle's assets and accounts abroad to ground UNITA since he has already done this in Angola. I plan to use this money to safeguard my future It is very essential that you understand that the kind of trust and confidence I want to put in you is extraordinary and an act of desperation on my part in order not to lose this money Please treat this contact with utmost secrecy and confidentiality for security and safety reasons. The help I need from you is clearing the box containing the money from the security company after which it will be deposited in an account in your name . The money shall remain in your custody till my asylum application is granted and I have the permit to conduct business then you will transfer the account to me Meanwhile the money can be invested into risk-free profitable ventures and there will an agreement to protect my interest. I have all the documents that will enable you claim the consignment from the security company. To make this deal relisable i need a committment from you that it will be kept confidential,your tel nd fax numbers including mobile for easy communications,your permanent address as well as some form of identification. For your reliable assistance I will reward you with 20% of the money and we shall use 5% to carry out every expenses that we incurr during the transaction and the investment process. 75%shall be for my family. I thank you in advance in anticipation for your assistance in enabling me achieve this goal. Please contact me whether or not you are interested in assisting me. This will enable me scout for another partner in the event of non-interest on your part. Please reply to savimbicar1@fizgigs.com NOTE YOUR PROMPT RESPONSE WILL BE APPRECIATED. Sincerely, CARLOS SAVIMBI. --------- This email has been sent by http://www.dogmail.co.uk. The superior free email service for dog lovers

FROM:CHIEF.(DR.)BODE GEORGE ADEMOLA ADETOKUNBO STREET VICTORIA ISLAND LAGOS-NIGERIA Dear Sir, RE: BUSINESS PROPOSAL - STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL. I am CHIEF(DR.)BODE GEORGE., Chairman to the Contract Review Panel that was recently inaugurated by the President of the Federal Republic of Nigeria to review the activities of past military government with particular reference to contracts awarded by all ministries between 1990 to 1999. In the course of carrying out our assigned duties, we discovered the sum of USD40.5 (forty million, five hundred thousand dollars) only lying idle in a suspense account with our apex bank. This funds emanated from grossly over-invoiced contracts awarded to conglomerate of foreign firms by the Petroleum Ministry on behalf of the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation. On completion of our assignment, this amount was deliberately not included in our report because we want to capitalize on this once in a lifetime opportunity to benefit and make a fortune out of it. The only option we have to achieve our aims and objective is to have this fund transferred to a count ry of our choice where it can be kept in trust and safe custody for us. We are however handicapped at the moment by our status as civil servants, which barred us from operating foreign accounts while still in government service. Thus, through some discreet inquiries from our Chambers of Commerce, you and your organization were revealed as being quite astute in private entrepreneurship. On this premise, we have no doubt in your ability to handle a business of this nature, which informed our desire and wish to enter into a partnership with you. This business involves the remittance of this amount into your bank account with the hope of travelling down to meet you physically in order to receive our share. We hope to invest some in profitable ventures in your country based on your advise while the balance will be repatriated home as foreign earnings. We have mapped out strategies and all paperwork is in place to ensure a 100% success. The nature of your business at present does not really matter because in the world over, bigger firms do bid for big contracts especially in third world countries like ours and can subcontract part of it to other firms for execution. That is you or your firm will be regarded as one of those that executed one of such projects and therefore entitled to receive the over-invoiced amount of the contract value since the original contractor has been paid. Be rest assured that this transaction is 100% risk free as there is actually no risk is involved either now or in the future for we are well connected in official circle. Given our level of commitment at the moment, we want to assure you that with full dedication on your part, the objective of having this fund remitted would have been realized within a period of two weeks. It is hereby expressly agreed in principle that at the end of the transaction, you will be entitled to 25% of the entire sum, 75% will be for m y colleagues and I. If you are interested in this proposal, please call or send me an e-mail VIA:bodegeorge@phantomemail.com for more clarifications. If however you are not interested, still let me know to enable me search for someone else to carry out this business with. I anticipate a timely response from you. Thanks. Yours Sincerely, CHIEF(DR.)BODE GEORGE

Dear Sir, I am Mr Steve Ibeto, the personal accounting officer to Mr Williams Hales, a national of your country, who used to work with shell development company in Nigeria. Here in after shall be referred to as my client. On the 21st of April 1999, my client, his wife And their three children were involved in a car accident along sagbama express road. All occupants of the vehicle unfortunately lost there lives. Since then I have made several enquiries to your embassy to locate any of my clients extended relatives this has also proved unsuccessful. After these several unsuccessful attempts, I decided to trace any of his relation but to all avail.After investigation,i discovered that his next of kin dead along with him during the accident Hence i have contacted you to act as his next of kin to assist in repartrating the money and property left behind by my client before they get confisicated or declared unserviceable by the bank where this huge deposits were lodged. Particularly,the Zenith International bank plc where the deceased had an account valued at about 5.5million dollars has issued me a notice as his accounting officer to provide the next of kin or have the account confisicated within the next ten official working days. since i have been unsuccesfull in locating the relatives for over 2 years now i seek your consent to present you as the next of kin of the deceased since you have the same surname so that the proceeds of this account valued at 5.5million dollars can be paid to you and then you and me can share the money. I have all necessary legal documents that can be used to back up any claim we may make. All I require is your honest cooperation to enable us see this deal through. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. Thanks and God Bless Best Regards. Mr Steve Ibeto. ___________________________________________________________ Kukamail.com - Free Email for the World! Open your account here: http://www.kukamail.com ___________________________________________________________ SPONSOR MESSAGE: Get Email @YOURFAMILY, @YOURBUSINESS, or @YOURDOMAIN Visit: http://www.entergroup.com today!

STRICTLY PRIVATE & CONFIDENTIAL ENGR.ALI RAZAK. Pretoria, South Africa. Dear Sir/madam, It is my great pleasure to write you this letter on behalf of my colleagues. Your information were given to me by a member of the South African Export Promotion Council (SAEPC) who was with the Black Economic Empowerment Commission (Government) delegation on a trip to the United States during a bilateral conference talk to encourage foreign investors. I have decided to seek a confidential co-operation with you in execution of a deal hereunder for the benefit of all parties, and hope you will keep it confidential because of the nature of this business. Within the Department of Mining Resources where I work as the Director of Project Implementation, with co-operation of two other top officials, we have in our possession, an overdue payment in US funds. The said funds represent certain percentage of the contract value executed on behalf of my Ministry by a foreign contracting firm, which we the officials over-invoiced to the amount of US$26,400,000.00 (Twenty Six Million Four Hundred Thousand United States Dollars). Though the actual contract cost has been paid to the original contractor, leaving the excess balance unclaimed. The Government of the Republic of South Africa believe that private investment in general, and foreign direct investment in particular, are the real engines for sustainable economic development, for which reason it has continued to encouraged investment in the key growth-oriented sector of Mining with sincere determination to pay foreign contractors all debts owed to them, so as to continue to enjoy close relationship, and mutually beneficial co-operation with foreign governments and non-governmental financial agencies. As a result we included our bills for approvals with the co-operation of some officials at the Department of Finance and the Reserve Bank of South Africa (RBSA). We are seeking your assistance to be the beneficiary of the unclaimed funds, since we are not allowed to operate foreign account. The changing of beneficiary's information/ details and other forms of documentation upon application for claim to reflect the contract money and its approvals will be secured on behalf of your company or your self. I have the authority of my colleagues involved to propose that, should you be willing to assist us in this transaction your share as compensation will be 20% while my colleagues and I shall receive 70%, and the balance of 10% shall be used to reimburse all expenditures, taxes and miscellaneous expenses so incurred. It does not matter whether or not your company does contract projects of the nature described here. The assumption is that your company won the major contract and subcontracted it to other companies. More often than not, big trading companies and firms of unrelated fields win major contracts, and subcontract to more specialized firms for execution. This business itself is 100% safe, provided you treat it with utmost confidentiality. Also your specialization is not a hindrance to the successful execution of this mutual beneficiary transaction. I have reposed my confidence in you and hope that you will not disappoint us. Kindly notify me for further details, upon your acceptance of this proposal. Regards, Engr. Ali Razak

STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL & URGENT. TEL: 871 - 762535915 FAX: 871 - 762535916 TEL: 27 - 835948129 Alternative: E-mail address:erickerick39@latinmail.com Dear Sir, I am Mr.Tambo, a native of Cape Town in South Africa and I am an Executive Accountant with the South Africa Department of Mining & Natural Resources. First and foremost, I apologized using this medium to reach you for a transaction/business of this magnitude, but this is due to Confidentiality and prompt access reposed on this medium. Be informed that a member of the South Africa Export Promotion Council (SEPC) who was at the Government delegation to your country during a trade exhibition gave your enviable credentials/particulars to me. I have decided to seek a confidential co-operation with you in the execution of the deal described hereunder for the benefit of all parties and hope you will keep it as a top secret because of the nature of this transaction. Within the Department of Mining & Natural Resources where I work as an Executive Accountant and with the cooperation of four other top officials, we have in our possession as overdue payment bills totaling Twenty - Six Million, Five Hundred Thousand U. S. Dollars ($26,500,000.) which we want to transfer abroad with the assistance and cooperation of a foreign company/individual to receive the said fund on our behalf or a reliable foreign non-company account to receive such funds. More so, we are handicapped in the circumstances, as the South Africa Civil Service Code of Conduct does not allow us to operate offshore account hence your importance in the whole transaction. This amount $26.5m represents the balance of the total contract value executed on behalf of my Department by a foreign contracting firm, which we the officials over-invoiced deliberately. Though the actual contract cost have been paid to the original contractor, leaving the balance in the tune of the said amount which we have in principles gotten approval to remit by Telegraphic Transfer (T.T) to any foreign bank account you will provide by filing in an application through the Justice Ministry here in South Africa for the transfer of rights and privileges of the former contractor to you, hence provide me with your private/direct fax number for the form to be send across to you. I have the authority of my partners involved to propose that should you be willing to assist us in the transaction, your share of the sum will be 25% of the $26,.5 million, 70% for us and 5% for taxation and miscellaneous expenses. The business itself is 100% safe, on your part provided you treat it with utmost secrecy and confidentiality. Also your area of specialization is not a hindrance to the successful execution of this transaction. I have reposed my confidence in you and hope that you will not disappoint me. Endeavor to contact me immediately through my above Tel/Fax number or my e-mail address, whether or not you are interested in this deal. If you are not, it will enable me scout for another foreign partner to carry out this deal I want to assure you that my partners and myself are in a position to make the payment of this claim possible provided you can give us a very strong Assurance and guarantee that our share will be secured and please remember to treat this matter as very confidential matter, because we will not comprehend with any form of exposure as we are still in active Government Service and remember once again that time is of the essence in this business. I wait in anticipation of your fullest co-operation. Yours faithfully, Mr. Tambo

From:Mr.Wilson Ajala Lagos-Nigeria. Tel: 234-80-34069502 Attn:President/Ceo. First, I must solicit your confidence in this transaction. This is by virtue of its nature as being utterly confidential and top secret. I got your contact in my private search for a reliable person to handle this transaction. We shall base this transaction on mutual respect and honesty. Hence,it is neccessary for you to assure us of your ability to prosecute this transaction of great magnitude,your ability and reliability to prosecute a transaction of great magnitude involving a pending business transaction requiring maximum confidence. We are top officials of the Federal Government Contract Review Panel who are interested in importation of goods into our country with funds which are presently trapped in Nigeria. In order to commence this business we solicit your assistance to enable us transfer into your account the said trapped funds. The source of this fund is as follows: During the past Military Regimes here in Nigeria, the government officials set up companies and awarded themselves contract which were grossly over-invoiced in various Ministries. As a result the Government of Chief Olusegun Obasanjo deemed it neccessary to set up a Contract Review Panel to investigate and recommend accordingly. After a thorough investigation, we discovered a lot of inflated contract funds which are presently floating in the Central Bank of Nigeria.. We (members) have unanimously agreed to transfer part of these funds to a foreign account However, by virtue of our position as civil servants and members of this Panel, we cannot acquire this money in our names. I have therefore, been delegated as a matter of trust by my colleagues in the Panel to look for an Overseas partner into whose account we would transfer the sum of US$21,500,000.00 (Twenty One Million, Five Hundred Thousand US. Dollars). Adequate logistics and strategies had been worked out to ensure a successful transfer with your maximum co-operation. Hence we are writing you this letter. We have agreed to share the money thus: 1. 25% for the account owner (you) 2. 70% for us (the officials) 3. 5% to be used in settling taxation and all local and foreign expenses. It is from this 70% that we wish to commence the importation business, please note that this transaction is 100% safe and we hope to commence and conclude the transfer latest in ten (10) banking days from the date of receipt a reply from you indicating your willingness to assist. The above information will enable us write letters of claim and job description respectively. Moreso, we will use your name or company's name to apply for payments and re-award the contract in your name or company's name. We are looking forward to doing business with you and solicit your confidentiality in this transaction. Please acknowledge the receipt of this letter using the this mail box . I will bring you into the complete picture of this lucrative project when I have heard from you. Yours Faithfully, Sincerely yours, Regards, Wilson Ajala.

Investment proposal from: Dr.Kunle Owolo. Tel:234-8042136866 Fax:234- 1-7597626 Block 4 Federal Secretariat Road, Ikoyi-Lagos REQUEST FOR ASSISTANCE STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL I am Dr.Kunle Owolo, the chairman of contract award and review committee set up by the federal government of Nigeria under the present civilian dispensation to award new contracts and review existing ones. I came to know of you in my search for a reliable and reputable person to handle a very confidential transaction, which involves the transfer of a huge sum of money to a foreign account. There were series of contracts executed by a consortium of multi-nationals in the oil industry in favor of the Nigerian National Petroleum Cooperation (N.N.P.C.) the original value of these contracts were deliberately over invoiced to the sum of USD$25,000,000.00 (twenty five million united state Dollars). This amount has been approved and is now ready to be transferred being that the companies that actually executed these contracts have been fully paid and the projects officially commissioned. Consequently, my colleagues and I are willing to transfer the total amount to your account for subsequent disbursement, since we as civil servants are prohibited by the code of conduct bureau (civil Service law) from operating and/or opening foreign accounts in our names. Needless to say, the trust reposed on you at this juncture is enormous, in return, we have agreed to offer you 20% of the transferred sum, while 10% shall be set aside for Incidental expenses (internal and external) between both parties in the course of the transaction you will be mandated to remit the balance to other accounts in due course. Modalities have been worked out at the highest level of the ministry of finance and the central bank of Nigeria for the immediate transfer of the funds within 14 working days subject to your satisfaction of the above stated terms. our assurance is that your role is Risk free and to accord this transaction the legality It deserves and for mutual security of the funds the whole approval procedures will be officially and legally processed with your name or the name of any company you may nominate as the bona- fide beneficiary. Once more I want you to understand that having put in over twenty five years in the civil service of my country, I am averse to having my image and career dented. This matter should therefore be treated with utmost secrecy and urgency it deserves. Please you should signify your intention to assist by sending me a fax on my confidential fax number ( 234 17 597626) or mail to private email address,so that I can brief you further. I want to assure you that this business proposal is 100% risk free as we have done our homework properly. I quite believe that you will protect our interest by taking this deal strictly confidential, as we are still in government service, which we intend to retire from. Kindly expedite action as we are behind schedule to enable us include this transfer in the first batch which would constitute the second quarter payments for the 2003 financial year. Thanks and God bless, Dr.Kunle Owolo.

Dear Sir/madam This business proposal to you is strictly confidential, with due respect.Sorry at this perceived confusion or stress you may have receiving this letter from me, Since we have not known our selves or met previously.Despite that, I am constrained to write you this letter because of the urgency of it.By way of self introduction, I am Mrs. jennifer kobe, the wife of late Brigadier - Gen.Maxwell Kobe former ECOMOG ARMY COMMANDER [West African peacekeeping force in Sierra Leone] who died in the Sierra Leone civil disturbance[War]. My three daughters and I are trapped in obnoxious custom and traditional norms. We have suffered maltreatment and untold hardship in the hands of my late husband's family, simply because I did not bear a male child [heir apparent] for my late husband. By tradition, all that my late husband had, [wealth] belongs to his brothers/family. And myself is to be remarried by his immediate younger brother which I vehemently refused. They have taken all that I suffered with my husband to acquire including treasures, houses and his bank particular seized by them. I wanted to escape to the United State of America [USA} with my children on exile, but again they conspired and stole my international passport and other traveling document to further frustrate me. Thank God, two weeks ago, I received Key Text Code from a Security Company abroad, that my late husband deposited U.S$15.5 Million cash with this company. It has therefore, become very necessary and urgent to contact someone, a foreigner like you to help me receive/secure these funds overseas in a reliable bank Account(presumably an empty Bank Account, if vailable) and to help invest it on our behalf as well, while we find a way of getting out to meet with you in your country. These funds are kept on an "OPEN BENEFICIARY MANDATE"with the Security Company to avoid detection, seizure or diversion. I have had several telephone discussions with the Assistant Director of the security company,who has express willingness to help me on meeting the company's demands. This is why I have contacted you to help save my children and I, receive these funds on our behalf. But, you would need to give me sufficient assurance that if you help me, you would not divert the funds. My children and I have resolved to give you 20% of the total sum. This is all my children and I have got to live on. I wish to state here that we are left with nothing as we survive by the grace of God. I hope you understand our predicament so as to save me and my family from hopeless future (S.O.S.) We want to believe that you will not withhold the money when finally paid into your account. I want you to understand that there is no risk involved as we have perfected all modalities for the smooth actualization of this transaction. The boxes,is presently in a security vault of the said security company at their offshore office. You are hereby,expected to forward the following: 1] Your international passport details or driving license to assure us about your person. I will send the following: (1) The receipt of the shipment Airway Bill for the consignment and the password being the security code will be forwarded to you as soon as you indicate you sincere interest to fully assist us. (2) The deposit certificate (3)The Diplomatic shipment certificate. All these will be sent to you as they will be required from you by the security company at the point of retrieving the consignment from their offshore office us all. The secret codes (e.g Pin No., Secret Access Code)for this fund are safely kept with me which I can give you as soon as you express desire to help me. NB: Because of the security being mounted on the members of my family, l have decided That this transaction be kept in utmost secrecy and as such all phone contacts should be through my lawyer Please, I have reposed my confidence in you and hope you will not disappoint me. I look forward to your urgent response, including your private phone / mobile No and also your fax no for easier communication. Stay blessed. mrs. jennifer kobe MY PERSONAL CONTACTS please you can reply through this email address for security reasons.(jenniferkobe@bored.com)

FROM: DR THOMAS AUDU No. 300 BOL AHMED WAY LAGOS-NIGERIA. STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL ATTN: THE PRESIDENT / C.E.O I am the Chief Medical Doctor and close confidant of Mrs. Maryam Abacha, the former first lady and wife of the late Gen.Sani Abacha, the former head of state and commander in chief of the armed forces of the Federal Republic of Nigeria. She (MRS. M.ABACHA), has as a result of the trust and confidence,she has in me mandated that I search for a reliable and trust worthy foreign partner, who will help receive some funds which she had in cash totaling US$80M (Eighty Million United States Dollars only) into a personal, company or any reliable foreign bank accounts within or outside your country as all their personal and family Bank accounts within and outside Nigeria have all been frozen by the Nigerian authorities. For further information about this money and the ABACHAS) go to http://www.econdad.org/AbachaLoot.htm This money in question has however, been Deposited with a security company that has branches in Africa, Europe and various parts of America. It may also interest you to note that she (MRS. ABACHA) and her family have, since the inception of the present democratic government, been placed under partial house arrest, with their international travelling passports seized pending when the current fund recovery face off between them and the present (RTD) GEN, OBASANJO led Democratic Government is resolved, in which from all indication will not exceed this year. She has decided to offer anybody who will be willing to render this tremendous assistance, 40% of the total sum. Note that this transaction involves no risks whatsoever, as you will have no dealing with my country, Nigeria. Rather you will deal directly with the Security Company, which is based where the money is right now. Let me have your confidential Tel/Fax numbers in your response to this proposal. I shall let you into a complete detailed picture of this mutual beneficial transaction when I have received your anticipated positive reply. Reply to this e-mail address: thomasaudu@k.ro . This matter should be treated as urgent and confidential. Regards, DR THOMAS AUDU

{URGENT AND CONFIDENTIAL} (RE: TRANSFER OF ($30,000.000.00 USD} Dear We want to transfer to overseas ($30,000.000.00 USD) Thirty million United States Dollars)from a Bank in Africa,I want to ask you toquietly look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable and fit to provide either an existing bank account or to set up a new Bank a/c immediately to receive this money,even an empty a/c can serve to receive this money, as long as you will remain honest to me till the end for this important business trusting in you and believing in God that you will never let me down either now or in future. I am Mr. Kalu Idika Kalu,the Auditor General of a bank in Africa,during the course of our auditing I discovered a floating fund in an account opened in the bank in 1990 and since 1993 nobody has operated on this account again,after going through some old files in the records I discovered that the owner of the account died without a [heir] hence the money is floating and if I do not remit this money out urgently it will be forfeited for nothing.the owner of this account is Mr. Vijay Kumar,a foreigner,and a sailor,and he died,since 1993.and no other person knows about this account or any thing concerning it,the account has no other beneficiary and my investigation proved to me as well that Mr. Vijay Kumar, investigation revealed that is an Indian working with Halibuton an oil firm in Nigeria. We will start the first transfer with $15m upon successful transaction without any disappoint from your side,we shall re-apply for the payment of the remaining rest amount to your account, The amount involved is ($30,000.000.00 USD) Thirty million United States Dollars), only I want to first transfer $15,000.000 [Fifteen million United States Dollar from this money into a safe foreigners account abroad before the rest,but I don't know any foreigner,I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money can not be approved to a local person here,without valid international foreign passport,but can only be approved to any foreigner with valid international passport or drivers license and foreign a/c because the money is in us dollars and the former owner of the a/c Mr. Vijay Kumar is a foreigner too,and the money can only be approved into a foreign a/c. However, we will sign a binding agreement,to bind us together I got your contact address from the Girl who operates computer, I am revealing this to you with believe in God that you will never let me down in this business,you are the first and the only person that I am contacting for this business,so please reply urgently so that I will inform you the next step to take urgently.Send also your private telephone and fax number including the full details of the account to be used for the deposit. I want us to meet face to face to build confidence and to sign a binding agreement that will bind us together before transferring the money to any account of your choice where the fund will be safe. Before we fly to your country for withdrawal,sharing and investments. I need your full co-operation to make this work fine. because the management is ready to approve this payment to any foreigner who has correct information of this account,which I will give to you,upon your positive response and once I am convinced that you are capable and will meet up with instruction of a key bank official who is deeply involved with me in this business. I need your strong assurance that you will never, never let me down. With my influence and the position of the bank official we can transfer this money to any foreigner's reliable account which you can provide with assurance that this money will be intact pending our physical arrival in your country for sharing.The bank official will destroy all documents of transaction immediately we receive this money leaving no trace to any place and to build confidence you can come immediately to discuss with me face to face after which I will make this remittance in your presence and three of us will fly to your country at least two days ahead of the money going into the account. I will apply for annual leave to get visa immediately I hear from you that you are ready to act and receive this fund in your account.I will use my position and influence to obtain all legal approvals for onward transfer of this money to your account with appropriate clearance from the relevant ministries and foreign exchange departments. At the conclusion of this business, you will be given 25% of the total amount,70% will be for me,while 5% will be for expenses both parties might have incurred during the process of transferring. I look forward to your earliest reply through my email BOX or my alternative email:tbalewa@hotmail.com. Sincerely, Mr. Kalu Idika Kalu Please call me on my phone # 234-803-35525974immediately you recieve this mail for further details. ___________________________________________________ GO.com Mail Get Your Free, Private E-mail at http://mail.go.com

Engr.Makalele Johnson. Pretoria South Africa. FOR YOUR KIND ATTENTION. It is my great pleasure to write you this letter on behalf of my colleagues. I got your information from a personal search in the internet business index. I have decided to seek a confidential co-operationwith you in execution of a deal hereunder for the benefit of all parties, and hopeyou will keep it confidential because of the nature of this business. Within the Ministry of Energy and Mineral Resources where I work as a Director of Project Implementation, and with co-operation of four other top officials, we have in our possession, an overdue payment in US funds. The said funds represent certain percentage of the contract value executed on behalf of my Ministry by a foreign contracting firm, which we the officials over-invoiced to the amount of US$25,500,000.00 (Twenty-Five Million Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars). Though the actual contract cost has been paid to the original contractor, leaving the excess balance unclaimed. Since the present elected Government is determined to pay foreign contractors all debts owed, so as to maintain good relations with foreign governments and non-governmental financial agencies. As a result we included ours bills for approvals with the co-operation of some officials at the Department of Finance and the Reserve Bank of South Africa (RBSA). We are seeking your assistance as the beneficiary of the unclaimed funds, since we are not allowed to operate a foreign account. I have the authority of my colleagues involved to propose that, should you be willing to assist us in this transaction your share as compensation will be 25% while my colleagues and I receive 70%, and the balance of 5% for taxes and miscellaneous expenses incurred. It does not matter whether or not your company does contract projects of the nature described here. The assumption is that your company won the major contract and subcontracted it to other companies. More often than not, big trading companies and firms of unrelated fields wins major contracts and subcontract to more specialized firms for execution. I have reposed my confidence in you and hope that you will not disappoint me. Endeavor to contact me immediately through my e-mail address above,to indicate whether or not you are interested in this deal. If you are not, it will enable me scout for another foreign partner to carry out this deal.I want to assure you that my partners and myself are in a position to make the payment of this claim possible provided you can give us a very strong assurance and guarantee that our share will be secured.It is important that you treat this matter with utmost confidentiality as any form of exposure will negatively affect us since we are still in active Government Service. Also your area of specialization is not a hindrance to the successful execution of this transaction.I have reposed my confidence in you and hope that you will not disappoint us. Kindly notify me for further details, upon your acceptance of this proposal. Regards, Engr.Makalele Johnson ================================================== Single? Not for long. Find your dream lover at http://www.wheresinglesmeet.com/default.asp?ref=2000

Dr George Ineh 10 Broad Street Road Ikoyi, Lagos. Tel : 234 17767344 American Internet Fax: 1775-307-0634 REQUEST FOR ASSISTANCE. Grace, Peace And Love From This Part Of Atlantic To You I must sincerely solicit your strictest confidence in this transaction, this is by virtue of it's nature as being utterly confidential and top secret. What I am about to divulge to you in this mail is top secret and if it offends or does not meet with your business ethics, I crave your indulgence. I am George Ineh a member of a special committee set up by the present civilian Government of Nigeria. We are saddled with the task of auditing the Accounts of government parastatals and ministries for the last ten years. In the course of our work at the committee, we discovered this fund which resulted from gross re-valuation of contracts by top government officials of the last Administration. The companies that executed the Contracts have been duly paid and the contracts Commissioned leaving the sum of US$15.6 Million floating in the escrow account of the Central Bank of Nigeria ready for payment. I have therefore been mandated as a matter of trust by my colleagues in the committee to look for an overseas partner to whom we could transfer the sum of US$15.6M Legally subcontracting the entitlement to you/your company. This is bearing in mind that our civil service code of conduct forbids us from owning foreign company or running foreign account while in government service hence the need for an overseas partner. We have agreed that the funds will be shared after it has been paid into your nominated account based on each parties negotiation upon your acceptance and willingness to assist us in this transaction. We have also agreed that our own share of the fund will be used for importation business in conjunction with you as we can not bring back cash to Nigeria. All logistics are in place and all modalities worked out for the smooth conclusion of the transaction within ten to fourteen days of commencement after receipt of the following information: Your full name/ company name, address, company's details & activities, telephone & fax numbers. These information will enable us make the applications and lodge claims to the concerned ministries & agencies in favor of your company and it is pertinent to state here that this transaction is entirely based on trust as the solar bank draft or certified cheque drawable in any of the Central Bank of Nigeria correspondent bankers in America, Asia and Europe is going to be made in your name. In order to move forward quickly, please respond to me by Tel:234 17767344, American Internet Fax:1775-307-0634 (This number was acquired for confidentiality) so I can bring you into the complete picture of this pending project and provide more information as to the successful conclusion of this project. The best response, however, would be by telephone, so we can discuss fully all issues needed to complete this venture in good time, and successfully. I await your prompt and positive response to this business proposal thank you and God bless. Yours Faithfully, DR George Ineh.

ATTN: URGENT ASSISTANCE NEEDED You may be surprise to receive this Email from me since you do not know me personally. However, I would like to introduce myself. I am Michael Stevens Junior, the son of Doctor. Simon Stevens. Who was murdered few months ago in Zimbabwe, as a result of land dispute? Before the death of my father (Dr. Stevens), he had taken me to Amsterdam and deposit the sum of Fifteen Million United States dollars (US$15,000,000) in a security company, as he foresaw the looming danger in Zimbabwe. The money in question was deposited in a box as Gemstones to avoid much demurrage from the security company. The proposed amount was meant for the purchase of new machines and chemicals for the farms and establishment of new farms on Swaziland. As you may be aware this land problem came into force when Zimbabwe president Mr. Robert Mugabe Introduced the Land Reformed Act of which my father rich farmers and some black farmers where affected. This resulted to the killing and Mob action by Zimbabwe war veterans and some lunatics in the society, a lot of people were killed because of this Land reformed act of which my dad was one of the victims. It is against this background that my family and Iaugustim who are currently staying in Amsterdam decided to transfer my father's money to a foreign account. Since the Dutch law prohibit a refugee (asylum seeker) to open any account or be involved in any financial transaction. As The eldest son of my father, I am saddled with the responsibility of seeking a genuine foreign account where the money could be transferred. I am faced with the dilemma of investing this amount of money in Holland for the fear of going through the same experience in future since both countries have similar history. Moreover, The Netherlands foreign exchange policy does not allow such investment from asylum seekers. I humbly solicit for your assistance in the following: 1) Pay a short working day visit to Amsterdam the Netherlands so that we see face to face, Have a table talk that would create confidence in me that the funds will be safe in your hands and have an agreement from an advocate, which will be duly and legally sign in his chambers before taken any step in this transaction. 2) Get the entire necessary document regarding this transaction and claim the boxes from the security company, open an account in your name with a local bank here and deposit the money for onward transfer to your designated account in overseas. 3) Make a good arrangement for investment and do invest the money for me, I am willing to give you some percentage for your assistance on this, and I offer you 15%. 5% for any expenses, including your telephone calls and any other expenses that may arise during this process. 80% would be invested and you get your wages monthly for managing the funds. Contact me on the above Email, provide me with your telephone and fax number so we can discuss further and a chance for you to ask me any question you may have in mind, while you maintain the absolute secrecy required in the transaction. Please kindly get back to me with your detail contacts. Sincere Regards, Michael Stevens Junior.

Dear Partner, Following the sudden death of my husband General Sani Abacha the late former head of state of Nigeria in June 1998, I have been thrown into a state of utter confusion, frustration and hopelessness by the present civilian administration, I have been subjected to physical and psychological torture by the security agents in the country. My son is still under detention arraigned before the federal high court of Nigeria for an offernce he did not commit. As a widow that is so traumatized, I have lost confidence with anybody within the country.You must have heard over the media reports and the internet on the recovery of various huge sums of money deposited by my husband in different security firms abroad, some companies willingly give up their secrets and disclosed our money confidently lodged there and many outrightly blackmail us. In fact the total sum discovered by the Government so far is in the tune of US$700.Million dollars. And they are not relenting to make me poor for life. You may be surprise how I got to know but I will tell you when you reply. I repose great confidence in you hence my approach to you. due to security network placed on my day to day affairs I cannot afford to visit the embassy so that is why I decided to contact you and I hope you will not betray my confidence in you. I have deposited the sum of U.S 40.3 million dollars with a security firm abroad whose name is witheld for now until we open communication.I shall be grateful if you could receive this fund into your account for safe keeping. This arrangement is known to you and my son alone, my son will deal directly with you as security is up my whole being. The name of my son is Mustapha. I am seriously considering tore-marry if you desire as soon as this fund get into your account so that I can start all over again with you if you wish, but if don‘t want to marry me just help me in diverting this fund into your account which will accrue you 30% of this fund. Please honesty is the watch word in this transaction. Please forward your private your telephone and fax number so that we can commence communication immediately. In case you don‘t accept please don‘t let me out to the security. I will greatly appreciate if you accept my proposal in good faith.Please expedite action. Maryam A abacha

>From The Desk Of MR MR.ODIASE GEORGE ChairMan Contract Award Committe Federal Ministry of Aviation. Garki- Abuja-Nigeria Tel: 234-1-7761675 Fax: 234-1-7592687. Dear My nameis MR MR.ODIASE GEORGE.chairman of the contract award committe of the. Federal Ministry of Aviation. Sometime last year,the Federal Government of Nigeria decided to upgrade the Radar and Landing facilities at the Malam Aminu Kano International Airport,kano inNorthern Nigeria.The contract ran into several millions of Dollars. The contract was handled by a foreign firm but because of the huge monetary profit we envisaged we decided toover-invoice the contract sum. Now the contract has been completed and the original contractor has since been paid, but the contract balance of US$12.5 million, which resulted from the over invoiced contract sum that has been left in a suspense account with the CENTRAL BANK OF NIGERIA, is what me and my partners are planning to take out of the country for ourselves. The problem is as government officials, we are not supposed to own fat bank accounts, talk less of having foreign ones. To this end, we are soliciting your assistance as a foreign partner who can assist us and receive this amount into your account. We are ready to share this money with you on the basis of participation. We also have plans to invest part of this money in any viable business in your country under your care, as we are very close to retirement age. In any case, I received a reference of you on the net while looking for a potential and reliable partner. Please if you accept my proposal do not hesitate to send me an e-mail, so that I can provide you with the basic procedures for the release of the fund. It does not matter whether you or your company does contract project of the nature described here, the assumption is that you won a major contract and subcontracted it to another company, more often than not, big trading companies or individuals of unrelated field win major contracts here in Nigeria and subcontracts same to more specialized firms for execution. BENEFIT: For providing the account where we shall remit this money, you will be entitled to 15% of the entire funds, 80% will be for me and my partners, while 5% has been set aside to cover any expenses that may be incurred by both parties during this transaction, both local and international. Please I enjoin you to handle this transaction with utmost degree of maturity and confidentiality because I am still in active government service with the "FEDERAL MINISTRY OF AVIATION". If I receive your response on time, this whole transaction could be accomplished within the shortest possible time based on your interest and determination, since the money is already in transit. Please, try to reach me soon as there is no much time to waste on this . Yours faithfully, MR.ODIASE GEORGE

Dear Beloved in Christ, It is a priviledge to hear from God and it gives me joy to relate my testimony to you haven recieved instruction from God through divine revelation. I was a Moslem and a retired military top officer in Nigerian Army that served under the past military regime. I was the financial secretary to the Armed Force Ruling Council (AFRC). With my position as a financial secretary, I was able to divert up to $45,000,000.00 (Forty Five million U.S Dollars, into my personal Bank Account, hoping to invest the money when I'm retired. Immediately I got retired, I was converted from Moslem to Christian when I was preached the words of God through my cousin Pastor Paul Osakwe. I then gave my life to Christ and became a born again Christain. Since I gave my life to Christ, I had no rest of mind. Some times I think of the souls I killed when I was a soldier and the dubious ways I diverted my country's money into my Personal Bank Account.I then decided to seek the face of God for forgiveness and after fasting and prayer through Divine Revelation, the Almighty God revealed to me that the only way I could have rest of mind is when I used all my money to do the work of God. I immediately disclosed my revelation to my Pastor and he was happy with me. I have been thinking of the particular thing to do for my God before this present civilian president of my country set up a panel (Honourable Oputa Panel) to probe the Bank Account of the past Military officers like me. Instead of loosing this money to my government, I quickly withdrew my money out of my Account and deposited the money in a finance and security company for safety. My Pastor has adviced me to sneak out of the country with the money to sow it into a ministries abroad. I have decided to sow this money into your ministry. I am making arrangement to come over to your country but you need to receive this in cash before I come over. The cash has been packaged by the security company in consignments and ready for shipment but the security company requires the address of the money from the finance and security company receiver. Please send to me your names, address and your tele and fax number where I can fax the Airway Bill to enable you claim the consignment. I will be coming over to your ministry with my family for thanksgiving as soon as I sent out this money to you. I look forward to your response through my private yahoo account:zik_don@yahoo.co.uk God bless you. Deacon zik.

HOPKINS MBEKI & CO SOLICITORS & ADVOCATE SOUTH AFRICA OPERATIONS PRAVITE EMAIL:hopkinsmbek1@hknetmail.com Dear Sir, I am sure that this letter will come to you as a surprise, but i shall be grateful if you would read with the interest of assisting in the transaction tendered herein. My name is HOPKINS MBEKI, Attorney at law and legal advisor to MR JOHN NORMAN, I have an urgent and very confidential business proposition for you. an America Oil Consultant/Contractor with the Government of Benin-Republic, in 2001 MR JOHN NORMAN made a numbered times (Fixed) Deposited for twelve calendar month valued at US$25,800,030,00(twenty-five million eight-hundred and thirty dollars) in GUARANTEE OFFSHORE FINANCE in London upon maturity MR JOHN NORMAN. I sent a routine notification to his forward address but got a reply. that MR JOHN NORMAN died from an automobile accident, MR JOHN NORMAN did not declare any next of kin in his official document, including his bank deposit paperwork. This sum of us$25,800,030,00 is still sitting in GUARANTEE OFFSHORE FINANCE ESCROW ACCOUNT in London. Website:guaranteeoffshorefinance.com According to the laws of the country, at the end of expiration of 5 (FIVE) years, the money will revert to the ownership of Government if nobody applies to claim the funds. Consequently my proposal is that i will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to MR JOHN NORMAN. i want you to provide me with your name and address so I the (ATTORNEY) will prepare the necessary Document and Affidavits which will put you in place as the next of kin drafting notarization of the will and obtain the necessary document and letters of probate & administration in your favor for the transfer into an account you will provide which will facilitate the transfer of this fund the provide account as the beneficiary / next of kin. The money will be paid into your account for us to spare in the ratio of 60% for me 30% for you why 10% will be set aside for miscellaneous. Please reply immediately via the email address below. Upon your response, i shall then provide you with the necessary document that will enable you lay claim to the fund, all you need to do is to open an account with G.O.F for easy transfer of the funds this will save cause of transfer to your account and easy access, please observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because i shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Awaiting your urgent reply on my private email box :hopkinsmbek1@hknetmail.com Thank and Regards BARRISTER, HOPKINS MBEKI

Dear Sir, Before I introduce myself, I wish to inform you that this letter is not a hoax mail and I urge you to treat it serious. We want to transfer to overseas account ($35,000.000.00 USD) (Thirty Five Million United States Dollars) from a Standard Trust Bank Ltd here in Nigeria, I want to ask you, If you are not capable to quietly look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable and fit to provide either an existing bank account or to set up a new Bank a/c immediately to receive this money, even an empty a/c can serve to receive this money, as long as you will remain honest to me till the end for this important business trusting in you and elieving in God that you will never let me down either now or in future. I am Dr. Muhammad Khalil Hasan, the Auditor General of Standard Trust Bank Ltd here in Nigeria. During the course of our auditing, I discovered a floating fund in an account opened in the bank in 1996 and since 1998 nobody has operated on this account again,after going through some old files in the records I discovered that the owner of the account died without a [Heir/WILL] hence the money is floating and if I do not remit this money out urgently it will be forfeited for nothing. The owner of this account is Mr. Robert Chapman a Canadia and great industrialist. He was African Area Director of SIL International, who unfortunately died in the plane crash of Kenya Airways Flight 431 in Abidjan, Ivory Coast, January 30 2000. You will read more stories about the crash on visiting this website, news.airwise.com/airlines/archive/2 000/kenya2000.html and also in this website, www.sil.org/sil/news/2000/chapman.html where Chapman's company talked about his death in the Kenya crash. You shall as well find the pictures of Chapman and his wife there. No other person knows about this account or any thing concerning it, the account has no other beneficiary and my investigation proved to me as well that until his death he has a Gold/Diamond Consulting firm.I also found out that their only surviving daughter died last year. The total amount involve is ($35,000.000.00 USD) (Thirty Five Million United States Dollars) and we wish to transfer this money into a safe foreigners account abroad. But I don't know any foreigner, I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money can not be approved to a local person here, but to a foreigner who has information about the account, which I shall give to you upon your positive response. I am revealing this to you with believe in God that you will never let me down in this business, you are the first and the only person that I am contacting for this business, so please reply urgently so that I will inform you the next step to take urgently. I need your strong assurance that you will never let us down, me and a key bank official who is deeply involved with me in this business. I guarantee that this transaction will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. The bank official Will destroy all documents of transaction immediately we receive this money leaving no trace to any place. I will use my position and influence to obtain all legal approvals for onward transfer of this money to your account with appropriate clearance from the relevant ministries and foreign exchange departments. At the conclusion of this business, you will be given 40% of the total amount, 60% will be for us, I look forward to your earliest reply. PLEASE, TREAT THIS PROPOSAL AS TOP SECRET. Find in the attachment my Family Picture, to proof who I am. Best Regards Dr. Muhammad Khalil Hasan. __________________________________ Do you Yahoo!? Yahoo! SiteBuilder - Free, easy-to-use web site design software http://sitebuilder.yahoo.com

Dear Sir, I am contacting you in view of the fact that we will be of great assistance to each other likewise developing a cordial business relationship. As I am interested in your kind of business and wishing to invest in your country. I am Mrs. Maryam Abacha, wife to the late Nigerian military Head of State. General Sanni Abacha who died on the 8th of June 1998 still in office due to a protracted illness. I believe you must be aware of the recent face-off between my family and the present Civilian Government of President Olusegun Obasanjo who wants all my Late husbands foreign bank accounts and assets confiscated because of the monetary excesses of my la te husbands Military regime. Currently, within my reach is the sum of twenty-three Million seven Hundred thousand United States Dollars (US$ 23,700,000.00) cash, which I intend to use for investment purposes especially in your country. This huge sum of money came as result of a pay back contract deal between my late husband and a Russian firm on our country's Multi billion Dollar Ajaokuta Steel plant/complex. The Russian partners had since returned my husband's share of US$23.7Million after his death and lodged it with a security firm. Right now the new Civilian Government have revoked all our licenses that allows us to own financial and oil companies and has frozen some of my late husbands bank account in Switzerland and America. In view of these I acted very fast to withdraw this US$23.7M from the security company's vault well preserved and packaged in {1}trunk box and lodged in a private security firm OVERSEAS as Family Deposits (FD) No record ever existed concerning the money neither is the money traceable by the Government because there is no documents showing that we received the money from the Russians. However, due to the current situation in the country concerning the present civilian Government hostile attitude towards my family, it has become quite impossible for me to make use of the money within the country. Thus I seek your assistance in moving t his family Deposits (FD) into your account for safekeeping pending my arrival in your country for investment purposes. On your consent, I shall provide you with a POWER OF ATTORNEY to collect this deposit with the security company OVERSEAS on our behalf. Bearing in mind that your assistance is needed in this regards, I propose a commission of 20% (TWENTY PERCENT) of the total sum to you for the expected services and 10% for local and international expenses if any. Your urgent response is highly needed so as to start further contact . I therefore mandate Barrister GREG ADO who is our family Attorney to deal with you through out this transaction on my behalf. May I at this point, emphasize the high level of confidentiality which this business demands whatever your decision and hope you will not betray the trust and confidence which I repose in you. Please don't forget to indicate your convenient phone and fax number where we can always contact you. However, you may need to give me sufficient assurance that you will not sit on this fund when it is finally remitted into your account. Please direct your reply of this mail to my family attorney,GREG ADO at gregado@rxpost.net and discuss with him towards effective completion of this transaction. I believe I can trust you and I am willing to accept from you any useful and profitable investment proposal advice in your country. or reply me if my proposal interest you through my alternative email address: mcabacha@gawab.com s. Remain blessed. Best wishes, Mrs. Maryam Abacha. ---------------------------------------------------------------- Ce service de mailing vous est offert par http://www.freesurf.fr. FreeSurf, votre acces ADSL a partir de 29 euros/mois http://www.freesurf.fr/adsl/

PETROLEUM (SPECIAL) TRUST FUND LAGOS-NIGERIA. CONFIDENTIAL REQUEST FOR URGENT BUSINESS PROPOSAL >From the Desk of: Dr. Fahd A.Usman. Phone 234 80 33206813. Fax 234 1 7599055. Dear Sir, This letter may come to you as a surprise since it is coming from someone you have not met before. However, we decided to contact you based on a satisfactory information we had about you. I am a Medical Doctor currently working with the Petroleum Trust Fund (PTF). I and some of my close and trusted colleagues need your assistance in the transfer of US$21.8 million to overseas. This fund was generated from over-invoicing of contracts executed by the PTF under our control and supervision. This fund is now ready to be sent out by a special diplomatic courrier service.What we want from you include the following: 1. Name of Company & Address 2. Your Private Telephone & Fax Number 3. Beneficiary Name 4. Your international passport number Upon receipt of these informations, all arrangements asper movement of the funds which shall be by special diplomatic courrier services due to the amount involved shall commence.The company has banches in Dubai and Holland {Amsterdam} .The copies of the approval and other relevant documents shall be faxed to you for your perusal.please treat as strictly confidential for obvious reasons. The fund will be shared as follows: 1. 17% for your assistance 2. 80% for myself & my Colleagues 3. 3% for contingency expenses We wish to assure you that your involvement should you decide to assist us, will be well protected, and also, this business proposal is 100% risk free as the remittance will be made through the legal procedures. Note: your discussions regarding this transaction should be limited because we are still in government service. We intend to retire peacefully at the end of this transaction. Let honesty and trust be our watchword throughout this transaction and your prompt reply will be highly appreciated. Thank you for your anticipated cooperation while we look forward to a mutually benefiting business relationship with you. Best Regards. Dr. Fahd A.Usman.

Attn:My dear friend I am Dr Mike Odey, the Bank Manager of Diamond Bank of Nigeria, Lagos Branch. I have urgent and very confidential business proposition for you. On June 6, 1999, a FOREIGN Oil Consultant/Contractor with the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation, Mr. Barry Kelly made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at US$25,000,000.00(Twenty- five Million Dollars) in my branch. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation that Mr. Barry Kelly died from an automobile accident. On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL, and all attempts to trace his next of kin to date has fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr. Barry Kelly did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$25,000,000.00 is still sitting in my Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Nigerian Law, at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Nigerian Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as an Foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr. Barry Kelly so that the fruits of this old man’s labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full names, address, telephone and fax numers so that the Attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits, which will put you in place as the next of kin. We shall employ the service of another Attorney for drafting and notarization of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/administration in your favor for the transfer. A bank account in any part of the world, which you will provide, will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your nominated account for us to share in the ratio of 60% for me, 35% for you and 5% to cover any accidental expenses on either sides during the course of this transaction. There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the Attorney and my position as the Branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. Upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction better. Please observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Looking forward to hearing from you soonest. Best regards, Dr Mike Odey. PLAESE NOTE, SEND YOUR RESPONSES TO drmikeodey@rediffmail.com OR konkon@hknetmail.com & koso@hknetmail.com ------------------------------------------------- ___________________________________________________ Check-out GO.com GO get your free GO E-Mail account with expanded storage of 6 MB! http://mail.go.com

FROM THE DESK OF : DR AKIN DADA. DIRECTOR OF PROJECTS IMPLEMENTATION DEPT. FEDERAL MINISTRY OF WORKS AND HOUSING. INVESTMENT VENTURE I write to crave your indulgence for your assistance in the area of acquisition of estate in your country. I Dr. AKIN DADA the Director of contracts and my partner the Director of funds in the Federal Ministry of works and Housing in Nigeria, will prefer that this transaction be strictly confidential even after successful completion of this transaction as we will require you and your company to act as our oversea Agent for the Actualizations of this transaction. The funds to be used for the purchase of the estates and the proposals investment in your country is presently in a coded Bank Account owned by the Federal Ministry of Works And Housing in the Nigeria Apex Bank and we require your collaboration to transfer the funds to your Bank account in your country or any safe account where the funds would be received conveniently; this is to be provided by your humble self. You are to be considered to have executed a contract for the Federal Ministry of Works and Housing for a contract sum of USD15.5 Million which resulted from over invoicing from the original contractors who erected 392 Housing units for us in 1998 and their contract sum has long been settled remaining the outstanding over invoiced sum USD15.5 Million. We deliberately added amounting to $15.5m{USD}, if we agree to work together your share shall be 30% of the total contract sum we will have 60% and 10% will to be set aside by expenses incurred by both parties during the course of this transaction. Note that your area of common business is not an obstacle to this transaction but your willingness to a party of the business and also assist in the acquisition of estates in your country. As soon as payment is effected and your account is credited we will purchase the estates abroad an invest in your company. As soon you are advice with the information for the telegraphic transfer by the Apex Bank we shall be with you before the account be credited in your Bank to avoid any room for misappropriation of funds form any angle. And we will disburse the funds as soon as your account is credited together in your country. Note that we decided to carry out this transfer at this time because the formal Director Of Finance who has just be seconded to the Ministry of Art and Culture was aware of the existence of the fund and he has been a stumbling block . You are requested to communicate your assistance or otherwise of this proposal through my Email address by furnishing me with your Telephone and Fax numbers, after which we shall discuss the full modalities for seeing this transaction through. If however you are not dispose to assist, kindly destroy letter in view of the confidentiality of the proposed transaction and interest of personalities involved. Thanks for your anticipated co-operation. Best Rgards DR AKIN DADA.

Investment Proposal from: DR. GODWIN KALALA C/o Afri-Projects Consult Ltd., No. 53 Opebi Road, Ikeja, Lagos Nigeria. Fax:234-1-7598296. REQUEST FOR A MUTUALLY BENEFICIAL BUSINESS RELATIONSHIP:PERMISSION TO REMIT US$35MILLION INTO YOUR COMPANY OR PRIVATE ACCOUNT. With due respect, trust and humility, I write you this proposal believing that it will receive the most desired attention from you even as we have not had any previous correspondence before. Although I am constrained by insufficient information about you, but I will express in full the main objectives of this proposal. This request for your assistance is of mutual benefit to us all. Our company is specialized in contract syndication, projects consulting, monitoring/supervision and management services. We would like to solicit your kindness in assisting us to champion the transfer of some fund from our country to yours for safe keeping. The total amount of fund is US$35million (Thirty-five Million United States Dollars Only). SOURCE OF THIS FUND: We have used our network of relationships, to secure a contract valued at US$350,000,000.00 (THREE HUNDRED AND FIFTY MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS ONLY) from the Federal Ministry of Works & Housing (F.M.W.H.). This contract was in favour of a Foreign based Multi-national company. This contract has been fully executed and the contractors have already received their payments from the Ministry of Works & Housing. However, before the contract was awarded, we had understanding with officials of Federal Ministry of Works & Housing, that 10% (TEN PERCENT) of the total contract sum would be our commission for our services in recommending the contractors and for helping to conduct various negotiations leading to final agreement. This 10% amounting to US$35,000,00.00 (THIRTY-FIVE MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS ONLY) is due for payment to a foreign account of our choice. This amount is owned by our goodselves and some top officials of Federal Ministry of Works & Housing. Basically, you would be required to nominate a suitable Bank Account that will conveniently accommodate the total fund. Account could be a fresh or an already existing one, and could be individual or corporate account. All necessary arrangement have been made for the transfer of the funds into your account which they are awaiting for your above mentioned details to enable us make proper documentation of the payments in your favour and apply for the transfer of the funds into your account. PLEASE NOTE THAT THE TRANSFER OPERATION WILL TAKE SEVEN TO TEN WORKING DAYS TO BE COMPLETED. I would need your personal assurance that you would not sit on the money when its finally get into your account. SHARING MODALITIES: You shall be entitled to 25% of this fund for your envisaged efforts and assistance rendered. 5% has been set aside for reimbursement to both parties for incidental expenses that may be incurred in the course of this transaction. The remaining 70% would be for our company and the top officials. This proposal is strictly confidential, free from any form of risk and does not depend on any particular field of trade to prosecute. Therefore, the line of business of yourself/company is not a hindrance to the successful execution of this transaction. It however requires your adequate participation and support to enable its accomplishment on schedule. Be informed that on completion of this business our company will use part of its share of the money to invest in your country under your care. Please send email to me on my Private E-mail Address: gokalala5@tiscali.co.uk or you can send me a fax on my confidential fax number 234-1-7598296 so that we can commence the whole transaction. Thanks in anticipation and God bless. DR.GODWIN KALALA.

E-Mail, Address, hellenshakashaka@netscape.net Dear Friend You may be surprised to receive this letter from me since you do not know me personally. I am the first daughter of the most popular black farmer in Zimbabwe who was murdered in the land dispute in my country. I got your contact through network online hence i decided to write you. Before the death of my father, he took me to Johannesburg to deposit the sum of US$30 Million (thirty million United States dollars), in one of the security company, as he foresaw the looming danger in Zimbabwe. This money was deposited in a box as gem stones to avoid much demurrage from the Security Company. This amount was meant for the purchase of new machines and chemicals for the Farms and establishment of new farms in Swaziland. This land problem came when Zimbabwean President Mr. Robert Mugabe, introduced a new Land Act Reform wholly affecting the rich white farmers and some few black farmers, and this resulted to the killing and mob action by Zimbabwean war veterans and some lunatics in the society. In fact a lot of people were killed because of this Land reform Act for which my father was one of the victims. it is against this background that I and my family fled Zimbabwe to South Africa for fear of our lives. After which, I traveled to the Netherlands and I am currently staying in the Netherlands where i am seeking political asylum and more so have decided to transfer my father's money to a more reliable foreign account. Since the law of Europe prohibits a refugee (asylum seeker) to open any bank account or to be involved in any financial transaction throughout the territorial zone of European Union. As the eldest child of my father, I am saddled with the responsibility of seeking a genuine foreign account where this money could be transferred without the knowledge of my government who are bent on taking everything we have got. The South African government seems to be playing along with them. I am faced with the dilemma of moving this amount of money out of my family name for fear of going through difficulty in future. Both countries have similar political history. I am seeking for a partner who I have to entrust my future and that of my family in his hands, I must let you know that this transaction is risk free. If you accept to assist me and my family, all I want you to do for me, is to make arrangements with the security company to clear the Consignment (funds) from their affiliate office here in the Netherlands as i have already given directives for the consignment to be brought to the Netherlands from South Africa. But before then all modalities will have to be put in place like change of ownership to the consignment. I have two options for you. Firstly you can choose to have certain percentage of the money for nominating your account for this transaction. Or you can go into partnership with me for the proper profitable investment of the money in your country. Whichever the option you want, feel free to notify me. I have also mapped out 5% of this money for all kinds of expenses incurred in the process of this transaction. If you do not prefer a partnership I am willing to give you 20% of the money while the remaining 75% will be for my investment in any of the country of your choice. while I implore you to maintain the absolute secrecy required in this transaction. I await your immediate reply and God bless. Best regards, Hellen Shaka Zuma NOTE: ON YOUR INABILITY TO HANDLE THIS TRANSACTION RESPOND TO ME AND INFORM ME SO I CAN LOOK FOR SOMEONE ELSE.

(vinokoni5@hotmail.com) FROM:MRVINO.F.KONI TEL.+27-82-679-3775 FAX;+27-11-484-4082 NO 25 CLAIM STREET Johannesburg SOUTH AFRICA Dear SIR/MADAM, Peace and love of God be with You.I guess this letter may come to you as a surprise since i had no previous correspondence with you.Please excuse me the emberassment this letter might cause you and try to excesise a little patience in other to understand its content properly. I learnt that many Africans has used the advantage of what happened to us in my country to deceive some innocent souls and may be some has even used my fathers name because of his purpularity and greatness.But what we all need to understand in this world is that everybody will answer for him or herself on the last day. My name is Mr VINO.F.KONI and i am the only son of my parents. Myfather is Mr Johnson Koni and my mother is mrs Rose.s.Koni. I am a graduate of federal university of science and technology Harare,Zimbabwe and my discipline is Agricultural engineering.After my graduation,I decided to work for my father as his manager.My father has two big farms that are well known in Zimbabwe and has many workers that were working for him. I managed my fathers farms for two years before we had in my country.I got your contact through network online decided to write you to explain my situation and request for your assistance. This crises was as a result of a new land Act reform introduced by president Robert Mugabe which wholly affected most white farmers and few black farmers.This resulted in the killing and mob action by Zimbabwean war veterans and some lunatics in the society.Infact a lot of people were killed because of this land reform act of which my father was a victim. But before the death of my father, as if he knew he was going to die informed me about the money he deposited with a security and finance firm in South Africa.The total amount is twenty three million,two hundred thousand POUNDS (M23,200,000,POUNDS) and this money was deposited in a box as germ stones to avoid much demurrage from the Security and finance firm. This amount was meant for the purchase of new machines and chemicals for the farms and establishment of a new farm in Swaziland. One month after my father's death,I and my mother decided to travell to South Africa for our lives and decided to look for a trustworthy foreigner who will help us to transfer this money out of South Africa because we are staying as refugees here in South Africa and refugees are not alowed to open bank accounts or involved in any financial transaction in South Africa.I have all the documents concerning this money and what i am seeking for is a genuine foreign account where this money could be transferred into without the knowledge of my government who are bent on collecting everything that belongs to my father. All i am looking for is an honest business man or woman, whom I can entrust my future and that of my family . I must also let you know that this transaction is 100%risk free. If you accept to assist me and my family all I want from you is for you to make arrangements and come to Johannesburg South Africa, so that you can help me open a nonresident account in your name which will aid us in transferring the money into any account you will nominate overseas. If you are willing to help me,I have two options of compasaction for you,firstly you can choose to have certain percentage of the money for nominating your account for this transaction, Or you can go into partnership with me for the proper profitable investment of the money in your country. Which ever the option you chooses,feel free to notify me. I have also mapped out 5% of this money for all kinds of expenses we might incure in the process of this transaction. If you do not prefer a partnership I am willing to give you 25% of the money while the remaining 70% will remain for me and my family.If you are realy capable and willing to assist me please contact me immediately through my direct telephone number +27-82-679-3775 or this e-mail address with which i have sent you this message. Finally, please treat this matter as urgent as to save my family from much expences caused by demaurage being accumulating on daily bases for the money in the security company.Thanks for your mutual co-operation while i wait for your soonest response.Remain blessed. Yours Faithfuly, MR VINO.F.KONI (for and on behalf of my family) (vinokoni5@hotmail.com) _________________________________________________________________ Rain coat or t-shirt? Find out with MSN Weather http://www.msn.co.za/weather/

Good day to you compliment of the day I am using this opportunity to introduce my self to you I am Hilary Kamokai my contact with you today is concerning my family situation I need your assistance and reliability to be my trustee in other to help me to retrieve my late Father consignment.

I'm now confiding on you my families’ secret. I am the first Son of the LATE ENG.JOSEPH KAMOKAI WHO WAS THE MININTER OF MINES

AND DIAMOND OF THE REPUBLIC OF LIBERIANIN WEST AFRICA, before his suddenly death was occur by the Liberian rebels the west side boys, when he was traveling to Buaki with my younger Brother frank, there were attacked by rebels, where my Father driver and my younger Brother were shot to death on the spot and my Father had a bullet on his left shoulder before he was rescued by the United Nation Peace Keeping force immediately he was conveyed to COTE D'IVOIRE Specialist Hospital for medical treatment.

On his sick bed when he realized that his condition is beyond the treatment he called me and revealed to me concerning this consignment boxes which deposited in a security company in Accra Ghana. The boxes contain cash money wish I can not be able to state on Internet now till I know you better. He directed me to an attorney a lawyer in Ghana who is in position of the whole documents covering the consignment in the security firm to avoid any implication? Since the whole industries financial institutions including documents where burnt down on the crises in my Country Liberia.

Right now am in Refugee Camp with my family and We are here in Ghana before I came across your contact during the Meddle of the year party/seminal organized by the United Nations High Commission for Refugees (UNHCR), here in Accra I have now called on you to lecture me how best we can clear this boxes from the security company and transfer it to your country for onward utilization and investment, I am my Mother have worked out some percentage for you it you will of assistance to us.

This instruction was given to me by my late Father before his untimely death; He also said that I should make a good arrangement to move this FUND out of West Africa. I am waiting your urgent reply, with your private fax and telephone numbers so that I can send you all the legal documents Please there is no risk involved but you have to keep it top secret.

Yours sincerely

Hilary Kamokai

Add photos to your e-mail with MSN 8. Get 2 months FREE*.

Mr..John Chukwu Chartered Bank (CB). Lagos-Nigeria Attn: Sir/Madam. In order to transfer out Twenty Two Million United States Dollars from Chartered Bank (CB). I wish to ask for your assistance, believing that you will never let me down either now or in future. I got your e-mail address from the e-mail directory in the internet. I am Mr..John Chukwu, the Chief Auditor of Chartered Bank (CB). There was an account opened in this bank in 1983 and since 1989 nobody has operated on this account till date. After my long investigation to my greatest suprise I came to find out that the owner of the account who is Mr.Peter B. Andreas, a foreigner, crude oil exporter, who died in 1990. This account has no beneficiary, infact no other person knows about this account or anything about the account, and my investigation proved to me as well that this company does not exist anymore in NIgeria. The amount involved is USD 22M, which i seek your consent to transfer to a safe foreign account. I do not know any foreigner that i can trust either than you, I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money can not be claimed by a Nigerian because the rightful owner of the account (Mr. Peter) is a foreigner. I know that this mail will come to you as a surprise as we do not know each other before hand. we will be needed to sign an Agreement as a security so that we cannot betray the trust that will be given to eachother in this legitimate and joint venture, which demand utmost secrecy and confidential. I am contacting you because of the need to involve a foreigner with foreign account and foreign beneficiary. I need your full co-operation for us to have a successful transaction. Because the management is ready to approve this payment to any foreigner who has correct information of this account, which I will give to you immediately i receive your positive reply. With my position now in the office I can authorise the immediate transfer of this money to any foreign reliable account which you can provide with assurance that this money will be intact pending my physical arrival in your country for sharing and further investment. I will destroy all documents used in this transaction immediately we must have transferred this money to your nominated account sucessfully, so as to avoid any document trace by any person. I will apply for annual leave to get visa to your country immediately you confirm me that you are willing to assist me. I will also use my position and influence to effect legal approvals and onward transfer of this money to your account with appropriate clearance forms of the ministries and foreign exchange departments. At the conclusion of this business, you will be given 20% of the total amount, 75% will be for me, while 5% will be for expenses both parties might have incurred during the process of transferring. Awaiting your urgent reply through my private mail box (johnchukwu1@maktoob.com) and please do not FORGET TO INCLUDE YOUR PRIVATE FAX AND TELEPHONE NUMBERS FOR EASY COMMUNICATION. Thank you and God bless. Yours truly, MrJohn Chukwu

MINISTRRY OF MINES&POWER 3,MITAMAZ DRIVE ABUJA,NIGERIA. FROM THE DESK OF:DR BELLO BATURE. ATTN: I write to enquire of your personal or company profile and investment procedures, I am Dr Bello Bature and I work for the Ministry of Mines &Power in Nigeria, and by this letter, I am representing and also acting on behalf of my two senior colleagues (The Director General and the group General Manager) who have mandated that I got in contact a trusted and reliable foreign based businessman/woman concerning the business matter of mutual benefit toall.By thismandate given to me,we are in dire need of foreign partners to assist us in the transfer Investment of US$24,000,000.00(twenty four million united statesdollars). The key issue is the transfer and the subsequent Investment of the said sum. We are ready to go into anagreement with you and also offer you a negotiable fee for puttingtogether an Investmentportfolio. It does not matter whether or not you own a company or you have invested fundsbefore. We shall guide you on what to do. The basis will be that a major company won a contract andsubcontracted it toyou. More often, big trading companies and firm of unrelated field won contracts and subcontracts to more specialized firms for execution.We shall follows strictly all the legal procedures entailed the laws of our land and international laws in transferring the fund to you. The sources of the fund are legitimate and authoritative. Please be informed that Nigerian Government Monitory Policy, strategic positioned Government officials are not allowed to operate or own bank account overseas, hence,we are in need for a foreign partner to front for us.We pray that you take the essence of this letter in strict confidence, as the two offices involved would not like to be exposed on this. Kindly firstnotify me onyou wiliness to assist us through this email address Details will be made available to you as soon as you respond.You are to contact me only on this email address specifically for more information and you are to keep this business proposal very confidential for securityreason.Thank you and God bless as we wait for your urgent response. Yours faithfully, Dr.Bello Bature. TEL:23433704238. EMAIL:dr.bell_bat@portugalmail.com

From: Mrs Maryam Abacha Abacha Housing Estate Gidado Road, Kano-Nigeria (N/B) ***This message to you contains strictly confidential information which should be handled confidentially.As soon as you show intrest you can help all necessary documents shall be forwarded to you including all identities(My personal and family pictures)*** Asalam alekum, I salute you in the name of most High Allah. I am Mrs. Maryam Abacha, the widow of the late Gen. Sani Abacha former military Head of State who died mysteriously as a result of cardiac arrest. Since my husband's death, my family has been under restriction of movement and that notwithstanding, we are being molested and constantly under ?watch? by the seemingly agent, above all, our banks account here and abroad have been frozen by the Nigerian civilian government. Furthermore, my eldest son is in detention by the Nigerian Government for more interrogation about my husband's asset and some vital documents. Following the recent discovery of my husband's bank account by the Nigerian government with my son's bank in which a huge sum of US$700 million and 450 million Dutch Mark was lodged and 6 billion dollars belonging to my late husband was seized by the government of Nigeria. I therefore wish to personally appeal to you seriously and religiously for your urgent assistance to transfer the sum of $25.5 million United States Dollars into your account in your country which has already been lodged in a Global crossing Diplomatic ?security? in abroad by my Late Husband and I have a prove of the Certificate of Deposit with the telephone and fax number of the ?security? company in abroad, the name of the head of operation including the telephone and fax number of the agency whom help in packaging the consignment. since we can not leave the country due to the restriction of movement imposed on the members of my family by the Nigerian Government and my International pass port impounded at the Murtala Mohammed International Airport, Lagos in August 1998 and presently the consignment is incurring more demurrage and if the government discovered they might seize the fund (consignment) that was the reason I was advise by our Family lawyer for the safety of the fund, to look for an honest and reliable foreigner who is willing to be of assistant to enable the fund to be transfer to his account while you are entitled to 25% of the fund while 5% is for any expenses which might include your phone calls , stationary which must be deducted before sharing. Also, if you accept this proposal, I shall give you the telephone and fax number of the ?security? company in abroad where the consignment is lodge including agency for verification and you shall as well forward your data including your telephone and fax number to our Family Lawyer who shall help in the legal documentation to make you the legal owner of the fund by a prove of an affidavit from the Federal High Court for a change of fund ownership by me which my lawyer shall forward with an application to the Court to enable the court to issue an legal clearance certificate as a prove that the fund is no longer belong to ABACHA FAMILY but you as the new beneficiary which will now empowered the Security company to release the consignment (fund) to you. Please I will appreciate your quick response weather you accept this proposal or not to enable me to know the next step of action and please you can as well use your name or your company name as the beneficiary of the fund (consignment ) Yours Sincerely Mrs Maryam Abacha [***Striclty confidential***] Pour gagner une Playstation 2, envoyez un SMS avec le code PS au 61321 (0,35 euro hors coût du SMS).

Dear Sir, First, I must solicit your strictest confidence in this transaction.This is by virtue of its nature as being utterly confidential and 'top secret'. You have been recommended by an associate who assured me in confidence of your ability and reliability to prosecute a transaction of great magnitude involving a pending business transaction requiring maximum confidence. We are top officials of the Federal Government Contract Review Panel who are interested in importation of goods into our country with funds which are presently trapped in Nigeria. In order to commence this business we solicit your assistance to enable us transfer into your account the said trapped funds. The source of this fund is as follows: During the last Military Regime here in Nigeria, the Government officials set up companies and awarded themselves contracts which were grossly over- invoiced in various ministries. The present government set up a Contract Review Panel and we have identified a lot of inflated contract funds which are presently floating in the Central Bank Of Nigeria ready for payment. However, by virtue of our position as civil servants and members of this panel, we cannot acquire this money in our names.I have therefore, been delegated by my other colleagues in the panel tolook for an overseas partner into whose account we would transfer the sum of US $21,500,000.00 [Twenty-One Million, Five Hundred thousand U.S Dollars. Hence we are writing you this letter. We have agreed to share the money thus: 1. 20% for the account owner( you) 2. 70% for us [ Myself and other members of my panel ] 3. 10% to be used in settling taxation and all local and foreign expenses direct or incidental to the execution of this transaction. It is from the 70% that we wish to commence the importation business.Please, note that this transaction is 100% safe and we hope to commence the transfer latest Ten (10) banking days from the date of the receipt of the following information,company's name, Address, Telephone and Fax number. The above information will enable us write letters of claim and job description respectively. This way we will use your company's name to apply for payment and re-award the contract in your company's name. We are looking forward to doing this business with you and solicit your confidentiality in this transaction. Please acknowledge the receipt of this letter using the above Email address. I will bring you into the complete picture of this pending project when I have heard from you. Remember this is a Deal so treat with utmost confidentiality. Yours faithfully, Yinka Davis

Thomas Sesay Karimu Karimusesay@BigMailBox.net Dear sir, This letter may come to you as a surprise because we have not met. The decision to write you is out of a sincere desire to establish a business/mutual relationship with you. I got your contact through the international trade and commerce chamber (ITCC) in Madrid. My name is Thomas Sesay Karimu, the son of John Karimu (former secretery of state for mining and industry) who was killed and mutilated by the military junta led by Major Paul Koroma after over-throwing the elected government of President Tijan Kabba. Though, I don't know to what extent you are familiar with events and disturbances in Sierra-Leone but it had consistent features in the BBC, CNN news bulletins. The pressure of war drove my family out of Sierra-Leone into exile in Spain where we have been living under political asylum for three years. Sadly, my mother died of cancer 4 months ago and was buried in Madrid. Prior to her death, she gave me a certificate of a secret deposit that my father made in a security company in Europe (destination will be disclosed later for security reasons) The money $45,000,000.00 (forty-five million dollars) was deposited as family treasure. He did this with a view to converting it to his personal use at the end of the war but was killed as a result of his opposition to the rebel forces when the conflict intensified. I have however contacted the security company to confirm the deposit and establish ownership. Due to the death of my mother and the continued hostility in Sierra-Leone, I have decided to solicit the assistance of an honest and trustworthy person or company that will assist in investing the money. I cannot do it alone due to my present political status and total ignorance of the business world. You will be given a negotiable percentage of the money at the end of the transaction. If you are honest, trustworthy and interested in the above proposal, contact me immediately through my email address for more details. You must maintain absolute confidentiality in order to ensure success. Please, indicate your personal telephone/fax numbers when replying. Best Regards, Thomas Sesay Karimu.

FROM MISS ZAINAB UBA AND HER BROTHER ABIDJAN, IVORY COAST WEST AFRICA. ATTN , It is my pleasure to write you after my seven days fasting and prayers and much consideration since I can not be able to see you face to face at first. Being the first and the only Daughter of my father, late ALHAJI KALWA UBA from BETE in Republic of COTE D´IVOIRE Africa I am 21years of age. My father was limited liability cocoa and gold merchant in ABIDJAN before his untimely death after his business trip to SWITZERLAND, to negotiate on a cocoa business. A week after he came back from SWISS, he was assassinated with my mother by unknown assassins. Which my mother died, instantly, but my father died after five days in hospital, on that faithful afternoon. I didn´t know that my father was going to leave me after I had lost my mother. But before he gave up the ghost, it was as if he knew he was going to die. He my father, (may his soul rest in perfect peace) he disclose to me that he deposited the sum of $5 million U.S dollars in a PRIVATE BANK here in ABIDJAN. That the money was meant for his cocoa business he wanted to invest in Abidjan - Côte d´Ivoire. Though, according to my father he deposited the money in his own name . He single handed me over the document and logging and verifying informations , and instructed me to seek for a life time investment partner abroad. Now I have succeeded in locating the BANK in here and also confirmed the fund is in there , most honest and confidentiality. Now I am soliciting for your assistance to help me lift this money out from The BANK to your account abroad so that we should invest it in any lucrative business in your country. I am Waiting anxiously to hear from you so that we can discuss the modalities of this transaction, Thanks for your kind attention and mutual understanding. Best regards ZAINAB.

No. 5667 Allen Avenue, Victoria Garden City Marine Beach. Date: 4th October, 2003. Attention: Dear Sir, PRAISE GOD, THE MOST BENEVOLENT. I am Mrs. Victoria Bucknor,named person from Nigeria. I am married to Late Mr. George Bucknor of blessed memory who worked with Nigeria embassy in switzerland for nine years before he died in the year 2000. We were married for eleven years without a child. He died after a brief illness that lasted for only four days. Before his death we were both very devoted christain.Since his death I too have been battling with both cancer and fibroid problems.When my late husband was alive he deposited the sum of $5Million (Five Million U.S. Dollars) in a security company. Presently, this money is still with the Security Company. Recently, my Doctor told me that I would not last for the next three months due to cancer problem. Though what disturbs me most is my stroke sickness. Having known my condition I decided to donate this fund to either a church/organisation or devoted christain individual that will utilize this money the way I am going to instruct here- in. I want this church/organisation or individual to use this money in all sincererity to fund building church,orphanages,widows and also propagating the word of GOD and to ensure that the society upholds the views and beliefs of the holy bible. The holy bible emphasized so much on GOD benevolence and this has encouraged me to take this bold step. I took this decision because I don’t have any child that will inherit this money, and I don’t want my husband’s hard earned money to be misused by people I call unbelievers. I don’t want a situation where this money will be used in an unholy manner. Hence the reason for taking this bold decision. I know that after death I will be with GOD the most benevolent and the most merciful. I don’t need any telephone communication in this regard because of my health and also of the presence of my husband’s relatives around me always. I don’t want them to know about this development. With GOD all things are possible. As soon as I receive your reply, I will forward it to my family attorney and I will then instruct him to give you the contact of the Security Company. I will also issue you a letter of authority that will prove you as the original- beneficiary of this fund. I want you and the christains/Muslims communities where you reside to always pray for me. My happiness is that I lived a life of a true devoted christain worthy of emulation. Whoever that wants to serve the GOD must serve him in truth and in fairness. Please always be prayerful all through your life. Any delay in your reply will give me room in sourcing for a church/organisation or a devoted christain for this same purpose. Until I hear from you, my dreams will rest squarely on your shoulders. May the almighty GOD continue to guide and protect you. Regards, Mrs. Victoria Bucknor

Dear Sir, My names are Mac Johnson Bonida, I am the inmediate young brother to Mrs Jewel Charles Taylor of war tored country of Liberia-westAfrica, the wife of (Mr Charles Taylor) president of Liberia. After a peace deal in Ghana few weeks ago, my sister called me for introduction of what need to be done inmediately that her properties are no longer safe. He asked me to meet her contact in Ivory Coast to arrange my journey to Eruope. She said that she had made contact with a Security company to move a truck box containing $30,000,000.00 US Dollars, Thirty Million United State Dollars Only, and that the security company label the box which the funds are contained in as a box containing Africa artifacts. The Company has confirmed the arrival of this consignment in their office in Netherlands. I left for Ivory-Coast for my journey to Europe and at this moment I am in Netherlands but owing to what is happening in my country this time, my sister can not do nothing as to Claim the Consignment and she want this deal to be a confidential transaction, so she asked me to contact any partner who could stand as a beneficiary of this truck box, so that after the beneficiary must have claimed the box the money will be channeled into good business investments with low risk. She has agreed to give 10% of the total fund to you for assistance and moving of the fund to your private account in your country for the purpose of the investment. While 5% of the total fund will cover your expense during this transaction, and another 5% for me. You can contact me if you are interested by my e-mail address or kindly call me on this Netherlands telephone number, . I would be glad if you can help me out to complete this transcation and transfer this fund into your private account. Please endeavour to keep this transaction as confidentail as much as possible because my Sister and her husband is in trouble over the war in my country-Liberia. Your Sincerelly, Mac Jonson Bonida

Dear Sir/Madam. Permit me to inform you of my desire of going into business relationship with you. I got your name and contact from the Benin Chamber of Commerce and Industry. I prayed over it and selected your name among other names due to its esteeming nature and the recommendations given to me as a reputable and trust-worthy person that I can do business with as per the recommendations. I must not hesitate to confine in you for this simple and sincere business. I am Mrs Floxy Page, the legal wife of the elstwhile chief security officer to late major Johnny Page, My Husband was the former head of the presidential guard to Mr Charles Taylor the liberia president. Before the death of my Husband, on may 15th,2003 during an attempt by the rebels on the life of president C.Taylor, where he was brutally injured and subsiquently rushed to the presidential hospital in monrovia where he later died.Before his death,he secretly called me to his bedside and told me that he has the sum of US$18Million dollars (Eighteen million dollars)that he used my name as his legal wife as the beneficiary and next of kin in depositing the fund with a clearing house in European country. The major reason is that the fund was deposited in a Security Company in Europe it was because of the ways the president was ruling the country,that he foresee things might go wrong with him in due course. Right now, the rebels are at war with the ! president and the America government has asked the president to step down. I am now in cotonou-Republic of Benin as a refugee because i am being sought after by the rebels since my husband was seen as one of Taylor's strong men as they want to wipe out our family. In this respect,i am honourably seeking your assistance in thefollowing ways : 1.To present yourselve as my beneficiary and next of kin to the fund,since i am hiding my identity from the authority to avoid them confisicating the fund or sending it back to Liberia. 2.To serve as a trustee to the fund. 3.To make arrangement for me to come over to your country as an investor and to secure Residence permit in your county.Moreover, I will like us to agree on what might be your compensation for your effort input after the successful claiming of this fund.You can get in contact with me through my alternative email:floxypage444@hknetmail.com after establishing cordial relationship. Anticipating to hear from you soon. Thanks and God bless you. Best Regards, Mrs.Floxy Page

ATTENTION: Dear Sir, I am Dr (Mrs)Maryam Abacha, wife to the late Nigeria Head of state, General Sani Abacha who died on the 8th of june 1998 while still on active duty . I am contacting you in view of the fact we will be of great assistance to each other, likewise developing acordial business relationship. I currently have within my reach the sum of Thirty Million United States Dollars ($30,000,000.00) cash, which I intend to use for investment purposes specifically in your country. This money came as a result of a pay-back contract deal between my late husband and a Russian firm in our country's Multi-billion dollar Ajaokuta Steel plant. The Russian firm in our country's Multi-billion dollar Ajaokuta Steel Plant. The Russian partners returned my Husband's share of US$30,000,000.00 U.S.D after his death, and lodged it in my late husband's Security Company of which I am a Director Right now, the new Civilian Government has intensified their probe on my late husband's financial resources and have frozen our accounts. In view of these facts, I acted fast to withdraw the US$30,000,000.00 U.S.D from the company's vault and deposited it in a privately owned security safe in . I have since declared the security company bankrupt. No record whatsoever exists concerning the money traceable by the Government because, there is no documentation showing that we received the money from the Russians. Due to the current situation in the country concerning the Government's attitude towards my family, it has become quite impossible for me to make use of this money within; thus upon your consent, I shall expect you to contact me urgently to enable us discuss indetail about this transaction. Bearing in mind that your assistance is needed to transfer this fund, I propose a commission of 20% (Twenty percent) of the total sum to you for the expected services and assistance. Your urgent response is highly needed so as to stop further contact. All correspondence must be by e-mail. I must use this opportunity to implore you to exercise the utmost indulgence to keep this matter extraordinary confidential, whatever your decision, while I await your prompt response. Please visit this website : http://allafrica.com/stories/200203180074.html. Best Regards, MRS MARYAM ABACHA PLEASE SEND YOUR PHONE AND FAX FOR ORAL DISCUSSION.

>From Dr Mogogo Mogul Atten: Sir please reply to mogu1@survivormail.com URGENT ATTENTION I am Dr. Mogogo Mogul, Chairman of Contract Award and Verification Panel set up by the Nigeria Ministry of Aviation. I got your contact from the net during my personal search ,after thorough deliberations,my colleagues and I decided to contact you for a very confidential business transaction of mutual benefit. During our verification exercise, we came across an over-invoiced contract(Contract No: FMA/PED/1473/96). This contract was awarded in July,1996 and completed in August, 1998, and the original contractor has since been paid his contract sum leaving the over-invoiced sum of US$25.5m(Twenty Five Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) This amount have been left floating in our account with the federation bank, until our recent discovery. My coleagues and I have decided to seek for the assistance of a reliable foreign partner into whose account the fund will be transferred into for our own use. If this proposal is acceptable to you, a “Deed of Transfer” of the above contract will be obtained on your behalf, to empower you as the legal beneficiary of the contract and the sum to be transferred. All necessary and relevant documents will be procured for the release and transfer of the fund into your nominated account. An application for foreign exchange allocation will be made on your behalf from my office to the federal ministry of finance (FMF) and the federation bank for the subsequent release and transfer of the fund into your nominated account.Be informed that we are working in collaboration with top officials of the federal ministry of finance and the federation bank, who will assist us in the transfer of the fund. With your cooperation the success of this transaction is guaranteed. We have agreed to compensate you with 25% of the total sum, 70% will be for me and my colleagues here, while the remaining 5% have been mapped-out for miscellaneous expenses that might be incurred by both parties during the course of this transaction. All things being equal, this transaction will be concluded within 6 working days upon the day of receipt of your response. You are required to email us your nominated bank account details and your direct telephone and fax numbers. Please treat this transaction with top priority and remember to keep it as confidential as possible. As soon as we receive your response, more details about how to proceed will be given to you. Best Regards, DR. Mogogo Mogul Chairman, Contract Award & Verification Panel ____________________________________________________________ Akční model Volkswagen Golf Pacific s výbavou za 60 000 Kč zdarma! Cena od 440 800 Kč. http://ad2.seznam.cz/redir.cgi?instance=60629%26url=http://www.volkswagen.cz/golf

Dear sir/ma, Greetings to you in the name of our Lord. Please permit us to use this medium to thank you once more for given us this avenue to explain our problem to you. But firstly, We will like to tell you who we are so that you will understand and comprehend our point clearly. Our name is Selina&Gabriel Marinze and We are here in Benin Republic but We are from GHANA in West Africa but we are here in Benin Republic We entered as a result of the Death of our Parent in our country. And here in Benin We entered as a refugee . But We are still a student . Am Selina is 24years and gabriel is 22 years , am studying medicine before the out break of the death our parent. Please we need your assistance because our living here is not ok after our father and mother has leaving us alone in this world. But before the death of our father who is a GOLD MERCHANT S.A in Ghana, he has used our name to deposit some fund of $35.5 MILLION UNITED STATE DOLLARS in a finance house and he used our name as the beneficiary of the fund but we are not in access to the fund because,Our father as stated with the finance House that upon our present an investors to manage the fund for us they should release the fund for us. Please what we need from you is to assist us in transfer the fund to your personal account for investment purpose and immediately we hear from you we will summit your particulars to the finance house to effect the transfer to your name as the new beneficiary and the investors to invest the funds for us, so you can now instruct the bank for further transfer of the fund to your account over there so that we can now come over there for the continuation of our education while you help us to manage the fund. And Moreover we agreed to give you 30% of the total funds for your kindly assistance and the remain 70% for invest into any reliable business over there you suggest that is profitable. please if you are ready to assist us, Kindly forward the following so that we can forward it to the bank for open of account with them for you so that they can transfer the fund through telegraphic wire transfer to your nominated account in your country. We NEED YOUR FULL NAME, YOUR ADDRESS AND TELEPHONE NUMBER AND FAX. THIS WILL ENABLE US TO PROCEED FOR THE OPEN OF ACCOUNT IN YOUR FAVOUR AS THE NEW BENEFICARY OF THE FUND. LORD BE WITH YOU ALL Regard Selina&Gabriel Marinze ------------------------------------------ Faites un voeu et puis Voila ! www.voila.fr

STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL DR.YUSUFF KADOSO (PhD). DEAR SIR, RE:URGENT BUSINESS RELATIONSHIP/PARTNERSHIP. First I must solicit your utmost confidentiality in this transaction. I am making this contact with you based on reliable information available to us courtesy of our local chamber of Commerce and Industry, thus we are convinced that you would be capable of providing us with a solution to a money transfer transaction of US$36,400,000.00 (Thirty-Six Million, Four Hundred Thousand United States Dollars ). Source:During the last military regimes here in Nigeria,government officials set up companies and awarded themselves contracts that were to be paid from the Petroleum Trust Fund (PTF) set up by the military regime for the purpose of financing special projects and these were grossly over-invoiced.The present civilian government have constituted an Interim Management Committe (IMC) with the mandate to investigate all contracts awarded as well as carry out debt verification of all claims that have not yet been paid with a view of settling all legitimate debts owed by the Federal Government of Nigeria to both local and foreign contractors before the government wind up the Trust Fund. We as members of this committee have identified a lot of inflated contract funds which are presently floating in the Central Bank of Nigeria. In the meantime, the government has already made a budget allocation for the payment of these contracts, but by virtue of our Position as civil servants and members of this panel, we cannot acquire this fund in our names. I was delegated as a matter of trust by my colleagues to look for an overseas partner into whose account we would transfer the funds totaling (USD36,400,000.00) and you will be adequately compensated with 25% of the entire sum, hence we are writing you this mail. The present Civilian Government is determined to pay foreign contractors all debt owed so as to maintain an amiable relationship with both the Foreign Governments and Non Government Financial Agencies and to attract foreign investment into our economy. We have decided to include our bills for approval with the co-operation of some officials of the Federal Ministry of Finance (F.M.F) and the Central Bank of Nigeria (C.B.N.). We seek your assistance in providing us the a good company account or personal account into which we can remit this money, you will be acting as an ORIGINAL CONTRACTOR in this deal, the fund will be paid to you. This we can do by SWAPPING of account information and changing of beneficiary information to apply for payment. We prepare letters of claims and job description on your behalf, on receiption of the following information (your banker's name and address, account number, your telephone and fax numbers) It is our intention therefore, while having your understanding and co-operation to invest 70% of this funds in the importation of agricultural and oil prospecting equipment to sub-western region of Africa. While the balance 5% will cater for all local and foreign expenses incurred in facilitating the transfer of this funds. Please contact me immediately you receive this mail by contacting me on my confidential email address (yusuffkadoso101@yahoo.com) thus signifying your capability and willingness to assist us. We are building our trust on sincerity of purpose, mutual understanding and recommendation. The business itself is 100% safe and fail proof, provided you treat it with utmost secrecy and confidentiality and you follow my instructions carefully and religiously. Your line of specialization does not matter as it cannot hinder the successful execution of this transaction. Again we look forward to doing business with you and solicit your utmost confidentiality in this transaction. Thank you for your co-operation. Yours faithfully, DR. YUSUFF KADOSO. N.B. The telecommunication system in my country is very poor, please do not be discouraged if you have difficulty in contacting me, your efforts will be much appreciated. PLEASE,DO QUOTE REFERENCE NUMBER (YK/01) IN YOUR RESPONSE.) ____________________________________________________________ Charle con sus amigos online usando CHAT 123 http://www.123.com/sp/chat/section.php?id_section=329

Dear Friend, Greetings!! I come to you with a sincere heart believing in Almighty Allah that you will consider my plight and come to help and also benefit from me. I am Mrs. Amina Mohammed, cousin and Personal Assistant to former Nigeria Head of State, Late General Sanni Abacha who died on the 8th July 1998 while in power. Before I proceed please accept my apology for the embarrassment this mail might cause you for coming from a total stranger who you do not know. Actually I got your contact from the Internet; please do not feel bad about it because I am compelled to reach you due to urgent need to safeguard the money in question. Once again, forgive me and come to my aid. Please read the following carefully. Sometime in early 1997, my boss late Gen. Sanni Abacha entrusted to me the sum of US$20.5M in cash (Twenty million, five hundred thousand US dollars) due to the trust and confidence he had in me. This money was meant for campaign in is self-succession bid but unfortunately he suddenly died before actualization of his aspiration. This amount of $20.5M in CASH was deposited with a security company, which I will disclose in subsequent mail in a giant trunk box as diplomatic consignments In agreement with Mr.Mohammed Abacha who is the son of Late General Abacha and the heir to the money. I write to solicit your Assistance for the money to be transferred to your custody. Note that Mr.Mohammed Abacha is currently in detention by the present Nigeria Government for reasons linked to activities of his father when he was in power. Now based on the business trust I have on you, I would want you to come forward and receive this consignment containing the ! money in cash on our behalf from the security company for subsequent disbursement between you and us. Understand that we are soliciting your assistance because the present Nigerian Government is seizing/freezing any Bank Account or valuables belonging to the late Head of State's family and relatives. Infact we do not have enough money now to sustain our family so, I will appreciate if you can consider our plight and assist us.For your assistance, we have agreed to compensate you with 20% of the total amount ($20.5) while the remaining 80% is for us. We hope to invest part of our share in your country on viable area of investment as you may advise us. If you are interested you will need to visit the Security Company for clearance of the consignment. I assure you that the transaction is 100% risk free. Please I implore you to keep this transaction absolutely secret against negative exposure. I would want you to contact me immediately so that we can proceed with the business. You should please on reply enclose your private telephone, fax number so that we can have more confidential correspondence. Best regards, Mrs. Amina Mohammed.

FROM THE DESK KOLA JOHNSON: CHIEF ACCOUNTING OFFICER BUSINESS PROPOSAL. ATTENTION: I AM DR. KOLA JOHNSON THE CHIEF ACCOUNTING OFFICER OF A BANK. HE FINANCIALSTATEMENT OF OUR BANK IS OVER US($500,000,000.00 (FIVE HUNDRED MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS) AND THE CURRENT ASSETS OF OUR BANK IS RELATIVELY LIQUID RESOURCES. THIS CATEGORIES INCLUDES CASH, INVESTMENTS IN MARKETABLE SECURITIES, RECEIVABLE, INVENTORIES AND PREPAID EXPENSES. IN RECENT YEARS THE ANNAUL REVENUE OF OUR BANK HAS EXCEEDED TO US$700M (SEVEN HUNDRED MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS) AND MY RESPONSIBITY IS FOR ME TO MAINTAIN ADEQUATE MONETARY INTERNAL ONTROL,CONTROLLING THE BANK CASH POSITION, BUDGETTING AND FOR THE PREPARATION OF ACCOUNTING RECORDS AND FINANCIAL STATEMENT. THE NUMBER OF CAPITAL SHARES WHICH HAS BEEN ISSUED FOR THE YEAR 2003 IS UNDER MY JURISDICTION IS US$300,000,000.00 AND THE OUTSTANDING SHARE THAT IS PRESENTLY UNDER MY CONTROL AND SUP ERVISION IS US$48,000,000.00 (FOURTY EIGHT MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS). WE ARE IN THE FIRST QUARTER OF THE YEAR 2003 AND I NEED A RELIABLE FOREIGN PARTNER THAT WILL ASSIST ME TO TRANSFER THE FUND INTO HIS BANK ACCOUNT. I HAVE MANAGERIAL AUTHORITY TO TRANSFER THIS FUND INTO YOUR BANK ACCOUNT BY ELECTRONIC WIRE TRANSFER. I NEED THE FOLLOWING BANKING INFORMATION: 1. THE NAME OF YOUR BANK 2. THE BANK ADDRESS 3. THE BANK ACCOUNT 4. THE BANK ROUTING/SWIFT CODE 5. THE BANK BENEFICIARY 6. YOUR COMPANY NAME 7. YOUR PRIVATE TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBER FOR EASY COMMUNICATION WITH THE ABOVE INFORMATION, I WILL EFFECT THE PAYMENT OF US$48 MILLION DOLLARS INTO YOUR NOMINATED BANK ACCOUNT AND THIS WILL ONLY TAKE US 24 BANKING WORKING HOURS TO EXECUTIVE THIS FINANCIAL BUSINESS TRANSACTION THAT WILL BENEFIT BOTH PARTIES. WE HAVE AGREED TO SHARE THE FUND AS FOLLOW: 30% WILL BE GIVING TO YOU HAS THE OWNER OF THE ACCOUNT WHERE THE FUND WILL BE TRANSFER AND 60% WILL BE FOR ME AND 10% FOR VALUE ADDED TAX THAT WILL BE REQUIRED BY YOUR BANK OFFICIAL. THE BANK WILL SEND YOU VALID CONCRET E AUTHORIZATION DOCUMENT AND TELEX CONFIRMATION WILL BE SEND TO YOUR BANK AND FOR YOU TO VARIFY FROM YOUR BANK AS SOON AS THE FUND HIT YOUR BANK ACCOUNT.NOTE: Please kindly state your early responseimmediately on this email:john48752003@yahoo.com for more details on the modalities involves in this business and it is top secret you have to keep strictly confidential. I WILL BE EXPRECTING YOUR URGENT COMPLIANCE AND FEED BACK. YOURS TRULY, DR.KOLA JOHNSON ______________________________________________________ Get Paid... With Your Free Email at http://www.zwallet.com/index.html?user=kolajohnsons1

MRS. SUSAN SHABANGU Deputy Minister of Minerals and Energy South Africa. Website:www.gov.za/profiles/shabangu.htm Dear Sir, After due deliberation with my children, I decided to contact you for your assistance in standing as a beneficiary to the sum of US$15.5M ( Fifteen Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars Only) First, let me start by introducing myself, I am MRS SUSAN SHABANGU, a mother of three children and the Deputy Minister of Minerals and Energy since 1st April 1996 to date under the President of South Africa MR THABO MBEKI. You can view my profile at my website www.gov.za/profiles/shabangu.htm After the swearing in ceremony making me the Deputy Minister of Minerals and Energy, my husband Mr Ndelebe Shabangu died while he was on an official trip to Trinidad and Tobago in 2002. After his death, I discovered that he had some funds in a dollar account which mounted to the sum of US$15.5M with SYNTHEX TRUST SECURITY AND PRIVATE COMPANY. This fund emanated as a result of an over-invoiced contract which he executed with the Government of South Africa. Though I assisted him in getting this contract but I never knew that it was over-invoiced by him. I am afraid that the government of South Africa might start to investigate on contracts awarded from 1998 to date. If they discover this money in his bank account, they will confiscate it and seize his assets here in South Africa and this will definetely affect my political career in government. I want your assistance in clearing this money from SYNTHEX TRUST SECURITY AND PRIVATE COMPANY. As soon as the fund is cleared, you are expected to move it immediately into another personal bank account in your country. I will see to it that the account is not traced from South Africa. As soon as you have confirmed the fund into your account, I will send my eldest son with my Attorney to come to your country to discuss on business investments. For your assistance, I am offering you 4 Million (Four million United States Dollars Only) However, you have to assure me and also be ready to go into agreement with me that you will not elope with my fund. If you agree to my terms, kindly as a matter of urgency send me an email. Due to my sensitive position in the South African Government, I would not WANT you to call me on phone or send a fax to me. All correspondence must be by email to my private email. If you want to speak with my Attorney, that is fine and okay by me. His chambers will be representing my interest with you.All correspondence must be made either to my Attorney Barrister James Ndlovu of kuramo lodge chambers on <jnchambers@justice.com> or send me an email to my private email box on mrs_susan00@yahoo.com or <mrs_susan2@123.com>. I will also like you to give me your contact address of telephone, fax and email to enable my Attorney call or reach you from time to time. Please I do not need to remind you of the need for absolute Confidentiality if this transaction must succeed. YOU MUST NOT CALL ME! If you do not feel comfortable with this transaction,do not hesitate todiscontinue. Thanks for your anticipated co-operation and my regards to your family. Yours faithfully MRS. SUSAN SHABANGU ____________________________________________________________ Charle con sus amigos online usando CHAT 123 http://www.123.com/sp/chat/section.php?id_section=329

NIGERIAN TELECOMMUNICATION LIMITED. FEDERAL SECRETARIAT COMPLEX, GARKI, ZONE II ABUJA. E-MAIL: kendikko01@123.com DATE:13th Oct. 2003 REF:rf/ntl-fgn Dear Friend, Please do not be disturbed about this mail as I am contacting you for the first time through this medium, while nursing no doubts that you will be of great assistance to this business proposal I am about disclosing to you for our both mutual benefit. I am Dr. Ken Dikko, the Project Director of Nitel at the above address. Following my intentions of owning an offshore investment, I was urged to contact a foreigner to assist in facilitating the immediate release of $14Million United States Dollars into his/her bank account to jointly execute my motive of securing an offshore investment. This was because Nigeria's civil service code of conduct does not allow a civil servant to own an offshore account or investment outside the shores of Nigeria. Sequel to this, I was able to contact a foreigner (Mr. Jim Walsh) an American based in Nigeria to assist with the transfer. He agreed and we proceeded in procuring all documents necessary to facilitate the immediate release of the funds into his custody using him as a Project Consultant to the Nigerian Telecommunication. The money was as a result of an over-invoiced contract on contract number "ntl-fgn01/ped-98" for the procurement, supply and installation of Telecommunication equipment to Nitel regional offices up to the tune of $52Million United States Dollars. It was awarded to a Swiss Contractor who executed the contract and was fully paid i.e $38Million United States Dollars leaving aside $14Million United States Dollars. Final payment approval was granted on behalf of Mr. Jim Walsh by the Federal Ministry of Finance (FMF) to the paying bank while waiting for the payment application from him to the bank but he suddenly died of Cardiac Arrest leaving no Next of kin/beneficiary to the funds. It is as a result of this, that I am contacting you to please stand as the next of kin to Mr. Jim Walsh and new beneficiary to the funds to enable the funds to be transfered into your custody. All documents to back up your claim will be giving to you adequately while a Memorandum of Understanding (MOU) will be reached between us to safe guard our both interest in line of this transaction. I am willing to compensate you with 25% of the total funds while the rest 75% will be for me for the investments in your country as well as assuring you that this transaction is 100% risk free and legal. If this proposal is okay to you, please kindly get back to me to enable me demand certain informations and briefing for the commencement of this transaction. Please always quote the reference number above in all correspondences to me while confidentiality should be our watch word. I await your urgent response. Sincere regards, Dr. Ken Dikko. Project Director, Nitel. ____________________________________________________________ Charle con sus amigos online usando CHAT 123 http://www.123.com/sp/chat/section.php?id_section=329

FROM:Mr DAVIDMAPUKA JOHANNESBURG SOUTH AFRICA

ATTN: DIRECTOR/C.E.O

My names is PRINCE DAVID MAPUKA, the elder son of Mr. ANTHONY MAPUKA,of Zimbabwe. It might be a surprise to you where I got your contact address, I got it from net work on line South African . During the current crises against  the farmers of Zimbabwe by the supporters of our President Robert Mugabe to  claim all the white owned farms in our country, he ordered all the white  farmers to surrender their farms to his party members and their followers.

My father was one of the best farmers in the country and knowing that he did not support the president’s political ideology, the president’s supporters invaded my father’s farm burnt down everything, shot him and as a result of the wounds sustained, he became sick and died after two days.  And after his death, I with my younger Brother decided to move out of Zimbabwe for the safety of our lives to South-Africa.

BUT, before he died HE WROTE HIS WILL, which reads "(MY BELOVEED SON ,I WISH TO DRAW YOUR ATTENTION TO THE SUM OF ($21,000,000).TWENTY ONE MILLION U.S DOLLARS WHICH I DEPOSITED IN A BOX WITH A SECURITY COMPANY INJOHANNESBURG (SOUTH-AFRICA). IN CASE OF MY ABSENCE ON EARTH CAUSED BY DEATH ONLY". You

should solicit for reliable foreign partner to assist you to transfer this money out of South Africa for investment purpose. I deposited the money in your name and it can be claimed by you alone with the  deposit code. your mother has all the documents. Take good care of your mother and brother."  From the above, you will understand that the lives and future of my family depends on this money as much, I will be very grateful if you can assist us.

 I with my younger brother are now living in South-Africa as POLITICAL ASYLUM SEEKERS and the financial law of SOUTH-AFRICA does not allow ASYLUM SEEKERS certain financial rights to such huge amount of money .In view of this, I cannot invest this money in South-Africa, hence I am asking you to assist me transfer this money out of South-Africa for investment purposes. For your  efforts, I am prepared to offer you 20% of the total fund, while 5% will be set  aside for local and international expenses and 75% will be kept for me and  my family .

Finally modalities on how the transfer will be done will be conveyed to you once we establish trust and confidence between ourselves. Looking forward to your  urgent reply .For detailed information. NOTE: THE KEY WORD TO THIS TRANSACTION IS ABSOLUTE CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECRECY. THIS TRANSACTION IS 100% RISK FREE. YOUR URGENT RESPONSE WILL BE HIGHLY APPRECIATED.  All the best,

PRINCE DAVID MAPUKA.

(FOR THE FAMILY)

Yahoo! India Matrimony: Find your partner online. Post your profile.

ECONOMIC RECOVERY COMMITTEE, FEDERAL SECRETARIAT, LAGOS-NIGERIA. Dear Sir, BUSINESS PROPOSAL: TRANSFER OF US$19.2 M (NINETEEN MILLION, TWO HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS) & BUSINESS INVESTMENTS PARTNERSHIP. First, I must solicit your strictest confidence in this transaction, this is by virtue of it's nature as being utterly confidential and top secret as you were introduced to us in confidence through the Nigerian Chamber of Commerce, foreign trade division. and if the contents of this mail does meet with your approval, i humbly crave your indulgence. I am the chairman of the Economic Recovery Committe (ERC) set up by the present civilian Government of Nigeria to review economic policies of government parastatals, and find out ways to reduce waste and maximise revenues allocated to them. In the course of our work at the ERC, we discovered this fund which resulted from gross re-valuation of contracts by top government officials of the federal ministry of Aviation (FMA). The company that executed the contracts have been duly paid and the contracts commissioned leaving the sum of US$19.2 Million lying unclaimed in the escrow account of the Central Bank of Nigeria. Upon interogation of the directors of engineering and finance, who both happens to be my contemporaries in the university, they confessed to me in confidence that they had an agreement with the original contractor to re-value the original contract by 30%. This 30% which amounts to USD19.2m was to be their share from the contract, since the original contractor was well disposed towards giving them the conventional 10% kickback. When I now asked them what they intended to do now that my committee has discovered this USD19.2M. They begged me not to disclose this information to the government as they will likely lose their jobs and their family names destroyed. I was at at a crossroad, as I did not want my friends to suffer for what other top government officials do and get away with. I discussed with the other two members of my committee and we all unanimously agreed to transfer this fund out and share amongst ourselves. I have therefore been mandated as a matter of trust by my colleagues in the committee to look for an overseas partner to whom we could transfer the sum of US$19.2M legally sub-contracting the entitlement to you/your company. This is bearing in mind that our civil service code of conduct forbids us from owning foreign company or running foreign account while in government service hence the need for a foreign partner. Should this transaction interest you, you are to contact me on my personal e-mail address, so that I can brief you fully, and discuss your renumeration for this undertaking. All logistics are in place and all modalities worked out for the smooth conclusion of the transaction within ten to fourteen days of commencement after receipt of the following information: Your full name/ company name, address, company's details & activities, telephone & fax numbers. These information will enable us make the applications and lodge claims to the concerned ministries & agencies in favour of your company and it is pertinent to state here that this transaction is entirely based on trust as the solar bank draft or certified cheque drawable in any of the Central Bank of Nigeria correspondent bankers in America, Asia and Europe is going to be made out in your name. Please acknowledge the receipt of this letter using my personal E-mail address. Yours Faithfully Abayomi Davies.

From:Mohammed Abacha Lagos-Nigeria Dear Sir/Madam This letter is not intended to cause any embarrassment but just to contact your esteem self-following the knowledge of your high repute and trustworthiness. I am Mohammed Abacha,the son of the late Nigerian Head of State who died on the 8th of June 1998. If you are conversant with world news,you would understand better,while I got your contacts through my personal research.Please,I need your assistance to make this happen and please; do not undermine it because it will also be a source of upliftment to you also.You have absolutely nothing to loose in assisting us instead, you have so much to gain. The then head of state General Sani Abacha,transferred the money through a Lebanese businessman,Chagoury and a Jewish business man,Mark Rissar to bank accounts overseas,Instead,he used PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION NUMBERS (PIN) and declared the contents as Bearer Bonds and Treasury Bills. Also the firm issued him with a certificate of deposit of the consignments notes, which I have these information in my custody now. You must have heard over the media reports and the Internet on the recovery of various huge sums of money deposited by my late father in different Banks and security firms abroad. Some of these banks and security firms willingly gave-/divulge their banking secrets and disclosed to the present civilian administration of Chief Olusegun Obasanjo,about my family’s cash lodgement and monetary transactions with them. Please my dear,I repose great confidence in you and I hope you will not betray my confidence in you.I have secretly deposited the sum of $30,000,000.00 with a security firm abroad whose name is withheld for now until we open communications. The money is contained in a metal box consignment with Security Deposit Number 009GM. I shall be grateful if you could receive this fund into your Bank account for safekeeping. This arrangement is known to you and my junior brother (Abbas) only. So I will deal directly with you.I am proposing a 20% share of the fund to you for your kind assistance.I shall provide for you all the documents of the fund deposit with the security firm, and raise a power of attorney to enable you claim and receive this fund into your bank account.I have done a thorough homework and fine-tuned the best way to create you as the beneficiary to the funds and effect the transfer accordingly. Is rest assured that the modalities I have resolved to finalize the entire project guarantees our safety and the successful transfer of the funds.So, you will be absolutely right when you say that this project is risk free and viable.If you are capable and willing to assist, contact me at once via email with following details: 1. YOUR NAME 2. POSTAL ADDRESS 3. PHONE AND FAX NUMBERS Also this transaction demands absolute confidentiality.On no condition must you disclose it to anybody irrespective of your relation with the person.Remember,Loose lips sinks ship.I am looking forward to your urgent and positive response via my email address above. Best Regards, Mohammed Abacha. View this website for more info: http://news.bbc.co.uk/hi/english/world/africa/newsid_909000/909972.stm http://news.bbc.co.uk/hi/english/world/africa/newsid_877000/877113.stm

Greetings from UAE HIGHLY CONFIDENTIAL. I decided to contact you by email because I feel that it is more secured and private. I am Nasser Bin Nasiri, Director of Procurement and Contract Award with, Ministry of Petroleum and Mineral Resources [MPMR]. I am contacting you concerning the transfer of US$43 Million Dollars (FOURTY THREE MILLION DOLLARS) Sometime ago, a contract was awarded by my Corporation, [MPMR] to a Japanese Firm, to carry out Turn Around Maintenance and rehabilitation work on Emirates Petroleum Products Company (EPPCO) This contract was over invoiced by us to the tune of US$43. Million {Forty Three Million United States Dollars). Myself and my partner reached a compromise to transfer the fund into a Foreign bank account that will accommodate this fund. We have all modalities set. We were disappointed last time by a US Senator, Late Paul Wellstone whom we trusted with a transaction of this nature up to the tune of $45 Million USD in 2001. They sat on our money for no apparent reason and was still holding our money until his family were killed in a plane crash last December. We still believe that good people still exist in this world and we are willing to try again with you, bearing in mind that God will all way fight for us. You can confirm the above transaction from Mr. Clarence Barnes, Uncle to the Senator, who provided the receiving bank account. His email address is cbarnes@worldemail.com and phone 1-661-310-2112. He is enjoying our collective money and refused to give us our share but we believe, he shall meet his doom as Senator did. Because of this we are afraid and we need your total trust and assurance that you must be an honest and straight forward person. We made a costly mistake with the Senator, by not going into agreement. Based on our status as senior government officials in top sensitive position of trust, we cannot stand to claim this money ourselves without the assistance of a foreigner. The process will not require your presence here in UAE. I guarantee that this transaction will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. We intend to share the money in the following manner: 30% for you, 60% for us and 10% will be for any expenses incured during the transfer. Contact me immediately if you are interested for further details. We look forward to a fruitful business relationship with you and your urgent response. Best Regards, Mr. Nasser Bin Nasiri.

From: J. Rodney Chesson Chesson Family Corporation, Liberia. Email: jrchesson@rediffmail.com Kindest attention, I am very sorry for the informal manner in which this mail is reaching you. This is necessitated by my urgent need to reach a dependable and trustworthy foreign partner. This request may seem strange and unsolicited but I crave your indulgence and pray that you take my request very serious. I am Mr. J. Rodney Chesson, the first son of Late J. J. F. Chesson (Liberian Minister of Justice 1979 to 1980). On April 22, 1980, my father along with 12 other Liberian Government officials was assassinated as a result of a military coup that toppled the government of President William R. Tolbert, Jr. May his soul rest in Eternal Peace. Since then, my family has always been seen as a symbol of peace in Liberia. I received information from a reliable source that described your country as being economically conducive for investment and her people as transparent and trustworthy to engaging business, which made me to write you. As you may want to know and to make you less curious, I got your email address from an Internet site that portrayed you in good light. Early this year, Liberia rebels agitated for the removal of President Charles Taylor, who portrayed a very good example of a bad leader. The President who needed support from prominent Liberia citizen gave me the sum of twenty-eight million United States Dollars (US$ 28M) cash (stalked in two trunk boxes) as compensation for my late father and solicited for my support. I quickly made an arrangement with a courier company here in Monrovia and moved the consignment to an asset management company in Europe. I did not support President Charles Taylor because my conscience is not for sale. Some months later heavy fight broke up in Liberia, he placed all the eligible members of my family under travel watch confiscated all our traveling documents and frozen all our account in Liberia. Later in July, foreign troops invaded Liberia and different peace keeping meetings were held and President Taylor was advised to step down for national peace. On the 11th August 2003 President Charles Taylor flied into exile and handed over power to his Vice-President Moses Blah who is even more wicked and dangerous. He was the person that instigated Taylor to confiscated all our traveling documents and frozen all our account in Liberia. On Tuesday 14th October 2003, Gyude Bryant took office in Liberia as the head of an interim government. Bryant, 54 was by picked b! y the warring factions and this step has offered Liberia a new chance to end nearly 14 years of violence. My lawyer approached him as regards releasing our traveling documents and the embargo on our bank accounts but he declined and told us that his priority is disarm fighters and pave the way for elections that is why I requested for your sincere assistance pending when a fresh election will be held here. WHAT YOU ARE EXPECTED TO DO FOR US: I will transfer the ownership of the consignment /boxes containing the cash to you and issue you a power of attorney through my Lawyer. With these document you will claims to the money as my proxy from the asset management company in Europe. The entire operation is risk free since it is only you and me and my Lawyer that knows the details of the money after you must have taken the money to your country where it is save my lawyer will then meet you in your country to use my share of the money for investment. Bearing in mind that your assistance is needed to transfer this fund, I propose a commission of 20% (twenty percent) of the total sum to you for the expected services and assistance. Your private fax and telephone numbers are needed to enhance the speedy conclusion of this transaction (our only hope in life now) urgently. Your urgent response via the above email address is highly needed so as to stop further contact. I must use this opportunity to implore you to exercise the utmost indulgence to keep this matter extra ordinarily confidential whatever your decision while I await your prompt response. Our phone line both home and abroad are bugged. So don't call me. I will always call you at my convenient time and in a conducive atmosphere. Best regards, J. Rodney Chesson. N.B. Please reply with above email address (jrchesson@rediffmail.com). I want you to note that neither the Chesson Family Corporation nor any of its officials are soliciting money of any kind or financial or other assistance from organizations, agencies, or individuals. Visitors to our website are advised that there is a current scam by unknown individuals using our corporation website and my name to solicit money or goods from the public. We advise that all who receive letters soliciting funds, etc, in my name or the name of our corporation to report them to your local law enforcement authorities. This notice is a sufficient legal warning to all who visit our website. You can view our family web page below. (www.chessonfamily.com/chessonfamilypage.htm

From: Mrs Serena Jones PLEASE ENDEAVOUR TO USED IT FOR THE CHILDREN OF GOD. I am the above named person from Kuwait. I am married to Dr. Harry Jones who worked with Kuwait embassy in Ivory Co ast for nine years before he died in the year 2000. We were married for eleven years without a child. He died a fter a brief illness that lasted for only four days. Before his death we were both born again Christia ns.Since his death I decided not to re- marry or get a child outside my matrimonial home which the Bi ble is against.When my late husband was alive he deposited the sum of$8.6Million (Eight Million six hundred thousand U.S. D ollars) with one finance/security company in Amsterderm Hollan d. Presently, this money is still with the Security Company. Recently, my Doctor told me that I would not last for the next three months due to cancer problem. Though what disturbs me most i s my stroke sickness. Having known my condition I decided to donate this fund to church or better still a christian individ ual that will utilize this money the way I am going to instruc t here in. I want a church that will use this fund to fund chu rches, orphanages and widows propagating the word of God and t o ensure that the house of God is maintained. The Bible made us to understand that Blessed is the hand that giveth. I took this decision because I don?t have any child that wil l inherit this money and my husband relatives are not Christi ans and I don?t want my husband?s hard earned money to be misu sed by unbelievers. I don?t want a situation where this money will be used in an ungodly manner. Hence the reason for taking this bold decision. I am not afraid of death hence I know whe re I am going. I know that I am going to be in the bosom of th e Lord. Exodus 14 VS 14 says that the lord will fight my case and I shall hold my peace. I don?t need any telephone communi cation in this regard because of my health because of the pres ence of my husband?s relatives around me always. I don?t want them to know about this development. With God all things are p ossible. As soon as I receive your reply I shall give you the contact of the Finance/Security Company in Amsterderm Holland . I will also issue you a letter of authority that will prove you as the original- beneficiary of this fund. I want you and the church to always pray for me because the lord is my shephard. My happiness is that I lived a life of a worthy Christian. Whoe ver that wants to serve the Lord must serve him in spirit and truth. Please always be prayerful all through your life. Any d elay in your reply will give me room in sourcing for a chuch or christian individual for this same purpose. Please assure me that you will act accordingly as I stated herein. Hoping to hearing from you. N.B- PLEASE I WILL ADVICE YOU TO GIVE THE LAWYER IN CHARGE A CALL IN HOLLAND IMMEDIATELY, HE DOES EVERYTHING ON MY BEHALF AND HE'S VERY UNDERSTANDING AND I BELIEVE HE WILL LEAD YOU TO YOUR SUCCESS IN JESUS NAME, THE LAWYER'S NAME IS GERRY SLY HIS CONTACT PHONE NUMBER IS 00-31-620-668-086. Remain blessed in the name of the Lord. Yours in Christ, Mrs Serena Jones

PETER BUNO. Tel:+41 79 530 99 35 Good Day, With warm heart I offer my friendship, and my greetings, and I hope this letter meets you in good time. It will be surprising to you to receive this proposal from me since you do not know me personally. However, I am sincerely seeking your confidence in this transaction, which I propose with my free mind and as a person of integrity. My name is PETER BUNO, the first son of Phillip BUNO Personal assistant to the president Charles Taylor Liberia,a country in West Africa is presently torn apart by strife and armed rebellion.These upheavals have led to the intervention of the American government which has insisted that the incumbent president Charles Taylor,vacate his position and allow an international peacekeeping force to act as a transitional government. The embattled president Charles Taylor,has been offered political asylum by the Government of the Federal Republic of Nigeria, and he intends to grasp this lifeline that has been provided. The Government of the United States of America have clearly stated their intentions to investigate the finances and financial dealings of president Charles Taylor and have also threatened to freeze his personal accounts. In the light of these circumstances,My father has instructed me, to source for a foreigner who can take possesion and control of a large portion of his personal fortune which he has amassed over the period of his regime, which is stashed away in a financial institution in Europe. I was continually threatened to abandon my inheritance from my father. I resited for a while, but when the danger became unbearable, and I survived two murder attempts,I fled Liberia.I am currently staying in the Switerland where I am seeking political asylum. These monies amount to approximately (US$56. 000.000)Fifty - six million United States Dollars).Adequate remuneration will be provided for services rendered by you. It is important that you expedite action in this transaction if you are interested, because time is of the essence.Confidentiality is also of great importance. Thank you PETER BUNO Contact me through my direct line which is 00 41 79 530 99 35

BOARD OF TRUSTEES, NIGERIAN NATIONAL PETROLEUM CORPORATION [NNPC] Victoria-Island,Lagos. FROM THE OFFICE OF:DR. JEFF MBOMA (MNIM) Attn: President/CEO. BUSINESS PROPOSAL: TRANSFER OF US$25.6 M (TWENTY-FIVE MILLION SIX HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS) & BUSINESS INVESTMENTS PARTNERSHIP First, I must solicit your strictest confidence in this transaction,this is by virtue of its nature as being utterly confidential and top secret as you were introduced to us in confidence through the Nigerian Chamber of Commerce, Foreign Trade Division. I am Dr.Jeff Mboma, the Secretary of the Federal Government of Nigeria Contract Award and Monitoring Committee (CAMC) of the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation [NNPC].Sometime ago, a contract was awarded to a conglomerate of Foreign Companies by my committee on behalf of NNPC, the contract was over-invoiced to the tune of US $25.6 Million.This was done deliberately, the over-invoicing was a deal by members of my committee to benefit from the project, we now desire to transfer the money, which is presently in a suspense account of NNPC in the Central Bank of Nigeria (CBN) into an overseas account which we expect you to provide We have agreed that the following funds will be shared thus after it has been paid into your account; a) 30% of the money will go to you for acting as the beneficiary of the fund. b) 10% has been set aside as an abstract projection for reimbursement to both parties for incidental expenses that may be incurred in the course of the transaction. c) 60% to us the government officials (which we wish to commence an important business in conjunction with you). I Would Require a) Name and address of Company/ Beneficiary b) Proforma Invoice / Letter-Head Paper The above information would be used to make formal applications as a matterof procedure for the release of the money and onward transfer to your nominated account. It does not matter whether or not your company or you does contract projects of the nature described here, the assumption is that you won a major contract and subcontracted it out to other companies, more often than not,big trading companies or individuals of unrelated field win major contracts and subcontracts to more specialized firms for execution of such contracts. We have strong and reliable connections and contacts at the Central Bank of Nigeria (CBN) and The Federal Ministry of Finance and we have no doubts at all that this money will be released and transferred if we get the necessary foreign partners to assist us in this deal. Therefore, when the business is successfully concluded we shall through the same connections withdraw all documents used from all the concerned government ministries for 100% security. We want this money to be transferred to the foreign account which you are going to provide bearing in mind that our civil service code of conduct forbids us from owning foreign company or running foreign account, all expenses regarding the account opening if not already in existence shall be borne by you, all expenses are however reimbursable as already stated above on conclusion of business. Please acknowledge the receipt of this letter if you are interested. I wait in anticipation of your co-operation. Yours Faithfully, Dr.Jeff Mboma (MNIM)

Dear Friend. I am Mr. Phil Ipenza, Provincial Manager Development Bank of Southern Africa(DBSA). I have urgent and very confidential business proposition for you. On June 6, 1999, a foreign mining consultant/contractor with the South Africa Mining Corporation, Mr. Richard Moss made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at US$12,5 00,000.00 (Twelve Million,Five Hundred Thousand US Dollars) in my branch. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the South Africa Mining Corporation that Mr. Richard Moss died from an automobile accident. On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL, and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr. Richard Moss did not declare any kin or r! elations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$12,500,000.00 is still sitting in my Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to South African Law, at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the South Africa Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr. Richard Moss so that the fruits of this old man's labour will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that the Attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits which will put you in place as the next of kin. We shall employ the service of two Attorneys for processing and notarizat! ion of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and lett! er of pr obate/administration in your favour for the transfer. A bank account in any part of the world which you will provide will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 60% for me and 40% for you. There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the Attorney and my position as the Branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately via the private email address below. Upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Awaiting your urgent reply via my email: Ipenza@themai! l.com Thanks and regards. Mr. Phill Ipenza.

140GC2 GARDEN PARK IKOM ROAD. BAKASSI PENINSULA. (URGENT FUND TRANSFER) -------------------------------------------------- GREETINGS, IN ORDER TO TRANSFER OUT (USD 26 MILLION DOLLARS) FROM OUR BANK. I HAVE THE COURAGE TO ASK YOU TO LOOK FOR A RELIABLE AND HONEST PERSON WHO WILL BE CAPABLE FOR THIS IMPORTANT BUSINESS BELIEVING THAT YOU WILL NEVER LET ME DOWN EITHER NOW OR IN FUTURE. I AM MR.DANDY NNAJI, THE EASTERN DISTRICT BANK MANAGER OF UNITED BANK FOR AFRICA PLC. (UBA). THERE IS AN ACCOUNT OPENED IN THIS BANK IN 1980 AND SINCE 1990 NOBODY HAS OPERATED ON THIS ACCOUNT AGAIN. AFTER GOING THROUGH SOME OLD FILES IN THE RECORDS I DISCOVERED THAT IF I DO NOT REMITT THIS MONEY OUT URGENTLY IT WILL BE FORFEITED FOR NOTHING. THE OWNER OF THIS ACCOUNT IS MR. SMITH B. ANDREAS, A FOREIGNER, AND THE MANAGER OF PETRO - TECHNICAL SUPPORT SERVICES, A CHEMICAL ENGINEER BY PROFESSION AND HE DIED SINCE 1990. NO OTHER PERSON KNOWS ABOUT THIS ACCOUNT OR ANY THING CONCERNING IT, THE ACCOUNT HAS NO OTHER BENEFICIARY AND MY INVESTIGATION PROVED TO ME AS WELL THAT THIS COMPANY DOES NOT KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT THIS ACCOUNT AND THE AMOUNT INVOLVED IS (USD 26 MILLION DOLLARS). I WANT TO TRANSFER THIS MONEY INTO A SAFE FOREIGNERS ACCOUNT ABROAD BUT I DON'T KNOW ANY FOREIGNER, I AM ONLY CONTACTING YOU AS A FOREIGNER BECAUSE THIS MONEY CAN NOT BE APPROVED TO A LOCAL BANK HERE, BUT CAN ONLY BE APPROVED TO ANY FOREIGN ACCOUNT BECAUSE THE MONEY IS IN US DOLLARS AND THE FORMER OWNER OF THE ACCOUNT IS MR. SMITH B. ANDREAS IS A FOREIGNER TOO. I KNOW THAT THIS MASSAGE WILL COME TO YOU AS A SURPRISE AS WE DON'T KNOW OUR SELVES BEFORE, BUT BE SURE THAT IT IS REAL AND A GENUINE BUSINESS. I ONLY GOT YOUR CONTACT ADDRESS FROM THE COMPUTER, WITH BELIEVE IN GOD THAT YOU WILL NEVER LET ME DOWN IN THIS BUSINESS YOU ARE THE ONLY PERSON THAT I HAVE CONTACTED IN THIS BUSINESS, SO PLEASE REPLY URGENTLY SO THAT I WILL INFORM YOU THE NEXT STEP TO TAKE URGENTLY. SEND ALSO YOUR PRIVATE TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBER INCLUDING THE FULL DETAILS OF THE ACCOUNT TO BE USED FOR THE DEPOSIT. NOTE THAT AN EMPTY ACCOUNT CAN SERVE AS LONG AS IT CAN RECIEVE FUNDS. I WANT US TO MEET FACE TO FACE OR SIGN A BINDING AGREEMENT TO BIND US TOGETHER SO THAT YOU CAN RECIEVE THIS MONEY INTO A FORIEGN ACCOUNT OR ANY ACCOUNT OF YOUR CHOICE WHERE THE FUND WILL BE SAFE. AND I WILL FLY TO YOUR COUNTRY FOR WITHDRAWAL AND SHARING AND OTHER INVESTMENTS. I AM CONTACTING YOU BECAUSE OF THE NEED TO INVOLVE A FOREIGNER WITH FOREIGN ACCOUNT AND FOREIGN BENEFICIARY. I NEED YOUR FULL CO-OPERATION TO MAKE THIS WORK FINE. BECAUSE THE MANAGEMENT IS READY TO APPROVE THIS PAYMENT TO ANY FOREIGNER WHO HAS CORRECT INFORMATION OF THIS ACCOUNT, WHICH I WILL GIVE TO YOU LATER AS SOON AS YOU EXPRESS YOUR INTEREST TO DO THIS BUSINES WITH ME, IF YOU ARE ABLE AND WITH CAPABILITY TO HANDLE SUCH AMOUNT IN STRICT CONFIDENCE AND TRUST ACCORDING TO MY INSTRUCTIONS AND ADVICE FOR OUR MUTUAL BENEFIT BECAUSE THIS OPPORTUNITY WILL NEVER COME AGAIN IN MY LIFE. I NEED TRUTHFUL PERSON IN THIS BUSINESS BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO MAKE MISTAKE I NEED YOUR STRONG ASSURANCE AND TRUST. WITH MY POSITION NOW IN THE OFFICE I CAN TRANSFER THIS MONEY TO ANY FOREIGNER'S RELIABLE ACCOUNT WHICH YOU CAN PROVIDE WITH ASSURANCE THAT THIS MONEY WILL BE INTACT PENDING MY PHYSICAL ARRIVAL IN YOUR COUNTRY FOR SHARING. I WILL DESTROY ALL DOCUMENTS OF TRANSACTION IMMEDIATELY WE RECIEVE THIS MONEY LEAVING NO TRACE TO ANY PLACE. YOU CAN ALSO COME TO DISCUSS WITH ME FACE TO FACE AFTER WHICH I WILL MAKE THIS REMITTANCE IN YOUR PRESENCE AND TWO OF US WILL FLY TO YOUR COUNTRY AT LEAST TWO DAYS AHEAD OF THE MONEY GOING INTO THE ACCOUNT. I WILL APPLY FOR ANNUAL LEAVE TO GET VISA MMEDIATELY I HEAR FROM YOU THAT YOU ARE READY TO ACT AND RECEIVE THIS FUND IN YOUR ACCOUNT. I WILL USE MY POSITION AND INFLUENCE TO EFFECT LEGAL APPROVALS AND ONWARD TRANSFER OF THIS MONEY TO YOUR ACCOUNT WITH APPROPRIATE CLEARANCE FORMS OF THE MINISTRIES AND FOREIGN EXCHANGE DEPARTMENTS. AT THE CONCLUSION OF THIS BUSINESS, YOU WILL BE GIVEN 35% OF THE TOTAL AMOUNT, 60% WILL BE FOR ME, WHILE 5% WILL BE FOR EXPENSES BOTH PARTIES MIGHT HAVE INCURED DURING THE PROCESS OF TRANSFERING. BEST REGARDS, MR.DANDY NNAJI.

Dear Friend, After deliberation with my children, I decided to contact you for your assistance in standing as a beneficiary to the sum of US$15.5M(Fifteen Million,Five hundred Thousand United States Dollars ). Firstly, let me start by introducing myself as MRS SUSAN SHABANGU, a mother of three children and the former Deputy Minister of Minerals and Energy under the auspices of the President of South Africa MR THABO MBEKI. You can view my profile at my website www.gov.za/profiles/shabangu.htm THE PROPOSAL After the swearing in ceremony making me the Deputy Minister of Minerals and Energy, my husband Mr Ndelebe Shabangu died while he was on an official trip to Trinidad and Tobago . After his death, I discovered that he had some funds in dollar, US$15.5 million United States Dollars currently in a coded security company vault in Europe which I now intend to use to establish a profitable business for my children to enable my children and I start life again.As a result, I am urgently in need of a very reliable investor participant who is not known as my associate,that I could entrust with the pin and certificate of deposit to help me remove the box including Gold and Diamond Platinium since no one name were used in securing the vault. I can not successfully claim it myself as the government searchlight is still on me.Though, I do not know you in person but I still maintain my late husbands theory that business is people and contacts. hence I crave your assistance,you will also Bank and assist me in investing this money with my lawyers approval on project. Finally,more details on the logistics and modalities of the trasaction will be given to you as soon as I receive your acceptance letter. Do not forget the confidenciality sorounding this transaction, while awaiting for your letter I am calling on the Almighty God to be with all of us . This fund emanated as a result of an over-invoiced contract which he executed with the Government of South Africa. Though I assisted him in getting this contract but I never knew that it was over-invoiced by him. I am afraid that the government of South Africa might start to investigate on contracts awarded from 1990 to date. If they discover that he has this kind of money, they will confiscate it and seize his assets here in South Africa and this will definetely affect my status. The money is contained in a strong steel security box in cash and it is presenting deposited with a security firm in Armsterdam- Holland where it is registered as family treasures and valuables for security reasons.In side the box are all documentation for funds. WHAT I WANT YOU TO DO FOR ME . 1.You are to come to Armsterdam ,open a non-resident account in one of the commercial banks where funds will be deposited before finally being transferred to your nominated account overseas(as may be mutually agreed). 2.I have made arrangements to give the transaction the legal cover as overseas investment. 3. Security storage and demurrage charges have accumulated considerably since my husband death. I am making arrangement to raise money to settle this.It is imoportant that you and my Attoney are together throughout the transaction in Armsterdam, Holland. 4.I would appreciate at the end of the day ,if part of the money is invested in developing countries like South Africa. 5.We will need to sign a legally binding agreement relating our benefits and commitments in this transaction For your assistance, I am offering you 20% of this fund,Please honesty is the watch word in this transaction .However, you have to assure me and also be ready to go into agreement with me that you will not elope with my fund. If you agree to my terms,kindly as a matter of urgency, send me an email. Due to my sensitive position in the South African Government, I would not want you to call me on phone or send a fax to me. All correspondence must be by email to my private email address, If you want to speak with my Attorney, that is fine and okay by me. His chambers will be representing my interest. All correspondence must be made either to my Attornery,or send me an email. I will also like you to give me your contact address of telephone, fax and email to enable my Attorney call or reach you from time to time. Please I do not need to remind you of the need for absolute Confidentiality if this transaction must succeed. YOU MUST NOT CALL ME! If you do not feel comfortable with this transaction, do not hesitate to discontinue. Thanks for your anticipated co-operation and my regards to your family. Yours Faithfully, Mrs. Susan Shabangu (Former Deputy Minister of Minerals and Energy ,South Africa) ____________________________________________________________ Charle con sus amigos online usando CHAT 123 http://www.123.com/sp/chat/section.php?id_section=329

Dear Friend, Warmest greetings in the name of ALLAH,the most gracious. I pray that he may grant you the wisdom to understand the pathetic story i am about to tell and the courage to offer the much needed support i solicite for in this letter. I am a mother of two and the wife of late General YOUSSEF EL HADIDI of the defuct Republican Guard of ousted President Saddam Hussein . During the hay days of ex-president Saddam rulership in iraq my late husband was head of secret Army's procurement unit of the Republican Guard. His position and resposibility availed him with so much power and financial liquidity that he was able to amass substantial amount of money some of which he wisely move to secret custody out side iraq. Having forseen the caputilation of Saddam Hussein government my late husband quietly moved his family (my two kids & I) to Europe and tried to desert the Iraqi Army to join us in Europe, but was cought up with by the dangerosu secret security mechinary of Saddam. He was brutally murdered on the order of Saddam himself and all our properties and estate including bank account were consficated by the infamosu regime. Ever since my kids and i have lived in pennary until we uncovered through the help of his life -long solicitor some funds he left in a safe custody in London here. It is for the purpose of entrusting and investing this huge fund with little or no trace to our family that i send you this propostition. The funds in question is $35 Million (Thirty Five Million) and is presently deposited in a trust company awaiting directives from me as my husband next of kin to move it. It is true that i have never known you but i am desprately in need of somebody to trust, it has become a matter of expediency and total surrended to the will of God , the Almighty. If you do understand my story willing and capable of handling this trustteeship proposition, kindly oblige me by sending your personal and business profile including all contact details for us to move forward without delay. You can reach me direclt on my fax +447092041337. Awaiting your response, Yours truly, Jumai Hadidi Tel/fax: 4470920341337

From: The Desk of Dr.PETER CLAPTON Director, Investments and Portfolio Management, Royal Accounting and Trust LLC, Switzerland. Tel: 41 79 530 99 35     Dear Sir/Madam,   I am the expert director heading Investments and Portfolio Management in the above-mentioned firm in Switerland.   I am contacting you in view of an urgent assistance to carry out a pending transaction, which will develop a cordial business relationship between you and me. One of my clients whom I have personally managed his portfolio for 10 years now was a victim of a fatal car crash. His name is Late Mr Saud Ed Abad AlKharj, he was survived by a fiance and a two-year-old son from her as they intended getting married but where trying to be cautious because of Islamic law attitude on adultery. This were his only family and no next of kin, as he was the only child of Late Sheikh Hamza Al Kharj Al Faisal, who received royalties from the Kuwaiti Government on one of his fields which oil was discovered and subsequently explored (the Al Jazriah Oil Field).   All subsequent investigation to find a next of kin was privately conducted by me and was futile. It was at this juncture that I and other officials Managing his portfolio and 2 bank managers where he had his accounts now decided to make this proposal and transfer ownership of the portfolio to an Agreeing party as beneficiary to the portfolio of the deceased.   The reason why ownership cannot be transferred to his wife to be and only son is that Islamic law will not recognize such and if an attempt is made on that it may put her in trouble with the authorities for giving birth outside marriage. So we have decided to help her by making this proposal and making sure she gets a substantial part of Late Mr Saud Alkharj’s property for her and her son.   You must be asking where I got your mail address, it was made available to me by a junior director Mrs Cynthia Philips in charge of customer services on request for contacts for investment expansion for a client but she is not aware of this contact. All records and accounts regarding the assets of deceased were managed by me for 10 years running, if you are interested to assist us, all I will do is to incorporate in the old records recognizing you as the only beneficiary.   The banking law here stipulates that if such portfolio remains unclaimed after four years it will go to the public department. The need for a foreigner as beneficiary is occasioned by the fact that the deceased was not permanently resident in Switzerland.   For your assistance, we made up of I, 2 senior directors in my firm and 2 bank managers in banks which the Kuwaiti Government pay royalties, accruing to the deceased have agreed in fairness to make available 25% of all bank funds cleared and 15% of the royalties which you will continue to receive on behalf of the deceased as sole beneficiary every year. However we do not intend to share any interest with you as far as the estates and property are concerned, as they will be going to the surviving wife and child.   If you are okay with the above explanations, you may reply us including all your contact telephone and fax numbers so that we may confirm you genuine, after which we will make more information available to you on how we will proceed.   I must further assure you that this transaction is 100% legitimate and the modalities for this transaction is being handled by top executives which assure a risk free transaction.Kindly visit my firms website at www.royaltrust.com.   We await your timely response.   Best Regards   DR PETER CLAPTON

DR JAES MORGAN(PRINCIPAL AUDITOR) NIGERIA NATIONAL PETROLEUM CORPORATION(NNPC) FALOMO OFFICE COMPLEX IKOYI, LAGOS NIGERIA. TELL:234-1-7756759. E-MAIL:charlsmorgan2@yehey.com

Dear SIR, I guess my letter would not embarrass you since I have no previous correspondence with you.  The foreign  trade office of the Nigeria Chamber of Commerce and

Industry gave me your company's details.  My request however  centers on mutual collaboration and your unflinching support to confidentially set-up a Joint-Venture outfit in your country.

I hope I  would not regret approaching you in this matter.

I am at present working as the Chairman of the Task Force that is reviewing all previous and present contract awarded by various ministries in the country.

This appointment is from the office of the Presidency in the Federal Republic of Nigeria.  Since the appointment took effect from November, 2000.  The Task Force have jointly discovered some irregularities  comprising of over invoice contract values.

In the   meantime, we have discovered about Nine Hundred and Eighty  Million United States Dollars US$980,000,000.00).

In our respective positions and status, this is an opportunity to enrich ourselves and our family, as a matter of fact, this is a timely opportunity considering the economic situation in this country, we have agreed to declare only Nine Hundred and Fifty-Six Million United States Dollars US$956,000,000.00) to the government while the balance of (US$24,000,000.00)Twenty - Four Million United  States Dollars only will be remitted to your private/company's account.

We hope to establish a Joint-Venture Business with you in your country. This money if accepted by you will be used in financing the cost of equity and other expenses for the take-off of the Joint Business.We have set out the machinery to enable us secure the effective remittance of this fund to your account, if only you can work with us.It is however noteworthy that this business is extremely sensitive and must be kept confidential.

Furthermore, 30% of the money will be due for you as compensation for your effort and assistance, 10% for incidental expenses to be incurred on the course of transferring this fund while the rest goes into the Joint-Venture Project.  Please note that remittance would be effective from 14 working days on receipt of your Bank Account details as follows: 1. Bank Name and Address 2. Account Number 3. Beneficiary's name and address 4. Private Telephone/Fax number for easy

communication  and confidentiality  of this transaction.

However, do endeavour to reply me if your capacity does not meet up our  proposal so that I can

further more negotiation.

Best Regards,

DR JAMES MORGAN.

Dear friend, Compliment of the day, I JULIET UGAGA, The daughter of late General KuJI UGAGA of the Democratic Republic of Congo.im married with two children. My father was a General in the Congolese Army. In his position (My father) with the office of the presidentcy during the regime of Laurent kabila, he was assigned on a secret mission to source and acquire arms internationally in order to strengthen the Government forces against the rebels, which already had the support of Rwandan and Uganda Army. Meanwhile, he was still negotiating for the purchase of the arms, he received on the 16th January 2001 news of the assassination of Laurent Kabila which force him to call off the assignment and deposited the sum of US$12.5M, Packed in a diplomatic case in a private security company in the Hague, the Netherlands, though he registered the content as precious stones while the real content is (US12.5M) meant for the purchase of arms for the Congolese Army. My father went home for the funeral of the late president, but on his arrival he was arrested, detained and tortured, unfortunately my father suffer cardiac arrest and died on the 17th of March 2001. However,one of our numerous visits, my mother and I paid him while in prison, my father was able to reveal this secret to me and advice that we should proceed to the Netherlands to claim the money, he handed me all the relevant documents that will enable me claim the box from the security company.Already, I have made my first visit to the security company and the document entitled to clear this money is with a finance security company in Holland. On our arrival in the Netherlands few months ago, we sought for political asylum; which was granted. My mother and I are making frantic effort on the best way to handle this money. We sought advice from an attorney who advised that we must seek for a trustworthy foreign business partner whom can invest this fund in a profitable venture. This we view as the best option because our refugee status dose not permit us to operate a bank account, hence we seek your assistance and hope you could be trusted. Meanwhile, I sincerely ask for your assistance to get this money through your account, Your share for assisting us will be 25% of the totalsum, 5% will be use for upsetting all the expenses incurred in the courseof concluding this venture and the remaining 70% that will be for me and my family. Also you stand to gain from any investment you might introduce us into after the conclusion of the transfer. Please keep this confidential until we finalize and get this money into your account for security reasons. This is my e-mail address you can reach me:julietugaga21@netscape.net Thanks and GOD bless. MISS JULIET UGAGA

FROM THE DESK OF DR. FRANK BELLO, EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR, FINANCE, N. N. P. C. CONFIDENTIAL ATTN: Compliments of the day and sorry for the embarrassment my letter might cause you. I am Dr. Frank Bello, the Executive Director Finance, of the Nigeria National Petroleum Corporation (NNPC). Because of my position and that of other strategic officials who are heads in their departments, we have in our possession since 1997 the sum of US$60M Dollars (Sixty million United States Dollars) which we amassed through over invoicing of foreign contracts fully executed and commissioned with the different foreign Contractors duly paid their full contract amounts. Following the peaceful life ushered in by the current democratic dispensation in Nigeria, I and my colleagues have decided to transfer the sum of US$60 Million into a foreign account operated by a foreigner for onward transfer into our accounts. I request your assistance in transferring and safeguarding the sum of US$60M Dollars for our mutual benefits. For assisting us in transferring and safeguarding this fund, you will be entitled to 35% of the total sum, 60% belongs to my colleagues and me while 5% will go for reimbursement of all expenses made by both parties. It is imperative to note that this transaction is risk free as my colleagues in the relevant ministries have perfected all modalities for the successful transfer of this fund. However, we should see absolute confidentiality as our watchword throughout the course of this transaction for we are civil servants and will want to safeguard our jobs, so as to receive our pension, since we have put in a lot of years on active service for the N.N.P.C. I will not be ungrateful if you can urgently furnish me with your full name as you want it to appear in the necessary documents, address, private telephone, fax and mobile numbers so as to enable us conclude all modalities associated with the transfer of the funds for onward transmission into your nominated bank account because the Central Bank of Nigeria has authorized the Guaranty Credit Bank of Nigeria to make payments to all contractors and you will be included among the contractors by me and my colleagues. Looking forward to hear from you soonest so as to stop further contacts . Regards, Dr. Frank Bello. ------------------------------------------------- Email Enviado utilizando o serviço MegaMail

PARAMOUNT SECURITY COMPANY HOLLAND, LAGOS BRANCH. Private Email:{femimartins876@fsmail.net <mailto:femimartins876@fsmail.net> Dear Friend, I am Mr.femimartins,Manager of paramount security company, Lagos Branch. I apologize for using this medium to reach you for a transaction/business of this magnitude, but this is due to confidentiality and prompt access reposed on this medium. Be informed that your enviable credentials/particulars were given to me by a member of the South African Export Promotion Council who was at the Government delegation to your country during a trade exhibition. I have decided to seek a confidential co-operation with you in the execution of the deal described hereunder for the benefit of all parties and hope you will keep it as confidential because of the nature of this transaction . I have an urgent and very confidential business proposition for you. On Dec. 19, 1998, a Canadian Oil consultant/contractor with the Ministry of Energy and Natural Resources, Mr. Antoine Blanc made a numbered timed(Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at US$25,000,000.00 (Twenty Five Million Dollars)in my branch. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the Ministry of Energy and Natural resources that Mr. Antoine Blanc died from a plane crash. On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a Will, and all attempts to trace his next of kin was futile. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr. Antoine Blanc did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my security company. This sum of US$25,000,000.00 is still sitting in my security company and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Nigerian Law, at the expiration of 6 (six) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Nigerian Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as an Foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr. Antoine Blanc so that the fruits of this old man's labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that the Attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits which will put you in place as the next of kin. We shall employ the services of one Attorney for drafting and notarization of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/administration in your favor for the transfer. A bank account either newly created or existing in any part of the world which you will provide, will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 75% for me and 20% for you. Then 5% will be used to offset any expenses incurred during the entire processing. Please your percentage is not negotiable. it is considerate enough. There is no risk at all as the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the Attorney, and my position as the Branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately via the private email address below. Upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. I am awaiting your urgent reply via my email: .femi-martin876@fsmail.net <mailto:.femi-martin876@fsmail.net> However, after your initial response by email, I would suggest that you contact me via phone 234 8055467101, for a verbal and detailed explanation of this transaction .This is imperative, because I would like to speak with you in order to be sure of who I would be with carrying out this transaction with. Regards.

IT IS WITH HEART FULL OF HOPE THAT I WRITE TO SEEK YOUR HELP IN THE CONTEXT BELOW.I AM MRS, MARIAM ABACHA (WIDOW) THE WIFE OF FORMER HEAD OF STATE OF NIGERIA, GENERAL SANI ABACHA WHO'S SUDDEN DEATH OCCURRED ON THE 8TH OF JUNE, 1998. AS A RESULT OF CARDIAC ARREST WHILE STILL IN GOVERNMENT. I GOT YOUR EMAIL CONTACT FROM ONE OF THE MY FAMILY FRIEND A DIRECTOR, WITH THE NIGERIA CHEMBERS OF COMMERCE AND INDUSTRY. I HAVE NO DOUBT ABOUT YOUR CAPACITY AND GOOD WILL TO ASSIST ME IN RECEIVING INTO YOUR PERSONAL BANK ACCOUNT (FOR SAFETY)THE SUM OF US$ 32,800,000.00 (THIRTY TWO MILLION, EIGTH HUNDREDTHOUSAND US DOLLAS)"WILLED" AND DEPOSITED IN MY LATE HUSBAND'S FAVOUR THIS MONEY IS CURRENTLY DEPOSITED WITH A SECURITYCOMP ANY IN TWO TRUNK BOXES AS BELONGINGS AWAITING COLLECTION. AS IT IS LEGALLY REQUIRED, THE ADMINISTRATION OF MY LATE HUSBAND'S PROPERTIES IS UNDER THE AUTHORITY OF THE FAMILY'S LAWYER NAMED (BARRISTER BENSON &ASSOCIATES). SINCE THE DEMISE OF MY HUSBAND, THE PRESENT REGIME(GOVERNMENT) HAS BEEN PROBING MY LATE HUSBAND'S WEALTH. PRESENTLY, SOMECASH ASSETS WITHIN AND OUTSIDE NIGERIA HAVE BEEN FROZEN AND SEIZED.FORTUNATELY, OUR FAMILY LAWYER HAD SECRETLY PROTECTED THE PERSONAL WILL OF MY LATE HUSBAND FROM THE NOTICE OF THE GOVERNMENT MEANWHILE, I AND EVERY MEMBER OF MY FAMILY ARE BEING MONITORED AND ALSO DENIAD ACCESS TOFINANCIAL DEALING WITHIN AND OUTSIDE NIGERIA. HENCE, I WAS ADVICE BY MYPERSONAL ASSISTANCE TO EMPLOYE THE ASSISTANCE OF A NEUTRAL INDIVIDUALOUTSIDE NIGERIA AND WITH THE LEGAL BACKING OF MY FAMILY LAWYER TO POSE ASTHE BENEFICIARY OF THE WILLED MONEY AND THEREFORE CLAIM THE CONSIGNMENT FROM THE SECURITY COMPANY FOR BENEFIT OF US ALL. THE GOVERNMENT HAD EARLIER PLACED FOREIGN EMBARGO ONALL OUR FAMILY MEMBERS, SEIZED ALL KNOWN LOCAL AND INTERNATIONAL OUTFITS OF OUR BUSINESS EMPIRE. THE SITUATION HAS BEEN SO TERRIBLE THAT WE ARE VIRTUALLY LIVING ON THE ASSISTANCE OF OUR WELL WISHERS. IN VIEW OF THIS PLIGHT THEREFORE, I EXPECT YOU TO BE TRUST WORTHY AND KIND ENOUGH TO RESPOND TO MY MAIL TO SAVE MY FAMILY AND I FROM A HOPELESS FUTURE. I HEREBY AGREE TO CONPENSATE YOUR SINCERE AND CANDID EFFORT IN THIS REGARD WITH 20% OF THE FUND WHEN FINALLY RECEIVED INYOUR PERSONAL BANK ACCOUNT. MY LAWYER WILL MAKE EVERY ARRENGMENTS TO EFFECT COMPLETE DISLODGMENT OF THIS MONEY WITHIN A WEEK OF THE RECEIPT OF YOUR RESPONSE THROUGH E-MAIL.PLEASE, ALL CONTACT ON PHONE MUST BE THROUGH OUR FAMILY LAWYER- BENSON & ASSOCIATES OR MY PERSONAL ASSISTANCE WHILE YOU COMMUNICATE WITH ME ON EMAIL AS I AND MY FAMILY MEMBER IS BEEN HEAVELY MONITORED BY THE GOVERNMENT. I WILL ALSO FORWARD THE EMAIL AND PHONE NUMBER OF BARRISTER BENSON & ASSOCIATES OR THAT OF MY ASSISTANCE TO YOU AS SOON AS I RECIEVE YOUR RESPONSE. I LOOK FORWARD TO YOUR QUICK RESPONSE. MAY ALLAH BLESS YOU.PLEASE REPLY ME THROUGH MY PRIVATE EMAIL ADDRESS:mariamabacha4real@444.net BEST WISHES, MRS. MARIAM ABACHA (WIDOW). NB: PLEASE I WILL WANT YOU TO GO THROUGH THE FOLLOWINGWEBSITE IN OTHER TO CONFIRM MORE ON THE ISSUES OF THE ABACHA ANDTHEFEDERAL GOVERNMENT SEIZURE AND FROZON ON THE ABACHA'S WEALTH. http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/877113.stm (http://www.econdad.org/Abacha.

FEDERAL MINISTRY OF WORKS AND HOUSING. FEDERAL SECRETARIAT COMPLEX, FALOMO, IKOYI, LAGOS. FROM THE OFFICE OF ENGR. BABATUNDE PEDRO. TEL: 234-8037269805. RE-BUSINESS PROPOSAL:TRANSFER OF US$12.4M (TWELVE MILLION FOUR HUNDRED THOUSAND)UNITED STATES DOLLARS AND BUSINESS INVESTMENT PARTNERSHIP. Dear Friend and Partner, I solicit your strictest confidence in this proposal. This is by virtue of it's nature as been utterly confidential and top secret as you were introduced to us through the Nigeria Chamber of Commerce Foreign Trade Division. We are top government officials drawn from the Federal Ministry of Works and Housing FMW&H, the Presidency and the Federal Ministry of Finance FMF making up the Contract Review Panel CRP set up by the present administration to review all contracts awarded by the past government. In the course of our work on the CRP, we discovered grossly over-invoiced contracts which were awarded to foreign contractors. The contract have been duly executed and commissioned but leaving the contract commission US$12.4M Dollars floating in the escrow account of the Central Bank of Nigeria CBN ready for payment. The funds resulted from connivance between our predecessors and the foreign contractors. The contractors have been duly paid their contractual entitlement US$81M Dollars but leaving the over-invoiced funds US$12.4M Dollars in CBN's escrow account. We are therefore seeking your assistance in the transfer of these funds out of this country by providing your company name and address to be registered as a subsidiary or afilliate of the real company that executed the contract so as to effect the ballance of the funds into your account as part of the executor. This is necessary as we cannot use the help of a local contractor here since the job was executed by a foreign company. Hence the need for your assistance. All logistics and modalities are in place to ensure the smooth conclusion of this transaction within the nest 10 to 14 working days of commencement after the receipt of your company name and address as stated above including your telephone/fax numbers for better communication. These informations will enable us make the application and lodge claim to the concerned ministry and agency in favour of your company. It is pertinent to state here that this transaction is entirely based on trust as the solar bank draft or certified cheque drawable in any of the Central Bank of Nigeria corresspondent bankers around the World is going to be made in your name. Finally, when the funds hits your account, I and my associates will come over to your country for the sharing purpose as outlined categorically clear below. (i) US$10M Dollars for us the 3 members of the Contract Review Panel (ii)US$2M Dollars for you for acting as the beneficiary of the funds. (iii)US$.4M Dollars as an abstract projections for re-imbursement to both parties for any incidental expenses that may be incured during the process of the transaction. If you are interested, please write or call my direct access line above. I await your response in this regard. Your's Faithfully, Babatunde Pedro.(Engineer/director of Project FMW&H).

Kojo Adams, Accounting Department, EcoBank. Cotonou, Attn my friend , I am Mr kojo Adams, Auditor, with Accounting Department,Ecobank here in Cotonou, Benin Republic. I got your very good name and e-mail address from the online classified posted on the net.I have decided to contact you purely on the personal conviction of trust andconfidence that we can co-operate with one another and do a very lucrative business for our mutual benefit.The Business I am proposing to you is in respect of the sum of US$11,183,000.00 (Eleven Million One Hundred and Eighty-Three Thousand United States Dollars Only) deposited in Dollar account with my bank which belonged to Mr Mohamed Saleh Ibrahim who died on 25th July,2000 in a plane crash, is an Engineering contractor.My bank has made several efforts at contacting the family of Mohamed Saleh Ibrahim or his relatives, but all have proved abortive as he had no identifiable kins men. This sum of US$11.183M has remained unclaimed ever since then and nobody has come forward as his next of kin. The management under the influence of our chairman and member of the board of directors has made an arrangement for the fund to be declared unclaimable and subsequently be turned to the reserve account of the bank. It is against the background of the foregoing,that two of my colleagues and myself in the bank have decided to contact you for assistance and partnership, for you to stand as the next of kin to Mr Mohamed Saleh Ibrahim. With your permission this fund will be transferred to your private account abroad as the beneficiary and next of kin to Mr Mohamed Saleh Ibrahim . All proof of claim and necessary documentation will be carefully worked out in your favour and we assure you of 100% risk free involvement and protection. consequently, if you find this proposal acceptable to you and you wish to assist us, I expect your urgent response and upon receipt of that,we shall discuss and agree on the disbursement and sharing ratio.Let me therefore expect your very urgent response through my phone,or e-mail addresses. Please endeavour to include your private phone and fax number and also your private e-mail where available. Please keep this proposal very secret and confidential. Thank you and best regards as I await your urgent response. yours Faithfully, Adams. +229-280-899 ------------------------------------------ Faites un voeu et puis Voila ! www.voila.fr

From: Carl Eblon Tel: 27-83-689-6084 Email: eblon@martinsfarms.com Dear Friend, Naturally this mail will come to you as a surprise, but if I may crave your indulgence, I'm MR. Carl Eblon, the first son of Dodi Martins Eblon, the most popular black farmer in Zimbabwe who was recently murdered in the land dispute in my country. I APOLOGISE FOR INVADING YOUR PRIVACY, BUT PLEASE, I appeal to you to exercise a little patience and read through my letter, and I guarantee you will not have wasted your time. I am contacting you, as the need to for me to have a foreign partner in your country has become necessary due to my plans to relocate and establish a private company in that region, as the present political instability in my country Zimbabwe, does not encourage financial investment as the environment is not conducive for investment and most of all security is not insured,just as reported by international media. This land problem came when Zimbabwean President Mr. Robert Mugabe introduced a new Land Act Reform wholly affected the rich white farmers and some few black farmers. This resulted to the killing and mob action by Zimbabwean war veterans and some lunatics in the society. Infact a lot of people were killed because of this Land reform Act for which my father was one of the victims. This was after the leadership of president Robert Mugabe announced a degree on May 31st 2000 to seize more than 849 white-owned farms and 104 Black owned farms (the white associates who are against the government which includes my father and some of his friends). So far, more than 1,400 white and black owned farms have been invaded and confiscated, as well as claiming the properties of the farmers. During these periods, as reported by international media, more than 8 white and 4 black farmers were killed, the government is not stopping at this, as just recently the government have asked all white-farmers to give up their farms to black farmers or risk going to prison. Before the death of my father, he deposited the sum of US6.5 Million (Six Million, Five Hundred United States dollars) in one of the private security company, as he foresaw the looming danger in Zimbabwe. This money was deposited in a box as gemstones and photographic materials to avoid much demurrage from Security Company. This amount was meant for the purchase of new machines and chemicals for the Farms and establishment of new farms in Swaziland. It is against this background that, my family and I fled Zimbabwe for fear of our lives and are currently staying in South Africa where we are seeking political asylum and more so have decided to transfer my father's money to a more reliable foreign account. as the eldest son of my father, I am saddled with the responsibility of seeking a genuine foreign account where this money could be transferred without the knowledge of my government who are bent on taking everything we have got. As a businessman, I am seeking for a partner who I have to entrust my future and that of my family in his hands, I must let you know that this transaction is risk free. If you accept to assist me and my family, all I want you to do for me, is to make arrangements with the security company to clear the consignment (funds). But before then all modalities will have to be put in place. I have two options for you. Firstly you can choose to have certain percentage of the money for nominating your account for this transaction. Or you can go into partnership with me for the proper profitable investment of the money in your country. Whichever the option you want,feel free to notify me. I have also mapped out 5% of this money for all kinds of expenses incurred in the process of this transaction. If you do not prefer a partnership I am willing to give you 15% of the money while the remaining 80% will be for my investment in your country. I implore you to maintain the absolute secrecy required in this transaction. Thanks, GOD BLESS YOU Best Regards CARL EBLON MARTINS FARMS ZIMBABWE

Attention to: CEO/PRESIDENT From: Sam KOROMA Tel: 27 733 624 034 Fax: 27 115 076 062 Email: sarakoroma@hotmail.com Johannesburg/SOUTH AFRICA Dear Sir, May this reach you in peace of mind and good health. It will be pertinent to first make myself known to you, my name is Mr. Sam Koroma. I am the first son of Chief Omoh Koroma, the former Chairman of Sierra Leone Mining Corporation. Unfortunately, my father was brutally murdered in 1999 by the RUF rebels led by Mr. Forde Sankoh "the monster" who due to his selfish interest destroyed a nation and devastated the land because of the diamonds. This is a story that has to be imagined than to express because of the ugly memory and cost. Since the demise of my father, we the entire family has been grieving and honestly, very hard for us to trust people especially here in Africa. I had only confided in few close friends as we were in need of securing the wealth of my father. It was within these meditation that I got your contact through a reliable source. Honestly I have not reveal this to anyone. Based on this, I decided to write you first because this is my family last hope of living comfortably as we do when my father was alive. Before my father passed away, he had already acquired a vast estate and a considerable wealth in Sierra Leone. In our neighboring country, my father deposited two boxes containing cash of thirty-three Million Dollars (US$33,000,000.00) in a security company. When he deposited this boxes, my father purposely registered it as a precious item in order not to attract the attention of the security company officers, and also for safety reasons until he is ready to use it for investments. Unfortunately, as an adage says, Man propose but God disposes my father could not live to achieve all his dreams. In his declaration, he use my name as the next of kin. As the war broke out, we shifted to Johannesburg, South Africa for the safety of our dear lives. Right now, I am writing you from Johannesburg, looking for a way to remove the money out of the security company with a reliable person overseas for a proper investment. We cannot establish any businesses here in Africa due to instability of Government in most countries. Base on this, I am seriously soliciting on your kind assistance to aid me on how to invest this money with you in your good country. When my beloved country was in war, I was still a student and I had a little or no knowledge about business, this is one of the reason I need your help most. Please this is a family affair and because of my family name, it should be strictly between you and myself, and for safety! of my mother and my younger ones. Have this in your mind, this business is 100% risk free. My family have agreed to give you (15%) of the total amount if you are ready to assist us in this transaction. Your soonest reply will be much appreciated. Kind regards, Sam Koroma , for the family.

Dear Sir, CONFIDENTIAL BUSINESS ASSISTANCE I am Mr. Mohammed Jaja, Deputy Secretary-General to the Nigerian Football Association parent body of the World Youths Championship, NIGERIAN 99 Local Organising Committee. An affiliate of Federation of International Football Association (FIFA). In the course of our preparation to host the World Youth Soccer Championship Tagged (NIGERIAN 99) two years ago. Huge sum of money running into millions of United States Dollars was budgeted by the then Military Government for the successful organisation of this competition. In the same vein, the FIFA President Mr. Joseph (Sepp)Blaster donated some millions of Dollars for the same project, not to talk of Corporate bodies, Organisations and Football loving individual as the Deputy Secretary to both the Local Organising Committee (LOC) and the Nigerian Football Association (NFA), I and some of my colleagues in sensitive position were able to Over -Invoice most of the contracts, construction and refurbishing of the 8 stadia,Press Conference Rooms,Communication facilities and all other infrastructures used for the competition.The contractors who handled these projects had been paid off. I wish to inform you that the sum of US$18.5 million was realised as a result of Over-Invoicing after the successful competition and the said sum is presently lying in my Organisations (NFA) coded account with the Central Bank of Nigeria,ready for transfer into an overseas account of our choice.It might interest you to know that the New Civilian President of Nigeria has ordered that all Debt owned to foreign contractors should be paid immediately in order to woo more foreign investors into Nigeria. In the light of the above, I has been mandated by my colleagues to seek for an honest and trustworthy foreigner who will assist us in ensuring the successful Transfer of the above sum into his Personal/Companies Account. All necessary modalities/plan is duly worked out accordingly, you the account owner will be entitled to 20% of the Total fund while 5% will be used to settle any expenses that might be incurred by both parties and 75% will before me and my colleagues. You might be surprised and curious on how I got your detail in particular,it is courtesy of the Chamber of Commerce,Mines and Industry. All we require from you is your Co-operation as this Transaction is absolutely risk-free. We kindly request that you handle this transaction with utmost secrecy.We are hoping to develop a good business relationship with you. Your immediate response will be highly appreciated.I will want you to respond or through this email address;mjaja01@ecplaza.net because of the confidentiality which this transaction needs. Yours sincerely, MR. Mohammed

I am Dr. Usman ali, I am a former special Adviser on Petroleum matters to the late Head of State Of Nigeria Gen. Sani Abacha. Because of my strategic Position in the former Government and also being a Close confidant of the late Head of State. I was able to acquire personally the sum of $12,500,000.00 USD (Twelve Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars only) presently lodged In Security Company inform of Gold Bars in a security company here in Nigeria. I did not want the management of the Security Company to know the content of the consignments; therefore I registered the content of the consignments as Gold Bars. Now, the security company believes that what I deposited with them was Gold Bars I made this money largely through "CONSULTANCY FEE" And "Good Faith Fees" paid by foreign Oil companies Prior to Allocation of Deep Water Oil Blocs and other Lifting/prospecting Rights (Nigeria is the 6th largest Producer/Exporter of Crude Petroleum in the World. As you are probably aware Nigeria is prone to Military Coups and the resultant Political/Economic Instability has fueled hyper Inflation, amongst other problems. I have therefore resolved to invest my money abroad, preferable in Real Estate Properties and Importation of Goods from your country for safety and optimum returns on Investment. However, straight transfer of this money into a bank abroad will present two major problems one, the tax incidence will be too high, as much as 60% of this money will go up in Taxes, Levies, Penalties etc. as a result of Government deliberate restrictions on flight of capital Abroad. And also been accused of money laundering and terrorism, The solution is to Courier this money cash abroad in form of consignment, through Courier service Company here in Nigeria in Conjunction with an embassy here in Nigeria, the money will be packed in a "Diplomatic Bag/Carton" tagged Diplomatic luggage that will be address to you. This system is secret and the money is therefore Untraceable. It is system used by most top Government officials to remove their fortunes to safety abroad. I have therefore concluded every arrangements with a Courier Company in Nigeria to Courier this money abroad using the courtesy and safety of Diplomatic Bag. All I now need is an honest partner who can receive the money on my behalf and help me to invest as aforementioned. There is absolutely no risk involved in this transaction as the money will be delivered to you in United States Dollars Bills. If you are interested in assisting me, please send to me by email immediately your preferred contact address where this money will be delivered to you, upon delivery, you are to lodge this money in a bank account and contact me for necessary arrangements for the investment. For your help and assistance in this deal, you will receive 15% of this money in cash or Equity if you wish to join the proposed company. I have notified the Security Company where I deposited the consignments that contained the fund, that I am moving the consignment abroad and the security company has since been waiting for my authority for the consignment to leave my country and move to abroad. So if you know that you will use this fund honestly as I have instructed. and the details will be given to you on how you will be able to receive the fund in your country through the security company. You should also forward to me your telephone and fax number for easy communication and to fax you the documents concerning the consignments. Your prompt response will be highly appreciated. Best regards Dr. Usman ali

FROM: MRS RAMA IDRIS In Lordship. I am the above named person from Tunisia but now undergoing medical treatment. I was married to Dr.Roberts IDRIS who worked with Malaysia embassy in ABIDJAN for nine years, before he died in the year 2002. We were both married for eleven years without children. He died after a brief illness that lasted for only four days. Before his death we were both Christians and since his death I decided not to re-marry. When my late husband was alive he deposited the sum of USD5,500,000.00 (Five Million Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) with a African Devlopment bank I will send you details as soon as you indicate your interest. Recently, my Doctor told me that I would not last for the next Six months due to my cancer illness. Having known my condition and believing the doctor I have decided to donate this fund to avoid total loss to church, Less privilege, or better still a Christian individual that will utilize this money the way I am going to instruct herein. I want interested church or individual that will receive and use this money to help churches, orphanages ,widows and propagating the Gospel and to ensure that the house of God is maintained. Please do not fail to spread the funds across the globe especially AFRICA as soon as you receive the money. The Bible made us to understand that it is more blessed to give than to receive. I took this decision because I don't have any child that will inherit this money and my husband relatives are fighting over the properties and I don't want my husband's hard earned money to be misused by their greedy attitude. I don't want a situation where this money will be used in an UNGODLY manner, hence the reason for taking this bold decision. I am not afraid of death since I am a good christian. I know that I am going to be in the bosom of the Lord. Exodus 14 VS 14 says that the lord will fight my case and I shall hold my peace. I don't need any telephone communication in this regard because of my health, and because of the presence of my husband's relatives around me always. I don't want them to know about this development. With God all things are possible. As soon as I receive your reply I shall give you the contact information of the bank and other details that will enable you claim the funds.please i want you to be aware that according to my attorney there are some important document that will be required by the bank for the transfer this is where i will need your little assistance before the fund can be transfer with the help of my attorney. I will also issue you a letter of authority/Power of Attorney that will make you the beneficiary of this fund. I want you to always pray for me because the lord is my shepherd. My happiness is that I lived a life of a worthy Christian. Whoever that wants to serve the Lord must serve him in spirit and truth. Please always be prayerful all through your life. I sent you this mail under severe pains. Any delay in your reply will be detrimental. Please assure me that you will act accordingly. Hoping to hear from you immediately. Remain blessed in the name of the Lord. Yours in Christ, Mrs. Rama idris.

>From Mr collins ngobe bank of africa cotonou Plot 15 rue 17 port novo Benin republic west Africa Tel/+229 459050 Attn; Director Dear sir I am Mr Collins Ngobe . I am accounting officer in foriegn accounts department in our bank.During our last auditing in our Bank,My Department came across a very huge sum of money (6.5 million dollars)six million five hundred thousand dollars,belonging to a deceased customer of our Bank a national of your country,who died in the plane crash of 31 october 1999[Egyptian airline 990] with other passengers aboard confirmable at this,WEB-SITE(www.cnn.com/us/9911/02/egyptair990.list/index.html). Since then I have made several enquiries to your embassy to locate any of our clients extended relatives, this has proved unsuccessful.After these several unsuccessful attempts, I decided to trace his relatives over the Internet, to locate any of his family member but of no avail. hence I contacted you for similarety of your name with that of our late customer. I need your assistance in evacuation of the funds left behind by our client in the Bank before they get confisicated or declared unserviceable by the Government, because official, financial laws here stipulate it that after five years any fund or assets deposited with bank/security firm without claim or servicing, the money or assets will be divert to central bank as unclaime bill. since I have been unsuccesfull in locating the relatives for over 2 years now, I seek your concent to present you as the next of kin of the deceased since you are from the same country so that the proceeds of this deposit valued at $6.5 million dollars can be paid to you and then you will share me part of the money, I have all necessary legal documents that can be used to back up claim we may make. All I require is your honest cooperation to enable us see this deal through. I guarantee that this business will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. You have to assure me that you will not sit on the fund when it is finally claimed. expecting your quick response Best regards,

Mr. Donga Kabaka. P. O. Box 241. Sharjah, United Arab Emirate UAE Email:dongakabaka555@yahoo.com Dear Sir/Madam You may be surprised to receive this letter from me since you do not know me personally. For the purpose of introduction, I am Mr. Donga Kabaka, the son of Dr. James Kabaka, a wealthy black farmer/politician in Zimbabwe who was murdered in the land dispute in my country. The land problem, in our country came when our President Mr. Robert Mugabe in a bid to win his re-election, introduced a new Land Act Reform wholly affecting the rich white farmers and the black farmers who are members of the opposition (MDC) party. This resulted in killings and mob action by Zimbabwean war veterans and some lunatics in the society. It is against this background that I and my immediate family had fled Harare our capital for fear of our lives and are currently staying in a country side of United Arab Emirate. We are planning to leave the country and seek political asylum in Europe and we have decided to move our family wealth to Europe. We got your contact through the Internet based on our urgent need for a dependable and trustworthy foreign partner and hence decided to write to you. Before the death of my late father, he had taken me to United Aram Emirate several times and had deposited the total sum of US$20.5 million (Twenty million, Five Hundred thousand United States dollars), in one of the private security companies, as he foresaw the looming danger in Zimbabwe. This money was deposited in two boxes as Family Treasures to avoid much demurrage from the security company. This amount was meant for the purchase of new machines and chemicals for the Farms and the establishment of new farms in Swaziland. As the eldest son of my father, I am saddled with the responsibility of seeking a genuine partner that could assist us without the knowledge of my government who are bent on taking everything we have got, and the United Arab Emirate seems to be playing along with them. I am faced with the dilemma of moving this amount of money out of United Arab Emirate for fear of going through the same experience in future. We are seeking a partner whom I have to entrust my future and that of my family in his/her hands. To this end, we need your assistance to stand as the Beneficiary of the Consignments in Europe. This is because we are under restricted movement and watch and hence we want to be very careful in order not to lose this fund, which we have worked so hard for. I have a sufficient CONTACT person at the Security Company in United Arab Emirate who can help us move this money to Europe under DIPLOMATIC COVER to another Security Company in Europe with your details as the Beneficiary. This is 100% legal and will not pass through normal Customs/Airport Screening. Thus, if you are willing to assist us to move this fund out of UAE, you can contact me through my email address with your telephone, fax number and personal information to enable us discuss further details. I must let you know that this transaction is risk free as far as we keep it as confidential as possible. Thank you and many blessings to you. Yours Faithfully, Mr. Donga Kabaka.

Dear Sir, I got your esteemed address from the internet during my search for a reliable Individual/company who can jointly handle strictly confidential transaction with me which involves a reasonable sum of money. Due to the nature of this business transaction, a neutral person like you is preferred. For introductory purpose, I am JAMES Momodu Pujeh, The son of Momdu Pujeh, former transport and communications minister in Sierra Leone who has been recently convicted for two years for illegally possessing 638.81 carats of diamonds valued at $36,500. My father was sacked in November 2001 after the Anti-Corruption Commission alleged that he and my mother had been involved in diamond trafficking in Kenema, in the eastern part of Sierra Leone. My father won a seat in parliamentary elections held last year but is expected to resign following his conviction. My mother, Mary Momodu, is under investigation on a similar charges. You may have heard how a lot of my father's bank account in Switzerland and North America has been frozen. Following the outlined reasons for investigation, I am soliciting for your esteemed organization's confidential assistance to take custody of Thirteen Million, five hundred thousand United States Dollars (US$13,500,000.00) and also to front for my family in the areas of business you consider profitable. These Consignments containing the funds have secretly been concealed and deposited with a Diplomatic Security firm where it can easily be taken delivery of by a recommended beneficiary. The consignment containing the funds will be released to your organization by the Security firm based on my recommendations on that note; you will be presented as our partner who will be fronting for me and my family in any subsequent ventures. I have made my first visit to the security company and the document entitled to clear this money is with a finance security company in Holland. On our arrival in the Netherlands few weeks ago, we sought for political asylum; which was granted. Already, my sister and I are making frantic effort on the best way to handle this money. We sought advice from an attorney who advised that we must seek for a trustworthy foreign business partner whom can invest this fund in a profitable venture. This we view as the best option because our refugee status dose not permit us to operate a bank account, hence we seek your assistance and hope you could be trusted. Meanwhile, I sincerely ask for your assistance to get this money through your account. I and my mother have decided to give 25% to your organization if you are able to help us claim this consignment. And 5% will be use for upsetting all the expenses incurred in the course of concluding this venture and the remaining 70% that will be for me and my family. Please, I need your entire support and co-operation for the success of this business ventures, your utmost confidentiality and secrecy is highly required, due to my family's present predicament. Also you stand to gain from any investment you might introduce us into after the conclusion of the transfer. Please keep this confidential until we finalize and get this money into your account for security reasons. I am presently in the refugee camp here in the Netherlands under the United Nations and I can be reached by responding to the following email address: jamepuj2@zwallet.com jamepuj@fsmail.net Kind regards, Mr. James Momodu

Hello my beloved kind hearted, THIS IS HUMANITERIAN SERVICE THAT REQUIRES YOUR ATTENTION! I simply want to take this occasion to tell you about my intention to contribute toward the fight against Cholera and HIV/AIDS and I need your help as my representative overseas. I need you to receive my financial entitlements from my financiers overseas on my behalf for the fight against Cholera and HIV/AIDS and hope you would not let me down. It might interest you to know that in my supporting role to the Minister of Public Works here in Pretoria, South Africa it is my responsibility to handle some very intrinsic matters for, on behalf or with the Minister. By my duties, it is almost impossible for any file/Contract Proposals to get to the Minister for approval, without it passing through my scrutiny. By my religious status and as the South African Deputy Minister of Public Works, I have cause to help a lot of foreign contractor-companies (mainly American) to secure the release of their entitlements from the coffers of the government of South Africa. I did this, principally, as a help to the concerned companies, but in appreciation of my efforts, most of them committed themselves to paying some handsome monetary honorarium to me. However, because of my position as a political appointee, it is impossible for me to collect such money immediately or even directly. Hence, I need you to collect this money on my behalf and use it as you would be further directed for the fight against Cholera and HIV/AIDS. Of course your effort will not be in vain. You would be well rewarded for your help in this regards. All the money from the various companies put together is totaling amount to Eight Hundred and Fifty Five Thousand United States Dollars (US$855,000) only. The snag is that I just discovered that I couldn't collect this money, directly, from these companies in my name or the name of any of my family members, because government will investigate "why?" and "what for? Therefore, to forestall any such problems, I decided to contact you through this secured and private medium, to solicit your assistance in this regard. You will receive this money on my behalf, and use it as you would be further directed. That way, there will be no link between the companies and me. I will instruct the concerned companies to make the money available to you on installment either via swift means or by cheque as you so desire of not more than $75,000, as the case may be. >From the money you receive on my behalf, you would be entitled to retaining 10% of the sum while you would be required to wire the balance 90% for its purpose of humanitarian services as would be advised. For example, if you receive $75,000, you would be required to retain 10% ($7,500) while you wire the balance $67,500 for its purpose. This is basically on trust. It is a simple job you do for me and all expenses for the cost of transfer of funds would be from the 90% and you will not spend a single cent from your money to actualize this project. No financial commitment from you and it's simple and risk free. You receive the money on my behalf, take away your 10% and redirect the remaining 90% as would be instructed. I can assure you that if you keep to our agreement, this will be the beginning of a mutually beneficial relationship between the two of us. Afterward, there are a lot of other things we can do together that will fetch you a fortune. If you are interested and would like to work with me for the fight against Cholera and HIV/AIDS, I would need you to provide me with the following: (1) IF YOU DESIRE TO HAVE THE PAYMENT BY SWIFT MEANS: Provide me with: a). Name of your bank. b) Address of your bank. c) Bank Telephone and Fax. d) Account Number. e) Swift Code/Routing Number. d)Account Names. (2).OTHERWISE, IF YOU DESIRE TO HAVE THE PAYMENT BY CHECK: Then, you do not have to provide your banking information. Simply provide me with: a) Your full names (As would be on the check). b) Contact/Mailing address c) Your Telephone and Fax Number. Furthermore, as surety for the money that would be paid to you on my behalf, I would need a scanned copy of your International Passport or Drivers License for record purpose. When I receive all the aforementioned, I will then send a working AGREEMENT between you and I, to guide and guard this relationship. Once all these are sorted out, I will notify the first company of my desire to receive my money through you and instruct them accordingly. In conclusion: I wish to draw your attention to the wise observation of Marlene Gill, who wrote: "To exist is to change, To change is to mature, To mature is to go on creating one's self endlessly," As we continue to change and to mature as individuals and as a nation, let us continue to dream that one-day, very soon, Cholera and HIV/AIDS will no longer devastate our nation, that all of our young people will resort to responsible behavior and that the moral values of our forebears will once more dominate our society. LET US DARE TO DREAM. For it is not an impossible dream. This is simply from my heart to you. I wish you the very best while giving my thanks in anticipation of a lasting business relationship with you. Kindly send the requirements as mentioned above via my private email addresses as stated. My regards, K. M. ZONDI (REV), Deputy Minister of Public Works, Central Government Building, 6th Floor, Room 623, cnr Bosman and Vermeulen St., Pretoria, SOUTH AFRICA. Email (PRIVATE): revmzondi@netscape.net INTERNET (PROFILE): http://www.gov.za/gol/gcis_profile.jsp?id=1075

SHELL PETROLEUM DEVELOPMENT COMPANY 44 MARINA, LAGOS NIGERIA. OUR REF.SPDC/03 ATTENTION: THE MANAGING DIRECTOR, SIR, FIRST, I MUST SOLICIT YOUR CONFIDENCE IN THIS TRANSACTION, THIS IS BY VIRTUE OF ITS NATURE AS BEING CONFIDENTIAL. I AM ASSURING YOU THAT ALL WILL BE WELL AT THE END OF HE DAY. WE HAVE DECIDED TO CONTACT YOU BY E-MAIL DUE TO THE URGENCY OF THIS TRANSACTION. LET ME START BY INTRODUCING MY SELF PROPERLY TO YOU. I AM MR DANJUMA WILLIAMS M, THE AUDITOR OF THE SHELL PETROLEUM DEVELOPMENT COMPANY (SPDC). I CAME TO KNOW OF YOU IN MY PRIVATE SEARCH FOR A RELIABLE AND REPUTABLE PERSON TO HANDLE THIS CONFIDENTIALTRANSACTION WHICH INVOLVES THE TRANSFER OF THE SUM OF NINE-FIVE MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS WITH SECURITY COMPANY IN EUROPE. THIS AMOUNT WAS SECURED FROM EXCESS OIL SALES FROM NIGERIA CRUDE OIL. THE SUM OF $1.2 BILLION OIL WINDFALL WAS RELIEZED BY THE SHELL PETROLEUM DEVELOPMENT COMPANY FOR THE MONTH OF AUGUST 2003.ORGANISATION OF PETROLEUM EXPORTING COUNTRIES (OPEC) CRUDE OIL PRICE WAS PEG AT $22.00 PER BARREL AND FORTUNATELY FOR OIL PRODUCING COUNTRIES LIKE NIGERIA, THERE WAS RISES IN OIL PRICE TO ABOUT $27.00 AND $28.00 PER BARREL AND AS A RESULT THERE WAS EXCESS OIL SALES AND I BELIEVE YOU WOULD BE AWARE OF THIS RISE IN OIL PRICE THIS YEAR. OUT OF THESE $1.2 BILLION EXCESS OIL FUNDS, MY COLLEAQUES AND MYSELF DECIDED TO CONTACT YOU, BECAUSE OF OUR POSITION IN THE ACCOUNT DEPARTMENT OF THE SHELL PETROLEUM DEVELOPMENT COMPANY DIVERTED THE SUM OF NINE-FIVE MILLION UNITED STATE DOLLARS, WE AGREED TO TRANSFER THIS SUM INTO YOUR NOMINATED ACCOUNT, THE EXCESS CRUDE OIL SALES IS BEING KEPT WITH SECURITY COMPANY IN EUROPE. TO ENABLE THE SECURITY COMPANY PAY YOU THIS THIRTY-FIVE MILLION U.S DOLLARS YOU WILL BE ACTING AS ONE OF OUR CONTRACTOR AND THIS MONEY WILL BE PAID IN YOUR FAVOUR. NOTE, THE REASON FOR THE PAYMENT OF THIS THIRTY-FIVE MILLION U.S DOLLARS INTO YOUR HAND WILL BE FOR A MOBILISATION FEE FOR A CONTRACT THAT IS AWARDED TO YOU BY MY COMPANY THE SHELL PETROLEUM DEVELOPMENT COMPANY. ALL THE NECESSARY DOCUMENTATION FOR THE APPROVAL OF THIS FUND WILL BE TAKEN GOOD CARE OF AND THIS BUSINESS IS 100% RISK FREE AS ALL THE MODALITIES FOR THE SMOOTH PAYMENT OF THIS FUND INTO YOUR HAND HAS BEEN CONCLUDED ALREADY. 1)THAT THIRTY PERCENT (30%) WILL BE FOR YOU FOR HELPING US RECEIVING THIS FUND. 2)THAT TEN PERCENT (10%) WILL BE MAPED OUT FOR REIMBURSEMENT FOR ANY EXPENSES INCURED BY THE TWO PARTIES (YOUR PARTY AND MY PARTY) DURING THE TRANSFER OF THIS FUND INTO YOUR ACCOUNT. 3)THAT SIXTY PERCENT WILL BE FOR MY PARTY, WHICH I WELL USE TO IMPORT YOUR COMPANIES PRODUCTS INTO MY COUNTRY. TO ENABLE US PROCEED WITH THIS BUSINESS, YOU ARE URGENTLY REQUIRED TO SEND ME YOUR DIRECT PHONE AND FAX NUMBERS, REPLY TO MY PRIVATE E-MAIL(danjumawilliams@fsmail.net) NUMBER SO THAT WE CAN APPLY FOR IMMEDIATE PAYMENT OF THIS FUND INTO YOUR HAND, WAITING TO RECEIVE YOUR IMMEDIATE REPLY. YOURS FAITHFULLY, MR DANJUMA WILLIAMS M, THE AUDITOR OF SHELL PETROLEUM DEVELOPMENT COMPANY

INVESTMENT RELATIONSHIP REQUEST!!! >From Tabel D. Micheal Hello Dear One, I am Tabel Djedje Michael 23yrs and my younger sister is Maria Micheal 19yrs, we are the only children of late Dr .and Mrs. Djedje Michael our late father was a former Minister of Interieur (in Ivory Coast) and he was a very wealthy Merchant and Politician with a good name in Abidjan the Economic Capital of Ivory Coast. Our father was a victim of the recent political unrest in this Country, he was assasinated on 20th september 2002 in our house in Abidjan, that same day we excape death because we were in the Church that fateful morning, our house was also burnt down by these evil agents government, futhermore our mother died some 2 years ealier and since then our father had took us so special and did not re-marry and we have an aged grandmother who is 69 years of old, which our father was her only son. Mrs Lim S. Tsing is a pen friend who work with an information center in Japan,she recommended group contacts for us and of which your contacts was among and we chose to contact you for this business relationship, our main purpose of sending your this mail is because of the way we found you and perhaps trustworthy to give you this priority of transfering our funds to you, We inherited the sum of (11.183Millions Us Dollars) from our late father, this funds is presently in a AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK in REPUBLIC OF BENIN, may you provide an active personal or Company bank account into which this funds can be transfered into for onward investment. Before the death of our father on September 20th,2002, He secretly told us that he has the sum of US$11.183(eleven million one hundred and eight three thousand dollars) left in suspence/fixed deposit Trustee account in a AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK in REPUBLIC OF BENIN, that he used my name as his next of kin and the beneficiary to this said the funds, he also told us that we should seek for a reliable foreign partner in your country where we can transfer this funds to and invest it in a valuable venture while we continue our Education there. Because we are still very young some unfaithful Persons who claim to be our late father's partners have taking away many of our father's assets and have being trying to pin us down dead so that they can have access to the document covering this funds, then we ran into hidout location here REPUBLIC OF BENIN. >From this you can see that our lives are not save here as we are presently in hide out location so your assistance is highly needed and with sense of urgence and we will highly appreciate your care at the successful end of this transaction. Please, we are honourably seeking your assistance in the following ways : 1. To provide an active Company or Personal bank account into which this funds would be transfered into for onward Investment there in your country. 2. To take care of the investment of the funds/and be a Co-Beneficiary of the funds to enable us to be able to make the transfer. 3. To make arrangement for us, me Tabel, my little sister Maria and our Grand-mother Mama Micheal to come over to your country to stay and further our education 4 Secure Residence permit in your country. 5. To help us look for funds managers to manage the funds at the successful end of the transfer. 6. To provide Investment plan for this funds with the help of experts. 7. To Fund the transfer process. Moreover, we'll offer you any percentage of which we shall chat soon as this becomes a successful transfer of this fund into your personal or company nominated account overseas. Further more, if this transaction intrest you reply this email message. We Anticipating to hear your Favourable respond. Thanks and May God bless you. Best regards, Tabel and Maria Djedje Michael 00 229 280 899. ------------------------------------------ Faites un voeu et puis Voila ! www.voila.fr

Heru Nurwarsito Col (Ret) David Wong. OCBC Bank Singapore. www.ocbc.com PRIVATE AND URGENT. I am contacting you on a business transfer of a hugh sum of money from a deceased account. Though I know that a transaction of this magnitude will make any one apprehensive and sceptical, but I am assuring you that its been accurately planned and will be carried out successfully with your full cooperation as long as you follow our plans and instructions religiously. We decided to contact you due to the urgency of this transaction. PROPOSITION; We discovered an abandoned sum of US$25,500,000.00 ( twenty million five hundred thousand united states dollars) in an account that belongs to one of our foreign customers who died along with his entire family. Since his death, none of his next-of-kin or relations has come forward to lay claims for this money as the heir. We cannot release the fund from his account unless someone applies for claim as the next-of-kin to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines. Upon this discovery, we now seek your permission to have you stand as a next of kin to the deceased as all documentations will be carefully worked out by us for the funds (US$25,500,000.00) to be released in your favour as the beneficiary's next of kin through my banks funds managers/clearing house overseas. It may interest you to know that we have secured from the probate an order of madamus to locate any of deceased beneficiaries. Please acknowledge receipt of this message in acceptance of our mutual business endeavour by furnishing me with the following; 1. Beneficiary Name and Address. 2. Direct Telephone and fax numbers. These requirements will enable us file letter of claim to the appropriate departments for necessary approvals in your favour before the transfer can be made. We shall be compensating you with two million dollars on final conclusion of this project, while the rest shall be for us. Your share stays while the rest shall be for us for investment purposes. If this proposal is acceptable by you, do not take undue advantage of the trust we have bestowed in you,please contact me directly as i await your urgent mail. Regards, Heru. Col. Wong

Phone Number 882-1646685262. Private Email GOD_BEE_WITH_US@YAHOO.CO.UK. I Need Your Urgent Reply. {MONEY TRANSACTION} Dear Sir,Madam My name is Mr.Cyril Beko, and I work in the International operation department in a Local Bank here in South Africa. On a routine inspection I discovered a dormant domiciliary account with a BAL. Of 36,000,000 (Thirty Six Million USD) on further discreet investigation, I also discovered that the account holder has long since passed away (dead) leaving no beneficiary to the account. The bank will approve this money to any foreigner because the former operator of the a/c is a foreigner and from Iraq in particular and I am certainly sure that he is dead, and nobody will come again for the claim of this money A foreigner can only claim this money with legal claims to the account Holder; therefore I need your cooperation in this transaction. I will provide the necessary information needed in order to claim this money, But you will need to open an account where this can be transferred. If interested send your private Telephone No. And Fax number including full details of the account to be used for the Deposit I wish for utmost confidentiality in handling this transaction as my job and the future of my family would be jeopardized if it were breached. I want to assure you that the transaction is without risk if due process is followed accordingly. Finally, I will give you 25% for your corporation. I look forward to your earliest reply through this email or my private mail:GOD_BEE_WITH_US@YAHOO.CO.UK.You should try to call me on my satelite phone no. 882-1646685262. I look forward to a favorable response from you. Yours Mr.Cyril. ________________________________________________________________________ BT Yahoo! Broadband - Save £80 when you order online today. Hurry! Offer ends 21st December 2003. The way the internet was meant to be. http://uk.rd.yahoo.com/evt=21064/*http://btyahoo.yahoo.co.uk

Mr. James Nicholas Calabar, Dear Prospective Business Partner, I am e-mailing to you this business proposition having gone through your remarkable profile on the internet. Though, this medium (Internet) has been greatly abused, I choose to reach you through it because it still remains the fastest, surest and most secured means for me to communicate with you at this time. However, this correspondence is unofficial and private, and it should be treated as such. Official telephone calls and fax messages to me WILL NOT be entertained for security reasons and for the success of this project. For further briefing, you can reach me only via my private email address as stated below or through my lawyer whose contact shall be provided to you in due cause. My name is Mr. James Nicholas. I am the chief financial controller to Mr. Charles Taylor, the ex-president of Liberia who is presently on exile in Nigeria. As his private financial controller, I have access to his financial records more than any of his family members. Mr Charles Taylor has over $1 billion dollars outside Liberia and his family members or people around him are not aware of this. With his present notion of arrest and following his restricted movement and the recent proclamation by Zurich authority, the U.N war crimes court and the America Government, has agreed that all Bank account belonging to Charles Taylor should be reported and freezed. Therefore I want to use this opportunity to make good money for myself. I have worked for him for over 10 years and I have nothing to show for it. I am only leaving on his empty promises and hopes. Presently, I have complete information to authorize with documents for collecting /receiving $200 million from one of his financial sources in South Africa. And I need your assistance in receiving the funds in Europe on my behalf. Charles Taylor has prepared himself legally and secretly arranged with Top most Government agents to transfer the funds upon instructions. In light of the above, I am seeking your cooperation to act as the authorized beneficiary of the said funds to enable us claim the funds for our mutual benefit. As you probably already aware, Mr. Charles Taylor maybe handed over by his host country to the new Liberia Government to face trial soon hence the need for urgent attention to this matter. Your prompt responce to my proposal will be highly appreciated. As soon as I receive your geniue intention to cooperate with me, I will have my lawyer provide you with the necessary details as required to enable us conclude this transaction successfully. I thank you and look forward to hearing from you shortly. Regards James Nicholas please reply via my private e-mail below. e-mail: jnicholas@zwallet.com .......................................... Because of charles Taylors notion of arrest, and with the present development the security alert-ness is higher, so I will introduced my lawyer to you upon your responce to my proposal.

DR.WAHID MALLAM CITI TRUST BANK PLC FAX: 234-1-7592758 E-MAIL: foreignoperations@cititrust-bank.com ATTN: THE PRESIDENT/CEO I AM THE DIRECTOR IN CHARGE OF FOREIGN OPERATIONS AND FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPARTMENT OF THE CITI TRUST BANK OF NIGERIA PLC. I AM WRITING FOLLOWING THE IMPRESSIVE INFORMATION ABOUT YOU THROUGH ONE OF MY FRIENDS WHO RUNS A CONSULTANCY FIRM. HE ASSURED ME OF YOUR CAPABILITY AND RELIABILITY TO CHAMPION THIS BUSINESS OPPORTUNITY. IN MY DEPARTMENT, WE DISCOVERED AN ABANDONED SUM OF US$20.5M (TWENTY MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS ONLY) IN AN ACCOUNT THAT BELONGS TO ONE OF OUR FOREIGN CUSTOMERS WHO DIED ALONG WITH HIS ENTIRE FAMILY IN NOVEMBER 2001 IN A PLANE CRASH SINCE WE GOT INFORMATION ABOUT HIS DEATH, WE HAVE BEEN EXPECTING HIS NEXT OF KIN TO COME OVER AND CLAIM HIS MONEY BECAUSE WE CANNOT RELEASE IT UNLESS SOMEBODY APPLIES FOR IT AS NEXT OF KIN OR RELATION TO THE DECEASED AS INDICATED IN OUR BANKING GUIDELINES. UNFORTUNATELY WE LEARNT THAT ALL HIS SUPPOSED NEXT OF KIN OR RELATIONS DIED ALONG WITH HIM AT THE PLANE CRASH LEAVING NOBODY BEHIND FOR THE CLAIM. IT IS THEREFORE UPON THIS DISCOVERY THAT I AND OTHER OFFICIALS IN THE DEPARTMENT NOW DECIDED TO MAKE BUSINESS WITH YOU AND RELEASED THE MONEY TO YOU AS THE NEXT OF KIN OR RELATION OF THE DECEASED FOR SAFETY AND SUBSEQUENT DISBURSEMENT SINCE NOBODY IS COMING FOR IT AND WE DON'T WANT THIS MONEY TO GO DISBURSEMENT ACCOUNT AS UNCLAIMED BILL. THE BANKING LAW AND GUIDELINES HERE STIPULATED THAT IF SUCH MONEY REMAINED UNCLAIMED AFTER FOUR YEARS, THE MONEY WILL BE TRANSFERRED INTO FEDERAL GOVERNMENT ACCOUNT AS UNCLAIMED FUND. THE REQUEST OF A FOREIGNER AS NEXT OF KIN IN THIS BUSINESS IS OCCASIONED BY THE FACT THAT THE CUSTOMERS WAS A FOREIGNER AND A NIGERIAN CANNOT STAND AS NEXT OF KIN TO A FOREIGNER. WE AGREE THAT 30% OF THIS MONEY WILL BE FOR YOU AS FOREIGN PARTNER AND 10% FOR EXPENSES INCURRED DURING THE COURSE OF REMITTANCE. THEREAFTER TO THE PERCENTAGES INDICATED. THEREFORE TO ENABLE THE IMMEDIATE TRANSFER OF THE FUND TO YOU AS ARRANGED. YOU MUST APPLY FIRST TO THE BANK AS A RELATION OR NEXT OF KIN OF THE DECEASED INDICATING YOUR BANK ACCOUNT NUMBER AND LOCATION WHERE THE MONEY WILL BE REMITTED. UPON RECEIPT OF YOUR REPLY I WILL SEND TO YOU THE TEXT OF THE APPLICATION. AS SOON AS YOU RECEIVE THIS LETTER, YOU SHOULD CONTACT ME AT ONCE THROUGH MY E-MAIL SECURED ADDRESS: foreignoperations@cititrust-bank.com TRUSTING TO HEAR FROM YOU IMMEDIATELY. YOURS FAITHFULLY, DR.WAHID MALLAM HEAD: FOREIGN OPERATIONS.

BARRISTER BASIL EZE. NWOKES CHAMBERS. SUITE 109 OKON HOUSE MARINA VI LAGOS-NIGERIA. E-MAIL: bakko_bakko@yahoo.com Dear friend, I am Barrister basil eze personal attorney to Mr.Jeff Baroco, a national of your country, who used to work with Shell Development Company here in Nigeria herein after, shall be referred to me as my client. On the 21st of April 2001,my client, his wife and their three children were involved in a ghastly motor accident along Warri-Sagbama Express road. Unfortunately, all occupants of the vehicle lost their lives as the vehicle caught fire after the crash. Since then I have made several inquiries to your embassy to locate any of my clients extended relatives this has also proved unsuccessful. After these several unsuccessful attempts, I decided to track his last name over the Internet, to locate any member of his family hence I contacted you. My purpose of contacting you is to assist in repatriating the money and property left behind by my client prior to his death before they get confiscated or declared unserviceable by the bank where this huge deposits were lodged particularly, the CITY TRUST BANK where the deceased had an account valued at about US$12Million dollars. The bank had issued me a notice to provide the next of kin or have the account confiscated within the next thirty official working days. Since I have been unsuccessful in locating the relatives for over 2 years now I seek your consent to present you as the next of kin of the deceased since you have the same last name/surname so that the proceeds of this account valued at US$12 million dollars can be paid to you and then we can share the money afterwards. I have all the necessary official and legal documents that can be used to back up the claim we may make. All I require is your honest co-operation to enable us inseeing this deal through. I guarantee that this will be executed under legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. For your sevices you will have 35% of the total sum, while 5% have been mapped out for the orphanage Homes. Please get in touch with me by my email address no: bakko_bakko@yahoo.com Best regards, BARRISTER BASIL EZE.

DEAR PARTNER I GUESS THIS LETTER MAY COME TO YOU AS SURPRISE SINCE I HAD NO PREVIOUS CORRESPONDENCE WITH YOU. I AM THE CHAIRMAN TENDER BOARD OF INDEPENDENT NATIONAL ELECTORAL COMMISSION (INEC). I GOT YOUR CONTACT IN MY SEARCH FOR A RELIABLE PERSON TO HANDLE A VERY CONFIDENTIAL TRANSACTION INVOLVING THE TRANSFER OF THE SUM OF $30,000.000 D0LLARS (THIRTY MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS) THE ABOVE FUND IS NOT CONNECTED WITH ARMS, DRUGS OR MONEY LAUNDERING. IT IS THE PRODUCT OF AN OVER INVOICED CONTRACT AWARDED IN 1999 BY INEC TO A FOREIGN COMPANY FOR THE SUPPLY OF ELECTORAL MATERIALS THAT WERE USED FOR CONDUCTING 1999 ELECTION. THE CONTRACT HAS LONG BEEN EXECUTED AND PAYMENT OF THE ACTUAL CONTRACT AMOUNT HAS BEEN PAID TO THE FOREIGN CONTRACTOR LEAVING THE BALANCE OF US30 MILLION DOLLARS WHICH MY COLLEAGUES AND I NOW WANT TO TRANSFER OUT OF NIGERIA INTO A RELIABLE FOREIGN ACCOUNT FOR OUR PERSONAL USE. AS CIVIL SERVANTS WE ARE NOT ALLOWED TO RUN FOREIGN ACCOUNTS. HENCE WE HAVE CHOSEN TO FRONT AND SUPPORT YOU AS THE BENEFICIARIES TO BE PAID. IF YOU ARE INTERESTED IN THE PROPOSAL KINDLY GET BACK TO ME BY SENDING ME YOUR LETTER OF ACCEPTANCE ALONG WITH YOUR DIRECT TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBERS, WE HAVE DECIDED TO SHARE THE MONEY IN THE FOLLOWING PERCENTAGE, 60% FOR US 30% FOR YOU THE ACCOUNT OWNER AND 10% FOR ALL LOCAL AND INTERNATIONAL EXPENSES THAT MAY ARISE IN THE COURSE OF THIS TRANSACTION. FURTHER DETAILS ABOUT THIS TRANSACTION WILL BE DISCUSSED IN THE SUBSEQUENT CORRESPONDECE. THIS TRANSACTION IS STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL BUT 100% RISK FREE. NOTE ALSO THAT THE PARTICULAR NATURE OF YOUR BUSINESS IS IRRELEVANT TO THIS TRANSACTION AND THIS TRANSACTION IS EXPECTED TO BE CONCLUDED WITHIN 21 WORKING DAYS SINCE ALL LOCAL CON ACTS AND ARRANGEMENTS ARE IN PLACE FOR A SMOOTH AND SUCCESSFUL CONCLUSION OF THIS TRANSACTION. CONTACT ME VIA EMAIL WITH YOUR CONTACT TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBERS, SO THAT I CAN CALL YOU FOR A DISCUSSION. THANK YOU AS I AWAIT YOUR RESPONSE. SINCERELY, DR STEVE UWA , PLEASE SEND YOUR RESPONSE TO drsteveuwa@rediffmail.com

OFFICE OF THE CHAIRMAN CONTRACT AWARDING COMMITTEE ECOWAS HEADQUARTERS LOME,REPUBLIC OF TOGO 00228-9077-231 ACCOUNT PROVISION FOR USD45M Greetings!!. Dear, Forgive my indignation if this message comes to you as a surprise and if it might offend you without your prior consent and writing through this channel. I am DR Robinson Dike,The Chairman, Contract Awarding Committee of the ECONOMIC COMMUNITY OF WEST AFRICAN STATES (ECOWAS) with Headquarters in Lome, Togo.I got your information in a business directory from the Internet Website.when I was searching for a reliable,honest and trustworthy person to entrust this business with.I was simply inspired and motivated to pick your contact from the many names and lists in the directory. After discussing my view and your profile with my colleagues,they were very much satisfied and decided to contact you immediately for this mutual business relationship.We wish to transfer the sum of USD45,000,000.00 (Forty-five Million United States Dollars only.)into your personal or company`s bank account. This fund was a residue of the over invoiced contract bills awarded by us for the supply of ammunitions, hard/soft wares,phamaceauticals/medical items,light and heavy duty vehicles, apperals and other administrative logistics etc for the ECOMOG in Sierria-Leone and Liberia during the Peace Keeping Projects. This DEAL was deliberately hatched out and carefully protected with all the attendant lope holes sealed off.As the Chairman of CAC,I have the cooperation and mandate of the Financial Director and the Secretary of the Organisation.We arranged and over invoiced the contract funds supplied by different companies from different countries during the crisis. It was our consensus to seek the assistance of a willing foreigner to provide us with the facilities to transfer this money out of West Africa.This is borne out of our beleif in the non-stable and sporous political nature of this sub-region. The original contractors have been duely paid by the (Central Bank of the West African States)through our bankers-Progress Bank Of Africa Plc Lome Togo. This balance is suspended in the escrow accounts awaiting claims by any foreign company of our choice.We intend to pay out this fund NOW as the organisation is winding up its activities since the aim of returning PEACE to the countries and the coast has been achieved. Based on the laws and ethics of employment,we as civil servants working under this organisation, are not allowed to operate a foreign account.This is the more reason why we needed your assistance to provide an account that can sustain this fund for safe keeping and our future investment with your comprehensive advise,assistance and partnership in your country. It is however agreed,as the account owner in this deal to allow you 30% of the entire sum as compensation, 65% will be held on trust for us while 5% will be used to defray any incidental charges and cost during the course of the transaction. This transaction will be successfully concluded within 10 days if you accord us your unalloyed and due cooperation if you should provide the following: YOUR COMPANY`S NAME WITH COMPLETE ADDRESS,TEL AND FAX NUMBERS.(if available) YOUR COMPLETE MAILING ADRRESS WITH TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBERS. YOUR COMPLETE BANK PARTICULARS;NAME,ADDRESS,ACCOUNT NO,SWIFT CODE,TEL/FAX NOS ETC.. Upon the receipt of this informations,the documents and approval with the texts will be sent to you for confirmaton and then forwarded to the organisation for ratification and subsequent payment. As with the case of all organised (sensitive)and conspired DEALS,we solicit for your unreserved confidentiality and utmost secret in this business. We hope to retire peacefully and lead a honourable business life afterwards.There are no risks involved. I await your urgent response. Yours faithfully, Dr.Robinson Dike.

Dear Sir, How are you and your family today? I hope that you are all okay? I found information about you and decided to contact you for an important assistance. I am Michael Nkomo a citizen of Zimbabwe , but i am contacting from a neiboring country here in IVORY CAOST where i am now sicking political assylum. I am the only son of Kenneth Nkomo, a wealthy farmer and senior politician with the opposition political party in my country, Movement for Democratic Change [MDC]. My father was murdered by our wicked President, Robert Mugabe and I fled my country because I have become his next target to eliminate. My father was a fighter for Justice and a moving force in the MDC, a part wanting to end the several years of brutal dictatorship government of President Robert Mugabe. You will read more stories about President Mugabe's brutal acts by visiting this web sites; http://www.rte.ie/news/2000/0418/zimbabwe.html My father was accused of Treason and also assisting the White farmers in fighting the government. Few weeks after his arrest, he was reported dead. The government claimed he died of heart attack and his body was never seen for proper autopsy, they buried him in the government cemetery. My father's associate Mr. Martin Olds a White farmer from Britain assisted me in fighting my father's death through the Court and media; the government saw us as a big treat to them and decided to eliminate us. Mr. Olds was attacked and murdered in his house, but fortunately, before they came looking for me, I received the news and I had to flee through the border to South Africa to save my life. My arrival here in IVORY COAST still remains like a miracle to me. Here, is my reasons for contacting you, I am having a huge sum of money in the total sum of $13.6Million presently lodge with the security company in holland,My father kept this money in in two trunk boxes in disguise as family treasures and could not bank them, because of the situation in my country. My father's business, farms and banks account were seized by the government before his arrest and murder. He told me everything concerning the funds while he was still in detention and I have made several arrangements concerning the shipment of the boxes out of my country because we cannot invest it there. I was on the process when I fled the country. I need your assistance in securing the funds there in your country, so that I can arrange on how to come overto your country to invest with the fund I am willing to offer you 30% of the $13.6Million for your assistance. Please, let me know if you can assist me, so that I can give you more details on how we shall proceed. As I wait for your urgent response, please treat this information as top secret. Regards, Michael Nkomo Freeserve AnyTime - HALF PRICE for the first 3 months - Save £7.50 a month www.freeserve.com/anytime

PLEASE REPLY TO k_omidire@yahoo.com Good day and a happy and prosperous new year ! I am Kolapo Omidire, company secretary and manager, internal and external services of COMMERCIAL BANK OF AFRICA. I am writing in respect of a foreign customer of my bank who perished with his entire family (His wife and only son) in a plane crash (Korean Air Line 801) on August 6, 1997. Since the demise of this customer of ours , the bank management of COMMERCIAL BANK OF AFRICA has made valuable efforts to get in touch with any of the late customer's Next-of-Kin or relative anywhere in the world but unfortunately, all our efforts did not yield any positive results as no one has come to claim his funds to the tune of Twenty one million, five hundred thousand united states dollars(USD21.5m) which has been with my bank all these while. Recently, the Federal Government of Nigeria directed that all funds not claimed (which has exceeded the stipulated banking period of seven years for such money) should be confiscated to the Federal Government Treasury Because the banking ethics here does not allow such money to stay more than seven years.This means that this money will be recalled to the federal Government treasury as unclaimed after this period, precisely within this first quater of this year. On this note, the chairman of the board of directors of the bank recently called me and told me in confidence and trust to source for a reliable foreigner who would stand as our foreign customer's next of kin. We (myself and the chairman) have reasoned that if we fail to collect this money the Nigerian government will confisticate it and someone else will end up looting it. Thats's why we have decided to contact you, hoping you will prove to be a reliable foreigner to stand as next of Kin to the deceased customer to claim the total fund from his account with the bank so that the proceeds of his account can be paid to you. Be assured that this transaction is risk free and we will do all possible to give it the legal and legitimate backing it requirs so that both parties will be protected from breach of the law both locally and internationally. Upon receipt of your response, I shall furnish you with the next step to take on how you shall prosecute this claim to your account. The entire transaction should be completed within 10 official working days from the day the bank receives your initial application. When you receive this letter, Kindly send me an e-mail signifying Your acceptance or otherwise, include your private Telephone numbers for more explanation and confidential communication. Waiting to hear from you soon, Best Regards, K. Omidire. PLEASE REPLY TO k_omidire@yahoo.com ___________________________________________ Look Good, Feel Good www.healthiest.co.za

Good Day my dear friend, I wish to request for your assistance in a financial Transaction, I decided to contact you, based on a certain issue that is of paramount importance to me. But most importantly, I want you to show your credibility promise that you will be honest and trustworthy to me during my relationship with you, I am, until recently, a first year medical student at the University of Ghana,West Africa. on the 27th of November 2002, in my home town YENDI CAPITAL DAGBON, NORTHERN REGION OF GHANA, some unknown mub attacked and brutal murdering in my family home with the killing of both uncles and aunts including my sister and brothers most expecially my father who was the key target, king or"lion" of Dagbon,Ya-Naa, YAKUBU ANDANI II .WELL YOU CAN FIND OUT BY YOURSELF THROUGH(www.bbcafrica.com) search event on the(regicide in dagbon region of GHANA) . Fortunately for me, I was in school when the attack took place. I equally lost my only sister to the"ABUDU MUBS".When I got home for the remains of my parents,I discovered a document indicating that my late father had deposited $17.7M United States Dollars (Seventeen Million Seven hundred thousand USdollars) in a private security firm in JOHANNESBURG. This money, according to the document, was meant for the building of an ultra modern hospital for me by my late father, when I complete my studies. Upon the discovery of this document , I left GHANA in trace of the private security firm, and the safer of my life to make claims for the mentioned money as the only surviving next of kin to my father. But deliberately, I have decided to keep all my uncles and Aunts out of the issue as none of them will be happy to know I am in possession of such money and decided to invest it with you in your country. I have succeeded in making the people at the security company to believe that I am the next of Kin and all the documents related to it are now with me. I do not know what to do with it but I have decided to contact you to seek your assistance in helping me to take it out to your country or through your account and help me to come to your country to continue my education, so that you will help me to get the money invested until such a time that I will be ready to be in need of it. I am really desperate as I am left alone now in the world. Most importantly, I seriously appeal that you maintain high level of secrecy and confidentiality with the whole transaction. Thanks and may Allah bless and guide you. more details awaits your urgent response. PRINCE ABDULAH RAHMAN ANDANI: NB: I HAVE THE DEPOSIT DOCUMENTS IN MY POSSESSION THAT WAS ISSUED TO MY LATE FATHER BY THE SECURITY FIRM. IF YOU NEED TO HAVE A LOOK AT THEM, PLEASE DO REPLY AS URGENT, FOR ME TO SEND THEM DOWN TO YOU THROUGH YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS, AND ALWAYS WRITE ME THROUGH MY PRIVATE MAIL BOX:abdulah77@netscape.net, please, use only this telephone number +88-216-2166-85-88, and email address for some security reasons. Thanking you in advance for your anticipated kind assistance. regards to you and your entire family members. Prince. Abdullah Rahman Andani. +88-216-2166-85-88 NOTE: ON YOUR INABILITY TO HANDLE THIS TRANSACTION, RESPOND TO ME IMMEDIATELY SO THAT I MAY CONTACT SOMEONE ELSE.

Attn my friend, With due respect and huminity I propose this to you. I wrote to you last time no response and I decided to write you again. I am Mr.Nze Moore from Arab Bank Plc,Benin Rep. During the course of our auditing we discovered the sum of (USD$9.7m) floating in an account opened in this Bank since 1996 and as from 1999 nobody has operated on this account again, and after going through some old files in the records I discovered that the owner of the account died without a [HEIRE] on oct 31 1999 by plane crash, Egyptair flight 990, (http://www.cnn.com/US/9911/02/egyptair990.list/)hence the money is floating. After due verification I noticed that no other person knows about this account except his wife who was also invovled in the crash, and the account has no other beneficiary and my investigation proved to me as well that until his death he was the Director GOLD ARK [SARL] Since our Bank Arab Bank Plc Benin rep. got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come forward and claim his money because we cannot release it unless somebody applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines and policies but up to date nobody came up to this bank as his next of kin or relative. It is therefore upon this discovery that I and other officials in my department now decided to make this businness proposal to you and release the money to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming forth and we don't want this money to go into the Bank treasury as unclaimed Bill. On this note, I decided to seek for whom his name shall be used as the next of kin as no one has come up as his relation. And the country law here does not allow such money to stay more than Five years, for the money will be recalled to the government treasury as unclaimed after this period. Upon the receipt of your response, I will send to you the application form, bank's contact and the next step to take. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this business is hitch free and that you should not entertain any fear as all modalities for fund transfer can be finalized within five banking days, after you apply to the bank as a relation to the deceased. When you receive this letter, kindly send me an e-mail signifying your decision.Including your private Tel/Fax numbers for quick communication. I will be very happy if you can treat this business with the utmost secrecy it demands because of my position in this bank. Hoping for a very successful business relationship with you. Respectfully submitted, Mr Nze Moore. ALTHENTIVE EMAIL.nze_moore@wp.pl. Tel:00229601483. ------------------------------------------ Faites un voeu et puis Voila ! www.voila.fr

Mr. Zakir Mehmood Soneri Bank Limited Silver Jubilee Center, Britto Road, Garden East, Karachi,pakistan Dear Sir/Madam, I am Zakir Mehmood official of Soneri Bank Limited .This is an urgent and very confidential business proposition. On June 6, 2000,a Foreign Oil consultant/contractor with the pakistan Asian Institute of Mining and Metallurgy, Mr.kassim Hassan made a numbered time(Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at US$26,500,000.00,(Twenty-six Million, five hundred thousand Dollars) in my branch. Upon maturity,I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address,but got no reply. After a month,we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the National Petroleum Corporation that Mr.kassim Hassan died from an automobile accident.On further investigation,I found out that he died without making a WILL,and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr.kassim Hassan did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents,including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$26,500,000.00 has carefully been fixed in my bank for safe keeping. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Asian Law, at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a Foreigner to stand in as the owner of the money which was fixed deposited in my bank. I am writing you because I as a public servant,i cannot operate a foreign account. I want to present you as the owner of the funds so you can be able to claim them with the help of my attorney.This is simple.I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that the Attorney will prepare the necessary documents which will put you in place as the beneficiary of the funds. The money will be moved out for us to share in the ratio of 80% for me and 20% for you. The paperwork for this transaction will be done by the Attorney and this will guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately via my email and Upon your response,I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please observe utmost confidentiality, and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in real estate within your country. Due to the nature of confidentiality in this Transaction our communication can only be via email and fax mostly. Thanks and my regards. Zakir Mehmood. Soneri Bank Limited

George Nduumba, Amsterdam, The Nederlands. Tel: +31 629 315 463                            CONFIDENTIAL BUSINESS PROPOSAL You may be surprised to receive this letter from me since you do not know me personally.I got your contact through network online hence decided to write you. I should have notified you about it at least for the sake of your integrity. Please accept my apology. The purpose of my letter is to seek for foreign assistance with regards my late father money. My name is Laurent Nkono, the first son of  Nkono Banjul ,one of the most popular black farmer in Zimbabwe who was recently murdered in the land dispute in my country. This land problem came when Zimbabwean President Mr. Robert Mugabe introduced a new Land Act Reform wholly affecting the rich white farmers and some few black farmers, and this resulted to the killing and mob action by Zimbabwean war veterans and some lunatics in the society. In fact a lot of people were killed because of this Land reform Act for which my father was one of the victims. . It is against this background that, I and my family fled Zimbabwe for fear of our lives and are currently staying in the Netherlands where we are seeking political asylum. Before the death of my father, he had taken me to Johannesburg to deposit the sum of US8.5 million (Eight million, Five Hundred thousand United States dollars), in one of the private security company, as he foresaw the looming danger in Zimbabwe this money was deposited in a box as gem stones to avoid much demurrage from security company. This amount was meant for the purchase of new machines and chemicals for the Farms and establishment of new farms in Swaziland. Now the family have decided to transfer my father's money to a more reliable foreign account. since the law of Netherlands prohibits a refugee (asylum seeker) to open any bank account or to be involved in any financial transaction throughout the territorial zone of Netherlands, As the eldest son of my father, I am saddled with the responsibility of seeking a genuine foreign account where this money could be transferred without the knowledge of my government who are bent on taking everything we have got. The South African government seems to be playing along with them hence I am faced with the dilemma of moving this amount of money out of South Africa for fear of going through the same experience in future and as you are aware both countries have similar political history. As a businessman, I am seeking for a partner who I have to entrust my future and that of my family in his hands, I must let you know that this transaction is risk free. Due to my current status in the Netherlands My lawyers shall work on my behalf to complete this transaction with you.   If you accept to assist me and my family, all I want you to do for me, is to make an arrangements with the security company to clear the consignment(funds) from their affiliate office here in the Netherlands as I have already given directives for the consignment to be brought to the Netherlands from South Africa. But before then all modalities will have to be put in place like change of ownership to the consignment and more importantly a concrete arrangement for the investment of part of the funds thereafter the clearance from the Security Company. I have two options for you. Firstly you can choose to have your percentage of the money immediately after the funds hit your account, or you can go into partnership with me for the proper profitable investment of the money in your country. Whichever the option you want, it is opened for negotiation. I have also mapped out 5% of this money for all kinds of expenses incurred in the process of this transaction. If you do not prefer a partnership I am willing to give you 15% of the money while the remaining 80% will be for my investment in your country. Please contact me as soon a possible via the above email address,  while I implore you to maintain the absolute secrecy required in this transaction. Thanks, GOD BLESS YOU Yours Faithfully, George Nduumba.     Freeserve AnyTime - HALF PRICE for the first 3 months - Save £7.50 a month www.freeserve.com/anytime

From: Mrs.Susan Martins 101 Jan Smuts Avenue Craighall Johannesburg South Africa Tel:+27-732250444.[Direct] With due respect trust and humility, I write you this proposal, which I believe will be a great interest to you. I found your contact while I was doing a private research on the Internet for a reliable and capable foreign partner that will assist my family and I. That's why I contacted you.I am Mrs. Susan Martins the wife of Mr. John Martins of Zimbabwe.During the current war against famers in Zimbabwe and from the support of our President Robert Mugabe to claim all the white owned farms in our country, all the white and black farmers were ordered to surrender their farms to his party members and his followers. My husband who was one of the best farmers in our country and treasurer of the farmer's Co-operation did not support his idea and so the party members invaded my husband's farms and burnt everything in the farm, killed my husband and made away with a lot of items in my husband's farm. After the death of my husband, my children and I decided to move out of Zimbabwe because our lives were in danger with the fund that my husband kept in his hidden safe in my house. The amount contained in the safe is US$30,5 Million (Thirty Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) and we decided to move this money to the Republic of South Africa, where we deposited it with a private Security Company as a valuables in a box/consignment. This I did for security reasons and to keep from public eyes.I have two options, firstly you can choose to have certain percentage of the money for nominating your account for this transaction, or you can go into partnership with me for proper profitable investment of the money in your country.Whichever the option you want, feel free to notify me. I have also mapped out 5% of this money for all kinds of expenses that might be incured in the process of this transaction. If you do not prefer a partnership, I am willing to give you 20% of the total money, while 75% will be for my family. If you are really capable and willing to assist me as soon as you get this message please contact my son Wodi Martins immediately with the above telephone number (+27-732250444) or by email he knows also about this transaction. for details on how to execute this transaction to the satisfaction of everybody. Finally I want you to know that your ability to keep confidential information about this transaction is very important as all our hope for a better life depends on this money. Best Regard, Mrs.Susan Martins (For The Family)

Attn:The President/CEO I crave your indulgence as I contact you in such a surprising manner. But I respectfully insist you read this letter carefully as I am optimistic it will open doors for unimaginable financial reward for both of us. This business transaction might not fall within the wide spectrum of your business activities, but I plead your assistance, as your flair for profitable business is needed. Permit me to introduce myself,I am Dr Blessed Ogbe the Banking officer to Engr.Johnson Creek who was a major contractor to oil companies,.On the 21st of April 2000,my lient, his wife and their three children were involved in a car accident along Sagamu / Lagos Express Road. Unfortunately they All lost their lives in the event of the accident. Since then I have made several enquiries to your Embassy to locate any of my clients extended relatives, this has also proved unsuccessful. After these several unsuccessful attempts, I decided to trace his relatives over the Internet to locate any member of his family but of no avail, hence I contacted you.I contacted you to assist in repartrating the money and property left behind by my client before they get confiscated or declared unserviceable by the bank where this huge deposits were lodged. Particularly,the Bank where the deceased had an account valued at about US$15.2M (Fifteen Million Two Hundred Thousand United Stated Dollars). Conseqently, the bank issued me a notice to provide the next of kin or have the account confiscated. Since I have been unsuccesfull in locating the the relatives for over 2 years now. I seek your consent to present you as the next of kin of the deceased since you are from the same country so that the proceeds of this account valued at US$15.2million can be paid to you and then you and me can share the money. 60% to me and 40% to you. I have all necessary legal documents that can be used to back up any claim we may make. All I require is your honest co-operation to enable us see this deal through. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. Kindly email your following confidential information to me urgently to enable us proceed: a.Your complete names b.Your private telephone number c.Your private fax number d.Your private email address Please direct your reply to my confidential email:blog333ng@mail.az or through the below fax.You can also reach me through my private telephone number stated below for any enquiries. Upon the receipt of your information,I will advise you on the modalities of the transaction.We have concluded details on how to achieve success. Yours Faithfully, Dr.Blessed Ogbe Position: Operation Director, Pacific International Bank Plc, 40,Marina Rd,Lagos,Nigeria. Tel: 234-803-302-5573 Fax:234-9-272-2046 ___________________________________________ Look Good, Feel Good www.healthiest.co.za

25 Adefobi Street, Ikoyi Island, Lagos.                                                                           FROM:DR.PAUL BUGATI   Dear Sir, I would like to firstly send to you the best wishes of good health and success in your pursuits particularly through my proposal as contained in this letter.   Before going into details of my proposal to you, I must first implore you to treat with the utmost confidentiality as this is required for its success and to have faith in this transaction, for opportunities like this only comes to one once in a life time.

My colleagues and I are senior officials of the Federal Government of my country's Contracts Review Panel (CRP) who are interested in diverting some funds that are presently floating in the accounts of the Apex Bank of my country. In order to commence this transaction, we solicit for your assistance to enable us transfer into your nominated account the said floating funds. We are determined to conclude the transfer before the end of this quarter of 2003 . The source of the funds are as follows: During the last military regime in my country, government officials set up companies and awarded themselves contracts that were grossly over-invoiced in various ministries and parastatals. The present civilian government set up the Contract Review Panel, which has the mandate to use the instruments of payments made available to it by the decree setting up the panel, to review these contracts and if necessary pay those who are being owed outstanding amounts.   My colleagues and I have identified quite a huge sum of these funds, which are presently floating in our (Apex) Central Bank, ready for disbursement and would like to divert some of it for our own purposes.

However, by virtue of our positions as civil servants and members of this panel, we cannot acquire these funds in our names or in the names of companies that are based in my country. I have therefore been mandated, as a matter of trust by my colleagues in the panel, to look for a reliable overseas partner into whose account we can transfer the sum of U.S.$20,500,000.00  (Twenty million, five hundred thousand U.S. dollars). That is why I am seeking your assistance. We have agreed to share the money to be transferred into your account, if you agree with our proposition as follows;   (i) 25% to the account owner (you). (ii) 65% for us (the panel officials). (iii) 10% to be used in settling all expenses (by both you and us) incidental to the actualization of this project.   We wish to invest our share of the proceeds of this project in foreign stock markets and other viable business till we are ready and able to have access to them without raising any eyebrows here at home. Please note that this transaction is 100% safe and risk-free.   We intend to effect the transfer within fourteen (14) banking days from the date of receipt of the following information through the fax number stated above: Your company's name, address, telephone and fax numbers; we will use your company’s name to  apply for the payment and backdate the award of the contract in favour of your company. We are looking forward to doing this transaction with you and we solicit for your utmost confidentiality in this transaction.   I will bring you into a more detailed picture of this transaction when I hear from you. Please get in touch either through my email address above or my American internet FAX number 1 775 535 4598.TEL +234 1 775 7784

 Best regards,    Dr. Paul Bugati

Freeserve AnyTime - HALF PRICE for the first 3 months - Save £7.50 a month www.freeserve.com/anytime

Deutsche Übersetzung unten. ----------------------------- SULE OKETAYO EAGLE BANK PLC suleoketayo@alexandria.cc Dear Sir/Madam, I am Sule Oketayo, the head of the Treasury Department of Foreign Operations Eagle Bank PLC of Nigeria. In my department, I discovered an abandoned sum of US$13,500,000.00 (Thirteen Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) in an account belonging to one of our foreign customers who died along with his entire family in 1998 in an auto crash. This account was open with the bank in 1993 and since 1998 nobody has operated it. After careful investigation, I discovered that the owner of this account was the president of MIRA CONSTRUCTION COMPANY LTD. Despite several attempts by the bank to trace the relatives/next of kin of the deceased, up to date nobody has yet come forward to claim the money. I later discovered that all his supposed next of kin died with him in the auto crash incident. I have spent the last five years monitoring the account and gathering necessary information and documents on it. Now that all papers are ready, I am asking for your assistant to release the money to you as next of kin or relation to the deceased for safekeeping and subsequent sharing. The banking laws of Nigeria stipulates that such money, if unclaimed after five years of maturity, will be transferred into the Central Bank treasury as unclaimed effect. The request for a foreigner as next of kin in this business is occasioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and presenting a Nigerian as the next of kin to a foreigner could raise concerns from the bank management. I am ready to give you 20% of the total sum for your help. 10% will be used to pay off all the necessary fees/charges involved in the transfer. 25% will go to two other officials of Eagle Bank that are with me in this and whose positions will greatly help in expediting the transfer. I will be taking 45%. Please note that these figures are negotiable. After the money has been transferred to your country, I will visit your country for the disbursement/investing of my share according to the percentages we agree upon. Note this transaction requires utmost confidentiality and I am assuring you that it is 100% risk-free so you need not be afraid. I will not contact any other person until I am convinced that you are not interested. Can you please send me your phone and fax number for safer communication when needed. Also please kindly note that all the money to finance this transfer will be provided and you will not be asked to contribute anything. When I hear from you, I will send you an online banking access code with which you can log in to verify the account and balance using the banks online banking website. Best Regards, Sule Oketayo soketayo@alexandria.cc ----------------------- SULE OKETAYO EAGLE BANK PLC soketayo@alexandria.cc Liebe Herr/Frau, Ich bin Sule Oketayo, der Kopf Abteilung der Schatzkammer Ausländischer Betriebe Eagle Bank PLC des Nigerias. In meiner Abteilung, habe ich eine verlassene Summe von US$13,500,000.00 (Dreizehn Millionen, Fünf Hundert Tausend Vereinigten Staaten Dollar) in einer Konto entdeckt, die Ein von unseren ausländischen Kunden gehört, die zusammen mit seiner ganzen Familie in1998 in einem Auto Sturz gestorben sind. Diese Konto war offen mit der Bank in 1993 und, da 1998 niemand es bedient hat. Nachdem vorsichtige Untersuchung, ich entdeckt haben, daß der Eigentümer dieser Kontos der Präsident von MIRA KONSTRUKTION FIRMA LTD.... war. Trotz mehrerer Versuche durch die Bank, dem Verwandten nächstem Verwandtem vom verstorbenen, auf verfzuolgen, niemanden zu datieren, noch ist hervorgetreten, das Geld zu beanspruchen. Ich habe später entdeckt, daß alle sein vermuteter nächster Verwandter mit ihm im Auto Sturz Vorfall gestorben ist. Ich habe überwachende die Konten und die Versammeln von notwendigen Informationen und Dokumente darauf die letzte fünf Jahre ausgegeben. Jetzt, daß alle Papiere bereit sind, ich um Ihren Assistenten bitte, das Geld zu Ihnen freizugeben, als nächster Verwandter oder Verhältnis zum verstorbenen für sichere Verwahrung und folgendes Teilen. Das Bankwesen Gesetze des Nigerias schreibt vor daß solch Geld, wenn nicht beansprucht nachdem fünf Jahre von Reife, werden in die Zentralbank von Nigeria Schatzkammer als nicht beanspruchte Wirkung übertragen werden. Die Bitte für einen Ausländer, als nächster Verwandter in diesem Geschäft von der Tatsache occasioned wird, die der Kunde ein Ausländer und überreichend ein Nigerianer war, als der nächste Verwandte zu einem Ausländer erheben könnte, geht von der Bank Leitung an. Ich bin bereit, Ihnen 20% von der gesamten Summe für Ihre Hilfe zu geben. 10% wird benutzt werden, ab alle notwendigen Gebühren/lädt zu zahlen, die in der Übertragung verwickelt werden. 25% wird zu zwei anderen Beamten von Eagle Bank gehen, der mit mir in diesem ist, und, dessen großartig einstellt, in Beschleunigen wird die Übertragung helfen. Ich werde 45% nehmen. Bitte Notiz, daß diese Figuren veräußerlich sind. Nachdem das Geld auf Ihr Land übertragen worden ist, werde ich Ihr Land für das Auszahlung/investierenden von meinem Anteil gemäß den Prozenten die wir auf besuchen übereinstimmen. Merken Sie diese Verhandlung erfordert, daß äußerste Vertraulichkeit und ich Ihnen zusichere, daß es 100% risikofrei so Sie ist, nicht müssen ängstlich sein. Ich werde andere Person nicht berühren, bis ich überzeugt bin, daß Sie sich nicht interessieren. Können Sie Sie bitte schicken mich Ihr Telephon und Fax zählt für sicherer kommunikationen wenn nötig. Auch bitte gütig Notiz, daß alle Geld zu finanzieren diese Übertragung versorgt werden wird, und Sie werden gebeten werden, nichts beigetragen zu werden. Wenn ich von Ihnen höre, werde ich Ihnen eine Online-Bankwesen Zugriffskennzahl schicken, mit den Sie in loggen können, die Konto zu beglaubigen, und die Ausgleich Gebrauch die Banken Online-Bankwesen Website. Die besten Beachtungen, Sule Oketayo suleoketayo@alexandria.cc

Hello,

I am Mr. Usman Ramat Shehu, Manager with UNITED BANK FOR AFRICAN PLC(U.B.A.).I have a confidential business proposition for you. Our Bank is a financial institution specialising in private banking to individual customers who likes confidentiality in their financial dealings.I have intrest of investing in your company as such i would like to make contact with you for assistance.

On January 13,1987 an Indian-American mining consultant with the Petrogas Gas Systems BV Environmental Systems, Mr. Dixit Shanti made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for Twenty Four calendar months, valued at US$49,500,000.00 (Forty Nine million, Five Hundred Thousand U.S. Dollars) in the Bank. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, that Mr. Dixit Shanti died in the 1988 Lockerbie flight Pan Am 103 plane crash. On further investigation, I found out that he died intestate (without making a WILL), and all attempts to trace his next-of-kin had been fruitless.Please see http://www.geocities.com/capitolhill/5260/passlist.html

I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr. Dixit Shanti did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents with us, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$49,500,000.00 is still sitting in my Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year.

Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr. Dixit Shanti.

This is simple, I will like you to provide your full names and home or office including your telephone and fax numbers so that I can seek the services of a lawyer/Attorney to prepare the necessary documents and court affidavits which will put you in good standing as the next-of-kin.

A bank account in any part of the world which you will provide later will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 80% for me and 20% for you.

Be informed that in other to provide more legality and legitimacy to this project, the paperworks for this will be done by the Attorney and my position as the head of bills and exchange guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please revert back to me.

Please observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country.If you are capable and intrested to do this business with me you reply me in this my email address: usmanramat1@web-mail.com.ar

Thanks and regards.

Mr. Usman Ramat Shehu

Freeserve AnyTime - HALF PRICE for the first 3 months - Save £7.50 a month www.freeserve.com/anytime

Dear Sir, My name is Hartman Onowu,I am the operational manager in account management section incharge of credit and foreign bills of one of the prime banks here in South Africa. I am writing in respect of a foreign customer of my bank who perished with his whole families on 25TH JULY,2000 CONCORDE PLANE CRASH [ Flight AF4590 ] with the whole passengers aboard. There is an account opened in this bank in 1998 by this great late INDUSTRIALIST who died without a written or oral WILL attatched to the account. Since his death , I personally has watched with keen interest to see the next of kin but all has proved abortive as no one has come to claim his funds and no other person knows about this account or anything concerning it,the account has no other beneficiary and until his death he was the manager of his company. The total amount involved is 16,000,000.00 USD.[Sixteen Million United States Dollar ]. We wish to start the first transfer with $6,000,000.00[Six million] and open successful transaction without any disappointment from your side, we shall re-apply for the transfer of the remaining balance to your account. I have secretly discussed this matter with the general manager of the bank who I must involve in order to have a smooth and a successful transfer of the fund to any foreign bank account which you are going to nominate. On this note, I decided to seek for a reliable foreigner who will act as the foreign beneficiary of the fund from the deceased by providing his/her bank account where the fund will be transferred for immediate investment on any viable project as no one has come up to be the next of kin. The banking ethics here does not allow such money to stay more than six years without claim hence the money will be recalled to the government treasury as unclaimed after this long period of domancy. In view of this I got your contact through my personal search to see if you can assist by providing your safe bank account for the transfer or find a reliable person who will be capable of receiving such amount in his or her personal account. At the conclussion of the transfer 65% of the fund will be for me, I will give you 20% of the total transfer sum, 10% for charity both in Africa and in your country while the remaining 5% will be set aside to settle expenses both parties might incure during the transfer process. Upon the receipt of your reply, I will send to you a detailed information about the transaction.I will not fail to bring to your notice that this business is 100% risk and trouble free and that you should not entertain any fear as all modalities for fund transfer can be finalized within 7 to 9 banking days, after you apply to the bank as the beneficiary of the fund from the deceased. When you receive this letter, Kindly send me an e-mail or you can call me or fax me. You should also include your private fax and phone numbers for easy and safe communication. TEL:870-763-648313 :870-763-648314. FAX:870-763-648315. Respectfully yours, Hartman Onowu. __________________________________ Do you Yahoo!? Yahoo! Hotjobs: Enter the "Signing Bonus" Sweepstakes http://hotjobs.sweepstakes.yahoo.com/signingbonus

Attn: Dear Sir, REQUEST FOR YOUR ASSISTANCE IN A FINANCIAL TRANSACTION. I am interested in your partnership in business dealing.This business proposal I wish to intimate you with is of mutual benefit and it's success is entirely based on mutual trust,co-operation and a high level of confidentiality as regards this business transaction. I am representing the board of the contract award and monitoring committee of the South African Ministry of Mining and Resources.I am seeking your assistance to enable me transfer the sum of US$20,000,000.00 (Twenty Million United States Dollars) into your private or company account. The funds came about as a result of a contract awarded and executed for and on behalf of my Ministry.The contract was supposed to be awarded to two foreign contractors to the tune of US$60,000,000.00 (Sixty Million United States Dollars).But in the course of negotiation between my board and the contractor to our benefit,the contract was awarded to a Bulgarian contractor at the cost of US$40,000,000.00(Forty Million United States Dollars).This contract has been satisfactorily executed and inspected as the Bulgarian firm is presently securing payment from my Ministry,where our Board is in-charge of all foreign contract payment approval/disbursement. As a civil servant still in active government service,I am forbidden by law to operate an account outside the shores of South Africa.Hence this message to you seeking your assistance so as to enable me present you or your company as the second contractor of contractual claims alongside that of the Bulgarian contractor,to enable me transfer the difference of US$20,000,000.00 (Twenty Million United States Dollars)into your provided account. On actualization,the funds will be shared as stated below. 25% for you and 75% for us. What We request from you:- 1)Your full names,company name if any(otherwise we will use your name to register a company). 2)Your address,tel,fax and cell phone numbers. All logistics are in place and all modalities worked out for a smooth actualization of the transaction within the shortest possible time frame.For further details as to the workability of this transaction,please reach me as soon as possible for further clarification. Thank you for your anticipated co-operation while I await your urgent response. Yours Sincerely, Mr James Radebe. ---- Msg sent via TruthMail - http://WebBasedEmail.com/

SULE OKETAYO EAGLE BANK PLC suleoketayo@alexandria.cc Dear Sir/Madam, I am Sule Oketayo, the head of the Treasury Department of Foreign Operations Eagle Bank PLC of Nigeria. In my department, I discovered an abandoned sum of US$13,500,000.00 (Thirteen Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) in an account belonging to one of our foreign customers who died along with his entire family in 1998 in an auto crash. This account was open with the bank in 1993 and since 1998 nobody has operated it. After careful investigation, I discovered that the owner of this account was the president of MIRA CONSTRUCTION COMPANY LTD. Despite several attempts by the bank to trace the relatives/next of kin of the deceased, up to date nobody has yet come forward to claim the money. I later discovered that all his supposed next of kin died with him in the auto crash incident. I have spent the last five years monitoring the account and gathering necessary information and documents on it. Now that all papers are ready, I am asking for your assistant to release the money to you as next of kin or relation to the deceased for safekeeping and subsequent sharing. The banking laws of Nigeria stipulates that such money, if unclaimed after five years of maturity, will be transferred into the Central Bank treasury as unclaimed effect. The request for a foreigner as next of kin in this business is occasioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and presenting a Nigerian as the next of kin to a foreigner could raise concerns from the bank management. I am ready to give you 20% of the total sum for your help. 10% will be used to pay off all the necessary fees/charges involved in the transfer. 25% will go to two other officials of Eagle Bank that are with me in this and whose positions will greatly help in expediting the transfer. I will be taking 45%. Please note that these figures are negotiable. After the money has been transferred to your country, I will visit your country for the disbursement/investing of my share according to the percentages we agree upon. Note this transaction requires utmost confidentiality and I am assuring you that it is 100% risk-free so you need not be afraid. I will not contact any other person until I am convinced that you are not interested. Can you please send me your phone and fax number for safer communication when needed. Also please kindly note that all the money to finance this transfer will be provided and you will not be asked to contribute anything. When I hear from you, I will send you an online banking access code with which you can log in to verify the account and balance using the banks online banking website. Best Regards, Sule Oketayo soketayo@alexandria.cc

KEN AMOBI ukpd@email.cz For The Attention of: OWNER / CHIEF EXECUTIVE This is for your urgent attention. First, I must solicit your strictest confidence as you read this letter. Though this might come to you as a surprise since we have not met or spoken with each other before. I plead for your understanding and tender my humble apologies if I had taken you unaware. My name is KEN AMOBI, a member of the committee set up by the Federal Government of Nigeria to supervise the activities of the Petroleum Trust Fund (PTF), the agency that manages proceeds from the sale of crude oil in my country. At the inception of the new democratic government in my country, the Petroleum Trust Fund was ordered to wind up its operation to enable the new committee to take over. The former Chairman of the agency in the person of Major General Muhammed Buhari (Rtd.) was also relieved of his position as the chairman. In its place a new committee in which I am a member was appointed to take over and oversee the activities of the agency. The duty of the committee amongst others includes verifying all outstanding contract claims and debts with the sole objective of settling such long overdue claims. I therefore decided to contact you directly having gotten your name and company's information from a business handbook of your country I discovered in the former chairman's official study, which he left behind in his office. Going through some of the files left behind by the former chairman, we discovered that he has secured out of the Central Bank of Nigeria a forex release to the tune of US$25,500,000.00 for the payment of goods and services supplied by foreign contractors for the execution of KUBUWA WATER PROJECT in the oil rich Niger Delta. He was trying to transfer the funds to a ghost company abroad when he was removed from office. In confidence, we know that the goods and services were not supplied but used his office to approve the payment in favour of a foreign firm with no fixed address. He confided in me as a member of the new committee that he used his position to over invoice the contract. After his removal from office, this over invoiced amount is floating in the system and left unclaimed. He has therefore requested me to help look for a foreign company into whose account the funds will be transferred. I am now soliciting for your cooperation to enable us process the transfer of the funds to your account. You should provide us your company's name or any other name as long as you will be able to receive the amount. It will be treated as one of the outstanding payments due to you on executed contract. We will take measure to duly register your company here in Nigeria to give it legitimacy. We need your company's name and account particulars to enable us file application for foreign exchange allocation order at the Federal Ministry of Finance. The moment we accomplish this, we will raise Contract Award Certificate in your company's name to show that a contract was actually awarded and executed by you. The nature of your business does not matter. For your participation and investing in this project, we are prepared to concede 30%of the total sum to you. On completion of the project, we will commit a substantial percentage of our share into investments in your country and we will direct you on how to repatriate the balance of our share. I wish to state here again that confidentiality should be our watchword. If the above proposal meets your approval, please respond immediately. Endeavour to furnish me with your secured private telephone and fax line for easy reach. KEN AMOBI ukpd@email.cz

Attention: It is my pleasure to contact you for assistance and business co-operation. I know the content of this letter might be surprising to you but I assure you that every word of it is true. Even though we hardly know each other I believe you can help me. . I am Dr. Rilwanu lukman,President Adviser on Petroleum and Energy and Alternate Chairman of N.N.P.C Board&also OPEC President Designate.My office monitors the sales and lifting of crude oil and petroleum product by foreign dealers. With the cooperation of my assistant and head of the audit committee attached to the task force, I have successfully saved about US$37.5 million. This money is as a result of allocation of excess crude oil to the foreign dealers, which has been sold but this money is not entered in the financial statement of my task force. This money was lying unclaimed in the account of the task force, known only to me and the chief security officer in our ministry who help me in moving the fund out through his security network and me involved in the excess allocation. However, the legislators of the new democratic Government of my country have set up a panel to look into the past activities of some government companies and parastatals. I do not want the panel to discover the money I saved. I cannot lodge this money into my private bank account. In my country, public servants are not permitted to operate any account in excess of $500,000 US Dollars. Now the idea is to have a foreign partner whom the sum will be transferred to. I have concluded arrangement and transfered this money to a finance company for safekeeping to avoid the government from seizing this fund . All you have to do is to give me your private address, phone and fax lines and . I will send you the details of the transfer and necessary document as soon as you provide them. If you can assist me transfer this money into your nominated bank account,I will give you 20% of the amount. You will keep the remaining sum for my wife pending her arrival to your country. We intend to invest 50% of the sum in business. With your knowledge and past experience your advice will be highly needed for the investment. We would want to know the lucrative business areas in your country we can invest on with the 50% of the sum. Don't worry about any problem in this business. I assure it is safe and no risk is involved. No other party is aware of the sum from the excess allocation except my partner and me. However, this transaction should be secret and confidential. I awaits your reply on your participation or not, so that I can search for another willing person. Your quick response matters. Best regards Dr. Lukman Rilwanu

INVESTMENT ASSISTANCES. Greetings, . How are you? And hope all is well? . You might be surprise to receive this mail but I will appreciate you read it carefully before responding or commenting, I hope at the end it will find you and your business in the best of interest. Let me quickly introduce the reason and myself why contacting you is very important. I am Kalister Maunda; a senior staff at the Office of the Minister of Petroleum Affairs in Angola. I have traveled along side with the Minister of Petroleum to your country in search of investors that would be interested to invest on our Petroleum Sector, it was in one of this trip that I was opportune to realize that the trips been made by the Minister is not for the search for an investor but for the search for what he will invest part of the Money made from Angolan petroleum sector that he has diverted to be his own. I was shocked at this discovery, but I later realized that I was the only one among other top staffs that was not aware of these happenings, investigation into this matter made me to know that even the president is involved. I suddenly realized that the BBC and the Excite news achieve below is true. http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/business/2546281.stm http://apnews.excite.com/article/20040113/D8023NJ01.html . On arrival from the trip I made with the minister and went straight to confront my Head of Department, of my findings and he told me that he is aware of the whole situation, he went further to show me some documents that was used to withdraw some millions of American Dollars that was meant to be used to pay Oil contracting Firms in Angola, he said I should assist him in the search for a reputable and trust worthy business man that can assist us in transferring the funds to a safe place where it will be used for Future Investment. . I am therefore asking for your opinion on this issue, will you be able to assist us in transferring and claiming the money of which some percentage of the total amount involved will be granted to you for assisting us and for the time you spent on the transaction. . If you are willing and capable to assist us kindly provide us with details of how we can reach you by phone or by fax so that we can proceed to conclude this transaction. . Yours Truly, Kalister Maunda [MISS] kalika@spinfinder.com . The information contained in this email message is confidential It is intended solely for the addressee. Access to this email by anyone else is unauthorized. If you are not the intended recipient, any disclosure, copying, distribution or any action taken or omitted to be taken in reliance on it, is prohibited and may be unlawful. Kindly delete if the content of the mail is not of interest to you.

Hello, I HAVE INTREST OF INVESTING IN YOUR COUNTRY AS SUCH I WOULD LIKE TO MAKE CONTACT WITH YOU FOR ASSISTANCE. IN ORDER TO TRANSFER OUT (USD 15 MILLION DOLLARS) FROM OUR BANK. I HAVE THE COURAGE TO ASK YOU TO ASSURE ME OF YOUR RELIABILITY AND HONESTY AND CAPABILITY FOR THIS IMPORTANT BUSINESS BELIEVING THAT YOU WILL NEVER LET ME DOWN OR IN FUTURE. I AM MR. USMAN RAMAT SHEHU, AM TOP MANAGEMENT STAFF IN THE EASTERN DISTRICT OF UNITED BANK FOR AFRICAN PLC(U.B.A.). THERE IS AN ACCOUNT IN THIS BANK IN 1987 AND SINCE 1990 NOBODY HAS OPERATED ON THIS ACCOUNT AGAIN. AFTER GOING THROUGH SOME OLD FILES IN THE RECORDS I DISCOVERED THAT IF I DO NOT REMIT THIS MONEY OUT URGENTLY, IT WILL BE FORFEITTED FOR NOTHING.THE OWNER OF THIS ACCOUNT IS MR.ADAM SMITH, A FOREIGNER, AND THE MANAGER OF PETRO-TECHNICAL SUPPORT SERVICES, A CHEMICAL ENGINEER BY PROFESSION AND HE DIED SINCE 1996. NO OTHER PERSON KNOWS ABOUT THIS ACCOUNT OR ANY THING CONCERNING IT. THE ACCOUNT HAS NO BENEFICIARY AND MY INVESTIGATION PROVED TO ME AS WELL THAT HIS COMPANY DOES NOT KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT THIS ACCOUNT AND THE AMOUNT INVOLVED IS (USD) 15 MILLION DOLLARS). I WANT TO TRANSFER THIS MONEY INTO A SAFE ACCOUNT ABROAD BUT I DON'T KNOW ANY FOREIGNER, I AM ONLY CONTACTING YOU AS A FOREIGNER BECAUSE THIS MONEY CAN NOT BE APPROVED TO A LOCAL BANK HERE, BUT CAN ONLY BE APPROVED TO ANY FOREIGN ACCOUNT BECAUSE THE MONEY IS IN USDOLLARS AND THE FORMER OWNER OF THE ACCOUNT MR.ADAM SMITH IS A FOREIGNER AND FROM YOUR COUNTRY. I KNOW THAT THIS MESSAGE WILL COME TO YOU AS A SUPRISE AS WE DON'T KNOW OURSELVES BEFORE, BUT BE SURE THAT IT IS A GENUINE BUSINESS. I ONLY GOT YOUR CONTACT FROM SEARCH IN THE INTERNET, WITH BELIEVE IN GOD THAT YOU WILL NEVER LET ME DOWN IN THIS BUSINESS YOU ARE THE ONLY PERSON THAT I BELIEVE COULD HANDLE THIS TRANSACTION UNTIL AM ABLE TO COLLECT MY SHARE, SO PLEASE REPLY URGENTLY SO THAT I WILL INFORM YOU THE NEXT STEP TO TAKE. SEND ALSO YOUR PHONE AND FAX NUMBERS FOR EASY ACCESS. AT THE CONCLUSION OF THIS BUSINESS, YOU WILL BE GIVEN 20% OF THE TOTAL AMOUNT, 70% WILL BE FOR ME, WHILE 10% WILL BE FOR EXPENSES BOTH PARTIES MIGHT HAVE INCURED DURING THE PROCESS OF TRANSFERING.I LOOK FORWARD TO YOUR EARLIEST REPLY. YOURS TRUELY MR.USMAN RAMAT. ------------------------------ Cosmo.com Email - 8 megs free! http://www.cosmo.com

FROM. The Desk OF: DR. RICHARD AKUEZE DIRECTOR PROJECT IMPLEMENTATION NIGERIAN NATIONAL PETROLEUM CORPORATION (NNPC). JOINT VENTURE I strongly apologize for this unsolicited mail, but I am constrained by circumstances surrounding my profession .I have the mandate of my colleagues in office to solicite for your assistance for a deal we want to execute The business involves the remittance of US$28.6M(Twenty eight million and six hundred thousand United States Dollars) to your bank account from the Central Bank of Nigeria. The money accrued through deliberate over-invoicing of old projects executed for the Government by some foreign firms. I and few officials here have worked out a scheme to benefit us along with any foreign partner who obliges us the materials and channel to push out the fund, our idea being to come over thereafter to share the fund with whoever assist us. To make things easy and legal, the fund is reflecting in our records as payable to a foreigner who did a consultancy service job for the ministry during the turn around maintenance of one our petroleum refinery.All necessary and relevant documents will be procured for the release and transfer of the fund into your nominated account Please get in touch with me immediately through my alternative email :richardakueze@sify.com.For your participation in realizing this transaction 20% will be for you,80% for me and other officials which will be invested in your country. I am awaiting your response most urgently and is rest assured that this transaction is 100% risk free, as there is no risk involved on both sides.Thank you and God bless. Yours sincerely, Dr Richard Akueze ------------------------------ Cosmo.com Email - 8 megs free! http://www.cosmo.com

Dear Friend, REQUEST FOR URGENT BUSINESS ASSISTANCE After due deliberation with my children, I decided to contact you for your assistance in standing as a beneficiary to the sum of US30.5M Thirty Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars Only) First, let me start by introducing myself as Mrs. Stella Sigcau, a mother of three children and the Minister of Public Works in South African Government (17 June 1999) to date under the auspices of the President of South Africa MR THABO MBEKI. You can view my profile at my website: <http://www.gov.za/gol/gcis_profile.jsp?id=1068> THE PROPOSAL After the swearing in ceremony making me the Minister of Public Works in South African Government (17 June 1999) , my husband Mr Edelebe Sigcau died while he was on an official trip to Trinidad and Tobago in 1996.After his death, I discovered that he had some funds in a dollar account which amounted to the sum of US$30.5M with a South African bank which had her offshore House in the CENTRAL BANK OF NIGERIA This fund emanated as a result of an over-invoiced contract which he executed with the Government of South Africa. Though I assisted him in getting this contract but I never knew that it was over-invoiced by him. I am afraid that the government of South Africa might start to investigate on contracts awarded from 1990 to date.If they discover this money in his bank account, they will confiscate it and seize his assets here in South Africa and this will definetely affect my political career in Government. I want your assistance in opening an account with CENTRAL BANK through my Attorney so that this fund could be wired into your account directly without any hitch. As soon as the fund gets to your account, you are expected to move it immediately into another personal bank account in your country. I will see to it that the account is not traced from South Africa. As soon as you have confirmed the fund into your account, I will send my eldest son with my Attorney to come to your country to discuss on business investments. SHARING PERCENTAGE For your assistance, I am offering you 20% of the principal sum which amounts to US$6,100.000.00 (Six million One Hundred Thousand United States Dollars Only) However, you have to assure me and also be ready to go into agreement with me that you will not elope with my fund. If you agree to my terms, kindly as a matter of urgency send me an email. Due to my sensitive position in the South African Government, I would not WANT you to call me on phone or send a fax to me. All correspondence must be by above mail address. If you want to speak with my Attorney, that is fine and okay by me. His chambers will be representing my interest at the CENTRAL BANK. All correspondence must be made either to my Attorney Barrister Richard Lithuli, of Lithuli Chambers,or send me an email. I will also like you to give me your contact address,telephone and fax to enable my Attorney call or reach you from time to time. Please I do not need to remind you of the need for absolute Confidentiality if this transaction must succeed. YOU MUST NOT CALL ME! If you do not feel comfortable with this transaction, do not hesitate to discontinue. Thanks for your anticipated co-operation and my regards to your family. Yours faithfully, MRS. STELLA SIGCAU, Minister of Public Works, South Africa.

MY DEAR, PERMIT ME TO INFORM YOU OF MY DESIRE OF GOING INTO BUSINESS RELATIONSHIP WITH YOU. I GOT YOUR NAME AND CONTACT FROM THE IVOIRIAN CHAMBER OF COMMERCE AND INDUSTRY. I PRAYED OVER IT AND SELECTED YOUR NAME AMOUNG OTHER NAMES DUE TO IT'S ESTEEMING NATURE AND THE RECOMMENDATIONS GIVEN TO ME AS A REPUTABLE AND TRUSWORTHY PERSON I CAN DO BUSINESS WITH AND BY THEIR RECOMMENDATIONS I MUST NOT HESISTATE TO CONFIDE IN YOU FOR THIS SIMPLE AND SINCERE BUSINESS. I AM Ms SILVIA AWILOBA, THE DAUGHTER OF LATE MR AND MRS.AWILOBA MY FATHER WAS A VERY WEALTHY COCOA MERCHANT BASED IN ABIDJAN, THE ECONOMIC CAPITAL OF IVORY COAST BEFORE HE WAS POISONED TO DEATH BY HIS BUSINESS ASSOCIATES ON ONE OF THEIR OUTING TO DISCUSS ON A BUSINESS.WHEN OUR MOTHER DIED ON THE 21ST OCTOBER 1984, MY FATHER TOOK US SO SPECIAL BECAUSE WE ARE MOTHERLESS.BEFORE THE DEATH OF OUR FATHER ON 29TH JUNE 2000 IN A PRIVATE HOSPITAL HERE IN ABIDJAN. HE SECRETLY CALLED ME ON HIS BEDSIDE AND TOLD ME THAT HE HAS A SUM OF US$ 11,500,000 (ELEVEN MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND,UNITED STATES DOLLARS) LEFT IN A SUSPENCE ACCOUNT IN A LOCAL BANK HERE IN ABIDJAN, THAT HE USED MY NAME AS HIS FIRST ISSUE FOR THE NEXT OF KIN IN DEPOSIT OF THE FUND. HE ALSO EXPLAINED TO ME THAT IT WAS BECAUSE OF THIS WEALTH THAT HE WAS POISONED BY HIS BUSINESS ASSOCIATES. THAT I SHOULD SEEK FOR A FOREIGN PARTNER IN A COUNTRY OF MY CHOICE WHERE I WILL TRANSFER THIS MONEY WITH MY BROTHER AND USE IT FOR INVESTMENT PURPOSE,(SUCH AS REAL ESTATE MANAGEMENT).SIR,WE HONOURABLY SEEKING YOUR ASSISTANCE IN THE FOLLOWING WAYS. 1)TO PROVIDE A BANK ACCOUNT WHERE THIS MONEY WOULD BE TRANSFERRED TO(2)TO SERVE AS THE GUARDIAN OF THIS FUND SINCE I AM A GIRL OF 24 YEARS AND MY BROTHER JEFFERSON IS 18(3)TO MAKE ARRANGEMENT FOR US TO COME OVER TO YOUR COUNTRY AFTER THE MONEY HAS BEEN TRANSFERRED. MOREOVER,SIR,WE ARE WILLING TO OFFER YOU 10%OF THE TOTAL SUM AS COMPENSATION FOR YOUR EFFORT/INPUT AFTER THE UCCESSFUL TRANSFER OF THIS FUND TO YOUR NORMINATED ACCOUNT OVERSEAS.FURTHERMOIRE, YOU CAN INDICATE YOUR OPTION TOWARDS ASSISTING US AS WE BELIEVE THAT THIS TRANSACTION WOULD BE CONCLUDED WITHIN SEVEN (7) DAYS YOU SIGNIFY INTEREST TO ASSIST US.ANTICAIPTING TO HEAR FROM YOU SOON OR PLEASE CALL ME ON TELEPHONE 00225 0590 2666 FOR MORE EXPLANATION. WITH THE BEST REGARDS SILVIA & JEFFERSON AWILOBA Alternative email:jsilvia_01@yahoo.fr

Good Day! It is with hope that I write to seek your help in this context. Firstly, let me start by introducing myself properly to you. My name is Ralph Taylor, the first son of President Charles Taylor of Liberia. I got your email address from network directory. I apologize if I have infringed on your privacy. You maybe aware, that my father President Charles Taylor has been embattled by rebel forces in my country, couple with his recent indictment by U.N backed tribunal. These issues have made world headlines. Visit, www.liberianews.com Now my father has accepted to quit power and leave Liberia on the arrival of peacekeeping force which might be headed by American troops. But the delay in deploying peace keeping force has worsened situation in the country. In spite of this, my country Liberia is like a herd of cattle without shepherd. The rebel who see my family as a threat to their ambitions, are planning to kill every one of us when capture. However, I am a young man who has ambitions and I am not in any way interested in wars, this is why I secretly left Liberia for Amsterdam to seek asylum. Besides, I am using this correspondence to seek and request your assistance and cooperation in a sensitive but highly beneficial financial arrangement. Prior to the Wars and embattlement of my father, himself and I deposited a huge amount of money in a security company’s vault overseas on my name. The funds were arranged into a consignment before deposited with the security company but, the security company did not know that the consignment contains money. Because, the consignment was declared to contain family treasure and valuables. The fact that the I remain in the Asylum camp and we continue to accumulate huge debts daily as long as the consignment remains in the security company’s vault, made me decided to get someone reliable to proceed as soon as possible to receive these funds for investment purpose. As a young man, I plan to use this money to safeguard my future. It is very essential that you understand the kind of trust and confidence I want to put in you. This is an act of desperation on my part, in order not to loose this money incase of any eventuality. For your reliable assistance, if willing, I will reward you with 25% of the money. As soon as you declare your willingness to assist, i shall furnish you with the details and information you will need to accomplish this task. Please, be rest assured that this arrangement is absolutely risk free And cannot implicate you in any way. However, I implore you to handle this matter with urgency, utmost secrecy and confidentiality for security and safety reasons, even if you do not intend to execute the project. Thank you in anticipation for your assistance in enabling me achieve this goal. Please contact me whether or not you are interested in assisting me. This will enable me scout for another person in the event of non-interest on your part. Yours sincerely, Mr. Ralph Taylor

Dear Sir RE: CONFIDENTIAL ASSISTANCE First I must solicit your confidence in this transaction. I am a highly placed official working with the ministry of state for finance and economic planning here in Banjul, Gambia, west .Africa my department the treasury department does transactions that run into several hundresds of millions of dollars quaterly. Myself and two other colleagues in this department are currently in need of a silent foreign partner, whose influence and bank account we can use, to transfer the sum of Eighteen Million Five Hundred Thousand US Dollars (US$18,500,000.00) This funds accrued legitimately but discretely to us as commission from foreign contracts through our private connections. The funds is presently waiting to be remitted by our offshore funds managers to any foreign beneficiary cleared for payment. However by virtue of our positions as civil servants in our country we cannot acquire this money directly, in our names. We are not allowed by the civil service code of conduct to own or operate bank account outside our shores, on the other hand it is not safe for us to keep the money here due to our unstable political environment in this part of the world. I have been delegated as a matter of trust by my colleagues to look for an overseas silent partner in whose account we would transfer the us$18,500,000.00 to, for our mutual benefit, hence the reason for this email. I am requesting that you assist us as our silent partner and receive the funds in your account for us on trust. We propose to share as follows, 20% to you as commision and 80 for us. You will be free to take your commission immediately the funds hit your account. since our objective for now is to invest the money, it would be appreciated if you can also of assistance by advising on short and long term investment possibilities your country. Should it not be convenient for you to assist with investing, we can end our cooperation after you hand over to our percentage of the money. The transaction although discrete is legitimate, the money will be transferred to your account with all necessary back-up documents showing legitimacy and source origin of funds. The transfer will be effected within seven working days to be completd. I plead with you on one issue, whether you are interested or not please do not expose this information to any one else. I confirm that the transaction is legitimate and without any risks either of us. Please give me your response immediately while keeping everything confidential. Yours Sincerely, Peter Saseh

I humbly introduce myself to you; I am Mrs. Alhaja Rashidat Azmil the wife Of Captain Azmil who served in Iraq.I am contacting you base on trust and humanitarian assistance which I urgently need from you. The recent concluded US led war against my country has left my family totally devastated as I lost my Husband to the cold hands of death and the children lost thei father.Long before this war started, my late husband had in his custody $20.7 Million U.S Dollars, but due to serious threat of war from the United States and the collision forces (if our dictator president does not amend his ways), my husband had to act fast and at such deposited these funds in a Diplomatic Condominium in a neighboring country for the purpose of our family survival after the war might have been over. I am writing you this letter because our dreams was not fulfilled as we could not leave Iraq before the war but we did however succeeded in getting the children to a neighboring country first before trying to proceed with getting ourselves out. It was in the process of us (my Husband and I) escaping to a neighboring country that we came under friendly fire. It was this mistake that took my husband’s life and critically injured me as the truck we were in went out of control into a brick wall. I was rushed to a military hospital in a neighboring country where I am currently admitted and writing this letter. I am recovering well and now that my health has improved dramatically, I need to think of the futureof my Children and who to trust in sending theentire amount kept by my late husband for investment and acquiring immigration papers for my children. If you believe you can assist me on this endeavor,kindly reply me at r_azmil@land.ru so that I shall forward to you all the details required to carry on this transaction successfully. I look forward to your prompt favorable response.Thanks for your understanding. Yours Respectfully, Mrs. Rashidat Azmil. N.B (If you have received this email in error, please accept my apology. If you no longer wish to receive email from me, please do not reply. Your request will be honored). ____________________ http://www.email.si/

FROM: MR. SIMON OKOH. DIRECTOR: KEY TESTED TELEX WIRE TRANSFERS DEPARTMENT, CENTRAL BANK OF NIGERIA, TINUBU SQUARE- LAGOS.

TEL: 234-8023139781.

PERSONAL/STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL

I am delighted to contact you on a private note based on your claim to your contract fund, which has been programmed for transfer into your designated bank account through my department.

I am hereby apologizing to you for the delay in releasing this fund into your account, which was caused by me because of breach of agreement between me and your so called partners in Nigeria who introduced you into this business.

Your Nigeria partners approached me that they want to present you as a beneficiary to this fund as it was an OVER-INVOICING made when they are awarding contract to foreign firms. So after the negotiation, we unanimously agreed that they (your partners) would give me the sum of US$200,000.00(CASH) on my acceptance to assist them to transfer the fund into your account. When I accepted the offer, they forwarded all your banking particulars to me for onward transfer. As soon as I made some fruitful efforts on the business and demanded my US$200,000.00 as agreed, your partners deviated from the agreement and decided to go through the International Remittance Department at my back and made a change of your bank account in other to disappoint me and not knowing that the International Remittance Department is also under my control. Then I got the knowledge of their evil plans and prove their illicit efforts abortive. That is why for many months you have been pursuing this payment, spending unnecessary funds to some fraudulent individuals in Nigeria who claimed to be in charge to release your fund.

I want to re-emphasize to you that your funds is still with me and under my control. Now with my whole heart, I want to enter into real business with you on a sincere agreement since your partners has disappear into tin-air and nowhere to be found and the fund is still floating in your name waiting for a proper documentation and claims.

1. On an agreement, I assure you that I am going to transfer this fund into your account. 2. You will assure me of keeping my dealings with you to an utmost secretary because of my position. 3. You will promise to give me 20% of the total fund as soon as the fund gets into your account with a written promissory note signed by you. 4. I will assist you in making a proper documentation to make claims genuine, as a bonafide Foreign Contractor and beneficiary to the said fund. 5. Reconfirmation of your receiving bank account so as to avoid wrong remittance. 6. Your private phone and fax numbers, this is important for confidential issues and payment release instructions.

I am aware that some fraudulent individuals has been impersonating my name and office to contact you and other contractors as reported by the Central Bank of Nigeria authorities. I advise you that henceforth, you should suspend any dealings from any group of person(s) either from the CBN or any other financial institution/parastatals in Nigeria or Overseas that might be contacting you in this purpose and endeavor to keep this information confidential until we finalize this transaction. Please reply this message urgently and call me on my confidential Tel Number: 234-8023139781as soon as you received this fax. While waiting for your favorable response, God bless you.

Yours faithfully,

MR. SIMON OKOH. DIRECTOR KEY TESTED TELEX WIRE TRANSFER DEPT.

N: B Sorry, I could not use my official Memo to write you due to the confidentiality of this transaction but will be used in other official communication during the transfer. My Email address and Tel Number is stated here once again: Tel Number: 234-8023139781. Please call in receipt of this letter. E-mail: SIMONOKOH@FSMAIL.NET All payments offshore has been recalled back to Apex Bank Head Office for a direct remittance, therefore, you should not be deceived by anybody / Bank out side CBN. Work faster to contacting me immediately as I have already created way for Immediate execution of payment release,

Freeserve AnyTime - HALF PRICE for the first 3 months - Save £7.50 a month www.freeserve.com/anytime

>From Engr Mansur Ahmed. Dear Sir, I know this mail may come as surprise to you,since we do not know ourselves or have any previous contact before now,my purpose of writting you is this. We believe that you would be in a position to help us in our bid to transfer the sum of twenty-seven million five hundred thousand dollars ($27.5m)into a foreign account. We are members of a special committee for budget and planning of the ministry of petroleum,this committee is principally consern with contract appraisals and approvals in order of priorities as regards capital project of the federal government. With our positions,we have successfully secured for ourselves the sum of twenty-seven million five hundred thousand united state dollars ($27.5m). The present government in my country are seeking the surport of foreign government,so they gave directive to all federal parastatals to compile and settle all foreign contractors being owned for contract that has been executed,so our plan is to include the name that you will provide us,as one of the contractors being owed in my corporation,the nigerian national petroleum corporation (NNPC) What we need from you is (1)a company name or a name of which to use as the company that did execute the contract (2)an account even if empty into which the fund will be transfered into,this is because our code of conduct prohibit government officials from operation or owning foreign account. It has been agreed that the owner of the account will be compensated with us$8.3 million of the remitted funds,we will keep us$16.5million,while us$2.7 million has been set aside to offset expenses and pay the necessary taxes. It may also interest you to know that two years ago similar transaction was carried out with one Mr George Brooks of ( BROGE INTERNATIONAL TRADING CORPORATION) at number 135, east 57th street, 28TH floor,new york 10022 with telephone (212)308-7788 and telex number 6731689,after the agreement between both partners in which he was to take 25% of the remitted fund (fifteen million united state dollars $15.000.000.)was duly transferd into his account only to be disappointed on our arrival in new york as we were told that Mr Brooks was no longer on that address,while his telephone number had been re-allocated to somebody else,that is how we lost our money to Mr Brooks. This time around we need a more reliable and trusted person or a reputed company to transact this project with hence this proposal to you,so if you can prove yourself to be trustworthy ready to partake in this project then we are prepare to do business with you. What we need from you is the assurance that you will let us have our share after the transfer of the fund ($27.5million)into your account. If this proposal satisfies you,please contact me through this private email address (mansurahmed@sify.com,so we can advice you on modalities of the transaction,and note that all modalities has been worked out and once started will take two weeks with the absolute support of all conserned. note that this transaction is 100% risk free and totally safe now or after the fund transfer to your account. Please treat as urgent and confidential as i look forward to your reply. Best Regards, Engr Mansur Ahmed.

CONFIDENTIAL Dear Sir, I am Franck Camara the only son of late former Director of finance,Mr.Camara Kingston Sierra-Leone diamond and mining corporation. I must confess my agitation is real, and my words is my bond, in this proposal. My late father diverted this money meant for purchase of ammunition, for my country, during the peak of disastrous civil war in my country, now he has deposited the money with BANK in Abidjan, where I am residing under political asylum with my younger sister. Now the war in my country is over with the help of ECOMOG soldiers, the present government of Sierra Leone has revoked the passport of all officers who served under the former regime and now ask countries to expel such person at the same time freeze their account and confiscate their asset, it is on this note that I am contacting you, all I needed from you is to furnish me with your bank particulars: 1) Account name 2) Account number 3) Bank address, telephone and fax number for easy communication For you to assist me transfer this money in your private bank account, the said amount is (NINE Million Dollars) $9 Million. I am compensating you with 15 % of the total money amount, now all my hope is banked on you and I really wants to invest this money in your country, were their is stability of Government, political and economic welfare. Honestly I want you to believe that this transaction is real and never a joke. My late father Mr.Kingston Smith gave me the photocopies of the certificate of deposit issued to him by BANK on the date of deposit, for you to be clarify because, I do not expose my self to anybody I see, I believe that you are able to keep his transaction secret for me because this money is the hope of my life, it is important. Please call me immediately after you must have gone through my message fill free and make it urgent. That is the reason why I offered you 15 % of the total money amount, and in case of any other necessary expenses you might incur during this transaction. N.B Try and negotiate for me some profitable blue chip investment opportunities which is risky free which I can invest with this money when itis transferred to your account, personally I am interested in estate management and hotel business, please advise me. Call me back immediately you receive this message for more explanation.And promisse me my younger sister to be a father considering our situation and not to betray us. Thanks and God bless Best regards Franck Camara.

Mr.Larry Brown. Email:larrybrown@starspath.com Date:13/02/04. Dear Sir/Madam, RE-INVESTMENT. My names are Larry Brown. I am the Family Secretary/legal adviser to the former Liberia President Charles Taylor who was oudted from power lately, and presently on Assylum in West Africa. The family has huge sums of money about Fourty Five Million United States Dollars ($45M) safely deposited CASH with a security Company in Europe. On the ouster of the former President Charles Taylor the family wants to invest the money but they want me to look for a trusted and honest person who can invest this money on the familys behalf as proxy. I have chosen you because of transparent honesty. You will be paid Management/Trusteeship fees for managing and investing the funds as proxy on behalf of the family, On this you and I will have to sign an agreement before I can bring you directly with the family. However there is a diplomat who is assisting to facilitate this transaction and he has concluded arrangements to have this funds transferred through a prime Bank in Europe to your nominated account. You will need to meet with him in Europe. You will be required to travel to meet with the diplomat in Europe who will assist you with everything for the wire transfer of the funds through a local Bank to your nominated account. There is no risk involved at all so long you can invest the money. You will also sign a formal working agreement with the Diplomat on behalf of the family during your meeting in Europe. I will issue you a letter of Power of Attorney and the Certificate of Deposit to enable you take delivery of the funds from the security company in Europe to be accompanied by the diplomat. Please tell me in confidence can you handle it? Can you invest this huge amount of money successfully? Have you ever handle such huge amount of money before? How old are you? Please advise most urgently. I look forward to your response. God Bless you! Regards, Mr.Larry Brown.

URGENT BUSINESS PLAN DEAR PARTNER, IN ORDER TO TRANSFER OUT ( TWENTY SIX MILLION U.S.DOLLARS) FROM OUR BANK. I HAVE THE COURAGE TO LOOK FOR A REALIABLE AND HONEST PERSON WHO WILL BE CAPABLE FOR THIS IMPORTANT BUSINESS. BELIEVING THAT YOU WILL NEVER LET ME DOWN EITHER NOW OR IN FUTURE. I AM MR. PASCAL IBE.THE MANAGER OF UNITED BANK OF AFRICA PLC (U.B.A). THERE IS AN ACCOUNT OPENED IN THIS BANK IN 1980 AND SINCE 1990 NOBODYHAS OPERATED ON THIS ACCOUNT AGAIN. AFTER GOING THROUGH SOME OLD FILES IN THE RECORDS I DISCOVERED THAT IF I DO NOT REMITT THIS MONEY OUT URGENTELY IT WILL FORFEITED FOR NOTHING. THE OWNER OF THIS ACCOUNT IS MR CLAYTON REIDFIELD A FORIGNER AND THE MANAGER OF PETROL CHEMICAL SERVICE, A CHEMICAL ENGINEER BY PROFFESSION AND HE DIED SINCE 1990. NO OTHER PERSON KNOWS ABOUT THIS ACCOUNT OR ANYTHING CONCERNING IT, THE ACCOUNT HAS NO OTHER BENEFICIARY AND MY INVESTIGATION PROVED TO ME AS WELL THAT HIS COMPANY DOES NOT KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT THIS ACCOUNT AND THE AMOUNT INVLOVED IS(U.S.$ 26,000,000.00). I WANT TO TRANSFER THIS MONEY INTO A SAFE FOREIGNERS ACCOUNT ABROAD BUT I DON'T KNOW ANY FOREIGNER, I AM ONLY CONTACTING YOU AS A FOREIGNER BECAUSE THIS MONEY CAN NOT BE APPROVED TO ANY LOCAL BANK HERE BUT CAN ONLY BE APPROVED TO ANY FOREIGN ACCOUNT BECAUSE THE MONEY IS U.S DOLLARS AND THE FORMER OWNER OF THE ACCOUNT IS MR CLAYTON REIDFIELD AND HE WAS A FOREIGNER TOO. I KNOW THAT THIS MESSAGE WILL COME TO YOU AS A SURPRISE AS WE DON'T KNOW OUR SELF BEFORE, BUT BE SURE THAT IT IS REAL AND A GENUINE BUSINESS. I ONLY GOT YOUR CONTACT FROM OUR CHAMBERS OF COMMERCE SEARCHING WITH BELIEVE IN GOD THAT YOU WILL NEVER LET ME DOWN IN THIS BUSINESS, YOU ARE THE ONLY PERSON THAT I HAVE CONTACTED FOR THIS BUSINESS FOR NOW. SO PLEASE REPLY URGENTLY. WHEN THE TRANSFER IS APPROVED AND PAYMENT SCHEDULE IS ALLOCATED OVERSEAS, THROUGH THE OFFSHORE PAYING DELEGATE FOR FINAL CLEARANCE AND SIGNING OF THE PAYMENT RELEASE FORM BY THE BENEFICIARY, I WANT US TO SEE AT THE OVERSEA PAYING CLEARANCE OFFICE FACE TO FACE OR SIGNING OF THE ORIGINAL BINDING AGREEMENT TO BIND US TOGETHER SO THAT WE CAN RECEIVE THIS MONEY INTO A FOREIGN ACCOUNT OR ANY ACCOUNT OF YOUR CHOICE WHERE YOU WANT THE FUND TO BE REMITTED. I AM CONTACTING YOU BECAUSE OF THE NEED TO INVOLVE A FOREIGNER WITH A FOREIGN ACCOUNT AS THE REAL BENEFICIARY. I NEED YOUR CO-OPERATION TO MAKE THIS WORK FINE, BECAUSE THE MANAGEMENT IS READY TO APPROVE THIS MONEY TO ANY FOREIGNER WHO HAS THE CORRECT INFORMATION TO THIS ACCOUNT. WHICH I WILL GIVE TO YOU WHEN SURE OF YOUR CAPABILITY TO HANDLE SUCH AMOUNT IN STRICT CONFIDENCE AND TRUST, ACCORDING TO MY INSTRUCTIONS AND MY ADIVICE FOR OUR MUTUAL BENEFIT BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO MAKE ANY MISTAKE, I NEED YOUR STRONG ASSURANCE AND TRUST. I SHALL DESTROYED ALL DOCUMENT CONCERNING THIS TRANSACTIONS IMMEDIATELY WE RECEIVED THIS MONEY LEAVING NO TRACE TO ANY PLACE. I WILL USE MY POSITION AND INFLUENCE ON OTHER STAFFS TO EFFECT LEGAL APPROVALS AND ONWARD TRANSFER OF THIS MONEY TO YOUR ACCOUNT WITH APPROPRIATE CLEARANCE FROM FOREIGN PAYMENT DEPARTMENT. WITH ASSURANCE THAT THIS MONEY WILL INTACT PENDING MY PHYSICAL ARRIVAL IN YOUR COUNTRY FOR THE SHARING AND OTHER INVESTMENT. AT THE CONCLUSION OF THIS BUSINESS, YOU WILL BE GIVEN 25% OF THE TOTAL AMMOUNT, 70% WILL BE FOR ME, WHILE 5% WILL BE FOR EXPENSES , BOTH PARTIES MIGHT HAVE INCURED DURING THE PROCESS OF THIS TRANSACTION. I LOOK FORWARD TO YOUR EARLIEST REPLY THROUGH THE E MAIL AS AT ABOVE OR HROUGH MY PRIVATE E MAIL ADDRESS: [richcoll88@tatanova.com] YOURS TRULY, MR. PASCAL IBE.

FROM: MRS MARIAM ABACHA NO:28b ABACHA'S CRESCENT GIDADO BY CLOSE KANO - NIGERIA. DEAR PATINER, COMPLIMENT OF THE SEASON TO YOU I am mrs.mariam Abacha, the wife to the late Head of State, of the federal Republic of Nigeria from 1993 -1998 - General Sani Abacha. My late husband made a lot of money as the Head of state of Nigeria for 5years. He has different accounts in many banks of the world. He has not left any stone unturned in accruing riches for his family. The present democratic government of Nigeria led by President (Gen.) (Rtd)Olusegun Obasanjo has not find favour with my family since their inception. This may be as a result of his hatred for my late husband who kept him in jail for over two years for a coup attempt, before the death of my husband. He was released immediately my husband died and he was later made the present President. He has confiscated and frozen all my family account in Nigeria and some other American, Europe and Asian continents, It has been in both the local and international news. Now, my purpose of all these introduction and proposal is just seeking for your candid assistance in saving this sum 0f $50.000,000.00 USD FIFTY- MILLION.DOLLARS]which my late husband had hidden from the Nigerian govt.during his regime. and which is presently somewhere in a financial and security company outside the entire Nigeria and West African region. This is a huge sum of money, I cannot trust much on most saboteur friends of my family in Nigeria who could not be trusted. I got your contact through a search made on net for a trustworthy person . I deemed it necessary to contact you for this trustworthy transaction. All whom I needed is a sincere, honest, trustworthy and God-fearing individuals whom my mind will absolve to help me in this deal.If you have feelings about my situation, don't hesitate to stand for me. If my proposal is sudden to you, all I need now is for you to standas the Beneficiary ofthis money to claim it and save for me. There is no difficulty, I will send your name as the recipient as well as the beneficiary of the money.On your identification and confirmation from me, the fund will be handle to you. All i need is your confirmention of willingness and i will give you the full details. You will be compensated with 25% of the total fund for all your efforts and 5% will be for whatever expenses that will be incurred, while 70% is to be used in buying share in any company provided this fund is save for me for your account in your country. Please this is a very serious matter, it is a save my soul request from you and I will be delighted too much to receive a positive response from you in order to move into action. I will give you details on request from you. N:B PLEASE YOU CAN CONTACT ME ON MY PRIVENT MAILBOX(mariam_9999@fsmail.net) THANKS YOURS FAITHFULLY MRS M ABACHA.

Please Reply to: partnerindeed@voila.fr Greetings from Mrs. M. Abacha, l am sorry for the embarrassment this my letter might cause you as we have not had any correspondence before this letter. I got your contact address through your country's embassy and high commissions here in Lagos Nigeria,during my research for a reliable and trustworthy foreign partner who i will do business with, though l did not disclose the nature of the business l intend to do with whoever they will recommend for me for security reasons. I am MRS MARIAM ABACHA (A Moslem), wife and the widow of the late Nigeria Military Head of State, Late General Sani Abacha who died on the 8th of June, 1998 while still on active duty. l am contacting you in view of the fact that we will be of great assistance to each other likeness developing a cordial business relationship. l currently have within my reach the sum of Twelve Million US Dollars (US$12,000,000.00) cash which l intend to use for investment purposes, like Real Estates Development specifically in your country. This money came as a payback contract deal between my late husband and a Russian Firm on our countries multi-billion dollars Ajaokuta Steel Plant. The Russian Partners returned my husband's share of USD$12,000,000.00 after the death of my husband and lodged in my husband's security company of which l a director. Right now, the new Civilian Government headed by president olusegun obasanjo have intensified their probe on my husband's financial and oil company. In view of these, l acted fast to withdraw this US$12,000,000.00 from our company's vault and deposited it with another Security Company for safe keeping. l have since declared our Security Company bankrupt. No record ever existedconcerning the money traceable by the government because there is no documentation showing that we received this money from our Russian business partners. Due to the current situation in the country concerning government attitude towards my family, it has become quite impossible for me to make use of this money within. Let me refer you to the front page of (BBC World News of 12th August & 4th September 2000). You can check it through their contact website at http://news.bbc.co.uk/hi/english/world/africa/newsid_909000/909972.stm and http://news.bbc.co.uk/hi/english/world/africa/newsid_877000/877113.stm The present civilian government in Nigeria had seized and frozen all our bank accounts both here in Nigeria and abroad. Thus consent l shall expect you to contact me urgently to enable us discuss in detail about this transaction. Bearing in mind that your assistance is highly needed in proceeding to the Security Company and claim this fund for onward invesment in your country. l proposed a percentage of 30% of the total sum to you for the expected service and assistance, 5% for offsetting all minor expenses incurred in the course of this Transaction. Your urgent response is highly needed as to stop all further contacts. All correspondence must be by my private email address above. I will give you my particulars including my personal picture for you to know me very clearly when l hear from you. I must use this opportunity to implore you to exercise the utmost indulgence and keep this matter extra ordinarily confidential whatever your decision while awaits your prompt response. I will also scan and send to you a copy of my photograph for your record keeping. Pls Note that some times to come,You might receive some messages that looks like this but you don't need to respond back to such messages because they are ikely to be our family enemies and impersonators who are trying to know the current financial strenght of my late husband. (Sani Abacha). NB: Because of the security being mounted on the members of my family by the present civilian government headed by president olusegun obasanjo, l have decided that this transaction transaction will exist between you and my family Attorney and also my son,Abba Abacha, Therefore you can contact my son through our contact telephone numbers at: 234-80-33464921. Remember to include your private telephone, fax and mobile numbers for easy communication. Kindly get in touch through my email address at: partnerindeed@voila.fr Best Regards. Mrs.Mariam Abacha. ------------------------------------------ Faites un voeu et puis Voila ! www.voila.fr

Dear Sir. I came to know you through your country's email directory in my private search for a reliable and reputable person to handle this confidential transaction . Currently I have a business that I think would be of interest to you and I .I am the Manager, Western District Union Bank of Nig.Plc. However, there is an account opened in the bank in 1980 and since 1990, no body has operated this account again. After careful investigation,I discovered that the owner of this account was the President of GUNN FINANCE PTY LTD, a Foreigner named Mr.John W.Clouson,a National of your country who died in 1990. The account has no beneficiary at present and investigations proved that his company does not know anything about the account. The total amount is US$75.5M (seventy Five Point Five Million United States Dollars only). In light of the above fact, I need your assistance in this rare opportunity by providing your Bank account or any account of your choice where this fund will be remitted. Your assistance as a Foreigner is necessary because the management is ready to welcome anybody, preferably a Foreigner who has the correct information of the account which I will give you immediately you express your interest and capability to conclude this transaction with me.Now that the management of the bank has ordered that all dormant accounts be frozen, On the strength of this order, I wish to take advantage of this situation and present your Names as the next of kin and get it transferred to your designated account.Be informed that all documents related to this transaction will be destroyed immediately after the transfer, since every arrangement to transfer this fund to any account you will provide has been concluded. Furthermore, on receiving your positive response, I will apply for annual leave for our face to face meeting in your country for the sharing. I will give you 30% of the total fund for your assistance though the percentage is negotiable and I will not contact any other person until I am convinced that you are not interested. Please reach me through my direct e-mail address below for confidenciality indicating your interest. This information is authentic and genuine and the transaction will only last for TEN bank-working days, so do comply urgently. Best Regards, Mr. Solomon Owen. wwsolomon2003@yahoo.ie

STRICTLY PERSONAL My name is MRS JULLIET ABRAMS. I am the credit manager in a bank here in the Republic of Benin. I am contacting you with regard to transfer of a huge sum of money from a deceased account. Though I know that a transaction of this magnitude will make any one apprehensive and worried, but I am assuring you that everything has been taken care off, and all will be well at the end of the day. I decided to contact you due to the urgency of this transaction. PROPOSITION; I am the account officer of a foreigner who died in an air crash along with his wife on the 31st October 1999 in an Egyptian airline 990 with other passengers on board. You can confirm this from the website below which was published by CNN.WEBSITE. http://www.cnn.com/US/9911/02/egyptair990.list/index.html Since his death, none of his next-of-kins has come forward to put claims for this money as his heir, because they all died in the same accident himself and his wife(May their soul rest in peace). Though, the bank has made several publications to locate the family members, but all was not successful. We cannot release the funds from his account unless someone applies for claim as the next-of-kin to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines. Upon this discovery, I now seek your permission to have you stand as a next of kin to the deceased, as all documentations will be carefully worked out by me for the funds (US$35,000,000.00) to be released in your favour as the beneficiary's next of kin. Because after five years the money will be called back to the bank's treasury account as unclaimed bills and the money shared amongst the directors of the bank. So it was as a result of this,we conceived the idea of searching for a foreigner who can apply as the next of kin/beneficiary. It may interest you to know that we have secured from the probate division an order of mandamus to locate any of the deceased beneficiaries. Please acknowledge receipt of this message in acceptance of our mutual business endeavor by furnishing me with the following informations, if you are interested. 1.A Beneficiary name? In order for me to prepare the document for transfer of the funds in your name. 2. Direct Telephone and fax numbers. For our personal contact and mutual trust in each other. We shall be compensating you with 25% on final conclusion of this project, we have set aside 5% for expenses and 70% shall be for my colleagues and I. I intend to retire after the conclusion of this transaction. If this proposal is acceptable by you, please endevour to contact me immediately. Do not take undue advantage of the trust I have bestowed on you, I await your urgent mail to my personal Email:julliet06@3xl.net Regards, Mrs Julliet Abrams Tel: 00229 07 14 19 ------------------------------------------ Faites un voeu et puis Voila ! www.voila.fr

Dear Friend, As you read this, I don't want you to feel sorry for me, because, I believe everyone will die someday. My name is BATES ALAN a merchant in Dubai, in the U.A.E.I have been diagnosed with Esophageal cancer. It has defiled all forms of medical treatment, and right now I have only about a few months to live, according to medical experts. I have not particularly lived my life so well, as I never really cared for anyone(not even myself)but my business. Though I am very rich, I was never generous, I was always hostile to people and only focused on my business as that was the only thing I cared for. But now I regret all this as I now know that there is more to life than just wanting to have or make all the money in the world. I believe when God gives me a second chance to come to this world I would live my life a different way from how I have lived it. Now that God has called me, I have willed and given most of my property and assets to my immediate and extended family members as well as a few close friends. I want God to be merciful to me and accept my soul so, I have decided to give alms to charity organizations, as I want this to be one of the last good deeds I do on earth. So far, I have distributed money to some charity organizations in the U.A.E, Algeria and Malaysia. Now that my health has deteriorated so badly, I cannot do this myself anymore. I once asked members of my family to close one of my accounts and distribute the money which I have there to charity organization in Bulgaria and Pakistan, they refused and kept the money to themselves. Hence, I do not trust them anymore, as they seem not to be contended with what I have left for them. The last of my money which no one knows of is the huge cash deposit of eighteen million dollars $18,000,000,00 that I have with a finance/Security Company abroad. I will want you to help me collect this deposit and dispatched it to charity organizations. I have set aside 10% for you and for your time. God be with you. BATES ALAN

Mr PIKKA SAAIMAN LAND AND AGRICULTURAL BANK. 192 Visagie St, cnr Paul Kruger, Pretoria Republic Of South Africa. Dear Sir/Madam, I am Mr Pikka Saaiman, General Manager(Treasury) of Land Bank,South Africa.This is an urgent and very confidential business proposition. I am in a position to influence the transfer of US$26,500,000.00,(Twenty-six Million, five hundred thousand Dollars). This fund was deposited by a customer who was a foreign contractor with the South African Institute of Mining and Metallurgy. Upon maturity of the deposit,The bank sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month,we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers,South African Institute of Mining and Metallurgy, that Mr.paul bryson was dead.On further investigation,I found out from his attorney that he died without making a WILL,and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr.paul bryson did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents,including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$26,500,000.00 has carefully been fixed in my bank for safekeeping. >From our records the funds was deposited in the year 2000 and according to south african Law, at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. I will need you to stand in as his next of kin,i have already made arrangements with an attorney who will prepare all the necessary documents that will make this possible as i will follow all the necessary protocols and laws governing inheritance in my country. I am willing to offer you 40% of the funds so that i can gaurantee your commitment to this project. If you are interested, please reply immediately via my email address and Upon your response,I shall then provide you with more details that will help you understand how i plan to implement this project. Please observe utmost confidentiality, and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in real estate within your country. Due to the nature of confidentiality in this Transaction our communication can only be via email and fax mostly. Awaiting your urgent reply Thanks and my regards. pikka saaiman

From: Mr John Obi. Lagos-Nigeria. 24/2/04. Dear Sir, I am Mr. John Obi, I work with Standard Financial Trust in Lagos office. I have urgent and very confidential business proposition for you. On July 6, 1999, our customer/Civil Engineer with the BM Interiors Corporation Company, Mr. Charles Anderson made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at US$11, 450, 000, 00 and in our Bahamas branch. Upon maturity, our bank in Bahamas sent a routine notification to us here in Nigeria and we forwarded it to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the BM Interiors Corporation Company that Mr. Charles Anderson died from an automobile accident. On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL and all attempts to trace his next of kin were fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr. Charles Anderson did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$11,450,000.00 is still sitting in my Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Nigerian Law, at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Nigerian Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as an individual to stand in as the next of kin to Mr. Charles Anderson so that the fruits of this old man's labour will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your 1] name and contact adress 2] your private telephone and fax number so that the Attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits which will put you in place as the next of kin. We shall employ the service of two lawyers for drafting and notarization of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/administration in your favor for the transfer. A bank account in any part of the world which you will provide will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 70% for me, 25% for you while 5% is for expenses. There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the lawyer and my position in the bank guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately via email address above. Please observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Thanks and regards. Mr John Obi.N/B Send your response to my confidential email address:johnobi222@myway.com

Dear freind, This is a proposal in context but actually an appeal soliciting for your unreserved assistance in carrying out an urgent transaction requiring maximum confidence. Though this approach appears desperate, I can assure you that whatever questions you would need to ask or any other thing you will need to know regarding this proposal will be adequately answered to give you a clearer understanding of it, so as to arrive at a successful conclusion. My name is Dr Pimentel luisa Estrada, wife of His Excellency Joseph Estrada, former President of The Philippines. My husband was impeached from office by a backed uprising of mass demonstrators and the Senate and is presently in jail on trumped up charges of corruption, embezzlement, and the mysterious charge of economy plunder which might lead to death sentence. The present government is forcing my husband out of Manila to avoid demonstration by his supporters. As God would have it,i realised some reasonable amount of money from various deals that I successfully executed, during my husband's regime as President of Philippines. I have plans to invest this money for my children's future on real estate and industrial production. I have carefully moved out these funds (US$30 million), before my husband was impeached to an offshore Deposit Company in the European Union. My husband is not aware of this because I want to handle it secretly for obvious resons. >From past experiences, many people I had regarded as close friends has capitalized on my family's travail to run away with my money. In order to avert this negative development, My son and i now seek your permission to allow my attorney do a CHANGE OF OWNERSHIP/REASSIGNMENT OF CREDIT of the stated funds from the deposit company to your name, so that the funds (US$30million) would be released to you as the new owner (on my familys behalf). I am writing because when I deposited the money in the deposit company, I told them that it belonged to a foreign business partner and my present position will not allow me to claim the funds. Consequently, I will present you as the owner of the funds in the Deposit Company so you can be able to claim the funds. This is simple. I will like you to provide immediately; 1. Full names 2. Contact address 3. Telephone and fax numbers Once I receive this information, I will prepare the necessary documents that will put you in place as the new owner of the funds. The money will then be released to your custody by the Deposit Company, for us to share in the ratio of 70% for us and 30% for you. There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the solicitor and this will guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately via my email address. Upon your response, I shall then introduce you to my son who is going to liaise with you for further explanation that will help you understand the transaction. No doubt this proposal will make you apprehensive, please we employ you to observe utmost confidentiality and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because we shall require your assistance to invest our share in your country (buying of properties like houses, hotels etc). This is why your urgent action and response is of priority to enable us concluded this transaction in a timely and professional manner.. Please reply me AT the email address below , my personal email , Email : drluisaestrada1@philippines.to For utmost confidentiality sake. I do expect to hear from you shortly , but if you are not interested , please accept my unreserved apology. Thanks and regards Dr.(Mrs.) Luisa Estrada

FROM THE DESK OF: MR.WANG QIN HANG SENG BANK LTD. DES VOEUX RD.BRANCH CENTRAL HONG KONG HONG KONG. I am Mr.Wang Qin, credit officer of Hang Seng Bank Ltd. I have an urgent and very confidential business proposition for you. On June 6, 1998, a British Oil consultant/contractor with the Chinese Solid Minerals Corporation, Mr. Smith Lawrence made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at $48,000,000.00 (Forty-eight Million American Dollars only) in my branch. Upon maturity,I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the Hong Kong Solid Minerals Corporation that Mr. Smith Lawrence died from an auto-mobile accident. On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL,and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr.Smith Lawrence did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents,including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank.This sum of $48,000,000.00 is still sitting in my Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end ofeach year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Laws of Hong Kong, at the expiration of (five) years,the money will revert to the ownership of the Hong Kong Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr. Smith Lawrence so that the fruits of this old man's labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that the attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits that will put you in place as the next of kin.We shall employ the services of an attorney for drafting and notarization of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/administration in your favor for the transfer. A bank account in any part of the world that you will provide the will, then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 70%for me and 25% for you and 5% for Expenses Incurred in the course of the transaction . There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and with my position as the credit officer guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately to my email box. Upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please send me your confidential telephone and fax numbers for easy communication. You should observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. For confidentiality Reasons, I advice that to respond strictly to this email address:w_qin@fastermail.com. Aaiting your response. Regards, Wang Qin Reply Strictly to: w_qin@fastermail.com

FROM CROCOMBE JOHNSON. AUDITING AND ACCOUNTING UNIT. FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPT. DEXTRA BANK, GRAND CAYMAN, CAYMAN ISLANDS, B.W.I. PLEASE REPLY THIS MAIL TO MY CONFIDENTIAL ADDRESS-(crocombe2000@702mail.co.za} I am CROCOMBE JOHNSON, the Director in charge of auditing and accounting section of DEXTRA BANK, GRAND CAYMAN, CAYMAN ISLANDS. I have decided to contact you on a business transaction that will be very beneficial to both of us at the end of the transaction. During our investigation and auditing in this bank, my department came across a very huge sum of money belonging to a deceased person who died on August 1997 in a plane crash and the fund has been dormant in his account with this bank without any claim of the fund in our custody either from his family or relation before our discovery to this development. Although personally, I kept this information secret within myself and my partner to enable the whole plans and idea be pofitable and successful during the time of execution. The said amount was USD$28m (twenty eight million united states dollars). I am glad to say that with the introduction of internet and,I was opportuned and pleasured to have come across your contact through this satellite media.As it may intrest you to know Meanwhile all the whole arrangement to put claim over this fund as the bonafide next of kin to the deceased, get the required approval and transfer this money to a foriegn account has been put in place and directives and needed information will be relayed to you as soon as you indicate your interest and willingness to assist us and also benefit your self to this great business opportunity. In fact I could have done this deal alone but because of my position in this country as a civil servant, we are not allowed to operate a foriegn account and would eventually raise an eye brow on my side during the time of transfer because, I work in this bank. This is the actual reason why it will require a second party or fellow who will forward claims as the next of kin with affidavit of trust of Oath to this bank and also present a foriegn account where he will need the money to be retransfered into on his request as it may be after due verification and clarification by designation bank account. I will not fail to inform you that this transaction is 100% risk free. On smooth conclusion of this transaction, you will be entitiled to 30% of the total sum as gratification, while 10% will be set aside to take care of expenses that may arise during the time of transfer both local and international like telephone bills,e-mail bills include the documents fees, while 60% will be for me and my partner. Please,you have been adviced to keep top secret as we are still in service and intend to retire from service after we conclude this deal with you. I will be monitoring the whole situation here in this bank until you confirm the money in your account.And ask us to come down to your country for subsequent sharing of the fund according to percentages previously indicated and further investment,either in your country or any country you advice us to invest in. All other necessary information will be sent to you when I hear from you. I suggest you get back to me as soon as possible stating your wish in this deal. Yours faithfully, CROCOMBE JOHNSON. NOTE-MAKE SURE THAT THE REPLY TO THIS PROPOSAL GOES TO MY CONFIDENTIAL E-MAIL ADDRESS(crocombe2000@702mail.co.za)

FROM THE OFFICE OF: BALA MANCHA 19,SYLVIA STREET, ANTHONY VILLAGE, LAGOS. NIGERIA. TELEPHONE NUMBER: +234 1 776 7324 INTERNET FAX: 1-775-213-6344 ALTERNATIVE EMAIL: balamancha@mail2director.com BUSINESS INVESTMENTS PARTNERSHIP: TRANSFER OF US$12.5 (TWELVE MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS). Dear Friend, I would like to firstly send to you the best wishes of good health and success in your pursuits this new year particularly through my proposal as contained In this letter. Before going into details of my proposal to you, I must first implore you to treat with the utmost confidentiality as this is required for its success and to have faith in this transaction, for Opportunities like this only come to one once in a lifetime. I am Bala Mancha, a director with the Power and Steel Department and the Secretary of my country’s Contracts Review Panel (CRP). This profitable venture involves the sum of US$12,500,000.00 (Twelve Million Five hundred thousand United States Dollars) which is presently floating in an account with the Central Bank of Nigeria (CBN) and we are interested in diverting some funds for ourselves. The reason for this letter is that your help is being sought in order to facilitate and successfully complete this profitable venture that is of immense benefit to you, and us the originators within a stipulated time frame as we are determined to conclude the transfer within two weeks. In order to commence this transaction, we solicit for your assistance as a foreigner, to enable us transfer into your nominated account this sum of US$12,500,000.00 (Twelve Million Five hundred thousand United States Dollars). We cannot make this transfer on our own or in our names for the fact that we are civil servants (still in active service). But you as a foreigner can assist us in the sense that the money to be transferred will be paid to you as a contract entitlement for a purported contract executed for my government. The source of the funds are as follows: During the last military regime in my country, government officials set up companies and awarded themselves contracts that were grossly over-invoiced in various ministries and parastatals. The present civilian government set up the Contract Review Panel, which has the mandate to use the instruments of payments made available to it by the decree setting up the panel, to review these contracts and if necessary pay those who are being owed outstanding amounts. The money in question is ready for transfer into an overseas account, which we expect you to provide. We have agreed that the money will be shared according to the ratio Stated below; (i) 25% to the account owner (you). (ii) 65% for us (the panel officials). (iii) 10% to be used in settling all expenses (by both you and us)incidental to the actualization of this project. We will require from you: a) Name and address of Company/Beneficiary, telephone and fax numbers. b) Bank name, address, telephone and fax numbers and Details of the Account, which you are the only signatory that the money will be Transferred into. We do not mind if the account is a zero-based account or an account with no funds in it so long as it is functional for this purpose. The above requirements are to legalize the claim for payment and transfer of the money to your account. Be informed that the reason we are sending you this letter is because we know that the only way to succeed is to seek the help of a foreigner. Your professional status is not a matter of hindrance in this transaction. Please, your assistance is highly solicited. We have no doubts at all that this money will be released and transferred if we get the necessary foreign partner to assist us in this deal. Therefore, when the business is successfully concluded we shall through the same connections withdraw all documents used from all the concerned government ministries for 100% security. All expenses regarding the opening of an account if not already in existence shall be borne by you, all expenses is however reimbursable on the conclusion of this business transaction. It is of high hope that you will consider this humble request and Respond positively. If you are still in doubt after the receipt of this letter please do not hesitate to contact and ask any question(s) that may hinder your decision on this matter via my telephone number 234-1-776-7324 or through the above email address and/or fax number. Please acknowledge the receipt of this letter if you are interested. While awaiting your early response, thank you in anticipation of your most valued assistance. Yours faithfully, BALA MANCHA P.S. PLEASE TREAT AS URGENT AND CONFIDENTIAL Alternative email address: balamancha@mail2director.com

MISS.CYNTHIA PEPPLE Sir/Madam, RE:ACCEPTANCE / INVESTMENT PROPOSAL INTRODUCTION: l am MISS.CYNTHIA PEPPLE first daugther to my late father and also a Civil Servant in the Ministry of Health. l know this proposal will come to you as a surprise because we have not met before either physically or through correspondence. I got your contact through a friend working with chamber of commerce here in Nigeria who have travelled far and wide and have no doubt in your ability to handle this proposal involving huge sum of money. THE SUBJECT: My Father CHIEF. Dominic pepple(Now Late) was the Royal Head of my community, ELEME (an oil rich town) in Nigeria. My community produces 5.8% of the total crude oil production in Nigeria and 0.5% of the Dollar value of each barrel is paid to my father as royalty by the Federal Government. My father was also the Chairman of ELEME Special Oil Trust Fund. In his position as the Royal head and Chairman of the Oil Trust Fund, he made some money which he left for me as the only heir to inherit.The money is FIVE Million Five Hundred Thousand US Dollars($5.5m). This Money originated from the accumulated royalties between 1976-1998 . Due to poor banking system in Nigeria and political instability as a result of past Military rules (1985-1999) , he deposited this Money in a VAULTS " with an open beneficiary to a security company pending when he would finish arrangement to get assistant abroad. He was planning this when he suddenly died late last year of Heart Attack. THE PROPOSAL: Just before my Father died he called my attention to the money and charged me to look for a foreigner who would assist me in accepting/investment of the funds abroad. So l would be very grateful if you could accept to help me achieve this great objective. I promise to give you 20% of the total funds as compensation for your assistance. Five percent (5%)would be set aside to take care of any expenses we may incure during the transaction. To indicate your interest, contact me urgently and confidentially for more information and the roles you will play in this business. All the legal Documents concerning this Money will be sent to you as soon as we agreed together. Send your reply through this box please. May the almighty God bless you. Yours faithfully MISS CYNTHIA PEPPLE ________________________________________________ Get your own "800" number Voicemail, fax, email, and a lot more http://www.ureach.com/reg/tag

Box 1287 Port Shepstone Chaka -South Africa. RE TRANSFER OF ($ 39,500.000.00 USD THIRTY NINE MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND DOLLARS] Dear Sir, We want to transfer to overseas ($$ 39,500.000.00 USD) Thirty nine million Five hundred thousand United States Dollars) from a Prime Bank in Africa, I want to ask you to quietly look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable and fit to provide either an existing bank account or to set up a new Bank a/c immediately to receive this money, even an empty a/c can serve to receive this funds quitely. I am Dr.John Solomon.,the accountant and personal confidant to Dr. Ravindra F. Shah who died together with his wife Dr.Mrs. Manjula Parikh-Shah in a plane crash on the 1st Oct. 2003 on their way to attend wedding in Boston. Mr. Ravindra F. Shah, is an American, a physician and industrialist, he died last year without having any beneficiary to his assets including his account here in South Africa which he opened in a prime bank in the year 2000 as his personal savings for the purpose of expansion and developement of his company before his untimely death in 2003. The amount involved is (USD 39,500,000.00)Thirty Nine Million Five Hundred Thousand USD, no other person knows about this account, I am contacting you for us to transfer this funds to your account as the beneficiary, I want to first transfer $9,500.000.00 (nine million five hundred thousand USD) from this money into a safe account abroad, after which we will transfer the remaining (30M) but I don't know any foreigner, I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money can not be approved to a local person here, without valid international foreign passport, but can only be approved to any foreigner with valid international passport or drivers license and foreign a/c because the money is in US Dollars and the former owner of the a/c Mr.Ravindra F. Shah is a foreigner too, and as such the money can only be approved into a foreign a/c. However, I am revealing this to you with believe in God that you will never let me down in this business, you are the first and the only person that I am contacting for this business, so please reply urgently so that I will inform you the next step to take urgently. Send also your private telephone and fax number including the full details of the account to be used for the deposit. I need your full co-operation to make this work fine. because the management is ready to approve this payment to any foreigner who has correct information of this account, which I will give to you, upon your positive response and once I am convinced that you are capable and will meet up with instruction of a key bank official who is deeply involved with me in this business. At the conclusion of this business, you will be given 50% of the total amount, 50% will be for me, we will bear the working cost together through the process of transfer to get payment approvals. I look forward to your earliest reply through my Email:{john_solomon14@hotmail.com}or you call me on +871-763-649-685, +874-763-649-685, +870-763-649-685. Sincerely, John Solomon. ______________________________________________________________________ Post your free ad now! http://personals.yahoo.ca

Name-DR JERRY M AHMED Email-(jerrymahmed@regards.net) BUSINESS PROPOSAL My name is DR.JERRY M AHMED a member of the Presidential Task Force on Oil Spillage Clean-up. Early last yearthere was a major oil spillage in the Niger Delta Region of Nigeria which rendered over 70% of the communities homeless.The contract was handled by a foreign firm but because of the huge monetary profit we envisaged, we decided to over-invoice the contract sum. Now the contract has been completed and the original contractor has since been paid,but the contract balance of US$31.50 million(THIRTY-ONE MILLION, FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS),which resulted from the over invoiced contract sum that has been left in a suspense account with the CENTRAL BANK of NIGERIA,is what me and my partners are planning to take out of the country for ourselves.The problem is as government officials,we are not suppose to own fat bank accounts,talk less of having foreign ones. To this end, we are soliciting your assistance as a foreign partner who can assist us and receive this amount into your account. We are ready to share this money with you on the basis of participation. We also have plans to invest part of this money in any viable business in your country under your care,as we are nearing our retirement age. In any case, I received a reference of you/organization from the Nigeria Chambers of Commerce and Industry 'Foreign Trade Division' as a reputable organ that can assist us on this transaction. Please if you accept my proposal do not hesitate to send me a send me an e-mail so that I can provide you with the basic procedures for the release of the fund. It does not matter whether you or your company does contract project of the nature described here, the assumption is that you won a major contract and subcontracted it to another company, more often thannot, big trading companies or individuals of unrelated field win major contracts here in Nigeria and subcontracts same to more specialized firms for execution. BENEFIT: For providing the account where we shall remit this money, you will be entitled to 25% of the entire funds, 70% will be for me and my partners,while 5% has been set aside to cover any expenses that may be incurred by both parties during this transaction, both local and international. Please I enjoin you to handle this transaction with utmost degree of maturity and confidentiality because I am still in active government service with the"NIGERIAN NATIONAL PETROLEUM CORPORATION". If I receive your response on time, this whole transaction could be accomplished within the shortest possible time based on your interest and determination,since the money is already in transit. Awaiting your urgent response and thanks for your anticipated co operation Yours faithfully, Dr.JERRY M AHMED REPLY TO (jerrymahmed@regards.net)

From: JOHN KABILA Baminda Cameroon central Africa PHONE 002377898587 FAX 002373361683 Greetings, In appreciation of your esteemed contact received through a reliable source and the choice of your country I wish to introduce myself, I am John Kabila the son of the late Democratic Republic of Congo President Laurent Desire Kabila of the blessed memory. ;I know this letter might come to you as a surprise but I honestly have to solicit your attention to this assistance and foreingn investment. I write this letter in respect of my intention to invest the sum of US $ 20 000,000.00 with you. I inherited this funds from my mother. This funds was generated through the sale of Diamond and Timber when my father was the head of state. My mother though not her legal wife used her privilege position to engage in the business of Diamond and timber since she knows that her survival will depend on how much she can get out of the privilege situation. When my father was assassinated on 16th January 01 by one of his bodyguards Lt. Rashidi Kasereke through the conspiracy of some Top Army officers that wanted to topple his government, I escaped to Cameroon because of the fear that I might be arrested by my half brother Lt. General Joseph Kabila the present head of state. Actually his mother and my mother are not in the best of relationship because of tussle for who among them will be the first lady and this ultimately affected us their children. Considering the relationship between South Africa and the Democratic Republic of Congo new government, my mother advised me to leave for Cameroon for security reason, while the funds were deposited with a security Company. On getting to cameroon where I have been living since then I am seeking for a reliable foreigner who can assist me in moving this funds out for safe banking and profitable foreighn investment. Honestly I contacted you because I don't want to invest this funds in Cameroon nor Africa due to my status in my country as a result of my fathers death. .And moreover I wouldn't want to take risk because this funds is all that I and my mother is depending on because my half brother has seized all my father's assets and funds and left I and my mother empty handed without knowing that this funds was deposited at the security company. so this is why I decided that investing this funds abroad should be the best safest typy of adventure for me. I will be honoured if I can be given the privilege of investing this fund through your help. In view of this plight, I expect you to be trustworthy and kind enough to respond to this distress call to save my mother and I from a hopeless future. And if you agree, I hereby agree to compensate your sincere and candid effort in this regard with 20% of the total fund and annual 5% of the after tax returns on investment for the first three years. Thereafter, the terms shall be varied. 5% for expenses, which may arise during this transaction, fax and phone bills inclusive,When the fund ($20,000,000.00) is moved into your discrete account, you will be allowed to draw 20% your favor, while the remaining 75% will be invested meaningfully for our future if possible in your area of business and deterrents sectors of the Economy in your country which are dividends yeilding. Should you for any reason not interested,please kindly reach me so as to make other contacts and please try to keep this letter tight secret for the interest of my family. Best regards. JOHN KABILA

DEAR FRIEND. This business proposal to you is strictly confidential, with due respect. Sorry at this perceived confusion or stress may have receiving this letter from me, Since we have not known ourselves or met previously. Despite that, I am constrained to write you this letter because of the urgency of it.By way of self introduction, I am Mrs. alice Kobe, the wife of late Brigadier - Gen.Maxwell Kobe former ECOMOG ARMY COMMANDER [West African peacekeeping force in Sierra Leone] who died in the Sierra Leone civil disturbance [War]. My three daughters and I are trapped in obnoxious custom and traditional norms. We have suffered maltreatment and untold hardship in the hands of my late husband's family, simply because I did not bear a male child [heir apparent] for my late husband. By tradition, all that my late husband had, [wealth] belongs to his brothers/family. And myself is to be remarried by his immediate younger brother which I vehemently refused. They have taken all that I suffered with my husband to acquire including treasures, houses and his bank particular seized by them. I wanted to escape to escape to your country with my children on exile, but again they conspired and stole my international passport and other traveling document to further frustrate me. Thank God, two weeks ago, I received Key Text Code from a Security Company in EUROPE, that my late husband deposited U.S $25.5 Million cash with this security company EUROPE . It has therefore, become very necessary and urgent to contact someone, a foreigner like you to help me receive/secure these funds overseas in a reliable bank Account (presumably an empty Bank Account, if available) and to help invest it on our behalf as well, while we find a way of getting out to meet with you in your country. These funds are kept on an "OPEN BENEFICIARY MANDATE" with the Security Company in EUROPE to avoid detection, seizure or diversion. I have had several telephone discussions with the Director of the security company in us,who has express willingness to help me on meeting the company's demands. This is why I have contacted you to help save my children and I, receive these funds on our behalf. But, you would need to give me sufficient assurance that if you help me, you would not divert the funds. My children and I have resolved to give you 30% of the total sum. This is all my children and I have got to live on. Please, I have reposed my confidence in you and hope you will not disappoint me. I look forward to your urgent response, including your phone/ mobile No and also your fax no for easier communication. NB: The secret codes (e.g Pin No., Secret Access Code) for this fund are safely kept with me which I can give you as soon as you express desire to help me. Stay blessed. ALICE KOBE

My proposal to you. Dear Sir, Greetings, I am Mr. Dan Patrick, a staff in Barclays bank, here in United Kingdom. However I got your contact through the International web directory. Recently we discovered a Dormant Account with a huge amount of Money Valued USD14, 000,000.00 (Fourteen Million Dollars only) that belongs to one of our late Customer who died in a plane crash. During our investigation and auditing in this bank, my department came across a very huge sum of money belonging to MOHAMED KAMAL YASSER who died along with his wife and his two sons and the fund has been dormant in his account with this bank without any claim of the funds in our custody either from his family or relation before our discovery of this development. The Banking law here stipulates that if such money remains unclaimed for Six years, it will be forfeited to the Bank treasury as an unclaimed bill. It is only an outsider from the bank that can stand as a next of kin and It is upon this discovery that I decided to contact you to collaborate with you to pull out this dormant fund. In order to avert this negative development, I on behalf of my trusted colleagues now seek your permission to have you stand in as next of kin to our late customer so that the fund will be released and paid into your account as the beneficiary next of kin, now that the bank is still expecting a next of kin or relative of the deceased, MOHAMED KAMAL YASSER. Please go through the website below to confirm this story www.cnn.com/us/9911/02/egyptair990.list/index.html We could have done this deal alone but because of our position in this country as civil servants, we can not do it on our own or with close friends because that would eventually raise an eye brow on our side during the time of transfer since we still work in this bank, this is the actual reason why we required a second party or fellow who will assist us forward claims as the next of kin and also provide either an existing bank account or to set up a new Bank a/c immediately to receive this fund, even an empty account can also serve for this purpose. On smooth conclusion of this transaction, you will be entitled to 25% as gratification for your assisting us, while 5%will be set aside to take care of expenses on our both sides that may arise during the time of transfer and also for telephone bills, and the remaining 70% will be for me and my partners. What I want from you is for you to act as the deceased next of kin. I have in my possession, all the necessary documents to successfully accomplish the operation. Please, bear in mind that this proposal is 100% risk free. Further information will be given to you as soon as I receive your positive response. I suggest you get back to me as soon as possible stating your wish. Best Regards. Dan Patrick. Note: Please, respond to this email address: danpatrick44@netscape.net ---------------- Powered by telstra.com

Dear friend, It is with my profound dignity that I write you this very important and highly confidential letter. First, I must solicit your strictest confidentiality in this transaction. This is by virtue of its nature as being utterly CONFIDENTIAL and "TOP SECRET". Though I know that a transaction of this magnitude will make any one apprehensive and worried,considering the fact that we have not met each other before,but I am assuring you that all will be well at the end of the day. I have decided to contact you by email due to the urgency of this transaction,as I have been reliably informed that it will take at least a minimum of two to three weeks for a normal post to reach you, so i decided it is best using the e-mail. However, let me start by introducing myself properly to you, i am Nzani Peter Taylor, the cousin of former Libarian President, Who is on exile in Nigeria and he is in hiding from the United Nations for war crimes. The reason i'm sending you this mail is to seek your help by assisting my cousin and my self in collecting some amount of money deposited in in europe, under my name. I nor my cousin cannot at this point in time try to collect the said funds because the United Nations will not fail to pick us up and set us before the world crimes tribunal. As its now, i am acting on behalf of my cousin to source for a reliable partner who will assist us in collecting the said funds, which in total is fifty six million dollars($56,ooo,ooo) deposited in my name when my cousin was president, and we have decided to give a total of 20% to who ever assists us to collect the money. We have also set aside 4% to be used in offsetting all debts/expenses. The trust reposed on you at this juncture is enormous. In return we demand your complete honesty and trust. You must however NOTE that this transaction will be strictly based on the following terms and conditions as we have stated below; a) Our conviction of your transparent honesty and diligence b) That you would treat this transaction with utmost secrecy and confidentiality c) That you will not ask for more share or try to sit on the funds once it is under your custody, or any form of blackmail. c) That upon receipt of the funds you will release the funds as instructed by us after you have removed your share of 20% from the total amount. We are looking forward to doing business with you and solicit your Total Confidentiality in this transaction. There is no cause for alarm. I give you my word that you are completely safe in doing business with us. Please acknowledge the receipt of this letter using the above e-mail address. I will bring you into the complete picture of this pending business transaction when I have heard from you and also receive your confidential telephone and fax numbers to enable me fax to you all necessary information you need to know about our pending business transaction. I will also send to you my private telephone and fax numbers where you can always reach me. Please, note that this transaction is 100% legal and risk free and we hope to conclude this transaction within 14 working days from the date of receipt of the necessary requirements from you . Thank you and God Bless. Yours faithfully, Nzani . P. Taylor.

From:Cyril Konan. Abidjan Cote D'Ivoire. Tel:0022-50786-5223. REQUEST ASSISTANCE Sir, It is my pleasure to write you after much considerations I can not be able to see you face to face at first. Being the first son of my father late prince mathew Konan, from Zulu in republic of South Africa. My father was a limited liability cocoa and gold merchant in South Africa before his untimely death. After his business trip to Abidjan Cote d'Ivoire, to negociate on a cocoa business a week after he came mother by unknown assassins . which my mother died , instantly , but my father died after five days in hospital on that faithful afternoon. I didn't know that my father was going to leave me after I had lost my mother . But before he gave up the ghost , it was as if he know he was going to die . He my father,may his soul rest in perfect peace ) disclose to me that he deposited $ 18.5 ( eighteen million five hundred thousand dollars ) in security and safe deposit company in Abidjan , Cote d'Ivoire. That the money was meant for his cocoa business he wanted to invest in Abidjan , Cote d'Ivoire through, according to my father he deposited the money in a trunk box, but declared it as ivory , and family belonging for the security reasons. He single handed me the key of the box and certificate of deposit and agreement certificate , and instructed me to seek for a foreign assistant who will help me to move it out from the security and safe deposit company for a life time investment abroad . Now , I have succeeded in locating the security and safe deposit company here in Abidjan , Cote d'Ivoire and also I confirmed the item with most honest and confidentiality. Now I am soliciting for your assistance to help me lift this money out from Abidjan to your account abroad so that we should invest it in any lucrative business in your country , strictly in your advice , because this is my only hope in life. As I am awaiting anxiously to hear from you so that we can discuss the modalities of this transaction . I have mapped out for you 15% of the total fund which stands for your commission for presenting a foreign bank account where the money will be transferred to and more so you shall benefit 5% of the monthly total interest of the said venture. Please if this proposal is acceptable to you kindly contact me through the above email address immediately for more discussion .Please help me with good spirit . Thanks for your kind attention and mutual understanding. Best Regards. Cyril Konan. =========================================================================================== Netkuis Instan untuk Divre 3 - SD,SMP,SMA berhadiah asuransi pendidikan puluhan juta rupiah... periode I dimulai 1 April 2004 ===========================================================================================

MR. MATAMELA C. RAMAPHOSA JOHANNESBURG SOUTH AFRICA Courtesy of business opportunity, I take liberty anchored on strong desire to solicit for your assistance on this mutual beneficiary and risk free transaction with you, which I hope you give urgent attention. To be precise, I am MR. MATAMELA CYRIL RAMAPHOSA the manager of bills/exchange at the foreign remittance department of First Rand Bank Limited. In my department, we discovered an abandoned sum of US$ 25.5 Million (Twenty five Million Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) in an account that belongs to one of our customers who died along with his entire family in 1988 Lockerbie Pan American Airline plane crash. Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless somebody applied for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking procedures, but unfortunately to no avail andnobody has come forward to claim the money. Therefore, upon this discovery that I and other two officials in my department now decide to establish a cordial business relationship with you,hence my contacting you. We want you to purportedly present your good self as the next of kin or relation of the deceased so that we can release the fund (money) into your account for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and again we do not want the money to go into the government account as unclaimed bill .The banking law and procedures herein stipulates that any accounts abandoned or dormant for a period of some years is subject to be closed and all money contained therein will be forfeited to the government treasury account. Now it is being speculated that the above sum will be transferred into government treasury account as unclaimed fund on or before May 2004. The reason for you to present your good self as the next of kin is occasioned by the fact that the deceased customer was a foreigner. Mode of Sharing After the successful completion of the transfer is as follows, for the role you will be expected to play in the whole exercise, we have agreed to give you twenty (20%) of the total sum,and 10% has been set aside for the expenses we are going to encounter by both parties in the process of this transaction and the remaining 70% shall be for my colleagues and I. In support of the aforementioned, you are urged to reply this letter indicating your readiness and interest to participate in the business. After your reply, you will be advised on the next step afterwards. I quite believe that you will protect our interest by keeping this business top secret and confidential. Your interest will be equally protected, as we must maintain maximum confidentiality. Trust to hear from you THROUGH MY PRIVATE EMAIL ADDRESS "cyrilmata2@zwallet.com'' Count on your earliest reply. Thanks Yours faithfully MR.MATAMELA C. RAMAPHOSA

From: The Desk of Ajibola James Senior Manager: Pacific International Bank PLC. 40 Marina Street Lagos Dear friend, First, I must solicit your confidence in this transaction. This is by virtue of its nature being utterly confidential and top secret. We have decided to contact you due to the urgency of this transaction, as we have been reliably informed of your discretness, trustworthy and ability to carry out legitimate business. THE PROPOSITION: An American, Mr. Shaline Adam, an Oil merchant with the Federal Government of Nigeria, until his death with his whole family on an EgyptAir Flight #990, which crashed into the Atlantic Ocean on October 31, 1999, banked with us at Pacific International Bank Plc Lagos and had a closing balance of US$3.5,000,000.00 (Three Milion Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars Only) as at the end of September, 2000. Attached here is a CNN webpage on the unfortunate crash in 1999: http://www.cnn.com/US/9911/02/egyptair990.list/index.html Valuable efforts have been made by the bank to get in touch with any of the Adam's family or relative, but to no avail. His Next of Kin was his wife that was involved in the crash so for now there is no trace of his family. It is because of the perceived impossibility of locating a relative of the Shaline Adam's family (since all his family are dead) that the bank is making plans to ceed the said amount to the Defence Ministry for the procurement of weapons of war. In order to avert this ugly situation, few of my colleagues and I have decided to contact you and seek your permission to have you stand as a relative to Late Shaline Adam so that the total amount of US$3.5 Million Dollars will be processed and released in your favour into your personal account. All documents and proofs to enable you get this fund will be carefully worked out. We have secured from the probate, an order of Madamus, to locate any of the deceased beneficiary. Be rest assured that this transaction is risk-free. Also, your share for offering to assist us and provide the receiving account will be 10% of the total sum, while 90% will be for my colleagues and I, which also would be in your account for safe custody and probable future investment purpose in your country. As soon as we receive an acknowledgement of your willingness to accept our proposal, we shall furnish you with further details as we concluded all arrangements to have the money transferred to you within 7 working days from the date of commencement. If this proposal is acceptable to you, then furnish us with your most confidential telephone and fax numbers at which time an application for the fund release will be forwarded in your favour. Thank you in advance for your anticipated cooperation. Regards, Ajibola James Alternative mail:jrade2000@caramail.com

Dear Sir, This letter may come to you as a surprise but I really prayed to God to help me choose somebody that will be my true partner. My name is James Nandu Savimbi.I am the first son of Mr. Jonas Savinbi, the leader of the UNITA movement in Angola. May be you know that my father was killed recently in Angola by the Angolan Government soldiers and he has since been buried. Two weeks before he died (May be he knows he will die), he called me and showed me a box containing US$20 million and some Diamond value about US$15 million. He sent the box to a security company in Europe for safe keeping with a false name. He give me the certificate of deposit and the code number. With that I can collect the box anytime I want. Now that my father is dead and I need the money to take care of the family left behind of about two wives and six children. I am now hiding as the government of Angola is desperately looking for me to assasinate and also the former commander of my father wants to get me at all cost.Also, I have to be very careful of my movement hence my search for you to help me to get the box and keep it until I can escape and meet you and you will also help me to invest the money in your country or where it is good. I will give provide you with all the power(necessary documents) to collect the box on my behalf when you tell me in your reply that you will help me and I can trust and count on you. I don't trust anybody in Angola and with the certificate and the code which I will give you, there should/will be no problem in collecting the box. You don't have to worry,as this is 100% risk free to you as only me, my dead father and the security company in Europe knows about this box. But I want you to keep this secret as there are some enemies of my father scattered all over the whole World who are friends to the government of Angola. The name of the country where the box is in Europe and how much I will give you for help shall be revealed upon your response to my mail. 1 YOUR FULL NAME 2. YOUR CONTACT (HOME)ADDRESS 3. YOUR TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBER 4. YOUR DATE OF BIRTH & YOUR OCCUPATION I await your quick answer and sorry for poor english if there is any. Thank you. James Nandu Savimbi.

Dear Sir, I am Memuna Mousa from Kuwait. I am married to late Moulla Abass mousa of blessed memory who worked with kuwait embassy in Sudan for twelve years before he died in the year 2000. We were married for eleven years without a child. he died after a brief illness that lasted for only four days. Before his death we were both devoted Muslims. Since his death I too have been battling with both Cancer and fibroid problem. When my late husband was alive he deposited the sum of ($10.5million (TEN MILLION,FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND U.S DOLLAS) with a Bank somewhere in Europe. Recently, my doctor told me that i would not last for the next six months due to cancer problem. Though w hat disturbs me most is my stroke sickness. Having known my condition I decided to donate this fund to either a Muslim organization or devoted Muslim individual that will utilize this money the way I am going to instructs here in. I want this muslim organization or individual to use this money all sincerity to fund mosques, orphanages, widows,and also propagating the word of ALLAH and to ensure that thesociety upholds the views and belief of the Holy Quran. The Holy Quran emphasiz es so much on Allah's benevolence and this encourage me to take the bold step. I took this decision because I don't have any child that will inherit this money and my husband relatives are new christian's converts and I don't want a situation where this money will be used in an Unholy manner. Hence the reasons for taking this bold decision. I know that after death I will be with Allah the most beneficent and the most merciful. I don't need any telephone communication in this regard becasue of my health and becasue of the presence of my husbands' relatives around me always. I don't want them to know about this development. With Allah all things are possible. As soon as I receiv e your reply I shall give you the contact of the Bank where the money was deposited. I will also issue you a power of Arttorney to the Bank authorizing them that the said fund have been willed to you and a copy of such authorization will be forwarded to you. I want you and muslim community where you reside to always pray for me. My happiness is that I lived a true devoted muslim life worthy of emulation. Whosever, that wants to serve Allah must serve him in truth and in fairness. Please always be prayerful all through your life. Any delay in your rely will give room in sourcing for a Muslim organzation or a devoted Muslim for this same purpose. Until I hear from you, my dream will rest squarely on your shoulders.May the Almight Allah contiune to guide and protect you.You can also reply to me through the alternative E-mail: memunamousa@survivormail.com Best regards, Memuna Mousa.

CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION. VERY URGENT REPLY REQUIRED I am DR AHMED SANI, I am a lawyer. I was the personal attorney to MR Josef Flubacher (hereinafter refered as my client) from Zurich,Switzerland,who was a contractor to Nigerian Government . On the 21 of April 2001, MR Flubacher was involved in a fatal road accident and died on the spot with his wife and two kids. Since then I have made several enquiries to the EMBASSY to locate any of my client's relatives or next of kin, this has also proved unsuccessful. I was appointed his trustee and sole admnistrator of his estate which includes his Bank Account. I am contacting you to assist in repatriating the money left behind by my client before it is confiscated or declared unserviceable by the bank where this deposit was lodged. Particularly the Global finance and Security company based in Amsterdam, Netherlands, where he deposited $20 million dollars ( Twenty million dollars ) have issued me a notice to provide the next of kin. I seek your consent and permission to present you as the next of kin so that the proceeds valued at $20 million dollars can be paid to you and then we can share the money. 65% to me while 30% to you. Then the balance of 5% will be reserved for incidental expences. I have all necessary legal documents that can be used to back up this transaction. All I require is your honest cooperation to enable us see this deal through. I am very sure with your trust and asistance, we will successfully and legally transfer this money to you before the finance company take any decision about it. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect both party from any breach of the law.You will be giving all the deposit documents to contact the finance company in Holland for clarification and verification of this matter. Please get in touch with me through my email or fax as stated herein and send to me your telephone and fax numbers to enable us discuss further about this transaction. I hereby attach the CERTIFICATE OF APPOINTMENT as his trustee and sole administrator of his estate. Please contact me immediately through my email:ahmedsani@myself.com and mohdsule@fsmail.net Note however, that your nature of business,sex or country of origin will not be a hindrance for you to act as his next of kin. Finally, I trust you keep this information private and confidential. This money shall be transfered through telegraphic online banking procedure. Truth,trust,and cofidence quaranteed Best regards, and peace be with you. DR AHMED SANI

Dear Friend. Greetings, With warm heart I offer my friendship and I hope this mail meets you in good time, however strange or surprising this contact might seem to you as we have not met personally or had any dealings in the past, I humbly ask that you take due consideration of its importance and immense benefit. I duly apologize for infringing on your privacy, if this contact is not acceptable to you, for I make this proposal to you as a person of integrity. First and foremost I wish to introduce myself properly to you. I am Mr Patrick F.Massaquoi the son of late formal Liberia sport minister Mr Francois Massaquoi, who was killed while in office in 2001. After the death of my father, the Charles Taylor control government have been providing my family with security, but resently the united nations and the united state government asked the liberia head of state (Charles Taylor) and members of his cabinet to go on exile. During the tenure of Late Francois Massaquoi,(my father) he enriched and accumulated a lot of money while in office but unfortunately for him he did not leave long to enjoy these wealth. These funds that were lodged in banks accounts in our country has been frozen. However, my family is not too comfortable with our present government as my late father was a very close aide of Charles Taylor, and on this backdrop the new government might decided to recall the frozen money back to the government purse, with exception of the US$8.5M(Eight million, five hundred United State Dollars)that was deposited in a Finance/security firm undiscovered uptil date. But due to the sanction place on my family by the International community i cannot reach this money myself or withdraw it back to Liberia for use. We have jointly decided within the family to relocate this funds outside Liberia for investment purpose. This is the only way and means we can utilize this money, consequently, we beg for your assistance in investing this money on real-estate and any other viable venture you might suggest. I got your contact through the internet during my search for a partner and i hope you will not disappoint us in this our time of need. We have also agreed to reward you with 25% of the total amount as your share in this transaction after you might have claim this funds from the security firm. Finally, i require the following informations to facilitate the documentation that will effect the change of ownership with the Finance firm. (a) Your complete names. (b) Your mailing address and nationality, (c) Your Telephone/Fax numbers. Again, all arrangement and logistics of this transaction are in place and we shall remain greatful if you can assist us in this our time of need. Please contact me whether or not you are interested in assisting us. This will enable me scout for another partner in the event of non-interest on your part. Thanking you in anticipations of your kindness while looking forward to hear from you soon. Best regards, MR.PATRICK MASSAQUOI. Confidential e-mail: pm1234@katamail.com

From: Mrs.Monica Martins 23 Rivonia Road Sandton City Johannesburg South Africa Tel+27-83-238-3440 ATTN: Sir, My name is Mrs.Monica Martins, the wife of late Mr.Zulu Martins, of Zimbabwe. It might be a surprise to you where I got your contact address I got it from the net.I am using this opportunity to express my predicaments to you During the current crises against the farmers of Zimbabwe by the supporters of our President ROBERT MUGABE to claim all the white owned farms in our country, he ordered all the white farmers to surrender their farms to his party members and their followers. My husband was one of the best farmers in the country and knowing that he did not support the president's political ideology, the president's supporters invaded my husband's farm, burnt down everything, shot him and as a result of the wounds sustained, he became sick and died after two days. And after his death I became a widow over night with my only son (Frank Martins) and one daughter (Russ) decided to move out of Zimbabwe for the safety of our lives to South Africa. Before he died, he wrote his 'WILL' which reads: 'MY BELOVEED SON (Frank) I WISH TO DRAW YOUR ATTENTION TO THE SUM OF US$20.7 MILLION U.S DOLLARS WHICH I DEPOSITED IN A BOX WITH A SECURITY COMPANY IN JOHANNESBURG (SOUTH-AFRICA) IN CASE OF MY ABSENCE ON EARTH CAUSED BY DEATH ONLY' you should solicit for reliable foreign partner to assist you to transfer this money out of SOUTH-AFRICA for the family care and investment purposes I deposited the money in your name(Frank Martins)and it can be claimed by you with the help of a foreign partner using the deposit code.Your mother has all the documents.Take good care of your mother and your sister. >From the above you will understand that the lives and future of my family depends on this money as much as I will be very grateful if you can assist us. We are now living in South-Africa as POLITICAL ASYLUM SEEKERS and the financial law of SOUTH-AFRICA do not allow an ASYLUM SEEKER any financial right to operate such huge amount of money .In view of this I cannot invest this money in South-Africa hence I am asking you to assist us transfer this money out of South-Africa for investment purposes. [1]. For your efforts I am prepared to offer you 30% of the total fund while 70% will be kept for my family and I for investments.Immediately we establish trust within our selves, I would go ahead to give you all the details you might require to know about this fund. YOU CAN GIVE US A CALL ON +27-83-238-3440.YOU SEND YOUR RESPONSE TO (monica_mtf4@yahoo.co.uk ATTACHED IS A PHOTOGRAPH OF THE CONSIGNMENT MY LATE HUSBAND TOOK BEFORE DEPOSITING THE FUND WITH THE SECURTY COMPANY. PLEASE YOU CAN READ ABOUT PROBLEMS IN ZIMBABWE FROM THE LINKS BELOW. http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/918781.stm http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/715001.stm http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/1063785.stm BEST REGARDS, MRS MONICA MARTINS. (FOR THE FAMILY

>From princess ifeoma The Palace of King of Ogoni Kingdom, Ogoni Oil producing community, Rivers State Nigeria. PRINCESS Email ADDRESS:princess_ifeoma201@hotmail.com My lawyer phone number 234-8033072775 Email: him for more information please Dear Sir, I am Princess IFEOMA , daughter of HRH King Solomon Abonime, the king of Ogoni Kingdom. I am 25 years old and a graduate of Mass Communication. My father was the king of Ogoni Kingdom the highest oil producing area in Nigeria. He was in charge of reviving royalties from the multi-national oil companies and government on behalf of the oil producing communities in Nigeria. After the hanging of the Ogoni Nine(9) including Ken Saro Wiwa by the late dictator General Sani Abacha, my father suffered stroke and died in August27th last year. But before his death, he called me and told me he has sixthy six Million United States Dollars (USD66,000,000.00) cash in his possession, specially deposited in a Security vault company in eroupe. He advised me not to tell anybody except my mother who is the last wife of the (8) eight wives that he married. My mother did not bear any male child for him. Which implies that all my father?s properties, companies e.t.c., we have no share in them because my mother has no male child according to African Tradition. My father therefore secretly gave me all the relevant documents of the said money, and told me that I should use this money with my mother and my younger sisters because he knows that tradtionally, if he dies we cannnot get anything, as inheritance. He importantly advised me that I should seek foreign assistannce and that I should not invest this money here in Nigeria because of his other wives and male children who happen to be my elders. I am soliciting for your immediate assistance to get a Bungalow for us, where I will live with my mother and two younger sisters and further advise me where and how I will invest the balance money overseas, possibly on products of your company and other profitable ventures. I believe that by the special grace of God, you will help us move this money out of eroupe to your country where we can invest this money judiciously with you. You are entitled to a reasonable part of this money based on our agreement, and God will bless you as you help us. PLease reply through my e-mail Looking forward to hear from you as soon as possibleand also my lawyer email address:(adekunle_smithmike@hotmail.com). Regards. Princess Ifeoma. NB This is my email address:princess201@fastermail.com

FROM: BARRISTER DENNIS KERRY ESQ. DENN KERRY & CO ATTORNEYS AT LAW NIGERIA. EMAIL: denniskerry@web-mail.com.ar WE NEED YOUR ASSISTANCE. ----------------------- DEAR FRIEND, COMPLIMENTS OF THE SEASON. GRACE AND PEACE AND LOVE FROM THIS PART OF THE ATLANTIC TO YOU. I HOPE MY LETTER DOES NOT CAUSE YOU TOO MUCH EMBARRASSMENT AS I WRITE TO YOU IN GOOD FAITH BASED ON THE CONTACT ADDRESS GIVEN TO ME BY A FRIEND WHO WORKS AT THE NIGERIAN EMBASSY IN YOUR COUNTRY. PLEASE EXCUSE MY INTRUSION INTO YOUR PRIVATE LIFE. I AM BARRISTER DENNIS KERRY ESQ. I REPRESENT MOHAMMED ABACHA, SON OF THE LATE GEN.SANI ABACHA, WHO WAS THE FORMER MILITARY HEAD OF STATE IN NIGERIA. HE DIED IN 1998. SINCE HIS DEATH, THE FAMILY HAS BEEN LOSING A LOT OF MONEY DUE TO VINDICTIVE GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS WHO ARE BENT ON DEALING WITH THE FAMILY. BASED ON THIS THEREFORE, THE FAMILY HAS ASKED ME TO SEEK FOR A FOREIGN PARTNER WHO CAN WORK WITH US AS TO MOVE OUT THE TOTAL SUM OF US$75,000,000.00 ( SEVENTY FIVE MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS ), PRESENTLY IN THEIR POSSESSION. THIS MONEY WAS OF COURSE, ACQUIRED BY THE LATE PRESIDENT AND IS NOW KEPT SECRETLY BY THE FAMILY. THE SWISS GOVERNMENT HAS ALREADY FROZEN ALL THE ACCOUNTS OF THE FAMILY IN SWITZERLAND, AND SOME OTHER COUNTRIES WOULD SOON FOLLOW TO DO THE SAME. THIS BID BY SOME GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS TO DEAL WITH THIS FAMILY HAS MADE IT NECESSARY THAT WE SEEK YOUR ASSISITANCE IN RECEIVING THIS MONEY AND IN INVESTING IT ON BEHALF OFTHE FAMILY. THIS MUST BE A JOINT VENTURE TRANSACTION AND WE MUST ALL WORK TOGETHER. SINCE THIS MONEY IS STILL CASH, EXTRA SECURITY MEASURES HAVE BEEN TAKEN TO PROTECT IT FROM THEFT OR SEIZURE, PENDING WHEN AGREEMENT IS REACHED ON WHEN AND HOW TO MOVE IT INTO ANY OF YOUR NOMINATED BANK ACCOUNTS. I HAVE PERSONALLY WORKED OUT ALL MODALITIES FOR THE PEACEFUL CONCLUSION OF THIS TRANSACTION. THE TRANSACTION DEFINITELY WOULD BE HANDLED IN PHASES AND THE FIRST PHASE WILL INVOLVE THE MOVING OF US$25,000,000.00( TWENTY FIVE MILLION UNITEDSTATES DOLLARS ). MY CLIENTS ARE WILLING TO GIVE YOU A REASONABLE PERCENTAGE OF THIS MONEY AS SOON AS THE TRANSACTIONIS CONCLUDED. I WILL, HOWEVER, BASED ON THE GROUNDS THAT YOU ARE WILLING TO WORK WITH US AND ALSO ALL CONTENTIOUS ISSUES DISCUSSED BEFORE THE COMMENCEMENT OF THIS TRANSACTION. YOU MAY ALSO DISCUSS YOUR PERCENTAGE BEFORE WE START TO WORK. AS SOON AS I HEAR FROM YOU, I WILL GIVE YOU ALL NECESSARY DETAILS AS TO HOW WE INTEND TO CARRY OUT THE WHOLE TRANSACTION. PLEASE, DO NOT ENTERTAIN ANY FEARS,AS ALL NECESSARY MODALITIES ARE IN PLACE, AND I ASSURE YOU OF ALL SUCCESS AND SAFETY IN THIS TRANSACTION. PLEASE, THIS TRANSACTION REQUIRES ABSOLUTE CONFIDENTIALITY AND YOU WOULD BE EXPECTED TO TREAT IT AS SUCH UNTIL THE FUNDS ARE MOVED OUT OF THIS COUNTRY. PLEASE, YOU WILL ALSO IGNORE THIS LETTER AND RESPECT OUR TRUST IN YOU BY NOT EXPOSING THIS TRANSACTION, EVEN IF YOU ARE NOT INTERESTED.LOOK FORWARD TO WORKING WITH YOU. THANK YOU. PLEASE,REPLY IMMIDIATELY TO MY PRIVATE EMAIL: denniskerry@web-mail.com.ar TRULY YOURS, BARRISTER DENNIS KERRY ESQ.

KALLA KABILA JOHANNESBURG SOUTH - AFRICA Dear Sir, I know you will be surprise to receive this lette from me. But this letter is a request from a Family in dare need of asistance. I am KALLA KABILA from Democratic Republic of Congo (DRC), the son of Mrs. MERCY KABILA, the youngest wife of the late President LAURENT KABILA, who was murdered recently. I got your name and address from a business Desk in Chamber of Commerce and Industry in Johannesburg. And I on behalf of my widowed mother Mrs. Mercy Kabila decided to solicit for your assistance. President Laurent Kabila got married to my mother who is now a widow currently residing in Johannesburg, South Africa, with me as the only child of the woman. But before his death he ?Willed? to us some certain portion of his wealth including some amount of fund due to the love he had for my mother this fund US$24m TWENTY FOUR million united States Dollars was deposited in a box in one of the well rec! ognized Security Company in South Africa, as valuables. He instructed us to solicit for the assistance of a reliable and sincere foreign partner to assist us transfer this money out of South Africa for investment purposes. Fortunately enough, I, my mother and the late President were the only people aware of this. Moreover, this box was deposited in my name and I can claim it alone with a deposited secret code of which my mother is still with the documents . Therefore, we need your assistance in transferring this huge sum of(US$24M) TWENTY FOUR Million United States Dollars inherited from my late father into your personal or company?s account and please bear in mind that the entire life and future of me and my mother depend on this fund. I will be grateful if you can assist us. For now, we live in South Africa as asylum seekers and due to this circumstances behind this fund and some family crisis we cannot invest this money in South Africa. Fo! r your effort we are prepared to offer you 20% of the total su! m, whi le 10% will be set aside for any expenses incurred during this transaction. Please, note that this transaction is 100% risk free and the major thing I demand from you is your assurance for the safety of this money when it finally gets to you. Further information and arrangement will commence as soon as trust, confidence and good relationship are established. I shall be grateful if you maintain the confidentiality of this matter. Please confirm your interest via my e-mail address. And dont forget to drop your phone and fax number for easeir communication. Best regards KALLA KABILA.

Dear Beloveth, I am Prince Fayad W. Bolkiah, the eldest son of Prince Jefri Bolkiah, former Finance Minister of Brunei, the tiny oil-rich sultanate on the Gulf Island. I will save your time by not amplifying my extended royal family history, which has already been disseminated by the international media during the controversial dispute that erupted between my father and his step brother, the sultan of Brunei Sheik Muda Hassanal Bolkiah. As you may know from the international media, the sultan had accused my father of financial mismanagement and impropriety of US$14.8 Billion dollars. This was as a result of the Asian financial crisis that made my father company Amedeo Development Company and government owned Brunei Investment Company to be declared bankrupt during his tenure in office. However my father was kept under house arrest, his bank accounts and private properties including a crude oil export refinery were later confiscated by the sultanate. Furthermore, during this unfortunate period i was advised to evacuate my immediate family outside the sultanate to avoid further prosecution from the sultan and his security operatives, but before I could do that I was placed under house arrest by the Sultan and i have no access to a phone but I have a Palm V hand-held computer from which I am sending you this mail. Before my In-castration, I went ahead to dispatch the sum of Five Hundred Million United States Dollars US$500 Million in cash under special arrangement into the custody of different Private security and Trustee companys for safe keeping abroad. The money where splitted and kept in the following countries in this proportion: US$50 Million is in Switzerland, US$100 Million is in London, US$100 Million is in Malaysia, US$80 Million is in United Arab Emirate and the balance US$US170 Million is in Holland. Hence I seek your good assistance to invest these funds into profitable investment in your country to facilitate future survival for my family abroad.I have decided to offer 10% of these funds to you as compensation for your strong cooperation. Please I count on your absolute confidentiality,transparency and trust while looking forward to your prompt reply towards a swift conclusion of this business transaction. I remain yours sincerely Prince Fayad .W. Bolkiah Brunei Darussalam. please reply to my privite email address-ROYALMAJESTY@K.RO

HELLO DEAR, MY NAME IS JOE M. DOUGLAS, I AM A DIRECTOR IN THE FINANCE DEPARTMENT IN THE NIGERIA NATIONAL PETROLEUM CORPORATION (NNPC). I KNOW MY MAIL WILL COME TO YOU AS A SURPRISE AND ALSO EMBARRASING, BUT I BEG FOR YOUR SINCERE UNDERSTANDING. I WANT YOU TO HAVE A GOOD UNDERSTANDING WITH ME AND HANDLE THIS URGENT BUSINESS PROPOSAL WITH ATMOST SERIOUSNESS AND CAREFULNESS FOR OUR MUTUAL BENEFIT. THIS BUSINESS INVOLVES US$22MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS) WHICH I WANT US TO SECURE IN YOUR PERSONAL OR COMPANY ACCOUNT BY TRANSFERRING IT FROM THE CENTRAL BANK OF NIGERIA (CBN) TO YOUR ACCOUNT.THIS US$22MILLION IS AN OVER-INVOICE OF A CONTRACT EXECUTED IN MY CORPORATION IN 2003. THE ORIGINAL FOREIGN CONTRACTOR WHO EXECUTED THIS CONTRACT. HE HAS BEEN PAID HIS REAL PAYMENT WHAT IS LEFT NOW IS THIS EXCESS US$22MILLION. I WANT TO ENCOURAGE YOU NOT TO BE AFRAID, WITH YOUR UNDERSTANDING AND DILIGENCE WE SHALL SECURE THE MONEY WITHOUT ANY TRACE IN LESS THAN 21 WORKING DAYS. EVERY THING ABOUT THE CONTRACT IS WELL KNOWN TO ME. WHAT IS NEEDED FROM YOU NOW ARE THE FOLLOWING:YOUR NAME AND COMPANY NAME IF ANY, YOUR PRIVATE PHONE, FAX AND EMAIL ADDRESS AND THE PARTICULARS OF THE BANK ACCOUNT WHERE YOU WANT THE MONEY TO BE TRANSFERRED. ON THE CONCLUSSION OF THIS BUSINESS I WILL VISIT YOUR COUNTRY AND THE MONEY WILL BE SHARED AS FOLLOWS: 25% FOR YOU, 70% FOR ME AND THE REMAINING 5% WILL BE USED TO PAY BACK ANY EXPENCES THAT MAY BE INCURED ON THE PROCESS LIKE PHONE BILL. ONCE MORE I WANT TO ASSURE YOU THAT THIS BUSINESS IS RISK FREE, YOU SHOULD NOT FEAR FOR I HAVE EVERY DATA ABOUT THIS MONEY BUT YOU MUST KEEP EVERYTHING CONFIDENTIAL. AND AGAIN, I WILL LIKE TO INVEST MY OWN SHARE IN YOUR COUNTRY, I LIKE REAL ESTATE OR HOTELS BUSINESS, SO I DON'T KNOW HOW THIS BUSINESS ARE IN YOUR COUNTRY? I AM EXPECTING YOUR IMMEDIATE REPLY THROUGH MY PRIVATE EMAIL ADDRESS: engrmdjoe@yahoo.co.uk THANKS ENGR. JOE M. DOUGLAS. __________________________________ Do you Yahoo!? Yahoo! Photos: High-quality 4x6 digital prints for 25¢ http://photos.yahoo.com/ph/print_splash

BURNOR DICKINS ABIDJAN COTE D'IVOIRE. Dearest one, I appologise for any inconvinient that this my mail may cause to you but it is the only way that I can communicate with you and explain my situation despite we have not met or known each other before but I believe through the humanitarian assistance we will have the opportunity to know each other better. I am BURNOR DICKINS, the only son of late Mr and Mrs ANTHONY DICKINS, a citizen of SIRRA LEONE and my sister LILIAN DICKINS. Our father was a very wealthy cocoa merchant in Abidjan, the economic capital of Ivory Coast before he was poisoned to death by his business associates on one of their outing to discuss on a business deal. When our mother died on the 21st October 1991,our father took me and my junior sister special because we are motherless. Before the death of our father on 30th June 2002 in a private hospital here in Abidjan. He secretly called us on his bedside and told us that he has a sum of $ 9.2,000.000 (Nine Million,Two Hundred Thousand united states dollar) deposited in a private financial and security company here in his name. He also explained to us that it was because of this wealth and some huge amount of money his business associates supposed to balance him from the deal they had that he was poisoned by his business associates, that we should seek for a God fearing foreign partner in a country of our choice who can come down and claim this fund from the security company for us and use it for investment purpose, (such as real estate management). We are honourably seeking your assistance in the following ways. ( 1) To act as the foreign partner of our father by claiming this fund from the security company for further transfer and investment to your designated bank account abroad. ( 2) To serve as the guardian of this since I am a young man of 25 years and my younger sister just 21. Moreover , we are willing to offer you 10% of the sum as compensation for effort input after the successful transfer of this fund to your designated account in your country overseas. Please we strictly apply for the confidenciality of this transaction for our personal security.Kindly reply me to my personal email address :- bunor_dickins@lycos.com Anticipating to hear from you soon. Thanks and God Bless. Best regards, BUNOR DICKINS.

Dear Friend, First, I must solicit your strictest confidence in this transaction. This is by the virtue of its nature as being utterly confidential. I am sure and have confidence of your ability and reliability to prosecute a transaction of this great magnitude. We want to transfer (US$150,000,000.00) One hundred and fifty million United States Dollars from an investment bank in Port Au-Prince, Haiti to a reliable overseas account.I solicit your assistance to enable us transfer the said amount into your safe account for onward investment. You can either provide us with an existing account or to set up a new bank account immediately to receive this money, even an empty a/c can serve to receive this money, as long as you will remain honest to me till the end for this important business trusting in you and believing that you will never let us down either now or in the future. My name is Rev.Ngo Ngoly. I am the Head of International Operations of a prime commercial bank here in Bangui, Central African Republic. I have been mandated by a senior Aide of the exiled Leader of Republic of Haiti, Jean Bertrand Aristide who have just been abducted and forced to exile in Bangui, CAR together with his families and aides by the American and French government, to solicit for a reliable individual or company whom we can present as a front to effect the transfer of this funds out of Haiti. The owner has secured this amount with a fictitious name at a bank in Haiti. This Aide has equally assured me that with the assistance of their colleagues who are still holding most key post in the financial power bases of their country, it is not a problem to have the funds transferred out of the investment bank in Haiti to any other part of the world except my county, CAR. It is not a good idea to transfer this amount to my country directly from Haiti due to the fact that my country is one of the poorest nations in the whole world. Secondly, the whole world is aware that Mr.Aristide has just arrived in this country some few days ago to live in exile, it must definitely raise a big dust when the money arrives here. With my position and influence in the bank over here, the money can be transferred to any foreign reliable account that you can provide within 10 days with assurance that this money will be left untouched until our physical arrival in your country for sharing. I have secretly discussed this business with my colleague who also holds a strategic portfolio in my bank and he has willingly agreed to join the train. The 20% of this amount will be for you while the remaining balance will be for all of us here. Please reply immediately if you are interested in this business but if you wish not to participate in the deal for any reason that will only be known to you and kindly keep all this details strictly to your self. I will provide you with the full details and our mode of the operations once I receive your positive response in these regards. Best regards, Rev.Ngo Ngoly

Allstate Trust Bank 16\17, Oyin Jolayemi Street, Victoria Island Lagos Website: http://www.allstatesbanking.com Dear Sir, I hope this will not meet you as a surprise, as I know that I have not heard any previous corressponding with you, but have taken interest in you, as a result of my choice of investment. I am Okpara Addey, Managing Director, Corporate Audit ,Allstate Trust Bank, Nigeria. This is an urgent and very confidential business proposition. I am seeking your assistance here to enable me transfer and invest the sum of $24M in LANDED PROPERTIES there in your country. The source of these funds is as follows: On June 6, 2002,a Foreign Oil consultant/contractor with the Nigerian Institute of Mining and Metallurgy, Mr.Steve Warren, made a numbered time(Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at US$24,000,000.00,(Twenty-Four Million Dollars) in my branch. Upon maturity,I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month,we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the Nigerian Institute of Mining and Metallurgy, that Mr.Steve Warren died from an automobile accident. On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL, and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr.Steve Warren did not declare any next of kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit documents in my Bank. This sum of US$24,000,000.00 has carefully been fixed in my bank for safekeeping. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to the Nigerian Law, at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that, since Mr.Steve Warren is a Foreigner, I will like you as a Foreigner to stand in as the owner of the money which was fixed deposited in my bank. I am writing you because I as a public servant, I cannot operate a foreign account, and moreso, my choice of investment, which is one of the reasons why I would want you to assist me, as I will need your assistance to invest these funds in the Real Estate business, to which which any PROFIT RETURN will be shared under an agreed percentage between the both of us, outside the normal percentage to be agreed on for your assistance. I want to present you as the owner of the funds so you can be able to claim them. This is simple.I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address, as well as phone and fax numbers,so that all the neccessary document can be prepared , which will put you in place as the beneficiary of the funds. The money will be moved out for us to share in the ratio of 80% for me and 20% for you. The paperwork for this transaction will be done in accordance to the law of the land and this guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately via my email address at: amokpara007@yahoo.co.uk, and upon your response,I shall provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please observe utmost confidentiality, and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in Real Estate within your country. This is the major reason why I have contacted you. Due to the nature and confidentiality in this Transaction, it should be accorded all the neccesary confidentiality required, as my job will be at stake in the event of any eventuality. I hope that this will meet you in a good state of mind. I will pause for now, as I await your urgent response Regards. Okpara Addey

Dear Friend, Greetings and complement of the season. My name is Mr. Colins Brown. I am the eastern manager of united bank of africa Plc (UBA),Abuja branch Nigeria.This letter might surprise you because we have not met neither in person nor by correspondence,but please you should exercise some patience and read through my message. I have a very urgent and confidential business proposal for you. I want to transfer out $USD 26 million ( TWENTY SIX MILLION U.S DOLLARS) from our bank. I have the courage to look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable for this important Business,believing that you will never let me down either now or in future. HOW THE MONEY CAME ABOUT: There is an account opened in this bank in 1980 and since 1990 nobody has operated on this account again,after going through some old files in the records I discovered that if I do not remitte this money out urgently it will be forfeited for nothing.The owner of this account is Mr. Jack Hamilton, he is a foreigner and the manager of of petrol chemical service,a chemical Engineer by proffession and he died since 1990, and since then no other person knows about this account or anything concerning it.secondly he did not clearify his next of kin in his deposition form when he deposited this fund in our bank.The account has no other beneficiary and my investigation proved to me as well that his company does not know anything about this account and the amount involved is (U.S.$ 26,000,000.00). I want to tranfer this money into a safe foreign account abroad but i don't know any foreigner,I am contacting you as a foreigner because this money can not be approved to any local bank here but can only be approved to a foreign account because the money is in u.s dollars and the former owner of the account (MR.JACK HAMILTON) is a foreigner too. I know that this message will come to you as a surprise as we don't know ourself before,but be sure that it is real and a genuine business.I believe in god that you will never let me down in this business,you are the only person that i have contacted for this business for now,so please reply urgently so that we can receive this money into a foreign account or any account of your choice where the fund will be remmited. I am contacting you because of the need to involve a foreigner with a foreign account as the real beneficiary,I need your co-operation to makethis work fine,because the management of our bank is ready to approve this payment to any foreigner who has the correct information to this account which i will give to you when sure of your capability to handle such amount with instrict confidence and trust,and according to my instructions and my advice for our mutual benefit because I don't want to make any mistake. I need your strong assurance and trust, I shall also destroy all documents concerning this transactions immidiately we received this money leaving no trace to any place. I will use my position and influence on other staffs to effect legal approvals and onward transfer of this money to your account with appropriate clearance from foreign payment department,with assurance that this money will be intact pending my physical arrival in your country for the sharing and other investment. Finally,at the conclusion of this business,you will be given 25% of the total ammount,70% will be for me ,while 5% will be for expenses both parties might have incured during the process of this transaction. I look forward to your earliest reply through my e-mail address: brown_colins@uymail.com}. Thanks and God bless you. Yours truly, Mr. Colins Brown

Date: Fri, 14 May 2004 06:59:43 -0400 From: monicayangani250@netscape.net To: monicayangani250@netscape.net Subject: Urgent and confidential (Assistance Needed) >From Monica Yangani Email monicayangani250@netscape.net Tel 27 8046828612 ATTN:Sir/Madam   I know you will be surprised to hear from me, but please consider this as a request from family in dire need of assistance.I am Mrs.Monica Yangani, writing to you from Government Reserved Area (GRA).I got your contact information from the Republic of Congo Chamber of Commerce and Industry. When I was searching for a reliable individual or private company that can assist me to transfer a reasonable amount in a safe account abroad on behalf of my late husband, two sons and two daughters. I decided to solicit your assistance to transfer this sum of US $20 Million (Twenty Million, United States Dollars)inherited from my late husband in to your personal company’s account or private account.Before his death, he was a Brigadier in charge of arms and ammunition procurement for the (DRC) army. In his WILL?he specifically draws my attention to this US$ 20 Million which he deposited in a safe box in Private Security Company in South Africa.  During the war, he was very dedicated and committed to winning the war against the rebels until when he found out that some Senior Army Officers and Government Functionaries were busy helping themselves with government funds and properties and sending them toforeign countries. Due to this, he and his former special advisers to the president were assigned by the President (Laurent Kabila) to purchase arms in South Africa, they saw this as a golden opportunity and diverted the money and divided it and he got a total sum of US $20 Million. He deposited the box in my son’s name and him alone with the deposit code canclaim it. I will be grateful if you can assist us now. I want you to do for us as an international partner to help us transfer this money which is in a safety box in the Security Company using your name as the beneficiary of this sum. You can contact  me or my son (George Yangani)  in South Africa on  this number+27 8046828612. Then, we will tell you more details about it. We are in position to inform you of the whole procedures mapped out of the transfer of this money.We have agreed to give you 25% of the total sum for your assistance, 5% for any expenses that might occur from both sides in the course of this transaction,while the remaining 70% will be for my son's investment, which you will assist him to do abroad. Further information and arrangement will commence as soon as trust, confidence and good relationship will be established and safety of this fund assured when transferred to your account.Please treat this matter with utmost urgency.May Allah (God) bless you as I earnestly hope for your assistance. Best Regards Monica Yangani (for the family) __________________________________________________________________ Introducing the New Netscape Internet Service. Only $9.95 a month -- Sign up today at http://isp.netscape.com/register Netscape. Just the Net You Need. New! Netscape Toolbar for Internet Explorer Search from anywhere on the Web and block those annoying pop-ups. Download now at http://channels.netscape.com/ns/search/install.jsp

Dearest friend From: Mrs. Juliana Faith Peters Bless the children of God. I am the above named person but now undergoing medical treatment now. I am married to Dr.Alan George Peters who worked with south africa embassy in nigeria for nine years before he died in the year 2001. We were married for eleven years without a child. He died after a brief illness that lasted for only four days. Before his death we were both born again Christians.Since his death I decided not to re-marry or get a child outside my matrimonial home which the Bible is against.When my late husband was alive he deposited the sum of$27.6Million (twenty-seven Million six hundred thousand U.S. Dollars) with one finance/security company in Europe. Presently, this money is still with the Security Company. Recently, my Doctor told me that I would not last for the next three months due to cancer problem. Though what disturbs me most is my stroke. Having known my condition I decided to donate this fund to church or better still a christian individual that will utilize this money the way I am going to instruct here in. I want a church or individual that will use this to fund churches, orphanages and widows propagating the word of God and to ensure that the house of God is maintained. The Bible made us to understand that Blessed is the hand that giveth. I took this decision because I don?t have any child that will inherit this money and my husband relatives are not Christians and I don?t want my husband?s hard earned money to be misused by unbelievers. I don?t want a situation where this money will be used in an ungodly manner, hence the reason for taking this bold decision. I am not afraid of death hence I know where I am going. I know that I am going to be in the bossom of the Lord. Exodus 14 VS 14 says that the lord will fight my case and I shall hold my peace. I don?t need any telephone communication in this regard because of my health,and because of the presence of my husband?s relatives around me always. I don?t want them to know about this development. With God all things are possible. As soon as I receive your reply I shall give you the contact of the Finance/Security Company Europe. I will also issue you a letter of authority that will empower you as the original- beneficiary of this fund. I want you and the church to always pray for me because the lord is my shephard. My happiness is that I lived a life of a worthy Christian. Whoever that wants to serve the Lord must serve him in spirit and truth. Please always be prayerful all through your life. Any delay in your reply will give me room in sourcing for a church or christian individual for this same purpose. Please assure me that you will act accordingly as I stated herein. Hoping to hear from you. please reply me through this email; <mrsjfpeters@postmaster.co.uk> Remain blessed in the name of the Lord. Yours in Christ, Mrs Juliana faith peters. __________________________________________________ Broadband from an unbeatable £15.99! http://www.tiscali.co.uk/products/broadband/home.html?code=SM-NL-11AM

Dear, In my quest for a reliable and reputable person to engage in a mutual business relationship, I got your email through my retune search for a suitable preson that can help me in my predicament. And I sincerely apologies for my contacting you in this form please bear with me. And accept my indecent introduction, it was bore out of my despiration to get off my inadequcy to takle my immediate problems. . As a matter of introduction, I am the only surviving daughter of late Chief Ibrahim Sessey Cola, the paramount chief of Munsh District of Sierra Leone who was killed on 8th January 1999, by the trigger happy rebels. Most unfortunately for me I came from a polygamous family, and a student but out of school because of this problem. During my father's lifetime he was actively engaged in ILLEGAL MINING AND SALES OF DIAMOND, from where he made his enormous wealth. Prior to my father's death, he left a WILL with his lawyer, which was made available to us upon observation and conclusion of his burial. And as the only daughter most of his properties were willed to me, most importantly is the sum of US$35M (thirty five million United States dollars)which he deposited in a private security company in Europe which is also among my inheritance from my deceased father. I obviously know that it might be very difficult for you to believe my story but it is what is really happing to me now for upon introduction of this WILL all my father's relatives have not been at peace with me, they were not happy how my father assigned all the enormous wealth to me. As a poor girl, they have systematically and forcefully collected from me all documents of the properties 'willed' to me. Not including a huge amount of money at ARE Bank of sierra Leone which they could not withdrawn due to a court order restraining either party from making withdrawals pending the determination of a Litigation filled by my father's relations challenging the WILL. Now since I am too hard for them{ the relatives) to subdue, they were making attempts to kill me so that nobody can stop them from carrying out their act, as they have succeeded in killing my mother last year. Infact the fear and warning of killing me has well griped me so much that I could not bear it anymore, hence I ran away from our family house to live with a school mate of mine whose father is a military man,with advise of my father*s lawyer to safeguard my life. Considering my age and inexperienced in business and investment procedures, please I want you to help me in retreving this fund which I will use to invest in a profitable venture in a country where there is Economic and political stability. And if I may ask....... 1 .Is your country good for such investment??? Because I do not want to make mistake. 2 Can you help me???? without trying to double cross me If you assent to help me in this regard, we shall then discuss what I will give you in return for your assistance. And before I disclose anything, we will firstly have to sign a Memorandum of Understanding upon which you shall proceed to the official premises of the Security Company to take delivery of the funds which I will use for forfurther investment with your help or with the help of another person pending what comes out between us. Please put into consideration my incapabilities in some respects, therefore I would prefer all correspondence to be through Email which is more secret and confidential, as I can not use my school mate father's telephone to avoid jeopardizing my staythere. Every document concerning these funds is with me, upon request I will sent it to you if need be. . Should you not be willing to collaborate with me in this, please inform me urgently to enable me look for another person. Or you email me at princesshasihatu@yahoo.com.hk. Thanks in anticipation to your positive response. Regards. PRINCESS HASIHATU SESSEY COLA.

To: President/Ceo From:Daniel Kabila Johannesburg,South Africa

INVESTMENT OFFER

Dear Sir

In appreciation of your esteemed contact received through a reliable source and the choice of your country I wish to introduce myself, I am Daniel Kabila the son of the late Democratic Republic of Congo President Laurent Desire Kabila of the blessed memory. I know this letter might come to you as a surprise but I honestly do not intend to surprise you. I write this letterin respect of my intention to invest the sum of US$28M(Twenty Eight Million United State Dollars) with you. I inherited this money from my mother. This money was got through the smuggling and sale of Diamond and Timber when my father was the head of state.

My mother though not her legal wife used her privilege position to engage in the business of Diamond and Timber since she knows that her survival will depend on how much she can get out of the privilege situation.

When my father was assassinated on 16TH Jan. 01 by one of his bodyguards Lt.Rashidi Kasereke through the conspiracy of some top army officers that wanted to topple him I escaped to South Africa because of the fear that I might be arrested by my half brother Lt. General Joseph Kabila the present head of state. Actually his mother and my mother are not in the best of relationship because of who among them will be the first lady tussle and this ultimately affected us their children.Considering the relationship between South Africa and the Democratic Republic of Congo new government, my mother advised me to leave For South Africa for security reason, while the funds were deposited with a security Company in Madrid Spain. On getting to South Africa where I have been living since then as a political refugee I am seeking for a reliable foreigner who can assist me in moving this money out for safe banking and profitable investment. Honestly I contacted you because I don't want to invest this money in South Africa due to my status here as a political Refugee. And moreover I wouldn't want to take risk because this money is all that I and my Mother is depending on because My half brother has seized all my father's assets and money and left I and my mother empty handed without knowing about this funds deposited at the Security Company in Madrid Spain so that is why I decided that investing this money abroad should be the best investment for me. I will be honored if I can be given the privilege of investing this money with your help. In view of this plight, I expect you to be trustworthy and kind enough to respond to this distress call to save my mother and I from a hopeless future.

And if you agree, I hereby agree to compensate your sincere and candid effort in this regard with 20% of the total money and annual 5% of the after tax returns on investment for the first three years. Thereafter, the term shall be varied. 5% for expenses, which may arise during the transaction, fax and phone bills inclusive.$28million US Dollars. when the money ($28million) is moved into your discrete account, you will be allowed to draw 20% your favor, while the remaining 70% will be invested meaningfully for our future if possible in your area of business and deterrents sectors of the Economy in your country which are dividends yielding. Whatever your decision is please reach me immediately through my private phone or Email, and keep this letter tight secret for the interest of my family.

Best Regards,

Daniel Kabila.

---------------------------------------------------------------- This email is powered by YEHEY!Mail - Your Online Mailman Get your free 6MB web based mail now!

FROM: MRS, FATIMA RASHEED KHALIFA ADDRESS:NORTH ZONE BAZRA IRAQ.) Please permit me your little endulgence to solicit for your unreserved attention, based on my urgly condition of life though one with almighty Allah is with majority. I am Mrs Fatima R. Khalifa, a widow to Late Sheik Mohammed Rasheed Khalifa. I am 64 years old of a born muslim faith. Presently i am suffering from long time cancer of the breast, from all indications, my condition is really deteriorating and is quite obvious that I won't live more than six months according to my doctor,because the cancer stage has gotten to a very bad stage. My late husband was killed during the invasion of collition forces from American and Britain in Iraq, unfortunately he died leaving behind a huge sum of money which he had looted from a supply of ammunition to the ex- Saddam Hussein Government. This money is now in the vault of a private security company oversea to be precise in Holland, but due to my present bad condition of health as I am suffering from Cancer of the breast its quite impossible for me to travel that distance to receive this money. To this effect I have writen a letter throgh my family lawyer requesting for the transfer of this box to Dubai United Arab Emirates pending when I can succeed in getting a trust and reliable person to utilize this money. Although, today, I have received a signal from the security company notifying me of the approval to transfer the consignment through their agent. Therefore, let me receive your total support and security assurance that the consignment will be save in your hand . I want you to understand that a neither have any son nor have any person to entrust this money to which I know that it is better make use of a total foreigner to achieve my aim. Atleast had it been that during the period of our marriage we could produce any child, my late husband was very wealthy and after his death, his offspring will inherited all his business and wealth. I got your contact through a desperate and personal search on the web, for someone I could really trust and I have prayed over it. Therefore my desire now is to contribute part of this wealth to the propagation of islam and in assisting the less-privileged Muslim faithful in Africa,Asia,Europe and in all Arab-Nation's . I have discussed this with my Family Lawyer hence I am willing to donate part of it atleast 40% of the total sum of US$16,250,00000. (sixteen Million two hundred and fifty thousand US Dollars)for the development of the holy work of islam, as well as distribution's to aid muslim's faithfuls. Please I want you to note that, this fund is lying in a Security Company in Holland The Netherlands so it can be transferred to you upon your readiness to co-join with me in this transaction and secure the money. For that, my lawyer will file application's that will back you up for the transfer of the money in your name as the beneficiary only if you promise to use this funds/my donations judiciouly for the said purpose. Therefore,I have decided to set-aside 40% for the promotion of holy islam and the work of Allah. while 30% will be retuned back to me through my lawyer so that I can offset my bills in the hospital because of the cancer treatment. If you have to die says the Allah, keep fit and I will give you the crown of life. May the Grace of Allah be our guide and be my refuge when i leave this world. Moreso,I further decided to offer you 20% While the remaining 10% is for the expenses incured during the facillitation of the project. Yours in Allah, Mrs Fatima Rasheed Khalifa

From:DR.FRANK OBI. E-mail:frankobi1@frankobi.net Tel:234-8042137980 19/05/2004 We are making this contact with you because of the reliable information available to us concerning your reputation and that of your company. This business request may seem strange, but I crave your indulgence and pray you, view it seriously as we are convinced that you would be capable to provide us with a solution to a moneytransfer of Thirty Two Million, Five hundred thousand United State Dollars (US$32,500,000.00) First of all I am an accountant and Auditor of the Petroleum (special) Trust Fund (N.N.P.C) the Apex Department of the Oil Industry in Nigeria. I am also a member of its Foreign Contract Tenders Committee (FCTC). My principal Job/function has to do with the Appraisal and Approval of payment of contract awarded by this parastatal. In the course of my duties, I discovered various over inflated contract values totaling US$32.5Million. The said amount emanated from deliberate over invoicing of old projects executed by some foreign firms through some government officials.These officials have since been moved or retired following the inauguration of the new administration. After due consultation with key members of the Tenders Committee (FCTC), I was mandated to seek and arrange with a trusted foreign National who can assist us in transferring the above state amount out of Nigeria. Now that all the contracts have been paid following the completion and commissioning of the various contract, the above mentioned sum through approved is still floating. We decided to transfer this money to a safe and trusted bank accounts with a very reliable person to assist us after which the funds be share in the understated ratio. Your assistance is needed for two main reasons; (i) As government employees ,we are not permitted by the Nigeria law to operate foreignaccounts. (ii)Since the initial contracts were executed by the foreign firms, only a foreign firm can make claims or as a beneficiary for the purpose of transferring the money out of Nigeria. We have unanimously agreed to compensate you with 35% of the total sum ( US$32.5Million ) if you are willing to render us your assistance as regards the transfer .it was also agreed that 5% shall be set aside to offset incidental expenses that might be incurred by either of us course of offsetting this transfer. The remaining 60% shall be our due share. All necessary arrangements required for a speedy conclusion of this transaction have been put in place with top officials of the Nigeria Federal Ministry of Finance and the Central Bank of Nigeria to enable us conclude the whole transaction within a very shortspace of time. What is required of you is first to furnish us with the following through my email address. 1.) Bank details to be used (that is banks name and account number ) 2.) The beneficiary's name. 3.) Your private / official telephone and fax number. While promising you a smooth and hitch -free transfer of this fund into the account nominated by you, we want you to know that this is very sensitive transaction which should not be disclosed to any other party. This is very important because this deals involves some high ranking Nigeria Government Officials who would not want to be involved in any form of scandal.We however trust that this will be the beginning of a lasting business relationship between you and us as we shall appreciate your advice on the investment opportunities in your line of business or any other type of viable business in your country. If this deal interest you,reply me immediately through my personal E-mail: frankobi1@frankobi.net or call me on my receiving number:234-8042137980 for more details. Best regards as we look forward to hearing from you soonest. Your Sincerely, DR FRANK OBI

From:Dan Wilson Kenya Commercial Bank City Centre, P.O. Box 44252,Nairobi. Kenya Email:dan@danielm.org Dear Sir/Madam, May I crave your indulgence to open this business discussion with you by an informal letter of this sort. It is pertinent that a business of this magnitude should have commenced properly with a formal meeting between you and us to enable both parties know ourselves, have a fore knowledge of the nature of the business, discuss and acquaint ourselves with the responsibilities and functions of both parties and appropriate shares accordingly. I am Dan Wilson Branch Manager of Kenya Commercial Bank in Kenya.This is an urgent and very confidential business proposition. On June 6, 2001,a Foreign Oil consultant/contractor with the Kenya Ministry Of Energy, Mr.Clifford Stone made a numbered time(Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at US$21,500,000.00,(Twenty-One Million, five hundred thousand Dollars) in my branch. Upon maturity,I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month,we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers,the National Petroleum Corporation that Mr.Clifford Stone died from an automobile accident. On further investigation,I found out that he died without making a WILL,and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr.Clifford Stone did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents,including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$21,500,000.00 has carefully been fixed in my bank for safekeeping. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to South African Law, at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a Foreigner to stand in as the owner of the money which was fixed deposited in my bank. I am writing you because I as a public servant,i cannot operate a foreign account. I want to present you as the owner of the funds so you can be able to claim them with the help of my attorney. This is simple.I will like you to provide immediately your telephone number,full names and address so that the Attorney will prepare the necessary documents which will put you in place as the beneficiary of the funds. The money will be moved out for us to share in the ratio of 80% for me and 20% for you.The paperwork for this transaction will be done by the Attorney and this will guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately via my email and Upon your response,I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please observe utmost confidentiality, and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in real estate within your country. Due to the nature of confidentiality in this Transaction our communication can only be via email and fax mostly. Awaiting your urgent reply via my private email: Thanks and my regards. Dan Wilson Branch Manager Kenya Commercial Bank mvurgxqhidbbalgifpkokhddeopgmrwuy

Dear Sir/Madam, This letter might surprise you because we have met neither in person nor by correspondence. But I believe it is one day that you get to know Somebody either in physical or through correspondence I sincerely write to seek your co-operation and trust to enable my colleagues and I carry out an urgent business Opportunity in my department. I am a director with the Citizens Trust Bank Plc. I used to be a business partner to one Mr. Ali B. Ashraf who died along with his family on the 8th of November 1999 in an ADC Boeing 727 plane crash at Egirin River. All 141 passengers on Boards were feared dead. He left in his domiciliary account the total sum of $25.5 million (Fifteen million five hundred thousand USA Dollars).Since the management got the information of his death we have been expecting any of his relation or his next of kin to come up and claimhis money. Unfortunately from the day of his death till the time of this letter none of his relation or friends has come up for the claim. The banking and financial law of Citizens Trust Bank Plc's stipulates that if such fund remained unclaimed after a period offour (5) it will be transferred into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill. On this discovery sir/Madam, I and two other senior staffs now decided do business with you and release the money to you as the next of kin to Ali B. Ashraf for safety and subsequent disbursement. I will soon proceed for my retirement leave this year, and I personally do not want this fund to be transferred into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill.That is why I wanted the fund to be move out of the bank before I proceed on my retirement from the banking services by December 15th 2004. The need for a foreigner as next of kin in this project is occasioned by the fact that the customer Mr. Ali Ashraf was a foreigner and a Nigerian cannot stand as his next of kin or heir. We have agreed that 20% of the Fund would be for you as foreign partner;thereafter my colleague and I will visit your country for disbursement according to the percentages indicated. To enable the immediate transfer of the fund into yournominated account, you will first apply to the bank as the next of kin of the deceased. Indicating your bank account number and location wherein the money will be remitted. Upon receipt of your acknowledgement indicating your interest, I will send to you the text of the application that youwill send to the Citizens Trust Bank authority for an approval to submit your claims. Indicates your direct Fax and telephone numbers for effective communication that this transaction needs.Please note that you are not to appear in person, as every thing regarding this project will be strictly on documentations and every banking documents needed for this transaction will be taken care of. Looking forward to urgently hearing from you. Yours Faithfully Chief Mark Duke Director Citizens Trust Bank Plc's

ATTN Dddddddd R. Rrrrr , I am BARRISTER P.T.GEORGE at law. I am the personal Attorney to MR Robert Rrrrr a national of your country, who used to work with shell development company in Nigeria and as well a one time secret agent in transfering of money overseas for the Late head of state of Nigeria {Late Gen.SANI ABACHA}.Before his death On the 21st of April 1999 my client,his wife And their three childrenwere involved in a car accident along sagbama express road in which alloccupants of the motor died}. My client{ROBERT} deposited as family belongings in a CONSIGNMENT {ie jewelries} the sum of $10m in a Global Security and finance company here in Nigeria for himself, with the hope of transferring it to his country as soon as he is on leave. Since his death I have made several enquiries to your embassy to locate any of my clients extended relatives this has also proved unsuccessful. After these several unsuccessful attempts, I decided to trace his last name over the Internet, to locate any member of his family hence I contacted you.I have contacted you to assist in repartrating the money and property left behind by my client before they get confisicated or declared unserviceable by the Security Company where this huge deposits were lodged. Particularly, the Global Security company where the deceased had an account valued at about 10million dollars has issued me a notice to provide the next of kin or have the account confisicated within the next ten official working days.since then I have been unsuccesfull in locating the the relatives for over 2years now I therefore seek your consent to present you as the next of kin of the deceased since you have the same last name so that the proceeds of this account valued at 10million dollars can be paid to you and then you and me can share the money. 40% to me and 60% to you I have all necessary legal documents that can be used to back up any claim we may make. All I require is your honest cooperation to enable us see this through. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protectyou from anybreach of the law. Please get in touch with me through my confidential email[ barrgeorge0040@yahoo.co.uk ]or you can call me on my phone number +234-80- 330-48048 . Best regards, BARRISTER P.T.GEORGE, ____________________________________________________________ Yahoo! Messenger - Communicate instantly..."Ping" your friends today! Download Messenger Now http://uk.messenger.yahoo.com/download/index.html

FEDERAL MINISTRY OF PETROLEUM RESOURCES FEDERAL SECRETARIAT COMPLEX HQ 11. P . M . B . 9749 ABUJA - NIGERIA TELFAX; 234-1-7591936 FROM: BARRISTER PETER UMEH. TO: YOUR HONOUR Alternate email: barrpeter@c2i.net Sir, ASSISTANCE REQUIRED FOR ACQUISITION OF ESTATE I have been detailed by the Director Audit / Accounts Allocations Department Federal Ministry of Petroleum Resources, Dr. John Akiga and other colleagues to write and inform you of our desire to acquire estates or landed properties in your country with funds currently trapped at our Accounts with the Central bank of Nigeria (CBN) Considering his very strategic and influential position, he would want the transaction to be as strictly confidential as possible. He would further want our identity and yours to remain undisclosed outside this circle at least for now, untill the completion of the transaction. We desire to have an overseas agent in order to make a smooth transfer without hitch. I therefore take this opportunity to inquire if you would agree to act as our overseas agent in order to actualize this transaction. The deal, in brief, is that the funds with which we intend to carry out our proposed investments in your country is presently in a coded account at the Nigerian Apex Bank (i.e. the Central Bank of Nigeria) and we need your assistance to transfer the funds to your country in a convenient bank account that will be provided by you before we can put the funds into use in your country. For this, you shall be considered to have executed a contract for the Federal Ministry of Petroleum Resources in Nigeria for which payment should be effected to you by the Ministry, The contract sum shall be US$17.4 Million, of which your share shall be 20% if you agree to be our overseas agent. As soon as payment is effected, and the amount mentioned above is successfully transferred into your account, we intend to use our own share in acquiring some estates abroad. For this, you shall be expected to serve as our agent in the acquisition of this properties and purchase of shares / Bonds. In the light of this, I would like you to forward to me the following information: 1.Your company name and address if any (Personal) 2.Your personal fax number 3.Your personal telephone number for easy communication. You are requested to communicate your acceptance of this proposal through my above stated FAX NUMBER / PHONE / email address after which we shall discuss in details the modalities necessary to see this transaction through. Your quick response will be highly appreciated. Thank you in anticipation of your cooperation. Yours faithfully, Barrister Peter Umeh. FAX: (private) 234-1-7591936 DISCLAIMER:This e-mail message and any attachments are confidential and may be privileged or otherwise protected by legal rules, and for use by the addressee only. If the message is received by anyone other than the addressee, please return the message to the sender and delete it and any attachments from your computer without copying it or disclosing its contents to anyone. Whilst all reasonable care has been taken to avoid the transmission of viruses, no responsibility is accepted in this regard and the recipient should scan and carry out such other checks as it considers appropriate.

FROM:TSEPO VUSI EMAIL_tsepovusi@netscape.net ATTN: DIRECTOR/C E O, I know you will be surprised to read from me, but please consider this as a request from a family in dire need of assistance.First, I must introduce myself I am MR. TSEPO VUSI from Angola. I am the first and only son of BRIGADIER VUSI JONES. I am presently resident in South Africa. I got your contact address from a business directory in Johannesburg Chamber of commerce and Industry. On behalf of my widowed mother MRS. ELIZABETH VUSI I desided to solicit for your assistance to transfer the sum of US$21.5 MILLION( TWENTY ONE MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS)inherited from my late father, into your personal company's account.Before my fathers' death, he was a Brigadier in charge of Arms and Ammunation procurement for the Angola Army. In his WILL, he specifically drew my attention to the said sum of money which he deposited in a safe box of a private Security Company in Johannesburg- South Africa in a treasure box, fully documented in my name. IN FACT MY FATHER SAID AND I QUOTE MY BELOVED SON, I WISH TO DRAW YOUR ATTENTION TO US$21.5 MILLION . I DEPOSITED THE BOX CONTAINING THIS MONEY IN A SECURITY COMPANY IN JOHANNESBURG, SOUTH AFRICA. DURING THE WAR, I WAS VERY DEDICATED AND OFFICERS AND GOVERNMENT FUNCTIONARIES WERE BUSSY HELPING THEMSELVES WITH GOVERNMENT FUNDS AND PROPERTIES AND SENDING THEM TO FOREIGN COUNTRIES. DUE TO THIS, WHEN I AND MY FORMER SPECIAL ADVISOR TO THE PRESIDENT WERE ASSIGNED BY THE PRESIDENT (EDUARDO SANTOS) TO PURCHASE ARMS IN SOUTH AFRICA, WE SAW THIS AS A GOLDEN OPPORTUNITY AND DIVERTED THE MONEY AND DIVIDED IT. i GOT A TOTAL SUM OF US$21.5 MILLION. IN CASE OF MY ABSENCE ON EARTH, AS A RESULT OF DEATH ONLY, YOU SHOULD SOLICIT FOR THE FUND FOR INVESTMENT PURPOSES. >From the above, you will understand that the lives and future of my family depens on this money, as such I will be grateful if you can assist us. We are now living in South Africa as political Asylum seekers and financial laws and regulation of the Republic of South Africa do not permit us financial rights to such huge sum of money. In view of this, I cannot invest this fund in South africa, hence i am prepared to offer you 20% of the total fund, while 10% will be set aside for local and international expenses and 70% will be for my family and me. Finally, modalities on howthe transfer will be bone will be conveyed to you once we have established trust and confidence between ourselves. Please treat this matter as very urgent. Best regards, TSEPO VUSI

>From GEORGE Amachree General Manager Finance Nigeria LNG Limited C & C Towers Plot 1684, Sanusi Fafunwa Street, Victoria Island, P. M. B. 12774, Marina, Lagos. Nigeria. WWW.NLNG.COM RE: TRANSFER OF USD20,500,000.00(TWENTY MILLION, FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS ONLY) TO A SAFE ACCOUNT. Sir, It is my warmest pleasure writing you this confidential business offer irrespective of the fact that we have not met before or done any thing that will re-impose absolute confidence but nevertheless, an adage says a day begins a story and it is in line of this strong perspective that I am very determined to communicate you with much conviction that you will give my proposal a second thought and consideration. As earlier stated I am Mr Daniel Amachree a General Manager Finance working with Nigeria Liquefied Natural Gas {NLNG}. My Agency is to produce and export NLG and NGL safely, reliably and profitable, and grow business to it full potential, helping to put out flares in Nigeria and by the virtue of my unique position in office as the General Manager Finance. I was elevated by the commission to become the chairman of foreign contract tender board committee whose responsibility is to award and supervise foreign contract to ensure it is executed promptly. Consequently, I the chairman of the tender board committee in collaboration with two other top committee members over-invoice certain contract for the supply of Petroleum Pipe, Computers. The initial cost of the contract was pegged at US$60 million, but after the feasibility study that was done, while submitting my report to the office of the presidency for final approval, we deliberately inflated the cost to an excess amount of US$ 20..5 million making the cost to be US$ 80.5 million. Right now, the gist of contacting you is we are constrained to claim the fund due to certain laws enacted by the government guiding civil service code of conduct Bureau which prohibits top civil servants working under Government establishment from operating offshore or foreign Account and this situation has kept us in a fix to openly come forward to claim the outstanding balance of US$20.5 million, hence after series of private meetings we decided to make contactin order to get a reliable foreign partner whom we will forward his or her credentials to claim the fund based on mutual trust and agreement. In a nutshell, we need your assistance and support to claim this fund so that at the later time convenient for us, we will come over to your country after the funds have been transferred to meet you and collect our own percentage while you will keep the rest as yours. For your support and total dedication to realize the objectives of this operation, you shall be entitled to 20% of the sum total, 5% for misslaneous expense like telephone bill, while 75% of the fund belongs to the three officials involved in the deal. Note, you are vividly assured that you will not be subjected to any kind of risk for your support and involvement in this venture hence we have piloted a good strategy to ensure the operations goes smoothly of which we have targeted two weeks duration to accomplished our Aim. Kindly treat this matter Absolutely confidential because the officials involved are still in serviceand some of us intend to resign our appointment immediately after the transaction is finalized. I look forward to hearing positively from you while further details will be given as soon as I get your response , forward your telephone number, fax number and mailing address for through which further correspondence will be made , as soon as i receive your reply . Best Regards Mr GEROGE AMACHREE NB:- FOR MORE INFORMATION ABOUT MY PERSON AND COMPANY I WILL ADVISE YOU LODGE ON TO MY COMPANY WEBSITE ABOVE

FROM THE DESK OF: BARRISTER AMINU KANO PRICIPAL ASSOCIATE MIKE & CO. ATTN: I was privileged to capture your names from the Internet. My name is Barrister. aminu kano a legal Practitioner and the personal Attorney to late Mr.Steffen,a National of your country who died along with his wife and his Two sons in a ghastly motor accident over 3 years now (August 13,2000). All the occupants in the vehicle lost their lives. I am Convinced that it was the grace of God that made me to Locate you.. My client was a successful and am accomplished family man, Who made enough fortune before his untimely death? Since Then I had made several inquiries through your Embassy to locate any of my clients extended relative but this Exercise has proved unsuccessful. After several Unsuccessful attempts, I decided to trace his relatives Through the Internet, to locate any member of his Family not Much progress was recorded My late client was an Influential wealthy businessman, an oil magnet here in Nigeria and he left behind a deposit of Thirty two Million, Two Hundred Thousand United States Dollars only ($32,200,000.00usd) in his domiciliary bank account in a Commercial bank here in Lagos. After the death of my client his bankers contacted me, as his Attorney to provide his next of kin who should inherit His fortune. The board of directors of his bank adopted a Resolution and I was mandated to provide his next of kin for the payment of this money within 28 working days or Forfeit the money to the bank as an abandoned property. The Bankers had planned to invoke the abandoned property decree of 1996 to confiscate the funds after the expiration of the period given to me. Despairing at the point of, exhaustiveness, fortunately I came across your name. to my utmost amazement, I discovered That Coincidentally, you are nationals of the same country. I am Convinced that you may be linked with my late client or that you might provide clue to my search. Therefore, i decided to contact with these facts before me because of the Similarities .By virtue of my closeness to the deceased and His immediate family, I am very much aware of my client financial standing and The bank account he operates. I have reasoned very Professionally and I feel it will be legally proper to present you as the next of kin of my deceased client, so That you can be paid the funds left in his bank account, hence I contact you. I seek your consent to present you as the Next of Kin to the Deceased since you are at an advantage, hailing from the same country, so that the proceeds of this Bank Account valued at $32.2 Million Dollars can be paid to you. we shall both share the funds.25% to me and 60% to you, while 15% should be for Expenses or Tax as your Government may require, I shall Assemble all the necessary Legal Documents that will be Used to back up our claim. All I require is your honest cooperation to enable us see This deal through. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of law. Best Regards BARRISTER AMINU KANO

ATTN: THE DIRECTOR FROM: MRS. SUSAN SHABANGU SOUTH AFRICA {MY CONTACT PRIVATE EMAIL {susanshabangu00@netscape.net} {MY SON CONTACT NUMBER+27-73-323-0163} Dear Sir, First, let me start by introducing myself as MRS SUSAN SHABANGU,a mother of three children and the Deputy Minister of Safety and Security since 29th April 1996 to date under the auspices of the President of South Africa MR THABO MBEKI. After due deliberation with my children, I decided to contact you for your assistance in standing as a beneficiary to the sum of US$30.5M ( Thirty Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars Only) You can view my profile at my website www.gov.za click on, Contact Information, then click on Deputy Minister, and finally, click on Safety and Security and read about me. THE PROPOSAL, After the swearing in ceremony making me the Deputy Minister of Safety and Security, my husband Mr. Ndelebe Shabangu died while he was on an official trip to Trinidad and Tobago in 1996. After his death, I discovered that he had some funds in a dollar account which amounted to the sum of US$30.5M with a security and finance institution in South Africa of which I will divulge information to you when I get your full consent and support to go for a change of beneficiary and subsequent transfer of the funds into you a comfortable and conducive account of your choice. This fund emanated as a result of an over-invoiced contract which he executed with the Government of South Africa. Though I assisted him in getting this contract but I never knew that it was over-invoiced by him. I am afraid that the government of South Africa might start to investigate on contracts awarded from 1990 to date. If they discover this money in his bank account, they will confiscate it and seize his assets here in South Africa and this will definitely affect my political career in government. I want your assistance in opening an account with bankers through my banker so that this fund could be wired into your account directly without any hitch. As soon as the fund gets to your account, you are expected to move it immediately into another personal bank account in your country. I will see to it that the account is not traced from South Africa. As soon as you have confirmed the fund into your account, I will send my eldest son with my Attorney to come to your country to discuss on business investments. For your assistance, I am offering you 20% of the principal sum which amounts to US$6,100.000.00 (Six million One Hundred Thousand United States Dollars Only)And 5% will be for Any expenses that both of us may Incure in this transaction. And another 5%will go for Motherless babes home. However, you have to assure me and also be ready to go into agreement with me that you will not elope with my fund. If you agree to my terms, kindly as a matter of urgency send me an email. Due to my sensitive position in the South African Government, I prefer you send me email than call. All correspondence must be by email to my private email address, {susanshabangu00@netscape.net} If you want to speak with my Banker or my elder son,that is fine and okay by me.you can contact my son on his dilect line {+27-73-323-0163}his name is {MR Morris shabangu}and You will have to send down you private telephone /fax number so that i can forward it to him to reach you from time to time this is for security reasons. Please I do not need to remind you of the need for absolute Confidentiality of this transaction.If you do not feel comfortable with this transaction, do not hesitate to discontinue. Thanks for your anticipated co-operation and my regards to your family. Yours faithfully, MRS. SUSAN SHABANGU Deputy Minister of Safety & Security, South Africa. _____________________________________________________________________ For super low premiums ,click here http://www.dialdirect.co.za/quote

ATTN: PRESIDENT (C.E.O) / MANAGER. MR.PAUL WEMBA #24 Ellwood Crescent, Pretoria. Email:(p_weba@yahoo.co.in ) I am Mr. Paul Wemba, the Chief auditor of African Development Bank (ADB). There was an account opened in this bank in 1980 and since 2001 nobody has operated on this account again. After going through some old files in the records, I discovered that if I do not remit this money out urgently, this funds will go down the drains, into the hands of either the board of directors of this bank or the funds may eventually be discovered by the government as a dormant fund in the forthcoming audit by the Nations auditors. They will confiscate it or it will be sent into the governments treasure. The question now is who is the government and where is the treasury? These are human beings like you and I. The owner of this account is DR.B.DREDO, a foreigner, and a miner at Kruger gold co., a geologist by profession and he died in 1999. No other person knows about this account or any thing concerning it, the account has no other beneficiary and my investigation proved to me as well that his company does not know anything about this account. The amount involved is (USD 10.5M) Ten million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars. I am only contacting you, as a foreigner because this money cannot be approved to a local bank here, but can only be approved to any foreign account and foreign beneficiary because the money is in US dollars and the real owner of the account DR.B.DREDO, is a foreigner too. I only got your contact address from my secretary who operates computer; with believe in God that you will never let me down in this business. So please reply urgently so that I will inform you the next step to take immediately. I need your full co-operation to make this work fine because the management is ready to approve this payment to any foreigner, who has correct information of this account, which I will give to you later, if you will be able to handle such amount in strict confidence and trust according to my instructions and advice for our mutual benefit because this opportunity will never come again in our life. I need truthful person in this business because I don't want to make mistakes and your strong assurance and trust is needed. With my position now in the office I can transfer this money to any foreigner's reliable account, which you can provide with assurance that this money will be intact pending my physical arrival in your country for sharing and investment. I will destroy all documents of transaction immediately we receive this money leaving no trace to any place. You can also come to discuss with me face to face after which, I will make this remittance in your presence and two of us will fly to your country at least two days ahead of the money going into the account. I will also use my position and influence to effect legal approvals and onward transfer of this money to your account with appropriate clearance forms of the ministries and foreign exchange departments. At the conclusion of this business, you will be given 50% of the total amount,50% will be for me which I would like to invest in your country. I look forward to your earliest reply via my personal Email address (p_weba@yahoo.co.in ). Friendly, Mr. Paul Wemba. ________________________________________________________________________ Yahoo! India Matrimony: Find your partner online. http://yahoo.shaadi.com/india-matrimony/

ASYLUM CAMP ABIDJAN FROM:NDIDI UWOMA Dear Sir, CONFIDENTIAL, I am NDIDI UWOMA the only son of late former Director of finance, CHIEF BENARD UWOMA Sierra-Leone diamond and mining corporation.I must confess my agitation is real, and my words is my bond, in this proposal. My late father diverted this money meant for purchase of ammunition, for my country, during the peak of disastrous civil war in my country, now he has deposited the money with a Security Firm in one sealed box here in Abidjan, where I am residing under political asylum with my younger sister PRECIOUS . Now the war in my country is over with the help of ECOMOG soldiers, the present government of Sierra Leone has revoked the passport of all officers who served under the former regime and now ask countries to expel such person at the same time freeze their account and confiscate their assets, it is on this note that I am contacting you. My main reason of contacting you to please come accept to take up the responsibilities of my late father's business foreign parner in the Security Firm and claim the box.Be informed that my late father deposited the box and registered it as containing a Photographic Equipements belonging to his foreign partner that is why it is note possible for us to make the claims ourselfs and he did it as such to prevent them from knowing the box contains money so note that it is only you and I knows that the content of the box is money and please do not let the security firm know for security reasons.All I need from you is to furnish me with your personal details 1) Your full name 2) Telephone/Fax number 3) Home address or office These requirements are to be submitted to the Security Firm as my late father's foreign business partner who will be coming for the claims of the box with the key as I have contacted the Security Firm once where the deposit was made by my late father and establish a relationship with them but the told me in confident that the box will not be released to me nor any other person unless my late father's foreign partner whom the deposit was made. I am compensating you with 20% of the total amount. Now all my hope is banked on you and I really want to invest this money in your country, were their is stability of Government, political and economic welfare. Honestly I want you to believe that this transaction is real and never a joke. My late father CHIEF BENARD UWOMA gave me the photocopies of the certificate of deposit issued to him by the Security Firm on the date of deposit, so I can send you the copies for you to be clarified because, I do not expose my self to anybody I see, I believe that you are able to keep this transaction secret for me because this money is the hope of my life, it is important. Please respond to me immediately after you must have gone through my message, Feel free and make it urgent. Please try and negotiate for me some profitable bluechip investment opportunities which is risky free which I can invest with this money as soon as it 's confirmed in your position and a good university where I and my sister will further our education as soon as we arrives to your country while you take care of the ivesment till when we are expose to the business world. Personally I am interested in estate management and hotel business, please advise me. Thanks and God bless Best regards NDIDI/PRECIOUS UWOMA. ________________________________________ Tutti i concerti da non perdere! http://musica.jumpy.it/2003jm_m_concerti.asp

EMAILjamesnzama012@hotmail.com PHONE:+ 27-833413608 NAME :JAMES NZAMA Attention president/ceo. Your contact was made possible by your country's Trade Journal at the World Trade Centre here in Harare, Zimbabwe and I decided to write for assistance. You may be surprised to receive this letter since you do not know me personally,first let me introduce myself,I am Mr.JAMES NZAMA the son of Late Mr. NZAMA KUMALO, who was recently murdered in the land dispute in Zimbabwe. My late father was among the few black Zimbabwean rich farmers, murdered in cold blood by the special agents of the ruling government of president Robert Mugabe for his alleged support and sympathy for the Zimbabwean opposition party controlled by whites. Before his death, he had taken me to Johannesburg to deposit the sum of US$20.100.000.00 (Twenty Million One Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) with a Security and Finance Company as if he forsaw the looming danger in Zimbabwe. The money was deposited in a box as a consignment for the Security Company to avoid seizure, and also to avoid much demurrage from the Security Company. This money was earnmarked for the purchase of new machinery and chemicals for the farm and establishment for the new farms in Lesotho and Swaziland. This land problem arose when president Robert Mugabe introduced a new land act which wholly affected the rich white farmers and some few blacks vehemently condemned the modus operandi adopted by the government, that resulted to rampant killings and mob actions by the war veterans and some political thugs precisely, more than thirty one people (31) have been killed. Heads of government from Western worlds, especially Britain and the USA have voiced their condemnation of Mugabe's plan. Subsequently the South African Development Community (S.A.D.C.) has continuously supported Mugabe's new land reform act. It is against this background that I and my family who are currently staying in South Africa, have decided to transfer my father's money into a foreign account. As the eldest son of my father, I am saddled with the resposibilty of seeking a genuine foreign account where this money could transferred without the knowledge of my government who had tactically frozen our family wealth and the South African government seem to be playing along with them. I am faced with the dilemma of investing this amount of money in South Africa for fear of seizure and encountering the same experience in the future since both countries have almost the same political history. Moreso, the South African Foreign Exchange policy does not allow such investment since I am an asylum seeker. As a businessman whom I must entrust my future and that of my family on his hands, I must let you know that this transaction is 100% risk-free. Therefore if you accept to assist us, we are willing to offer you 30% of the total sum for your assistance. 60% will be for my family, while 10% will be fo all expenses. If this proposal is acceptable to you, please send me an email but you should know that this business is highly confidential and shall be kept within yourself. So I will hang on until I hear from you. Best regards, James

Dear friend, Greetings and compliments to you. I am writing you this mail with an ardent hope that you will consider the message contained in it and respond accordingly.before I proceed I will like to introduce myself : i am Rev .Shadak Shari,an indian by nationality and and the catholic nusateure to Nigeria and Asia and the world at large I am contacting you for a hand of partnership in disbussing my wealth worth $8milliom( eight million US dollars).I got your contact through a personal search on the internet.I beleive that though we have not met before, with mutual cooperation we would be able toestablish the necessary trust needed for the execution of this project.I decided to with hold some informations in this mail for security reasons. I will give you just a brief of the details of this transaction now but as soon as we have been able to establish some trust,I will give you the complete informations that is relevant to this transaction. A while ago,i acquainted with some plans to establish a project with helping the ophanange and old people home with equipments and facilities This i intended to do when i became the achbisop of african diaoses For this purpose ie set aside the sum of $8 million(eight million Us dollars) I seperated this funds intwo parts and deposited them in two different security companies.One in (China). (U. A.E)and the other in Europe.The one in U.A.E. ($2,million) was deposited in My name and the one In China was In My brothers name who is Dead now. is worth( $7million) while the other in Europe($6million)was deposited in the church name where i serve. It will be sad to let you know now that i have been in the hospital for the past three months now as i am sick with canser i sitll have the mind that one day i will die as my doctor said that it cannot be cured that it is of the harth I have the intention of retrieving one of the monies to enable us finalise My plans.This is why i contacted you.I want you to be my partner who will assist me in travelling to any of the above mentioned locations to effect the claim of the funds deposited there.I assure you that you will not encounter any problem in this help as i will appriopriately direct you on how to go about it.Also be assured that there is no risk involved in this venture.It is absolutely risk free.All that you need do is to adhere strictly to my instructions which I shall give you from time to time. I shall negotiate what shall be your commision in this deal.I just want you to be rest assured that you will be handsomely rewarded at the end of this project. Please do reply me immediately if you are interested in assisting us in this regard. you can reach me via my direct email(shadak_foundation1@tiscali.it) Please also note that this must be kept in absolute confidentiality for security reasons even if you are not interested. I await your response to this mail.for you to trust and confide in me i will want you to call me(+234-8033-925-128) Best regards Rev Shadak Shari __________________________________________________ Broadband from an unbeatable £15.99! http://www.tiscali.co.uk/products/broadband/home.html?code=SM-NL-11AM

FOR THE LOVE OF HUMANITY Dear Friend, Reply to:naybet@web-mail.com.ar Your first reaction to this mail will be total rejection, scare and may be disbelief, owning largely to the atrocities people commit these days. But this mail comes from a devastated, sorrowful and emotional laden soul that needs compassion from a kind and good spirited person to wipe away my tears and appropriate my dream and humanitarian gesture. As you read this, I don't want you to feel sorry for me, because, I believe everyone dies someday.My name is Naybet Trabelsi a merchant in Dubai,in the U.A.E.I worked with Zambian Ministry of Mining and Resources for eight years as a contractor, I have been diagnosed with Esophageal cancer . It has defiled all forms of medical treatment,I am very worried as the doctors have informed me that its terminal. I don't know how much time I have left on earth, hence this mail to you. I have not particularly lived my life well, as I never really cared for anyone but my business. Though I am very rich, I was never generous, I was always hostile to people and only focused on my business as that was the only thing I cared for. But now I regret all this as I now know that there is more to life than just wanting to have or make all the money in the world. I believe when God gives me a second chance to come to this world I would live my life a different way from how I have lived it. Now that God has called me, I have willed and given most of my property and assets to my immediate and extended family members as well as a few close friends. I want God to be merciful to me and accept my soul hence, I decided to give alms to charity organizations, as I want this to be one of the last good deeds I do on earth. So far, I have distributed money to some charity organizations in the U.A.E,Algeria and Malaysia. Now that my health has deteriorated so badly, I cannot do this myself anymore. I once asked members of my family to close one of my accounts and distribute the money which I have there to charity organization in Bulgaria and Pakistan, they refused and kept the money to themselves. Hence, I do not trust them anymore, as they seem not to be content with what I have left for them. The last of my money which no one knows of is the huge cash deposit of $18,000,000,00 that I have with a finance/Security Company abroad. I will want you to help me collect this deposit and dispatch it to charity organizations. I have set aside 20% for you and for your time. God be with you. Reply to:naybet@web-mail.com.ar Naybet Trabelsi >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> FREE Email? You bet. http://www.aeneasmail.com Nationwide Internet, Local and Long Distance Telephone up to 30% less!! Aeneas Internet and Telephone - http://www.aeneas.com >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>

FROM MR MICHAEL.K.MARIOLE JOHANNESBURG SOUTH AFRICA Tel: +27-73-177-9131 URGENT AND CONFIDENTIAL ATTN; Sir, I know that this letter will come to you as a surprise? But please do receive it with humanitarian hearth, First of all let me introduce my self to you. I am Mr.MICHAEL KADUSO MARIOLE,The son of late Brigadier. Jonathan Sanui Mariole former Special Adviser on Arms and Acquisition to the former president of Liberia Mr.Charles Taylor who is presently on Political Asylum in CALABAR, NIGERIA.sequel to the political crisis which engulfed the entire LIBERIA for years now.He finally stepped down on the 11th day of August, 2003. President Charles Taylor delegated my father to arrange for arm purchase from the Republic of South Africa through an independent Arms dealer, he was directed to purchase arms worth US$18.5.M (Eighteen Million,Five Hundred Thousand, United States Dollars only) on arrival to South Africa, through diplomatic means,foreseing the extent of carnage in my country he decided to deposit the Fund with a private Security Company in my name(Mr.MICHAEL KADUSO MARIOLE) being the first Son of the family.Hence that is a singular opportunity he has to establish a strong financial base for his family. This consignment was deposited in disguise as a family valuable to tune of $18.5m.Shortly on arrival from South Africa, he died of gun short wounds he sustained during an attack at his official quarters. BUT, before he died HE WROTE HIS WILL, which reads "(MY BELOVED SON ,I WISH TO DRAW YOUR ATTENTION TO THE SUM OF($18,500,000=). MILLION U.S DOLLARS WHICH I DEPOSITED IN A BOX WITH A SECURITY COMPANY IN JOHANNESBURG (SOUTH-AFRICA).IN CASE OF MY ABSENCE ON EARTH CAUSED BY DEATH ONLY". You should solicit for a reliable foreign partner to assist you to transfer this money out of SOUTH AFRICA for investment purpose. I deposited the money in your name and it can be claimed by you alone with the deposit code. your mother has all the documents. Take good care of your mother and brother." However I wish to inform you that I came across your name and profile through South African Net work Service negotiation, For a credible and reliable foreign partner to assist me in the transfer of this fund .The major reason why I need your assistance is because I am presently residing here in South Africa as a REFUGEE and the Financial Laws of South Africa restricts ASYLUM SEEKERS from certain Political, Social and Economic Rights and as a result of that I am not allowed to work or even to operate an account, Thus I was advised by an Attorney here in South Africa to look for a foreigner in who's name the transfer will be made. I cannot invest this money in South Africa, hence I am asking you to assist me to transfer this money out of South-Africa for investment purposes. For your efforts, I am prepared to offer you 20% of the total fund, while 5% will be set aside for local and international expenses and 75% will be kept for my family investment in your country. Finally,all modalities on how the transfer will be made shall be conveyed to you once we establish trust and confidence between ourselves.Therefore,if you have interest in assisting me in the Transfer of this Fund,please do not hesitate to contact me on my direct line +27-73-177-9131,or my e-mail address. Remember, this transaction is 100% risk free so you have nothing to be scared of. Thanks for your anticipated understanding.Looking forward to your urgent reply .For detailed information, please contact me. Yours Faithfully, MR.MICHAEL. K. MARIOLE (FOR THE FAMILY). __________________________________ Do you Yahoo!? Friends. Fun. Try the all-new Yahoo! Messenger. http://messenger.yahoo.com/

Dear Friend, I am Mrs.Mercy Kume, wife of late Mr Anthony Kume, a wealthy Zimbabwean farmer who was brutally murdered in a land dispute together with his oversea partner Mr. pete Bailey and the whole of his family as result of land act reform by Zimbabwean president Robert Mugabe. The whole of our farmland amd properties were destroyed by the mobs. The new land act reform which affected the white and black farmers, resulting to massive killing by war veterans and lunatics in the society. My husband died without leaving a word neither to me nor our only son, but his partner was rushed to the hospital where he later died after 2 days. Before my husband partner died, he confided in me that he deposited US$29,000,000 (Twenty Nine million united states dollars) in one private security company in Europe, that the money was meant for the purchase of new machineries for mechanised agriculture for the Zimbabwean farmers movement and new farms in Swaziland. He said that all I have to do is to source for an oversea partner who can be placed as the Beneficiary of the fund so that I and my son can have a new lease of life again. He made me promise that since he has no other leaving relatives, that I will not let money go down the drain. I was later diagnosed to have cancer of the breast which resulted to my losing one part of the breast to surgery. Presently, I am hospitalised because my condition started deteriorating in a very strange manner. My doctor gave me the saddest news of life as he told me that the cancer has spread to every part of my body including my liver. I have been boldly told that I just have a very short time to leave. As things are now, I am not afraid to die, but I don¡¯t want my son to suffer and I don¡¯t want to let late Mr.Bailey down by not having this claimed. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Late Mr. Pete Bailey .This you can do by corroborating with my Kenneth who is currently seeking political asylum in Europe, and our family attorney to actualise this claim. I will request that you send me your personal details viz: Your full name and private home address, your telephone and fax number.this will enable the attorney to place you as the next of kin to late Mr.Pete Bailey.The sharing mode will be as follows. 1.30% of the fund will be for you 2.50% will be for my son which you will have to invest for him as his guadian. 3.10% will be donated to the Southern African research center for cancer. 4.While 10% will be set out for all the bills encured to conclude this transaction including the attorney fees. There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the Attorney and with my support and endorsement I can guarantee the successful execution of this transaction. I cannot answer to any phone calls here in the hospital because of my situation.So if you are interested in this transaction, kindly declare your interest by replying to this e-mail via my private mail mercykume@netscape.net For your information the success and safety of this transaction will depend on your co-operation to keep it confidential and secret.As soon as I receive your favourable reply , I will proceed to forward you with further information. Thank you and may God bless you. Yours respectfully, Mercy Kume(Mrs)

ALHAJI MOHAMMED ABACHA 2/8 GIDADO DRIVE,GRA, KANO - NIGERIA. PLEASE AS YOU READ KINDLY OPEN THE WEBSITE http://www.onlinenigeria.com/links/adv.asp?blurb=126 .PLEASE EXCUSE MY INTRUSION INTO YOUR PRIVATE LIFE AS I WRITE YOU THIS LETTER IN GOOD FAITH AND TO THE GLORY OF ALMIGHTY GOD WHO THUS BROUGHT ME OUT CLEAN AFTER ALL THE ALLEGATIONS LEVELLED AGAINST ME AFTER THE DEATH OF MY FATHER GENERAL SANI ABACHA (FORMER NIGERIAN MILITARY HEAD OF STATES).MY RELEASE FROM PRISON WAS NECESSITATED BY THE EFFORTS OF THE SENATE PRESIDENT CHIEF ANYIM PIUS ANYIM AND THE SPEAKER OF THE LOWER HOUSE ALHAJI GHALI NA'ABBA. SINCE MY FATHER'S DEATH AND MY DETENTION FOR CLOSE TO THREE YEARS, MY FAMILY HAS BEEN LOOSING A LOT OF MONEY DUE TO VINDICTIVE GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS WHO ARE BENT ON DEALING WITH OUR FAMILY. AFTER MY RELEASE THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT OF NIGERIA HAS MADE ME SIGN SOME DOCUMENTS THAT WILL ENABLE THEM EXTRACT THE SUM OF ONE BILLION FIVE HUNDRED MILLION US DOLLARS FROM MY FATHER’S BANK ACCOUNTS IN LONDON,SWITZERLAND,LUXEMBIURG,LIECHTENSTEIN AND JESEY ETC. MY FAMILY AND I ARE LOOKING FOR A TRUSTWORTHY FOREIGN PARTNER WHO CAN ASSIST US BY TAKING POSESSION OF THE TOTAL SUM OF US$25,000,000.00 ( TWENTY FIVE MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS ), WHICH THE GOVERNMENT DID NOT KNOW ABOUT. BECAUSE IN THEIR THINKING THEY WANT TO LEAVE ONLY ONE HUNDRED MILLION TO MY FAMILY THIS MONEY IS PRESENTLY IN THE POSSESSION OF A SECURITY COMPANY ABROAD. THIS MONEY WAS OF COURSE, ACQUIRED BY MY LATE FATHER AND IS NOW KEPT SECRETLY BY THE FAMILY. THE SWISS GOVERNMENT HAS ALREADY FROZEN ALL OTHER ACCOUNTS OF MY FAMILY IN SWITZERLAND, AND SOME OTHER COUNTRIES ALSO TRIED DOING LIKE WISE. THIS BID BY SOME GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS TO DEAL WITH THIS FAMILY HAS MADE IT NECESSARY THAT I SEEK YOUR ASSISITANCE IN RECEIVING THIS MONEY AND IN INVESTING IT ON BEHALF OF MY FAMILY. THIS MUST BE A JOINT VENTURE TRANSACTION AND WE MUST ALL WORK TOGETHER. SINCE THIS MONEY IS STILL CASH,EXTRA SECURITY MEASURES HAVE BEEN TAKEN TO PROTECT IT FROM THEFT OR SEIZURE. I HAVE PERSONALLY WORKED OUT ALL MODALITIES FOR THE PEACEFUL CONCLUSION OF THIS TRANSACTION WITH THE SECUITY COMPANY. HOWEVER, BASED ON THE GROUNDS THAT YOU ARE WILLING TO WORK WITH ME AND ALSO ALL CONTENTIOUS ISSUES DISCUSSED BEFORE THE COMMENCEMENT OF THIS TRANSACTION. YOU MAY ALSO DISCUSS YOUR PERCENTAGE BEFORE WE START TO WORK.AS SOON AS I HEAR FROM YOU, I WILL GIVE YOU ALL NECESSARY DETAILS AS TO HOW WE INTEND TO CARRY OUT THE WHOLE TRANSACTION. PLEASE, DO NOT ENTERTAIN ANY FEARS, AS ALL NECESSARY MODALITIES ARE IN PLACE, AND I ASSURE YOU OF ALL SUCCESS AND SAFETY IN THIS TRANSACTION.PLEASE, THIS TRANSACTION REQUIRES ABSOLUTE CONFIDENTIALITY AND YOU WOULD BE EXPECTED TO TREAT IT AS SUCH. IF YOU ARE INTERESTED IN ASSISTING ME PLEASE SEND ME YOUR CONCENT AND TELEPHONE NUMBER. PLEASE, YOU MAY ALSO IGNORE THIS LETTER AND RESPECT MY TRUST IN YOU BY NOT EXPOSING THIS TRANSACTION, SHOULD YOU NOT BE INTERESTED. I LOOK FORWARD TO WORKING WITH YOU. THANK YOU ALHAJI MOHAMMED ABACHA PLEASE YOU CAN AS WELL REACH ME VIA THIS EMAIL ADDRESS - mohammedabacha2004@indiatimes.com

Attn: President/CEO/SIR/MADAM REQUEST FOR URGENT BUSINESS RELATIONSHIP -STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL Firstly, I must solicit your confidentiality. This is by virtue of it'snature as being utterly "confidential" and "TOP SECRET". Though I know that a transaction of this magnitude will make anyone apprehensive and worried,but I am assuring you that all will be well at the end of the day. A bold step taken shall not be regretted I assure you. I am Mr iyang and I head a seven man tender board in charge of contract awards and payment approvals. I came to know of you in my search for a reliable and reputable person to handle a very confidential business transaction,which involves the transfer of a huge sum of money to a foreign account requiring maximum confidence. My colleagues and I are top official of Federal Government Contract Review and Award Panel. Our duties include evaluation, vetting, and approval for payment of contract jobs done for the Federal Ministry of Aviation(FMA) etc. We are therefore soliciting for your assistance to enable us transfer into your account the said funds. Our country looses a lot of money everyday that is why the international community is very careful and warning their citizens to be careful but I tell you "a trial will convince you".The source of the fund is as follow: During the last military regime here in Nigeria, this committee awarded a contract of US$400 Million to a group of five construction firms on behalf of the Federal Ministry of Aviation (FMA)for the supply and installation of landing and navigational equipment in Lagos and Port Harcourt International Airports. During this process my colleagues and I decided among us to deliberately over inflate the total contract sum of US$420.5 Million with the aim of sharing the remaining sum of US$20.5 million.The government has since approved the sum of US$420.5Million for us as the contract sum, but since the contract is only worth US$400M the remaining US$20.5 Million is what we intend to transfer to a reliable and safe offshore account,we are prohibited to operate foreign account in our names since we are still in Government. Thus, making it impossible for us to acquire the money in our name right now, I have therefore been delegated as a matter of trust by my colleagues to look for an oversea partner into whose account we can transfer the sum of US$20.5Million.My colleagues and I have decided that if you/your Company can as the beneficiary of this funds on our behalf, you or your company will retain 20% of the total amount (US$20.5Million) while 75% will be for us (officials) and the remaining 5% will be used in offsetting all debts/expenses incurred during this transaction We have decided that this transaction can only proceed under the following condition (a) Our conviction of your transparent honesty and that you treat this transaction with utmost secrecy and confidentiality (b) That upon Receipt of the funds you will release the funds as instructed by us after you've removed your share of 20%. Please acknowledge the receipt of this letter using the above e-mail address. I will bring you into the complete of this transaction when I've heard from you. Your urgent response will be highly appreciated as we are already behind schedule for the financial quarter. Please do be informed that his business transaction is 100% legal and completely free from drug or money laundering. Only trust can make the reality of this transaction. Best regards, Mr iyang

>From Mr.Abu M.Sesay I Need Your Assistance Please. Dear Friend, Through the courtesy of business opportunit, i take liberty anchored on a strong desire to solicit your assistance on this mutually beneficial and riskfree transaction which i hope you will give your urgent attention. I am Mr.Abu M.Sesay i am moved to write you this letter,this was incinfidence considration, our present circumstances and situation, i escaped with my wife and children out of Sierrial Leone to Ghana where we are presently residing on temporary political asylum. However, due to this situation i decided to change most of my Billions of Dollars deposited in Swiss Bank and other countries into other forms of money coded for safe purpose because the new head of state Ahmed Tijjan Kabba made arrangement with the Swiss Goverment and other European countries to freeze all my treasures deposited in some european countries, hence i and my family, decided laying low in Africa to study the situation till when things gets better, since president Tijjan Kabba taking over goverment again in Sierria Leone. One of my chateaux in Southern France was confiscated by the French Goverment, and as such we had to change our identity so thet our investment will not be trace and confiscated. I have deposited the sum of Thirty Million,Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars{US$30,500,000} with a security company for safekeeping. The funds are security coded to prevent them from knowing the actual content . What i want you to do now is to indicate your inetrest that you will assist me and my immediate family by receiving the money my behalf. The Account required for this project can be personal, company or an offshore account that you have been total control over, your area of specialisation will not be a hinderance to the successful execution of this transaction. Ackowledge this message, so that i can introduce you to my family as our foreign trusted partner who shall take charge of our investment abroad where we now plan to settle. I want you to assist us in investing this fund or money, but i will not want our identity revealed. I will also want to buy properties and stocks in multy- national companies and to engage in other safe and non speculative investments. We have been through a lot of health and spiritual turmoil, hence will need your understanding and assistance and may i at this junction emphasize the high level of confidentiality which this business demands and hope you will not betral the trust and confidence which we repose in you. shall put you in the picture of this buiness, i.e tell you where the funds are currently being maintained and also discuss other modalities including remuneration for your services. I shall also inform you with the next line of action as soon as i receive your response. Finaly if this preposition is attainable, Please kindly funish me immediately by E-mail with your direct telephone number and fax number to enhance the confidentiality which this business demands. Best Regards, Mr.Abu M.Sesay ___________________________________________________________________ Buy gifts for all occasions online from http://shop.di-ve.com

Mr. John Peters Nigeria National Orientation Agency Federal Ministry of Information Radio House-Abuja. e - mail: mrjohnpeters2@katamail.com Dear Friend, I am Director of Civic registration and finance Nigeria National Orientation Agency (NNOA) Federal Ministry of Information. I must start this email by acknowledging the wisdom in choosing to reveal my 26years AMBITION since the National Identity Card project was kicked off some 26years ago by a bill passed into law by the national assembly for the registration and identification of every Nigerian above the age of 18years. During our final verification exercise we discovered an excess allocation to our agency to the tune of Fourteen Million, Three Hundred Thousand United States Dollar and we intend to keep this money for our personal use by fronting you as one of the foreign contractors due for payment. This sum (US$14.3Million) will be paid into your account as your contractual entitlement. The good news is that precisely 1st of April, 2004, 26years after, the government has started distributing the national identity card. The reason am writing you this mail is that the presidency, federal republic of Nigeria have approved allocation for payment due to all contractor (Foreign and Local) to the agency and this gives us opportunity to transfer this over invoiced sum to you, who we shall present as a foreign contractor. We are handicapped in the circumstances, as the Civil service code of conduct does not allow us to operate foreign accounts hence your importance in the whole transaction. Therefore, we want to utilize this opportunity, as a lot of foreign contractors will be paid in this quarter of the year 2004 to transfer the fund out of the country. Please do not disregard this mail and for avoidance of doubt you can verify the National Identity card projectby visiting our website as posted by Nigeria business information in 2003 when the registration started. But do not disclose my identity or the actual nature of this transaction as I am still a serving officer in the ministry. http://www.nigeriabusinessinfo.com/id-card180203.htm In other to present you/your Company as the beneficiary of the sum of US$14.3M. For this purpose we will incorporate your company and register you as a contractor with the Nigerian National Orientation Agency (NNOA). We will also by virtue of our official positions secure for your company the necessary backup documentation that will facilitate the release/transfer of the fund into your account. These documents of course will be destroyed within 10-14 working days at the successful completion of the transfer. We want to assure you that your help will not in any way bring your company name into disrepute. Please reply urgently by or e - mail: mrjohnpeters09@uymail.com Also send me your confidential phone number and fax number. as we expect that the transaction will not take more than ten working days. We shall discus sharing ratio and other modalities when I get your response. Please note that this transaction must be top secret. Yours sincerely, Mr. John Peters e - mail: mrjohnpeters2@katamail.com

FROM BONGO WALE JOHANNESBURG,SOUTH AFRICA. TELL:+27-732112866. Dear sir, I am MR, BONGO WALE, the son of late MR.PATRICK WALE, who was murdered in a land dispute in ZIMBABWE.I got your contact during my search for reliable&compitent foreigner to handle a confidential financial transaction, then I decided to write you. My late father was among the few black Zimbabwean rich farmers murdered in cold blood by the agent of the ruling government of President ROBERT MUGABE for his alleged support and sympathy for Zimbabwean opposition party. Before the death of my father, he took me to South Africa to deposit the sum of Twelve million US Dollars ($12m) with a security and finance company, as if he knew the looming danger in Zimbabwe. The money was deposited as a gem/precious stone to avoid much dumourage from the security firm. This money was earmarked for the purchase of new machinery and chemicals for the farms and the establishment of new farms in Lesotho and Swaziland. This land problem arose when President R. MUGABE introduced a new land Act. which wholly affects the White rich farmers and some few blacks vehemently condemned the 'MODUS OPERANDI' adopted by the government. This resulted to rampant killing and mob actions. I and my family who are currently staying in South Africa as refugees or asylum seekers have decided to enter your name as foreigner/beneficiary of the Trunck Cases containing the Cash (USD12M) for futher transfer of the money to a foreign country where we can invest it. I am faced with the dilemma of claiming/investing this amount of money in South Africa for fear of encountering the same experience in future since both countries have the same political history. Moreover, the South African monetary policy/law does not allow such investment hence I am seeking for an asylum or refugee. I must let you know that this business is 100% risk free and the nature of your business does not necessary matter. So if you are willing to assist us claim the ownership of this money,I and my family have agreed to give you 20% of the total money, 40% will be for a joint business venture I will be doing with you and another 35% will be for me and my family which we shall also invest in your country and the remaining 5% will be mapped out for all expenses we may incure during the transaction. Therefor, if you are willing and interested to render the needed assistance. Please funish me your private phone and Fax number for easy and better communication. Remember that this is highly confidential and the success of this business depends on how secret it is kept. Expecting your reply soonest. Best Regard. BONGO WALE _________________________________________________________________ Find a friend, companion or lover at the world's largest dating service! http://match.msn.co.za/match/mt.cfm?pg=channel&tcid=1826

>From Mr.Ctibor Pilna. # 18 SILVER CRESCENT JOHANNESBURG SOUTH AFRICA. #874-763-427980. Fax874-763-427981. (URGENT AND CONFIDENTIAL) Dear Sir/Madam, In order to transfer from a Bank some amount of money,I have the courage to look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable for this important business believing that you will never let me down either now or in the future. I am Mr.Ctibor Pilna,a consulting auditor of prime banks here in South Africa. On June 6,1998,an American Mining onsultant/contractor with the South African Mining corporation, Mr.Gregory A.Williams made a numbered time (fixed)deposit for twelve calendar months,value US $14,200,000.00 an account. On maturity, The bank sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month,The bank sent another reminder and finally his contract employers,the South African Mining corporation wrote to inform the bank that Mr.Gregory A.Williams died from an automobile accident,that he died without MAKING A WILL, and all attempts by the American Embassy to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore, made further investigation and discovered that Mr.Gregory A.Williams in fact was an immigrant from Jamaica and only recently obtained American citizenship.He did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank deposit paper work. This money total U S $ 14,200,000.00 is still sitting in my bank as dormant Account. No one will ever come forward to claim it, and according to South African banking policy,after 5years, the money will revert to the ownership of the South African Government if the account owner is certified dead. This is the situation, and my proposal is that I am looking for a foreigner who will stand in as the next of kin to Mr.Gregory A.Williams,and a Bank Account abroad will then facilitate the transfer of this money to the beneficiary/ next of kin. This is simple, all you have to do is to immediately send me a bank account anywhere in the world for me to arrange the proper money transfer paperwork. This money total USD ($14.2M) will then be paid into this Account for us to share in the ratio of 70% for me, 25 % for you and 5% for expenses that might come up during transfer process. There is no risk at all, and all the paper work for this transaction will be done by me using my position and connection in the banks in South Africa. This business transaction is guaranteed. If you are interested, please reply immediately through my personal email sending the following details: (1) Your Full Name/Address. (2) Your Private Telephone/fax Number. (3) Your Bank Name And Address. (4) Your Account Number: And Sweft Code (If Any) (5) Account Name. Please observe the utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. I look forward to your earliest reply through my private email address <ctiboudey@yahoo.ca> Please for the security of this business ok. Thanks and god bless you and your family and bless me too. Have a nice day. Yours truly. Mr.Ctibor Pilna ______________________________________________________________________ Post your free ad now! http://personals.yahoo.ca

Dear, Friend. My proposal to you will be very surprising, as we have not had any Personal contact before. However, I sincerely seek your confidence in this transaction,which I propose to you as a person of transparency,honesty and high caliber. Let me first start by introducing myself properly to you. My name is Ron Sinclear, i was the Personal Assistance to the (Haitian) President . I apologize if I have infringed on your privacy. It may interest you to know that the former president of (Haiti) has been fighting serious war for United Democracy for quite some years now, which has been backed (all along) by some foreign powerful countries. Not quite long ago, the American government ordered (President, Jean Bertrand Aristed) to leave (Haiti) or be forced out of power by a Rabel force.Knowing fully well the capabilities of America and other powerful members of the United Nations, (President Aristed) decided,and left the seat of power into exile in South Africa country to seek asylum. now a new government is in place . In the light of all these sad happenings, there was this deposit he made with a Security Company in Europe in year May 2001 ,this took place while he was still in power as the president of Haiti, through my aid, his Personal Assistant, (Ron Sinclear) and some loyalist, he suceeded to secretely move the sum of ($9.5M USD) (NINE MILLION,FIVE HUNDERED THOUSAND, UNITED STATES DOLLARS] to a private security company vault in Europe. Now, we need your services as a highly reliable foreigner to receive the funds into your bank account for the future survival of my family because he (Aristed) cannot presently operate any foreign bank account in his name. These funds (US$9.5m USD.) arose from various money i received from the sales of diamonds deals, i had with ( President Charles Taylor) of Liberia, which are abound in great quantity around the coastal areas of liberia. I have decided that if you are able assist us,you shall be compensated with 25% commission of the funds, 5% of this money shall be set aside to take care of any local or foreign expenses that might be incurred along the line. My family will have the remaining 75% of the funds. It might also interest you to note that all security arrangements regarding this transaction has been put in place, therefore,you have nothing whatsoever to fear or worry about, as every arrangement will be co-handled by you and my former Personal Assistant (Ron Sinclear) who is now presentely in Europe The Netherlands for possible conclusion of this arrangement. Most part of this share (70%) for my family will also be invested in a lucrative business courtesy of your full advice, assistance and connections because that is the most importat part of this transaction. As you indicate interest to assist my family,please kindly send to us your telephone/fax numbers for further discussion and clarification.I will be expecting to receive your urgent response for us to proceed to more details on .this pending transaction. God bless you as you respond promptly via my private Email: ronsinclear@netscape.net Best regards, Ron Sinclear. ronsinclear@netscape.net

My dear friend, I got to know of you in my search for a reputable person to assist in An urgent deal requiring utmost trust and confidentiality. I am Chris EdU, am a senior advocate of Nigeria and I own a personal law firm here in Lagos and Abuja both in Nigeria, (CHRISEDU CHAMBERS), an attorney and close confidant of Mrs. Maryam Abacha, the former first lady and wife to the late gen. Sani Abacha, The former head of state and commander in chief of the armed forces of The federal republic of Nigeria. She (Mrs. M. Abacha), as a result of The trust and confidence she has in me, mandated that i search for a Reliable and trustworthy foreign partner, who will help receive some Funds, which she has in cash totaling us$30m (thirty million united States dollars only) into a personal, company or any reliable foreign Bank account for safe keeping for a short period of time. her family bank Accounts within and outside the country have all been frozen by the authorities. (I will refer you to this website of a leading Nigerian newspapers The website is www.ngrguardiannew.com page 56 back page 19/10/2001 www.thisdayonline.com 4th oct. 2001 front page www.thisdayonline.com 13th nov.2003 front page, for further information about this monies and the Abachas.) It may also interest you to note that she (Mrs. Abacha) and her family Have, since the inception of the present democratic government, been Placed under partial house arrest, with their international traveler's Passports seized pending when the current fund recovery will end Between them and present president Gen. Obasanjo led federal government Is resolved, which from all indications will not exceed this year. Already, the present regime has released Mohammed Sanni Abacha, the first son from prison custody. She has decided to offer your good self if you are willing to render This tremendous assistance, 30% of the total sum. Note that this Transaction involves no risk whatsoever, as you will have no dealing with my country, Nigeria. Rather, you will deal directly with the security company and Trust company in Europe, which is where the money is right now. p/s respond to This confidential email address: chrisedu@irangate.net Kindly forward your confidential Tel / Fax number in your response to this proposal. This matter should be treated as urgent and confidential. Best regards, Barr. Chris Edu

FROM: MR.james obi ATTENION: MONEY TRANSFER / INVESTMENT PROPOSAL INTRODUCTION: Please I do not wish to invade your privacy by sending this mail to you. I am Mr james obi , a Civil Servant in the Federal Ministry of Health . I know this proposal will come to you as a surprise because we have not met physically or through correspondence. I got your contact from our chamber of commerce here in Nigeria and have no doubt about your ability to handle a huge sum of money. THE SUBJECT: My father Chief Solomon Dama (Now Late) was the Royal Head of my community , Eleme (an oil rich town) in Nigeria . My community produces 5.8% of the total crude oil in Nigeria and 0.5% of the Dollar value of each barrel is paid to my father as royalty by the Federal Government . My father was also the head and chairman of Eleme Special Oil Trust Fund . In his position as the royal head and chairman of the Oil Trust Fund , he made some money which he left for me as the only heir to inherit. The money is Twenty Five Million, Two Hundred Thousand US Dollars ($25.2M). This money originated from the accumulated royalties between 1976-1998. Due to poor banking system in Nigeria and political instability as a result of past military interventions , he deposited this money in a vault with an open beneficiary to a security company pending when he will finish arrangement to transfer it abroad. He was planning this when he suddenly died late last year of heart attack. THE PROPOSAL: Just before my father died , he called my attention to the money and charged me to look for a foreigner who will assist in the transfer /investment of the funds abroad . So I will be very grateful if you can accept to help me in this regard . I promise to give you 20% of the total funds transferred to your vital bank account as compensation for your assistance . Five percent (5%) would be set aside to take care of all expenses we may incure during transaction. To indicate your interest , contact me urgenly and confidentially for more information and the roles you will play in this business. All the legal documents concerning this money will be sent to you as soon as we reach a compromise. Maybe this will be the beginning of an intimate and rosy relationship between my family and yours Send your reply asap and may the almighty God bless you Yours Faithfully, Mr james obi

Dear Friend, Sorry to enroach on your privacy,but this is very important. study this portion carefully if you will be able to handle,as i might not want to be exposed of the information;considering the source and reputation of my name. I am the director of project and the newly appointed chairman contract reviewing committee[CRC]of the federal ministry of works and housing[FMW&H]in abuja,nigeria. I am seeking your assistance to enable me transfer the sum of US$16,500,000.00 into your private/company account for our mutual benefits. This money came about as a result of a contract executed on behalf of my ministry[the Federal Ministry of Works and Housing]. The contract was officially assigned to be awarded and executed by two foreign contractors at the tune of US$80,500,000.00 but in the course of my negotiation,i bargained with only one foreign contractor,a bulgarian firm which now executed the contract at the cost of US$64,000,000.00. Thus leaving the remaining US$16,5M to my benefits unknown to the contractor and another person in my ministry.this contract has been satisfactorily executed and inspected as the bulgarian firm is presently securing his payment from my ministry. It is however to this effect that i seek your maximum assistance and approval to present your company/your name alongside the Bulgarian contractor as the second foreign contractor to enable me transfer the difference[US16.5M]into your account for investment. On actualization of the transaction,the funds will be share thus; 1, 30% of the money will go to you for acting as the beneficiary of the fund. 2. 10% for reimburstment to both parties for the incidential expenses that may be incurred in the course of the transaction for the insurance,phone bills,documentation and e.t.c. 3. 60% to me. All logistics are in place and all modalities worked out for the smooth actualization of the transaction within fourteen working days of commencement after receipt of the following information by e-mail:your company's name,address,phone/fax number and activities. The above information will enable me make the application and lodge claims to the concerned ministries in favour of your company or name and it is pertinent to state here that this deal is entirely based on trust and the fear of GOD. If you are able to handle this transaction,feel free to reach me on this email address robe878@tiscali.co.uk for a perfect understanding of the transaction Thanks in anticipation for your response. Yours faithfully Robert Majus.

>From The Desk Of, Dr Harry Obum{Deputy Secretary Nigeria Football Association}Please Reply To My Private And Security Email Address: harryobum001@asiamail.com Dear Sir, I am DR HARRY OBUM , Deputy secretary to the Nigerian Football Association, parent body of the World Youths Championship, Nigeria 99'Local Organizing Committee, an affiliate of Federation of International Football Association (FIFA). In the course of our preparation to host the World Youth Soccer Championship Tagged (Nig99) early last four years, huge sum of money running into millions of United States Dollars was budgeted by the then Military Government for the successful organization of this competition. In the same vein, FIFA via its President, Mr. Joseph (SEPP) Blatter, made millions of dollars available for the same project, not to talk of Corporate Organizations and Football loving individuals who made huge donations. However, in my capacity as the deputy secretary, to both the Local Organizing Committee (LOC), and the Nigerian Football Association(NFA), I,along with two of my colleagues in sensitive positions were able to over-invoice most contracts, which were awarded for the construction and the refurbishing of the 8 stadia used for the competition. The contractors who handled these projects have been paid-off. It is pertinent to note that a total sum of thirty-two million United States Dollars(US$32,000,000.00) was realized as over-invoice after the successful completion of the project. This over-invoiced sum is lying in my organization's (NFA) suspense account with the Central Bank of Nigeria (CBN), ready for transfer into the beneficiarys account oversea, waiting for the appropriate opportunity to do so. In this years (2003) budget speech, the new Civilian President has ordered that all foreign contractors debts should be paid in order to boost more Foreign investors into Nigeria. On this note, I have been unanimously mandated by my two colleagues to seek an honest and trustworthy Foreigner who will assist in ensuring the successful transfer of the above sum into a personal/company account since the Nigerian code of conduct does not allow us (Civil servants) to operate foreign accounts. It is pertinent also to let you know that 30% of the total fund will be for you, while 10% will be used to settle any expenses that might be incurred by both parties and the remaining 60% will be for us (my colleagues and I) to be invested in your country. We have chosen you /your company to benefit with us in this transaction due to the respect your country commands here. These are the necessary requirements we needed from you to complete this transaction: 1. Your bank Name, contact address and your account number where the money will be remitted. 2.Your bank telex, fax and telephone numbers. 3.Your personal phone/fax numbers for easy communication. The above-mentioned particulars will be used to write LETTER OF CLAIM on behalf of your company from my ministry as the beneficiary of the fund. You might be surprised and curious of an offer like this, be rest assured that the modalities and logistics towards the successful transfer of this fund has been worked out. All we require from you is your co-operation. This transaction is risk free. We kindly request that you accord it the highest level of secrecy it deserves. Email:harryobum001@asiamail.com for security reason. Your swift response will be highly appreciated. Best regards, DR HARRY OBUM

FROM:Mr.D Dumas. #24 garden Avenue, Sungu Johannesburg Rep Of South Africa. Dear Sir/Madam, I am Mr.D Dumas. a consulting auditor of prime banks here in South Africa. I have the courage to Crave indulgence for this important business believing that you will never let me down either now or in the future. Some year ago, an American Mining consultant/ contractor with the South African Mining corporation, made a numbered time (fixed)deposit for twelve calendar months, valued $142M.USD (ONE HUNDRED AND FORTY TWO MILLION US DOLLARS) in an account. On maturity, The bank sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, The bank sent another reminder and finally his contract employers, the South African Mining corporation wrote to inform the bank that he died without MAKING A WILL, and all attempts by the American Embassy to trace his next of kin was fruitless.I therefore, made further investigation and discovered that the beneficiary was an immigrant from Jamaica and only recently obtained American citizenship. He did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank deposit paper work. This money total amount$142M.USD (ONE HUNDRED AND FORTY TWO MILLION US DOLLARS)is still sitting in my bank as dormant Account.No one will ever come forward to claim it, and according to South African banking policy, after some years, the money will revert to the ownership of the South African Government if the account owner is certified dead. This is the situation, and my proposal is that I am looking for a foreigner who will stand in as the next of kin to beneficiary, and OPEN a Bank Account abroad to facilitate the transfer of this money.This is simple, all you have to do is to OPEN an account anywhere in the world and send me its detail for me to arrange the proper money transfer paperwork, and facilitate the transfer.The money will then be paid into this Account for us to share in the ratio of 60% for me, 30 % for you and 10% for expenses that might come up during transfer process. There is no risk at all, and all the paper work for this transaction will be done by me using my position and connections in the banks in South Africa. This business transaction is guaranteed.And the first phase of the transfer will be ($42M.USD) FORTY TWO MILLION DOLLARS as advised by our insider in the bank.If you are interested, please reply immediately through my personal email sending the following details: (1) Your Full Name/Address (2) Your Private Telephone/fax Number. (3)Your Full Account Details. A{BANK ACCOUNT: B}BANK NAME: C}BANK ADDRESS D}BENEFICIARY OF NAME: E}SWIFT CODE NO: THEN IMMEDIATELY YOU SEND ALL THIS INFORMATION REQUIRED BY THE BANK,THEY WILL IT TO CREDIT YOUR NAME AS THE TRUE BENEFICIARY OF THE FUND.AND YOU HAVE TO BEAR IN MIND THAT THE DECEASE PERSON DIED WITHOUT ANY {WILLS},YOU ARE STAND NOW AS THE OWNER OF THE MONEY THE BANK KNOW OK. Please observe the utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest some of my share in your country.I will give to you,My Private:Tele & Fax Number which I bought for this business upon your positive response for heart to heart discussion and once I am convinced that you are capable and will meet up with the instructions of a key bank official who is deeply involved with me in this business.I need your strong assurance that you will never let me down now or in future. I look forward to your earliest reply through my private email address.Pls you can reach me throught my private email account{dumas_10@yahoo.ca) Best Regards, Mr.D Dumas. PLEASE CALL ME IF YOU NEED TO CAL,BUT YOU HAVE TO CALL DIRECT,DUE TO IT IS STATELITE PHONE I JUST BOUGHT IT FOR THE SUCCESS OF THE TRANSACTION ONLY Phone No:874-763-427980. Fax No:874-763-427981.

ATTN: PRESIDENT/CEO Dear Sir, I am Dr. Ekiyoh Martins a native of Cape Town in South Africa and I am an Executive Accountant with the South African department of Mining and Natural Resources. Please accept my apology for using this medium to convey a transaction/business of this magnitude, but this is due to the confidentiality and prompt access reposed on this medium. I have decided to seek your co-operation in the execution of this deal described hereunder, for the benefit of all parties and hoping you will keep it as TOP SECRET because of the nature of the business. Within the department of Mining and Natural Resources (where I work as a director), and with the cooperation of four other top officials, we have in our possession as overdue payment bills totaling Fourty Five Million, Five Hundred Thousand US Dollars (US$45,500,000.00) which we want to transfer abroad with the assistance and cooperation of a company/or an individual to receive the said funds, via a reliable Bank Account. Quite frankly, we are handicapped as the South African civil service laws (Code of Conduct Bureau) strongly prohibits us from owning/or operating a foreign account hence your importance in this whole transaction. This amount (US$45.5M) represents the balance of the total value of a contract executed on behalf of my department by a foreign contracting firm which we the officials (involved) deliberately over-invoiced. Though the actual cost have been paid to the original contractor leaving the balance in the tune of the said amount which we have in principle gotten approval to remit by Key Tested Telegraphic transfer (K.T.T.) to any foreign bank account you will provide by filing an application through the justice ministry here in South Africa for the transfer of rights and privileges of the former contractor to you. I have the authority of my partners involved to propose that should you be willing to assist us i this transaction by way of providing the required account in receiving these funds, your share of the entire sum will be 30% amounting to Us$13.65Million of the US$45.5Million, 60% amounting to US$27.3Million for us and 10% amounting to US$4.55Million will be used to settle taxation and other miscellaneous expenses in the course of transferring the funds to your account. The business itself is 100% foolproof and safe, as long as you maintain utmost secrecy and confidentiality. Further more your area of specialization will not be a hindrance to the successful completion of this transaction. I have reposed my confidence in you and hope you will not disappoint me. Should you be willing to assist positively with a common goal, endeavor to contact me immediately through my above email address. If you are not interested, please also indicate so that it will enable me to contact other foreign partner with recommendations to carry out this deal. I want to assure you that my colleagues and I are in position to make the payment of this claim possible provided that you can give us a very concrete assurance of the safety of our share. Please, always treat this matter with utmost confidentiality, because we will not comprehend any form of exposure as we are still in active government service. Time is of essence in this business, so kindly act fast. I await in anticipation your fullest co-operation. Yours Faithfully, DR. EKIYOH MARTINS.

FROM: Dr. John Mikado. Director of Projects, DME, South Africa. I am Dr. John Mikado, Director of projects Implementation South Africa Department of Minerals & Energy. First and foremost, I apologized using this medium to reach you for a transaction / business of this magnitude, but this is due to confidentiality and prompt access reposed on this medium. In unfolding this proposal, I want to count on you as a respected & honest person to handle this transaction with sincerity, trust & confidentiality. I have decided to seek a confidential co-operation with you in the execution of the deal described hereunder for the benefit of all parties and hope you will keep confidential because of the nature of the transaction. Within the Department of Minerals & Energy where I work as a director of projects Implementation and with the co-operation of three other top officials, we have in our possession as overdue payment bills totaling 28.5million US dollars. which we want to transfer abroad with the assistance and co-operation of a company or individual to receive the said funds on our behalf. We are seeking your assistance to front as beneficiary of the said funds, More so, we are handicapped in the circumstance as the South Africa Civil Service code of conduct does not allow us to operate foreign account hence your importance in the whole transaction. This amount (US$28.5m) represents the balance of the total contract value executed on behalf of my Department by a foreign contracting firm which we the officials over-invoiced deliberately. Though the actual contract cost have been paid to the original contractor, leaving the balance of the US$28.5m. which we have in principle gotten approvals from the Department of Finance and the contract review and payment committee to transfer by telegraphic transfer to any bank account you will provide. It does not matter whether you or your company does contract projects as a transfer of power and privileges with details & change of information upon application to reflect payment in favour of you or your company will be secured on behalf of you or your company. I have the mandate of my partners involved to propose that should you be willing to assist us in the transaction, your share of the sum will be US$7.125m 25% of the US$28.5 million, US$19.95m 70% for us and US$1.425m 5% for taxation and miscellaneous expenses. The business itself is 100% safe and secure, on your part provided you treat it with ultmost confidentiality. Also, your area of trade or specialization is not an hindrance to the successful execution of this transaction. I have reposed my confidence in you and hope that you will not disappoint me. Please, endeavour to contact me immediately through my email for further clarifications. I want to assure you that myself and my partners are in the position to make the payment of this funds possible provided you can give us a very strong assurance and guarantee that our share will be secured and please remember to treat this matter as very confidential, and remember once again that time is of the essence in this business. I wait in anticipation of your fullest co-operation. Best Regards, Dr. John Mikado. NB: please reply with your confidential contact phone & fax numbers, to enable me contact you urgently for further clarifications.

Kind Attn: CEO/ Manager Director  Supply Quality China's EXCLUSIVE dimensions at Unbeatable Price. Dear Sir,  We are pleased to inform you as one of China's largest export & import stone company-Wanlistone Group, The Group its subsidiaries specialize in the quarrying, processing and Sales of dimension stone, slab and tiles and dimension stone products for the building materials sector and specialty markets.  The Group operations are based in Xiamen, South of China, which is the largest export and import business portals in China where Wanlistone owns and operates various natural stone deposits with 6,000 square meters through the country. In addition to the quarries Wanlistone has a fully automated processing plant for the processing of the granite and marble and granite products.  Wanlistone supplies granite in raw block form, granite and marble tile and strips of varying dimension, memorial materials and specialty products to both the local but more specifically the export markets.  The Group has a full rang of the China natural stone products including  Pink color G636, G617, G635, G663, Yellow color, G682,Dark G654, Black G684.  Light Grey: Imperial Grey, Huaan Grey.  Wanlistone owns and operates all its own quarries, including North Black, Huana White, Butterfly Blue, and Golden Beige. All block production is sold to both the local and international markets. The Group is very price competitive on all its products due to its low overhead structure. All blocks are ideally produced for gang saw processing and dimension of 240 x 120 are standard. Smaller blocks are also available for selection  We will feel it an honour if we could serve you and welcome your inquiry in our products. Looking forward to hearing from you soonest.  Sincerely yours, Sales Department  XIAMEN WANLI STONE GROUP, 8 F Fortune Building , 201 North Hubin Rd, Xiamen 361012, P.R.China.  Tel:+86-592 -5081199  Fax:+86-592-5620 971 Web site: www.wanli.com <http://www.wanli.com>  ------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------ Company profile:  Established in 1985  Located in Xiamen as No.1 port of stone Exp.& Imp. Total assets: US$10Million  Turnover of export in 2003: US$0.28 billion  Advantages in China:  The No.1 professional & over-sized stone group at present, its business are associated with import & export t, processing and manufacturing, and quarrying.  One of the largest exporters of stone products  One of the leading importers of stone blocks from the world  Group structure:  XIAMEN WANISTONE as headquarter of operation and management, total 9 business departments, 1 design department, 1 resource development section of which,  Subsidiary company list:  1.XIAMEN ORITENT WANLISTONE COMPANY, a joint venture with MARLING and DORKING in South African, specializes in all types of stone blocks worldwide. And two blocks depots of 6,000 square meter.  2.AMERICA SINASTONE CO.,LTD, a professional supplier of all kinds of  monuments business in USA market place  3.SOUTH AFRICA WANLINSTONE CO., LTD, a factory invested with MARLING and DORKING, is to process special monuments, slab and tiles  Own Factories list  1.XIAMEN WANLISTONE CO, LTD, with 8 modern high speed granite gang saws, Gaspari Menotti, , 2 sets marble gang saws, 30 sets circular saws, for slab, tile and all profile stone finish  2.XIAMEN WANLISTONE CRAFT CO, LTD, Monuments is key.  3.LINGFONG WANLISTONE FACTORY IN QUANZHOU CITY, Monuments is key. 4.TIANJING WANLISTONE FACTORY in north of China, Slab + Monuments produced  5.HUNAN HUAJIAN FACTORY in Hunan, Granite slab + tile available  Own quarries list  1．IMPERIAL GREY，located in HUNAN province  2．NORTH BLACK，Located in SHANXI province 3．HUNAN WHITE ， located in HUNAN province 4．BUTTERFLY BLUE ，Located in LEMONGGU province  5．GOLDEN BEIGE ，Located in SHANXI province Key market:  Japan   50% USA    15% EU     20% China   15% Products involve construction materials, monuments and stone finishes.  World stone connecting  Very good connecting with the famous stone companies as for growth up together.

FROM THE DESK OF: MR XIAO GANG, BANK OF OVERSEAS CHINESE TAIPEI,TAIWAN Dear Friend, How are you today and business in your country? I am Mr.Xiao Gang, Bank Manager,Bank Of Overseas Chinese North Shyn Lin District, Taipei, Taiwan. I would respectfully request that you keep the contents of this mail confidential and respect the integrity of the information you come by as a result of this mail. I contacted you independently of our investigation and no one is informed of this communication. I would like to intimate you with certain facts that I believe would be of interest to you. I know you would be wondering why I am writing you with a request such as this but I only urge you to read on. In November 1998, a British Oil consultant/contractor with the Chinese Solid Minerals Corporation, Mr. Mark Kogan, made a Fixed Deposit of the sum of US$10,000,000.00 (Ten Million United States Dollars) which accumulated to the sum of US$20,160,176.00 (Twenty Million, One hundred and sixty thousand, One hundred and seventy six United States Dollars for twelve calendar months in my branch. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address in America and Britain but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the Chinese Solid Minerals Corporation that Mr.Mark Kogan died alongside his wife, from an airplane crash. The bank immediately launched an investigation into possible surviving next of kin to alert about the situation and also to come forward to claim his estate. If you are familiar with private banking affairs, those who patronize our services usually prefer anonymity, but also some levels of detachment from conventional processes. In his bio-data form, he listed no next of kin. In the field of private banking, opening an account with us means no one will know of its existence, accounts are rarely held under a name; depositors use numbers and codes to make the accounts anonymous. This bank also gives the choice to depositors of having their mail sent to them or held at the bank itself, ensuring that there are no traces of the account and as I said, rarely do they nominate next of kin. Private banking clients apart from not nominating next of kin also usually in most cases leave wills in our care, in this case; Mr. Mark Kogan died interstate. In line with our internal processes for account holders who have passed away, we instituted our own investigations in good faith to determine who should have right to claim the estate. This investigation has for the past months been unfruitful. We have scanned every continent and used our private investigation affiliate companies to get to the root of the problem. This sum of US$20,160,176.00 has since been sitting in my Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to the Laws of Republic of China, at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Chinese Government if nobody applies to claim the funds. What I wish to relate to you will smack of unethical practice but I want you to understand something. It is only an outsider to the banking world who finds the internal politics of the banking world aberrational. The world of banking especially is fraught with huge rewards for those who occupy certain offices and oversee certain portfolios. You should have begun by now to put together the general direction of what I propose. There is US$20,160,176.00 deposited in my bank, I alone have the deposit details and they will release the deposit to no one unless evidence of relationship with the deceased, which I shall provide you with, is presented. I alone know of the existence of this deposit for as far as Bank of overseas chinese is concerned, the bank's management has no single idea of what’s the history or nature of the deposit. They are simply awaiting instructions to release the deposit to any party that comes forward. This is the situation. This bank has spent great amounts of money trying to track this man’s family; they have investigated for months and have found no family. The investigation has come to an end. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr. mark kogan so that the fruits of this old man's labour will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. Acting in this capacity really is simple, all you have to do is provide your full names and address so that an attorney here can prepare the necessary documents and affidavits that will put you in place as the next of kin. We shall employ the services of an attorney for drafting and notarization of the WILL and to obtain the necessary authentication, approval and a letter of probate/administration in your favour for the transfer to be done. A bank account in any part of the world that you then provide me with will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your account for us to share 90/10. I am aware of the consequences of this proposal. I ask that if you find no interest in this project that you should discard this mail. I ask that you do not be vindictive and destructive. If my offer is of no appeal to you, delete this message and forget I ever contacted you. Do not destroy my career because you do not approve of my proposal. You may not know this but people like myself who have made tidy sums out of comparable situations run the whole private banking sector. I am not a criminal and what I do, I do not find against good conscience, this may be hard for you to understand, but the dynamics of my industry dictates that I make this move. Such opportunities only come ones' way once in a lifetime. I cannot let this chance pass me by, for once I find myself in total control of my destiny. This is my chance and i wont let it pass me by. I ask that you do not destroy my chance, if you will not work with me let me know and let me move on with my life but do not destroy me. I am a family man and this is an opportunity to provide my family with new opportunities. There is a reward for this project and it is a task well worth undertaking. I have evaluated the risks and the only risk I have here is from you refusing to work with me and alerting my bank. There is no risk whatsoever as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and my position as the Branch Manager guarantee the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested in this lucrative role, I urge you to indicate to that effect. Upon your response, if favourable, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant information that will help you get full understanding of the transaction. I will appreciate it if you send me your confidential telephone and fax numbers for easier communication. If you find yourself able to work with me, contact me through this email address. If you give me positive signals, I will initiate this process towards a conclusion. I wish to inform you that should you contact me via official channels; I will deny knowing you and about this project. I repeat, I do not want you contacting me through my official phone lines nor do I want you contacting me through my official email account. Contact me only through the numbers I will provide for you and also through this email address. My official lines are not secure lines as they are periodically monitored to assess our level of customer care in line with our Total Quality Management Policy. Please observe this instruction religiously. Please, again, note I am a family man, I have a wife and children. I send you this mail not without a measure of fear as to what the consequences may be, but I know within me that nothing ventured is nothing gained and that success and riches never come easy or on a platter of gold. This is the one truth I have learned from my private banking clients. Do not betray my confidence. If we can be of one accord, we should plan a meeting, soon. In closing, please observe utmost confidentiality, and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Upon receiving your reply, I will then furnish you with a more comprehensive detail of this transaction and what is required of you. Please respond to my alternative mail box xg1002003@yahoo.com.tw Awaiting your urgent reply. Yours Sincerely, Mr. Xiao Gang.

My name is john paul, a member of Independent Committee of Eminent Persons (ICEP), Switzerland. ICEP is charged with the responsibility of finding bank accounts in Switzerland belonging to non-Swiss indigenes, which have remained dormant since World War II. It may interest you to know that in July of 1997, the Swiss Banker's Association published a list of dormant accounts originally opened by non-Swiss citizens. These accounts had been dormant since the end of World War II (May 9, 1945). Most belonged to Holocaust victims. The continuing efforts of the Independent Committee of Eminent Persons (ICEP) have since resulted in the discovery of additional dormant accounts - 54,000 in December, 1999. The published lists contain all types of dormant accounts, including interest-bearing savings accounts, securities accounts, safe deposit boxes, custody accounts, and non-interest-bearing transaction accounts. Numbered accounts are also included. Interest is paid on accounts that were interest bearing when established. The Claims Resolution Tribunal (CRT) handles processing of all claims on accounts due non-Swiss citizens. A dormant account of ORDNER ADELE with a credit balance of 35,000,000 US dollar plus accumulated interest was discovered by me. The beneficiary was murdered during the holocaust era, leaving no WILL and no possible records for trace of heirs. The Claims Resolution Tribunal has been mandated to report all unclaimed funds for permanent closure of accounts and transfer of existing credit balance into the treasury of Switzerland government as provided by the law for management of assets of deceased beneficiaries who died interstate (living no wills). Being a top executive at ICEP, I have all secret details and necessary contacts for claim of the funds without any hitch. The funds will be banked in the Cayman Island, being a tax free, safe haven for funds and we can share the funds and use in investment of our choice. Due to the sensitive nature of my job, I need a foreigner to HELP claim the funds. All that is required is for you to provide me with your details for processing of the necessary legal and administrative claim documents for transfer of the funds to you. Kindly provide me with your full name, address, and telephone/fax. I will pay all required fees to ensure that the fund is transferred to a secure, numbered account in your name in the Cayman Island, of which you will be capable of accessing the funds gradually and transferring to your country and other banks of choice in the world. My share will be 60 percent and your share is 40 per cent of the total amount. THERE IS NO RISK INVOLVED. You can find additional information about unclaimed funds through the internet at the following websites: www.swissbankclaims.com http://www.cnn.com/WORLD/europe/9902/09/germany.holocaust/ www.avotaynu.com www.icheic.org www.livingheirs.com www.wiesenthal.com The Holocaust Claims Processing Office has put funds in Escrow awaiting submission of valid claims for necessary disbursement. I find myself priviledged to have this information and this may be a great opportunity for a life time of success without risks. Due to security reasons, reply to my via email only. You may reply to me securely on the following email, gtmail_john@email.cz Thank you for your prompt response. john paul

Compliments of the seasons Dearest One, Hello. My name is Mohamed Zuba,the eldest son of late chief Dandy Zuba of Zimbabwe. This might be a surprise to you about where I got your contact address. I got your(CONTACT FROM THE SOUTH AFRICAN BUSINESS NETWORK ONLINE).During the current war against the farmers in Zimbabwe from the supporters of our President Robert Mugabe to claim all the white-owned farms to his party members and his followers, he ordered all farmers to surrender all farms to his party members and his followers. My father was Rated as One of the best farmers in our country 2003 before his untimely Death and because he did not support Mugabe's idea,Mugabe's supporters invaded my father's farm and burnt everything in the farm,killing my father and few workers and made away with a lot of items in my father's farm.But before his Death, he had deposited with a Security Company in SOUTH AFRICA the sum of US$24.600 MILLION (TWENTY FOUR MILLION SIXHUNDERD THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS).After the death of my father, I decided to move to the Republic of SOUTH AFRICA FOR SAFETY to leave for the main time and still continue my Quest of claiming this Consignment as my country is no longer SAFE for me. To this end,I decided to contact overseas firm and companies that will assist me to move this money out of SOUTH AFRICA because as Asylum Seekers we are not allowed to operate any Bank Account with in SOUTH AFRICA. I have secured the legal help of an Attorney here in DUBAI who will be working with you to lay claim to this Consignment and his contacts are: NAME: BARRISTERPAUL OKORO, EMAIL: brr_paulokoro@hotmail.comYou can contact him to get more details to proceed further to success. I have agreed to offer you 25% of the total sum for your assistance,while 75% will be for ME to invest in your country but I will like to invest in any INDUSTRY.All I want you to do is to furnish me with your personal phone and fax numbers for easy communication and follow up with my Attorney to achieve the needed result. I am taking you as my Parent because I lost all my siblings and family in the CRISIS. Note that this transaction is 100% Risk free,legal,and absolutely confidential. Thanks and God Bless. Truly Yours Son, >From Mohamed Zuba. SOUTH AFRICA, JOHANNESBURG. Alternative E-mail:mohamedzuba1000@hotmail.com

NJAMBA CHAMBERS & PARTNERS FROM THE DESK OF BARRISTER CHRIS NWOKE EMAIL: barristernwoke2004@pnetmail.co.za Dear Sir, I am Barrister Chris Nwoke, a solicitor at law. I am the personal attorney to Mr. Pitt Kay, a national of your country, who used to work with SILVIC OIL REFINERIES in Nigeria. Here in after shall be referred to as my client.On the 21st of April 2001, my client, his wife and their only daughter were involved in a car accident along Lagos - Ogun express road.All occupants of the vehicle unfortunately lost there lives. Since then I have made several enquiries to your embassy here to locate any of my clients extended relatives, this has also proved unsuccessful. After these several unsuccessful attempts, I decided to track his last name over the Internet, to locate any member of his family hence I contacted you.I have contacted you to assist in repartrating the fund valued at US$13 million Left behind by my client before it gets Confisicated or declared unserviceable by the Security Finance Firm where this huge amount were deposited. The said Security Finance company has issued me a notice to provide the next of kin or have the account confisicated within the next fourteen official working days. For the fact that I have been unsuccesfull in locating the relatives for over 3 years now, I seek the consent to present you as the next of kin to the deceased,since you have the same last name with my client,so that the proceeds of this account can be paid to you. Therefore, on receipt of your positive response, we shall then discuss the sharing ratio and modalities for transfer.I have all necessary information and legal documents needed to back you up for claim. All I require from you is your honest cooperation to enable us see this transaction through. I guarantee that this will be executed under legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. Please get in touch with me through my private email for more details. Best regards, BARRISTER CHRIS NWOKE !Navega con el Internet Gratis de Amnet! Descarga el Programa de Instalación. Para cualquier consulta llamar al 247-8000

>From Mr. Alfred Douglas, Head Audit Department, Continental Bank, Cotounu, Benin Republic. TEL: 00229 28 30 63 Please reply to; alfred_douglas1@yahoo.fr My dear, Good day and God bless you. It is with deep sence of commitment, faith and trust that I make this confidential risk free business proposal to you for your assistance/partnership. I am deeply sorry if I have in any manner disturbe your privacy. I am Mr. Alfred Douglas the head of the Audit Department of Continental Bank in Cotounu Benin Republic. Recently, I discovered a domant account with a huge amount of money valued at USD15.500,000.00 (fifteen million ,five hundred thousand US dollars) that belongs to one of our numerouse customers MR.PIERE JOHNSON from Germany who died in a ghastly motor accident in Cotounu on 5th OF May 2000. During the period of my investigation I discovered that the deceased left no will and nobody behind to come for the claim as his beneficiary. Since then several inquiries to locate any of MR. PIERE JOHNSON extended relatives have proved unsuccessful, hence I decided to contact you since the banking law here stipulates that if such money remain unclaimed for a period of time, it will be forfieted to the gorvernment treasury as an unclaimed fund which will be expended on acquiring dangeriouse weaponse for the support of their selfish political interest and promoting wars and ethnic crises in Africa. I have decided to contact you to assist me to pull out this fund from this bank as the business partner of MR. PIERE JOHNSON for the claim of the fund. I want to also bring to your notice that as the Head of the Audit department of this bank if this fund is not pulled out before our auditing the fund fund will be discovered by my colleagues and that will definately lead to the government confiscating the money into the federation account. You might ask what will be the proceedure to achieve this. As soon as I get your positive response to assist me, I will then send to you the proceedure and the next step to follow. So if this meets your interest then get back to me to enable me send to you the procedure of claiming this fund. I have in my possetion all the necessary information of the deceased (MR. PIERE JOHNSON) that will help us successfully accomplish this transaction. You shall be offered 30% for your assistance, while 5% shall be set aside for any expences that we might incure during the transaction. Futher response shall be giving to you as soon as I recieve your positive response. Fell free to call me on my private number (229) 28 30 63 for any question you may wish to ask me. Anticipating your urgent reply. Regards, Mr. Alfred Douglas Alternative email; alfred_douglas1@yahoo.fr

LT.COL Richard Egwu JOHANNESBURG, R.S.A. TELL: +27-83-535 5883 Email: egwu18@hotmail.com ATT: MANAGING DIRECTOR|C.E.O Sir|madam I know you will be surprise to read from me, more so when it came from a stranger. But please consider this letter as a request from somebody in dare of assistance. Firstly, I must introduce myself, I am lt. Col. Richard Egwu the former personal security to the late president Laurent Kabila of the democratic republic of Congo (DRC) formerly Zaire. I am presently in the republic of South Africa as an asylum seeker. I got your contact address from a business directory in Johannesburg chamber of commerce and industry and after going through your profile,I decided to solicit for your assistance to transfer the sum of US$ 25million (Twenty-five Million United States Dollars) into your company or personal account for investment purposes outside Africa. Before his death, late president kabila was aware that rebels will not leave any stone unturned in their attempt to remove him from government hence he started looting the countrys treasure. In May 2000, he directed me to oversee the movement of a certain box marked diplomatic documents into Zimbabwe but I decided to divert the box into the republic of South Africa where I found out that the box was actually containing the sum of US$ 25 million (Twenty-five million united states dollars). I therefore deposited the box containing the fund into a security and finance company here in Johannesburg. I have been in hiding since then but with the recent death of president Kabila I therefore decided to transfer this money out of Africa for investment. >From the above, you will understand that my life and that of my children depends on the fund as such, I will be grateful if you can assist me. I am now living in the republic of South Africa, as a political asylum seeker with my family and the financial rules and regulations of South Africa do not permit me financial right to such huge amount of money. In view of this, I cannot invest this fund in South Africa, hence I am prepared to offer you 20% of the total sum for your assistance, while 10% will be set aside for unforeseen expenses and 70% will be for me and my family's investment in your country with your assistance. Please call me on the above telephone or email me to signify your interest in this transaction. Thanks and God bless you for your anticipated co-operation. Lt.Col . Richard Egwu Engr. Richard Egwu

FROM THE DESK OF DR .WILLIAMS KOFFI CONFIDENCIAL! DEAR FRIEND, MY NAME IS DR WILLIAMS KOFFI I HAIL FROM THE FEDERAL REPUBLIC OF GHANA,41 YEARS YOUNG MARRIED, WITH THREE CHILDREN. I AM THE DIRECTOR OF STANDARD SECURITY AND FINANCE SERVICES LIMITED GHANA.I GOT THE INFORMATION CONCERNING YOU FROM THE INTERNET AND AFTER DUE CONSIDERATION,I DECIDED TO CONTACT YOU BELIEVING THAT BY THE GRACE OF GOD, THAT YOU WILL NOT DISAPPOINT ME OVER THIS DEAL. I HAVE BEEN WORKING WITH THIS COMPANY FOR OVER TEN YEARS. WITHIN THIS PERIOD, I HAVE WATCHED WITH METICULOUS PRECISION HOW AFRICAN HEADS OF STATE AND GOVERNMENT FUNCTIONARIES HAVE BEEN USING GLOBAL SECURITY AND FINANCE LIMITED TO MOVE SUMS OF MONEY USD, POUNDS STERLING, FRENCH FRANCS (CASH)TO THEIR FOREIGN PARTNERS. THEY BRING IN THESE CONSIGNMENTS OF CASH AND SECRETLY DECLARE THE CONTENTS AS JEWELRIES, GOLD, DIAMONDS, PRECIOUS STONES, FAMILY TRE ASURES AND DOCUMENTS ETC. GEN. SANI ABACHA OF NIGERIA, (DEAD), MOBUTU SESE SECO OF ZIARE (DEAD),FODE SANKOY OF SIERRA LEONE, BABANGIDA OF NIGERIA, FELIX HOUPHET BOIGNY OF COTE D'IVORE (DEAD), KANAN BEDIE OF COTE D' IVORE (ABIDJAN) ETC. ALL THESE PEOPLE HAVE HUNDREDS OF CONSIGNMENTS DEPOSITED WITH MY OFFICE.THEIR FOREIGN PARTNERS, FRIENDS AND RELATIVES ARE CLAIMING MOST OF THESE CONSIGNMENTS. ALOT OF THEM ARE LYING HERE UNCLAIMED FOR AS MUCH AS EIGHT YEARS. NOBODY WILL EVER COME FOR THEM BECAUSE IN MOST CASES, THE CERTIFICATE OF DEPOSIT ARE NEVER AVAILABLE TO ANY BODY EXCEPT THE DEPOSITORS HENCE MOST OF THEM ARE DEAD. I HAVE MOVED SOME TO OUR OFFICE IN HOLLAND AND LONDON (READY FOR COLLECTION). I AM WAITING TO HEAR FROM YOU. SINCE THE INCEPTION OF THE YEAR 2000, OUR COMPANY'S MANAGEMENT HAS CHANGED THE PROCEDURE OF CLAIMS OF CONSIGNMENT, AS SOON AS YOU ARE ABLE TO PRODUCE THE SECRET INFORMATION AS CONTAINED IN THE SECRET FILE OF ANY CONSIGNMENT, IT WILL BE RELEASED TO YOU UPON DEMAND FROM OUR RECORD, MORE THAN 160 CONSIGNMENTS BELONGING TO GEN.ABACHA, MOBUTU SESE SECO HAS BEEN CLAIMED IN THE PAST SIX MONTHS AND THIS IS WHY AM SOLICITING FOR YOUR MAXIMUM CO-OPERATION AND ASSISTANCE. GEN. ABACHA HAS 160 CONSIGNMENTS DEPOSITED WITH SEVERAL NAMES AND CODES.64 HAVE BEEN CLAIMED IN THE PAST SIX MONTHS. THE FIRST SON OF GEN. ABACHA DIED IN A PLANE CRASH AND THE SECOND SON (MOHAMMED) IS FACING A MURDER CHARGE AND EMBEZZLEMENT, THE FAMILY MEMBERS ARE UNDER HOUS ARREST WITHOUT COMMUNICATION WITH THE OUTSIDE WORLD. I HAVE FINALIZED EVERY ARRANGEMENT FOR YOU TO COME AND CLAIM CONSIGNMENT NO;1402,1401 CONTAINING $46 MILLION. I WILL SUPPLY YOU WITH ALL THE INFORMATION AND DOCUMENTS AND YOU WILL SEND IT BY ATTACHMENT TO THE MANAGEMENT OF OUR COMPANY. THE PROCEDURE IS SIMPLE; APPLY OFFICIALLY TO THE DIRECTOR OF FOREIGN OPERATIONS OF THE COMPANY, REQUESTING FOR THE RELEASE OF CONSIGNMENT NO; 1402, 1401. THEY WILL DEMAND FOR THE CERTIFICATE OF DEPOSITE AND THE SECRET CODE AND REFERENCE CODE OF THE CONSIGNMENTS. I WILL SUPPLY THEM TO YOU AND THEY WILL INVITE YOU TO COME AND RECEIVE YOUR CONSIGNMENTS. I WILL USE YOUR NAME, ADDRESS, PASSPORT NUMBER TO CHANGE THE ORIGINAL DOCUMENT IN THE FILE AND EVERY THING WILL BE OK HENCE I AM IN CHARGE. IN CONCLUSION, I ASSURE YOU THAT THIS BUSINESS IS RISK FREE. (OUR MODE OF SHARING IS 50-50), YOU CAN REACH ME BY EMAIL AND I WILL DIRECT YOU ON WHAT TO DO. YOUR'S SINCERELY, DR WILLIAMS koffi. REPLY NEEDED.

ATT: STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL I know you will be surprised to read from me,but please consider this letter as a request from a family in their need of your assistance.First I must introduce myself I am MR MARK BIYA from ANGOLA.I am the first and only SON of the late BRIGADIER PAUL , i am presently residing in South Africa. I got your contact from South Africa Information Exchange(S.A.I.E)here in Johannesburg and on behalf of my widowed mother,MRS PHILOMIN ,I decided to solicit for your assistance to transfer the sum of US$21,320,000.00,(Twenty One Million, Three Hundred and Twenty Thousand United State Dollars)inherited from my late father into your personal or company's account. Before my father's death,he was Brigadier in charge of arms and ammunition purchase for the Angola Armed Forced.in his 'WILL'he specific! ally drew my attention to this sum of US$21,320Million,which he deposited in a safe box of a private security company in south African FACT MY FATHER SAID IN HIS WILL AND QUOTE:- 'MY beloved son,I wish to draw your attention to the sum of US$21,320,000.00(Twenty One million,three hundred and twenty thousand united state dollars),which I deposited in a box with a security company in Johannesburg, South African case of my absence on earth caused by death only,you should solicit for reliable foreign partner to assist you to transfer this money out of south Africa for investment purpose deposited the money in your name and it can be claimed by you alone with the deposit code.Your mother has all the document.Take good care of your mother and sister.' >From the above,you will understand that the lives and future of my family depends on this money will be very grateful if you can assist us.We are now living in south Africa as political asylum seekers an! d the financial laws of south Africa does not allow asylum seeker certain financial rights to such huge amount of money.In view of this,I cannot invest this south africa,hence I am asking you to assist me transfer this money out of south africa for investment purpose.for your efforts am prepared to offer you 25%of the total fund, while 5%will be set aside for local and international expenses and 70%will be kept by my family and me. All I want you to do is to furnish me with your entire personal phone and fax numbers for easy communication. You can contact me on the above Telephone,Fax or E-mail Address. Note that this transaction is 100% Risk free and absolutely confidential. Thanks and God bless. Best regards, MR MARK BIYA.

FROM: DR Andrew Godson GRAND FINANCE AND TRUST RUE CLUB DE L' AMITIE, 0251 B.P. 1625 COTONOU, BENIN REPUBLIC. TELEX: 5394 SWIFT: GRAFITR CTNOU PHONE# + 229-40-35-48 Office email:projectag@latinmail.com Dear Sir, Compliments Of The Day, Permit me to introduce myself to you. My name is DR Andrew Godson,a top Management Official of the above Finance Corporation in Cotonou, Benin Republic. I came to know about you in my private search for a reliable person/company to handle an important assingment on behalf of my Colleagues and myself. PROPOSITION: An Australian Engr Donald Pepper, a prosperous Oil/Gold merchant had in our Bank the sum of $28.5million in a domiciliary account. Unfortunately, he was killed in a ghastly motor accident in Benin Republic in 2001. Efforts had been made by the management of my bank through the Australian Embassy to contact any of the deceased children but to no avail. We later discovered that he had no children.Given the skeletal information available to the bank,it has so far been impossible to reach any of the relatives. The situation left for the Management is to declare the deceased account dormant and revert the funds to trading for interest to the Bank. In order to avoid this development, my Colleagues and I now seek your approval to have you stand as a distant relative to Engr Donald Pepper,so that the money would be released to you. All documents and proofs to enable you get the money will be carefully packaged once we receive your consent on this proposal.I shall apply for a leave as soon as the funds get into your reliable account to come to your country for sharing and investments which you will assist me in doing. May I assure you that this is safe and risk-free, as we have taken care of all necessary modalities to ensure a hitch-free movement. I have the authority of my partners involved in this assignment to propose that should you be willing to assist us in this,your share would be 25%. I have reposed my confidence in you and hope that you will not disappoint me. Best Regards, DR Andrew Godson. ................... ANDREW GODSON GRAND FINANCE AND TRUST BANK AUDIT AND ACCOUNT SECTION COTONOU,REPUBLIC DU BENIN +229-40-35-48 ....................

Dear Sir, Good day. My name is Momoni Adoh . I am the regional manager of International Commercial Bank Takoradi branch eastern region of the Republic of Ghana (West Africa). I write you this letter in good faith. I got your contact address from a recent banking forum held in Lome the capital city of Togo our next door neighbor, hence I write you to ask for your assistance in a business venture that will benefit you and I. On January of 2000, one Mr. Dennis Burles who has been living and working in a gold company called Obuasi Goldfields died in the Kenya airways fatal air crash on the coast of Cote D Ivorie on its way to Accra the capital city of Ghana. I was the personal banker to the late Mr. Burles, before his untimely death. You see my friend, the late Mr. Burles had $3M USD deposited in a fixed deposit account in my branch, without any next of kin to inherit the sum, that is the reason I write you this letter. I need you to stand claim as the next of kin so that my bank will not declare this funds a deceased account non-grata, meaning that the bank has full and legal right to claim the funds, since the policy of the bank on deceased customer account is that after 5 years if there is no claim, the funds will be immediately taken by the bank. Frankly speaking I have been working in this bank for close to 10 years and I have nothing to show for it, my yearly income is barely about $2,500 USD after tax and the major reason I packaged this transaction is that I have a 9 year old daughter with leukemia and needs a bone marrow transplant or she will die. I have already made arrangement for this surgery in the UK but I could not afford it, so I really need your help to do this deal or my daughter will die. I am offering you 25% of the total sum after this money is wired to your account, because it is a simple bank-to-bank inheritance claim payment transfer. I will also like you to get me rest assured that you will not abandon me when the money gets to your account. You can reach me on tell: +233 244231712, I have all the payment claim information worked out. Bye for now and thanks for your understanding. Best regards, Mr. Momoni Adoh

ATTN: DIRECTOR/C.E.O My name is MR.PAUL MPOYO, elder son of MR. DANIEL MPOYO of Zimbabwe. This might be a surprise to you where I got your contact address. I got your address from South African Information Exchange in Johannesburg. During the current war against the farmers in Zimbabwe from the supports of our President Robert Mugabe to claim all the white-owned farms to his party members and his followers, he ordered all the white-owned farmers to surrender all their farms to his party members and his followers. My father was one of the best farmers in our country and because he did not support his idea,supporters invaded my father's farm and burnt everything in the farm, killing my father and mad away with a lot of items in my father's farm. After the death of my father, me and my mother and my younger sister decided to move out from Zimbabwe because our lives are still in danger with the money my father kept in his hidden safe in my mother's house. The amount contained in the safe is US$12.8m (Twelve million, eight hundred thousand US dollars)and we decided to move to the United Arab Emirate(U.A.E) where we deposited the money in a Security Company as valuables.So, I decided to contact overseas Firm that will assist me to move this money out of United Arab Emirate. We have agreed to give you from the total sum 20% for helping us to move this money to your country and 5%:will be mapped out for expenses both of us might incured during this transaction and 75% will be for me and my family to invest in your country. All I want is for you to furnish me with all your personal phone and fax numbers for easy communication. Note that this transaction is 100% risk-free and it requires mutual trust and absolute confidentiality and I have taken care of all formalities regarding it. Your urgent response will be highly appreciated in this regard. Thanks and God bless. Best regards, PLEASE REPLY (mpoyo_mpoyo2002@yahoo.co.uk ) MR.PAUL MPOYO.(For the family)

MR BADMUS IGWE BRANCH MANAGER GULF BANK PLC ILUPEJU BRANCH LAGOS NIGERIA. ATTN: PRESIDENT/C.E.O I am pleased to get across to you for a very urgent and profitable business proposal, though I don't know you neither have I seen you before but my confidence was reposed on you when the Chief Executive of Lagos State chamber of Commerce and Industry handed me yourcontact for a confidential business. I am the manager of gulf bank Plc (UBA),Ilupeju branch, Lagos Nigeria.The intended business is thus; We had a customer, a Foreign resident in Nigeria, he was a Contractor with one of the Government Parastatals.He has in his Account in my branch the sum of US 15.5 Million (Fifteen Million, Five Hundred Thousand U.SDollars).Unfortunately, the man died three years ago until today non-of his next of kin has come forward to claim the money. Having noticed this, I in collaboration with two other top Officials of the bank have covered up the account all this while. Now we want you (being a foreigner) to be fronted as one of his next of kin and forward your account and other relevant documents to be advised to you by us to attest to the Claim. We will use our positions to get all internal documentations to back up the claims . The whole procedures will last only five working days to get the fund retrieved successfully without trace even now or in future.Your response is only what we are waiting for as we have arranged all necessary things. As soon as this message comes to you kindly get back to me through my personal email address(adexmol@fastermail.com) indicating your interest, then I will furnish you with the whole procedures to ensure that the deal is successfully concluded. For your assistance we have agreed to give you twenty five percent (25%) of the Total sum at the end of the transaction while 65% would be for my colleagues and I and the remaining 10% would be for any form ofexpenses that may be incurred during the course of the transaction which would be given to us when the money is transferred into your account before splitting the balance on the agreed percentage of 65% to 25%. In order to get all the legal documents from the court, kindly send the following information to us immediately. Your full name,telephone,mobile and fax numbers as well as your resident or company address, Bank Name, Bank Address. I await your earliest response. Thanks, Yours Sincerely, MR BADMUS IGWE

>From Dr. Tony Devon, Road 6 No 74 Isieke Close, Sungu Johannesburg, South Africa. GLOBALPHONE:874:763:427980 GLOBALFAX:874:762:427981 (URGENT AND CONFIDENTAIL BUSINESS) Dear sir, We want to transfer to overseas the sum of One hundred and Forty Two Million United States Dollars (U.S.$ 142,000,000.00) from South Africa. I want to ask you to kindly look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable and fit to provide either an existing bank account or to set up a new bank account immediately to receive this money,though an empty bank account could serve this purpose as long as you will remain honest to me till the end of this important business trusting in you and believing in God that you will never let me down either now or in time to come. I am Dr. Tony Devon the external auditor of a Bank.During the course of our auditing,I discovered a floating fund in an account opened in the bank in 1995 and since 2000 nobody has operated on this account again.After going through some old files in the records, I discovered that the owner of the account died without a "Heir apparent to the throne" hence the money is floating and if I do not remit this money out urgently it will be forfeited for nothing. The owner of this account is a foreigner and an industrialist died, since 1995,until now no other person(s) knows about this account or could give any documentary evidence concerning this account. As such this account has no other beneficiary and my investigation proved to me as well that until his death was the manager Oriental Diamond Company,in South Africa. However, if you are interested in this business we will start the first money transfer with Forty Two Million U.S.Dollars(U.S.$42,000,000.00) upon successful transaction without any disappointment from you. We shall also re-apply for the payment of the remaining amount to your account. While the total amount involved is One hundred and Forty Two Million United States Dollars (U.S.$142,000,000.00)only. I would want us to make a first transfer of [Forty Two Million United States Dollar.(U.S.$42,000,000.00)from this money into a safe foreigners account abroad before the rest. I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money can not be approved to a local account, without valid international foreign "Agreement", but could only be approved to any foreigner with valid international credentials: passport or drivers license and foreign account because this sum is in U.S. dollars and the former owner of the account is a foreigner too, thus the money could only be approved into a foreign account. However, knowing all this, we will reach a binding agreement in this regards.As a matter of urgency, I will inform you the next step to take, while you Send your private telephoneand fax number including the full details of the account to be used for the deposit. I want us to meet face to face to build confidence and to sign a binding agreement that will bind us together before transferring the money to any account of your choice where the fund will be safe. Before we fly to your country for withdrawal, sharing and investments,I need your full co-operation to make this business a success, because the management is ready to approve this payment to any foreigner who has correct information of this account, which I will give to you,upon your positive response and once I am convinced that you are capable and will meet up with the instructions of a key bank official who is deeply involved with me in this business. I need your strong assurance that you will never let me down. With my influence and the position in the bank we can transfer this money to any foreigner's reliable account which you can provide with assurance that this money will be intact pending our physical arrival in your country for sharing. And to build confidence that you can come immediately to discuss with me face to face after which I will make this remittance in your presence and three of us will fly to your country at least two days ahead of the money going into the account. I will apply for annual leave to get visa immediately I hear from you that you are ready to act as directed. To prove the authenticity of the business I will use my position and influence to obtain all legal approvals for onward transfer of this money to your account with appropriate clearance from the relevant ministries, foreign exchange departments, embassy and Board of Internal Revenue Services. At the conclusion of this business, you will be given 35% of the total amount, 60% will be for me, while 5% will be for expenses both parties might have incurred during this process. I look forward to your earliest reply @{td321td@hotmail.com} call me at this number 874 763 427980 just call as you see the number do not put South Africa code ok becouse it is a satallite number. CALL ME NOW FOR HEART TO HEART DISCUSSION. Yours truly, Dr. Tony Devon, GLOBALPHONE:874:763:427980 GLOBALFAX:874:762:427981. __________________________________________________ Do You Yahoo!? Tired of spam? Yahoo! Mail has the best spam protection around http://mail.yahoo.com

Hello Friend. As you read this, I don't want you to feel sorry for me because I believe everyone will die someday. My name is Dasuki Al-Mehmood, a merchant in Dubai U.A.E. I have been diagnosed with esophageal cancer. It has defiled all forms of medical treatment, and right now I have only about a few months to live, according to medical experts. I have not particularly lived my life so well, as I never really cared for anyone (not even myself) but my business. Though I am very rich, I was never generous, I was always hostile to people and only focused on my business as that was the only thing I cared for. But now I regret all this as I now know that there is more to life than just wanting to have or make all the money in the world. I believe when God gives me a second chance to come to this world I would live my life a different way from how I have lived it. Now that God has called me, I have willed and given most of my property and assets to my immediate and extended family members as well as a few close friends. I want God to be merciful to me and accept my soul so, I have decided to give alms to charity organizations, as I want this to be one of the last good deeds I do on earth. Now that my health has deteriorated so badly, I cannot do this myself anymore. I once asked members of my family to close one of my accounts and distribute the money which I have there to charity organization in Bulgaria and Pakistan; they refused and kept the money to themselves. Hence, I do not trust them anymore, as they seem not to be contended with what I have left for them. The last of my money which no one knows of is the huge cash deposit of $6M. (Six Million United States Dollars) that I have with a finance/Security Company abroad. I will want you to help me collect this deposit and dispatched it to charity organizations. I have set aside 10 % for you and God be with you. Please All correspondence should be directed to Dasuk-al-mehmo@excite.com Regards, Dasuki Al-mehmood Dasuk-al-mehmo@excite.com

J.T. MARTINS & ASSOCIATES LEGAL CONSULTANTS, SOLICITORS & ADVOCATES OF THE SUPREME COURT OF NIGERIA OFFICE /CHAMBER: 112, LAW BUILDING COMPLEX ,VICTORIA ISLAND LAGOS. Dear Sir/Madam SUBJECT: THINK ABOUT IT REPLY TO: j.m@mail.lawguru.com I am Barrister J.T.Martins ( S A N ), a legal Solicitor. I was the Personal Attorney and legal adviser to Late Engr. Steven Cox, a national of your country, who used to work with Mobil Oil Company Nigeria Plc. Briefly, I got your contact when I accompanied our Minister of Justice to your country recently for global council of ministers meeting .On the 21st of August 2000, my client, his wife and their three children were involved in a car accident along Port Harcourt /Benin Express Road on their way for relocation to Warri Refinary where he was transfered by the Federal Government of Nigeria. Honestly,all the occupants in the vehicle inccidentally lost their lives. Since then I have made several enquiries to your embassy to locate any of my clients extended relatives, this has also proved very unsuccessful. However, after these several unsuccessful attempts, I decided to trace his relatives over the Internet, to locate any member of his family but to no avail, hence I contacted you. I have contacted you to assist in repatriating the money and property left behind by my client before they get confiscated or declared unserviceable by the bank where these huge deposits were lodged. Particularly, the bank where the deceased had a deposit valued at about fourty Million United States Dollars (US$40,000,000)with account no.0036577899, has issued me a notice to provide the next of kin to Late Engr. Cox, or have the account confiscated within the next fourteen(14) official banking days. Since I have been unsuccessful in locating the relatives for almost one year now, I seek your consent to present you as the next of kin of the deceased, Late Engr. Stephen Cox. Since my late client is of your national and you can easily undertake the required assistance which I will provide to you answer to any question the board of the bank might ask, so that the proceeds of this account valued at fiften Million United States Dollars (US$15,000,000) can be paid to you and then you and me can share the money. 55% to me and 40% to you, while 5% should should be set aside for expenses or tax as your Government may require. I wish to remind you that whatever share I have will authomatically be invested in your country under your advise and guidiance. NOTE: that I have all necessary legal documents that can be used to back up any claim we may make. In view of the above, all I require is your honest Cooperation to enable us see this deal through. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. Please get in touch with me only through my private email:ONLY Best regards, Barrister J.T.MARTINS( S A N ) Senior Principal Partner/ Leagal Adviser to Late Engr. Cox.

Dear Sir or Madam: We are keenly interested in setting up a new factory to produce 120,000 ERW oil casings per year to meet the big market of Shengli Oilfied. Since we lack some starting-up capital, we are seeking for investments. I will give you a brief introduction to the project as follow: I. Background: Shengli Oilfield, the second largest oilfield in China and the leading company of Sinopec Corp. (http://www.sinopec.com), as well as neighboring oilfields as Dagang Oilfield, Central Plain Oilfield and Jiangsu Oilfield are potential market of ERW oil casing. It is expected that the total oil casing needed in the above area is about 400,000 tons, including 260,000 tons in Sinopec and 150,000 tons in Shengli Oilfield. To meet the great need, we plan to set up a joint venture to produce 120,000 tons of ERW casings per year in Shengli Oilfield. With good management and market outlets, we believe that this JV also has the potential to expand beyond China to other nations. II. About us Shengli Oilfield Engineering Machinery Factory is one of sub-companies of Shengli Oilfield Co., Ltd, with total assets of 267 million yuan, net assets of 170 million yuan and 2462 staff. The factory mainly produces oilfield special equipment such as beam unit, Spiral-seam submerged-arc weldedsteel pipe, sucker rod, line pipe, casing, tubing, plastic compound pipe etc. It produces 200,000 tons of line pipes, 1 million meters of strengthened plastic compound pipes, 500 beam units, 2.5 million meters of sucker rods, 12,000 tons of PP gas pipes and 50,000 tons of oil tubings yearly, and has become important pipe base in Shandong and Shengli Oilfield. Its products have entering many areas as Shengli Oilfield, Daqing Oilfield, Liaohe Oilfield, Dagang Oilfield and so on. In 2002, the sale income amounted to over 600 million yuan. The Factory holds Quality accreditations as ISO9001, API and so on. III. Content of the project It is planned to introduce Japanese technology and equipment to set up one production line with range of casing diameter from¦Õ114 to ¦Õ339.7 and produce 120,000 tons of ERW casings and delivery pipes per year. IV. Product specifications For Casing: grade of steel are J55 and N80, specification ranges from ¦Õ114 to ¦Õ339.7 For delivery: grade of steel are X52¡¢X60¡¢X70, specification ranges from ¦Õ114 to ¦Õ339.7. V. Economic Analysis The total investment in this project is 142.41 million yuan. After the completion of the project, it is estimated that the internal financial rate of return before paying tax is 24.9 percent with a payback period of 5.6 years, and the internal rate of return after paying tax is 21.8 percent with a payback period of 5.9 years. The break-even point of the project is 46.95 percent, which means the project can keep balance if the annual output amount to 42,000 tons. VI. Plans for cooperation We have set up a joint venture with Japan's Marubeni in the early of the year, with a registered capital of 57 million yuan. The capital structure is as follow: a. Shengli Oilfield Bureau of Administration 19.95 million yuan 35£¥ b. Shengli Oilfield Engineering Machinery Facotry 17.10 million yuan 30£¥ c. Dongying District State Assets Operation & Management Co., Ltd 5.70million yuan 10£¥ d. Marubeni Engineering Technology Co., Ltd 14.25 million yuan 25£¥ To meet our capital need for this project, we are now planned to increase our registered capital to 118.88 million yuan. Taking our added investment into consideration, we need another 34.68 million yuan to get the plan executed. So we are seeking a new joint venture partner who'd like to join this project and meet our capital requirement. We would like to exchange the information with the manufacturers and suppliers who are interested in this project and have discussion on raw material supply as well as jointly investing the factory establishment. And we hope we could have good cooperation in future. For additional information regarding this project, please feel free to contact us. Looking forward to your prompt reply. Sincerely yours, Tony Leung Project officer Tel: +86-546-833 9362 Fax:+86-546-832 9817 Mobile: +86-133 4505 3225 Email: tony@mpbdy.com

Foreign Exchange Department First National Bank South Africa. DR. Taofeek Marvin. taofeekmarvin@netscape.net Dear Friend, I,DR Taofeek Marvin, the Director of Bills & Exchange of the foreign Remittance Department at FIRST NATIONAL BANK SOUTH AFRICA. I got your address while searching for trustworthy individuals in various countries. In my department, we discovered an abandoned sum of $25, 5 million US Dollars in an account that belongs to one of our foreign customers who died with his family in the September 11th plane crash. Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come to our bank and claim his money because we cannot release it unless somebody applies for it as a next of kin or relative to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed relatives died in the same plane crash leaving no relative behind to claim the fund. It is upon this discovery that l and other officials in my department decided to make this business proposal to you and release the money to you as the next of kin or relative to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we do not want this money to go into our bank treasury as an unclaimed fund. The banking law and guidelines here stipulate that if such money remained unclaimed after four years, the money will be transferred into the bank treasury as unclaimed funds. The request for a foreigner as a relative for this claim is occasioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and a South African cannot claim this fund as next of kin. We agreed that 20% of this money will go to the foreign partner who will supply the foreign account, 5% will be set aside for expenses incurred during the transaction and 75% will be for me and my colleagues. Thereafter and my colleagues will visit your country for disbursement of the percentages as indicated above. If you are interested to assist in this transaction, kindly contact the writer on the above mobile number or private e-mail address. Please this transaction is risk free and you should not entertain any atom of fear as all required arrangements have been made for transfer. Yours Faithfully, DR Taofeek Marvin Bill & Exchange Director

Dear Friend, Respectfully submitted, My name is Mohammed Bello, the Assistant Manager, credit and foreign bills of UNION BANK PLC. I am writing this letter to solicit for support and assistance from you to carry out this business opportunity in my department. Lying in an inactive account awaiting liquidation is the sum of us$5million belonging to a foreign customer(Mr. Bernard Scott)with account number 14-2552004 who happens to be deceased. He died with his wife and two children in a plane crash on board the EAS BAC 111-500 flight which crashed at the recent Lagos/kano plane crash at Kano Nigeria. I got your e-mail address through an internet marketing firm while searching for a reliable and reputable person to handle this transaction. Ever since he died the bank has been expecting his next of kin to come and claim these fund, the NDIC could not liquidate the account because I have filled a motion that a next of kin wrote in to the effect. To this effect, they can not release the money unless someone applies for it as next of kin, as indicated in our banking guideline. Unfortunately he has no family member in Nigeria or Europe who are aware of the existence of the money (as he was a contractor with the federal Republic of Nigeria). At this juncture I have decided to do business with you in collaboration with officials that matter in the bank, to this effect I solicit your assistance in applying as the next of kin then the money will be released to you. As I do not want this money to go into the bank treasury as an unclaimed bill. The banking law and guideline stipulates that if such money(s) remains unclaimed for a period of time up to seven years (7yrs) the money will be transferred into the banks treasury as an unclaimed bill. Our request for a foreigner as next of kin is occasioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and a Ben noise cannot stand as next of kin. To effect the immediate transfer of the fund to you as agreed, you must apply first to the bank as the next of kin to the decease, and then we will follow up all formalities for the transaction. Note that this transaction is legal safe and 100% risk free and all modalities has been worked out for a successful transaction and all legal formalities have also been perfected. In view of this, You will be entitle for 30% of the total. Upon receipt of your reply which should be sent to mohbell@mail2world.com for confidential reason, I will send to you by fax or mail the text of the application Form, as soon as you receive the text I will further clarify you in other issues as to affect the business. Await to hear from you. Respectfully submitted, Mr. Mohammed Bello.

FROM MRS.MAUREEN WUSU. COTONOU, REPUBLIC OF BENIN Dear friend, I am a SierraLeonean by nationality, presently residing here in the Neighboring Benin republic.I got your contact from a representative officer with the Benin centre for external trade, tourism department.We therefore solicit for your assistance to grant us the all moral and technical advise that we may require to relocate/invest overseas. It is true that I had not known you before, but I have no option than to risk believing that God will not let us alone. It's my pleasure to contact you for a business venture which I and my Son, intend to establish in your country. When war erupted in Freetown, there is certain amount of money totalling USD nineteen million($19,000,000.00) which my late Husband was able to move out of Sierraleon through a diplomatic channel,with the assistance of a securities and finance company before he was assassinated by unknown persons. Now me and my son decided to invest these money in your country or anywhere safe enough outside Africa for security and political reasons. We want you to help us to secure the funds and settle it in your nominated account in your country for a joint investment purposes on the followings below. 1) Manufacturing 2) Farming and acquisition of farmlands 3) Hospitality industry As it pleases you to be of assistance to us, we will be glad to Offer to you a 15% of the total funds. We are pleased to update you that the transaction requires little administrative fees to effect the release of the funds at the securities company, this is also one reason whywe rely on your capability to assist us considering my present situation as a widow. As soon as the funds is settled in your account,2% of the total sum shall be deducted to offset every expenses which both parties must have incurred in the process of completing the project including travel and communication.Then reasonable part of the remaining 83% shall be invested on your personal advise. I await your soonest response. Feel free to contact me urgently through my son Victor who is presently seeking asylum in Europe through this email address (victor_wusu1@codehot.co.uk ) information relative to the presence/position of funds which will authorize the securities company to release to you as our partner and beneficiary. NB.The inclusion of your private telephone and fax numbers will be appreciated for effective communication between us. Thanking you in advance for honoring our request and God bless. Mrs.M.Wusu

FROM: MR. WILLIAMS SAVIMBI TELL: 27-833-515247 E-MAIL: william_savimbi2001@yahoo.com JOHANNESBURG SOUTH AFRICA Private and Confidential Dear Sir, You may be surprised to receive this letter from me since you do not know me personally. I am Mr. Williams savimbi (Jnr) the first son of MR.NKONNOH SAVIMBI, who was recently murdered in the land dispute in Zimbabwe. I got your contact through my research in the South African Chambers of Commerce & Industries for a responsible and a God fearing person who I can trust by using his personality and his bank account for this transaction. When I got your contact, I prayed over it then I decided to write to you. Before the death of my father, he deposited the sum of USD$10 Million (TENMILLION UNITDED STATES DOLLARS) in one of the private security companies, in Johannesburg South Africa as if he fore saw the looming danger in Zimbabwe. This money is protected in a big metal box and was declared to the security company at the point of deposit as precious valuables e.g.: Gold, diamond and germ stone to avoid the security company knowing that the content of the consignment deposited with them contains cash. This amount was meant for the purchase of new machines and chemicals for the farms and establishment of a new farm in Swaziland. This land problem came when Zimbabwe President MR.ROBERT MUGABE introduced a New Land Act reform, which wholly affected the rich white and some few black farmers. This resulted to killing and mob action by Zimbabwean warveterans. In fact, a lot of people were killed because of this land reform act for which my father was one of the victims. It is for this reason that my family and i who are staying in South Africa now as refugees have decided to transfer my father's money to a foreign country since the law of South Africa prohibits a person with a refugee status to operate a bank account or do any banking transaction in South Africa. As the only son of my father, I am saddled with the responsibility of seeking for a genuine foreign account where this money could be transferred without the knowledge of my government who are bent on my family. I must also let you know that this transaction is 100%risk free. If you are really capable and willing to assist me, I and my family has promised to give you 30% of the total money, 10% is for the expenses that may occur during the time of the transaction and the rest of the 70%is for me and my family for the investment in your country. Please contact me immediately with the above recommended private e-mail:william_savimbi2001@yahoo.com phone 27-833-515247 indicating your interest. Please be aware that confidentiality and urgency is very vital to this transaction. Thanks for your mutual co-operation as I expect your soonest response. Best regards Mr. Williams Savimbi

Mrs. Grace Obaseki Flat 8 Block 12 NNPC Quarters Garki Abuja Nigeria Email, graceobaseki2004@yahoo.com HELLO DEAR. I presume this letter will come to you as a surprise, but as things unfold, we will know each other better. I will start by introducing myself to you. I am Mrs Grace Obaseki, the wife of Chief Jackson Gaius Obaseki, the Managing Director, and Chief Executive, Nigerian National Petroleum orporation (NNPC). I am really sure that you will be of a good assistance after going thoroughly through this letter. For many years of marriage now between me and my husband, I have not given birth, and this has really troubled my husband. As a result of the respect given to local tradition culture and custom here in Nigeria, my husband has decided to break the marriage. With the situation of things with me now, my matrimonial home look bleak. I am been threatened daily by my husband to get out from the home. My Husband s brothers are not left out in this matter. This situation has really affected me psychologically. As at now, I am no longer Assured of a matrimonial home, hence I seek your urgent assistance and help which I know will go a long way in getting me settled finally. I want to use this opportunity to move the sum of (US$18M) into your custody for safe keeping, pending my arrival in your country. This said amount was given to my husband as gratification from some Foreign Oil Companies he helped in getting Allocation for the Drilling of Crude Oil in Nigeria. As a civil servant, he does not want to be exposed, hence he gave me this money to keep in my personal account so that he can be exonerated from the eyes of government security operatives and the Civil Service Commission (CSC) which is a body that scrutinizes the activities of all civil servants in Nigeria as checks and balances for official misconduct. Be informed that this money is not connected with drugs; money laundry, firearms and looting which I believe will put fears in you to render the required assistance needed from you and consequently withdrawing your help for security reasons. Hence the source of this said money is clean and clear. This money was deposited in my personal name, and there is no way it can be transferred telegraphically under the banking procedures which could have been the easiest, but because of monetary transfer restriction by the Federal Government of Nigeria, that is defeated. Rather I have arranged a diplomat manager to move this money out in cash to any destination where it will be easy for you to collect under diplomatic immunity. This he has assured me of. As a soon as I see your response and willingness to help as regards to this, I will furnish you on the next line of action to take, but be rest assured that this transaction is 100% risk free, and my husband will not raise any alarm because he will not like to put himself, his job and office in jeopardy, and if he does, he stands the change of loosing his job. As soon as this money is moved to you, and you confirm to me that you have received it, I will be coming to meet you up there in your country where I wish to live the rest of my life. I will be offering you 20% of this money for all your help at this time of need, while some percentages has been set aside for my Brother to complement his efforts here. Be informed that this transaction will not last more than 14 working days and it will be concluded because every arrangement has been put in place. Your negative or positive response will be highly appreciated. Yours faithfully, Mrs Grace Obaseki -------------------------------------------------- Nuevo Depósito a un mes 6% T.A.E. de ING http://ingdirect.ozu.es/ -------------------------------------------------- Correo enviado desde http://www.ozu.es

Dear Sir/Madam, I beg you to carefully go through this email and should it not meet your business or personal ethics, please accept my apologies in advance. My name is David Roberts, the Chief Executive of Private Clients & International of the Barclays Group with head office at 54 Lombard street, London EC3P 3AH. I am writing this letter to solicit for your support and assistance to carry out a project concerning a late customer of the bank by name Dr. Victor Morgan, an oil magnet and philanthropist who died on the 14th of June 2002 in the London Hospital after being involved in fatal car crash which also claimed the life of his wife and two sons. Lying in his inactive account in one of our branches is the sum of Thirty Million United States Dollars. Ever since he died the bank has placed a stop on all transactions on this account pending when his next of kin would come forward for necessary actions, identification and collection. Unfortunately from our investigations and confirmations from his attorney he has no family members who are aware of the existence of the money and as such, we have decided to do business with you. If you stand in as the beneficiary of this funds the money will be released to you, after the due processes have being followed. Obviously we do not want this money to go into the Bank Treasury because the banking law and guideline stipulates that if such fund remains unclaimed for 3 years, the money will be transferred into the Bank Treasury as unclaimed debt. This would not take too much time to get done as his lawyer already has the necessary Letters of Administration and court orders from the British high court which are part of the documents required by the Barclays bank to process fund release approvals. To do this work 75% of the money will be for our end, 20% will be for you while 5% will be for any xpenses incurred during the transaction. Please reach me at my private email address above, if willing to do business with us. Thanks and regards, David Roberts. DISCLAIMER: This message contains confidential information and is intended only for specified addressee. If you are not the named addressee you should not disseminate, distribute or copy this e-mail. The sender therefore does not accept liability for any errors or omissions in the contents of this message, which arise as a result of e-mail transmission. Please note that we reserve the right to monitor and read any emails sent and received by the Barclays Group under the Telecommunications (Lawful Business Practice) (Interception of Communications) Regulations 2000.

Dear Sir You may be surprise to receive this letter from me, since you don?t know me personally, I am Larry Amu The SON of DR Edward Amu, Who was recently murdered in the land dispute in Zimbabwe. I got your contact as I was searching for a Reliable person to handle a very confidential business which involve a transfer of fund to a foreign account and I decided to write you, my late father was among the few black Zimbabwean opposition party rich farmers murdered by the agents of the ruling Government of president Robert mugabe, for his alleged support and sympathy for the Zimbabwean opposition party controlled by the white minority, Before the death of my father, he had taken to Johannesburg and deposited the sum of thirty eight million united state dollars (U$38,000,000 with a diplomatic company in South Africa, and transfer to NETHERLAND(EUROPE), as if he foreseen the looming danger in Zimbabwe. The money was deposited in a box as valuable items (photographic material) to avoid over taxed custom clearance. These land problems arose when president Robert mugabe introduced a new land act that wholly affected the rich white farmers and some blacks vehemently condemned the ideal. This result to rampant killings and mob action by the war veterans and some political thugs, precisely more than three thousand( 3,000) people have so far been killed. Heads of government from the west, especially Britain and United States have voice their condemnation of Mugabe's plans. Subsequently, south Africa have development community(S.A.D.C)has continuously supported mugabe's new land act, I am face with the dilemma of investing this money in the Netherlands because I am not having resident permit for fear of such investment, Hence I am seeking for (political asylum) in the Netherlands, I am looking for a business person whom I can entrusted this fund into his hands for investment, I must let you know that this transaction is 100% risk free and the nature of your business does not necessarily matter. For your assistance I am offering you 30% of the sum, 65% for me and my family, while 5% will be mapped out for any expenses that we may incurred during this transaction. We wish to invest our money on commercial properties based on your advice. Finally, I will demand for assurance that you will not sit on the money when it gets to your personal account or Company account in your country, If this proposal is accepted please confirm your interest by or sending me email with this email larryamu@netscape.net Thanks. larry amu __________________________________________________________________ Get Tiscali Broadband From £15:99 http://www.tiscali.co.uk/products/broadbandhome/

National Petroleum Investment Management Services (NAPIMS) NNPC Building 38 Kingsway Road Ikoyi, Lagos Tel: 234 80 28326956 Contact: Mr Chris Ogiemwonyi – Group General Manager Email: chris4120e@k.ro I am Mr Chris Ogiemwonyi a member of the Presidential Payment Verification Committee (PPVC) of the Federal Government of Nigeria, West Africa and also a Director of Project Implementation with the NNPC. I am presently on assignment with my colleagues in the ministry of finance and the presidency carrying out routine verification of contractual claims on behalf of the NNPC I apologize for using this medium to reach you for a Transaction/business of this magnitude, but this is due to Confidentiality and prompt access reposed on this medium. In unfolding this proposal, I want to count on you, as a respected and honest person to handle this transaction with sincerity, trust and confidentiality. I have decided to seek a confidential co-operation with you in the process of actualising our dreams described hereunder. For the benefit of all parties and hope you will keep it in confidence because of the nature of this transaction within the NNPC and Ministry of Finance (FMF), where I work as Director of Project Implementation. With the cooperation of four other top officials, we have in our possession overdue payment bills which we are presently verifying, to the tune of Twenty Six Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars (US$26,500,000.) which we want to transfer abroad with the assistance and cooperation of a foreign company/individual to receive the said fund on our behalf or a reliable foreign non-company account to receive such funds. More so, we are handicapped in the circumstances, as the Civil Service Code of Conduct does not allow us to operate offshore account hence your importance in the whole transaction. This amount $26.5m represents the balance of the total contract value executed on behalf of the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation (NNPC) by a foreign contracting firm, which we the officials over-invoiced deliberately in the course of our verification exercise. Though the actual contract cost have been paid to the original contractor, leaving the balance in the tune of the said amount which we have in principle gotten approval to remit by Key Tested Telegraphic Transfer (K.T.T) to any foreign bank account you will provide by filing in an application to NNPC and the Ministry of Finance for the transfer of Rights and Privileges to the contractual sum to you/your account. I have the authority of my partners involved to propose that should you be willing to assist us in the transaction, your share of the sum would be 30% of the $26.5million, 60% for us, while 10% has been mapped out from the total sum to cover any expenses that maybe incurred by us during the course of this transfer, both locally and international expenses.. The business itself is 100% safe, on your part provided you treat it with utmost secrecy and confidentiality. Your area of specialization is not a hindrance to the successful execution of this transaction. I have reposed my confidence in you and hope that you would not disappoint me. Should you be interested or not in this transaction, please notify me through this private email: chris4120e@k.ro or to call me with the tel number above. If not also let us know, so as to enable us enough time to scout for another credible foreign partner or not to help carry out this transaction. I assure you that my partners and I are in a position to make the payment of this claim possible provided you can give us a very strong assurance and guarantee that our share would be secured and please always remember to treat this matter with the utmost confidentiality, as any form of exposure would compromise our positions in this government, being active Government Civil Servants. Once again, remember time is of great essence in this transaction. I wait in anticipation of your fullest co-operation. Yours faithfully, Mr Chris Ogiemwonyi

DEAR Friend, Please reply to "nzangamobutu@ecplaza.net" I know that this letter will come to you as a surprise considering the fact that we have not met before.May the Almighty God bless you as you read this email.I am trully looking for someone that will assist me with a business that has to do with my family estate which my late father left behind for us.i am contacting you based on the fact that i want someone that is not known to my family to assist me in this business and this is for security reasons which i will explain to you as we make progress. I am the first son of the late Joseph Desire Mobutu, the former President of "ZAIRE" now democratic republic of congo .I am presently on political asylum in Nigeria . I got your contact over the internet during my search for a person that will assist me in this business.this became neccessary as i do not want anybody known to me or my family to be associated with this money. I want you to note that this business will benefit both of us and that it is 100% risk free. However, you must confirm your ability to handle this because it involves a large amount of money. The funds "THIRTY SEVEN MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS" ($37million)is my share of my father's estate. I boxed and shipped the money to a security company abroad at the peak of the a political uprising that rocked my country few years ago. Now that the crisis has ended , I need a trustworthy person to proceed to the place of the security company in order to clear the fund and afterwards,i will come to your country for us to start a joint business venture as i do not have the intention of bringing the funds back to Africa for a very long time.Note that I will send to you the relevant documents that will enable you take possession of the fund for onward investment for our mutual benefit. All I need from you is as follows: 1. Your confirmation of your ability to handle this business for me. 2.your word that you will keep this business as confidential as possible at all times until we conclude this business. 3. Your telephone and fax numbers for communication. 4. Your full permanent address. As soon as I get the above information from you, I will disclose to you the name and the country of the security company, the contact of the diplomat that i have hired to assist us in this business,as well as your name and particulars to the security company as my representative and my partner to enable them contact you accordingly. As we make progress,i will send to you a"LETTER OF AUTHORITY" and "AGREEMENT LETTER" to enable you clear the fund on my behalf. Note that this is a very safe transaction as this funds is my share of my father's estate.Please reply to "nzangamobutu@ecplaza.net" I await your response to enable us proceed. Regards, Nzanga Joseph Desire Mobutu ___________________________________________________________________________ Mail sent from WebMail service at PHP-Nuke Powered Site - http://www.blitz-krieg.de

CONFIDENTIAL/URGENT BUSINESS PROPOSAL. Dear Friend, I am delighted to write this letter to you hoping that you will understand my predicament and answer back without hesitation. I am Dr Maryam Abacha the wife of the late Nigerian head of State General Sani Abacha. I got your contact on the internet as I was making contact for a honest foreigner who will help save my life and my children, hence our country has been frustrating us since the death of my husband. I am in possession of $25 000.000 (TWENTY FIVE MILLION U.S DOLLARS ONLY) which I want to invest in your country. For your clarification and understanding,this money in a box which my husband deposited in the finance and security company in dis-guise as a family treasure since 11th of febuary 1998, is not an ill gotten wealth rather, it was generated from my organisation FAMILY SUPPORT PROGRAM (F.S.P). I will enlighten you more of this organisation if you indicate a helping interest to secure this money on my behalf. On your acceptance to render this assistance to me,I will instruct the finance company to effect a change of ownership of this fund in your name as the bona-fide owner to enable you claim the fund from the security and finance company,also I will disclose to you the country and the name of the finance and security company where this money is being deposited. What I demand from you now is to arrange for a visit to the finance company where this money is being deposited and claim it as the bona-fide owner.It is very ideal you forward to me your private telephone and fax numbers to enable me send all relevant documents pertaining the deposit of this fund for your clarification and more understanding. Bear in mind that this transaction demands absolute confidentiality because properties and bank accounts both local and international bearing the Abacha's family name, are being ordered to be confiscated by the newly elected civilian President of Nigeria (President Olusegun Obasanjo) hence I will not want to be exposed. Let me refer you to the front page of This Day Newspapers of 10th March 2001. You can check it through their website:www.thisdayonline.com , click on archives,8th.june,2001) The present government in Nigeria had frozen and seized all my bank accounts both here in Nigeria and abroad. Thus l shall expect you to contact me urgently to enable us discuss in detail about this transaction For your knowledge, 25% of this fund $25 000.000 (TWENTY FIVE MILLION U.S DOLLARS) will be given to you if you assist me to secure this fund and another 5% has been set aside for all the expenses you might incure during the process of securing this fund.Example: TELEPHONE BILLS, HOTEL BILLS, FLIGHT BILLS and other mislenous expenses. When you must have taken the agreed percentage, you will use part of the balance to buy a living house for my family there in your country, where we shall live in the future and the remaining part will be kept for investment package also in your country which will be under your supervision. Contact me through my son (OMAR ABACHA) who recently escaped from Nigeria to Johannesboug South Africa where he is now staying as a refuge on his email address omarabacha@hotmail.com to avoid us losing this money, since it is the only remaining fund for the survival of my family. Thanks for your anticipated co-operation. Yours sincerely, MRS.MARYAM ABACHA Please for security reasons reply to my alternative email address:mrs.maryam_abacha@outgun.com __________________________________________________________________ Get Tiscali Broadband From £15:99 http://www.tiscali.co.uk/products/broadbandhome/

Dear Sir/madam, This letter might surprise you because we have met neither in person nor by correspondence, but I believe that it takes just one day to meet or know someone either physically or through correspondence. I got your contact through my personal search, you were revealed as being quite astute in private Entrepreneurship, one has no doubt in your ability to handle a financial business transaction. However, I am the first son of His Royal Majesty Pepple Y. William, the traditional ruler of Bonny province in the Oil rich area of Rivers state in Nigeria. I am making this contact to you in respect of USD45, 000,000.00 (Forty Five Million United States Dollars), which I inherited from my late father. As You may be aware that my country is the third largest oil producing country in the whole world. My father is the ruler of the richest community in Nigeria. My community produce 5.8% of the total annual Oil production in Nigeria and 0.5% of the Dollar value of each barrel is paid to my father as royalty by the Federal Government to our community. In his position as the royal head and chairman of the Bonny Oil trust fund. Foreigners often refer to his kingdom as the Gas/Oil Land. This is because the island floats atop one of the largest gas and oil deposits anywhere in the world. This explains is why the island is home to several Multinational oil companies, such as Shell, Exxon-Mobil, Chevron and one of Nigeria's most expensive ventures in recent time, Nigeria Liquefied Natural Gas Company (NLNG), these companies also offers my father a lot of gratifications as the royal father of the kingdom where they operate. Some of this money was accumulated from royalties paid to my father as compensation by the Oil firms located in our area, for hampering Agriculture which is our main source of livelihood. Unfortunately my father died from protracted diabetes. Before his death secretely he willed the sum of USD45, 000,000.00 (Forty Five Million United States Dollars) and he safely deposited this money in cash into a consignment and kept it in the custody of a security company without the security company knowing the content. I have the certificate of Deposit and any information you wish to have as a proof to show for it. My problem actually started when my stepmother said that the next king must be her son instead of me as the heir apparent to the throne. I am the first son of my father but my stepmother has used her position and influence to convince some members of the council of elders that my biological mother was not properly married to my father because my mother is not living in the palace due to some problems within the family before the death of my father. This action by my step mother is just a bid to deny me of my right, which I challenged. In the process there was confusion that divided the community into two factions. This led to a revolution by the youths and women who are solidly behind me. Consequently, my international passport was seized just to stop me from traveling outside the country. Now I need help. I need someone who will claim the fund my father deposited with the financial security company and deposit it in his/her personal account pending when I will be free again. Please, help me to salvage the only hope of survival that I now have of which my step mother and the children do not know about this money. I am in need of help to safe guide this money so as to settle down and fight for my rightful throne. Right now, I am in hiding and I do not want this money to stay much more in the security company because I don't want to incur extra cost on the deposit since I don't know how long my problem will last. If you can help me in this my time of need, I will give you 20% of the total sum, while 80% will be kept for me. I look forward to your helping me. Yours sincerely, Prince Yobo William

RESIDENTIAL ADDRESS # 16 OBIOMA STREET, G. R A, ENUGU, ENUGU STATE. NIGERIA.   ATTN: MANAGING DIRECTOR/PRESIDENT   In order to transfer (USD$56 Million Dollars) from our bank, I have the courage to ask you to look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable of this important business believing that you will not me down.   I am MR. MARTINS AKUthe eastern district bank manager of united bank for Africa plc (UBA). There is an account opened in this bank in 1980 and since 1990 nobody has operated on this account again. After intensive investigations, I discovered that if I do not find a way to get the amount in question stacked out somewhere safe urgently it will be forfeited for nothing. The owner of this account, ENGR. SMITH U. WILLIAMS, a foreigner, the manager of Petro- technical support services, a chemical Engineer by profession and he died in 1990 and no other person knows about this account or any other beneficiary. My investigations prove to me as well that this company does not know anything about this account and has no attachment to the said amount. The amount involved is 56 MILLION USD (FIFTY-SIX MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS) ONLY.   In the light of the fact, I needed your assistance to open your door to this opportunity by providing your account or any account of your choice where the fund will be remitted. I want to transfer this money into a safe foreigner’s account abroad but I don’t know any one who could actually assist, I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money can only be approved to a foreign account because the money is in US Dollars and the owner of the account ENGR. SMITH U. WILLIAMS and a foreigner too.   I know that this mail will come as surprise to you as we don’t know ourselves, but be sure that is for real. I got your contact on the believing that you will not let me down in this business. You are the only person that I have contacted for this business, so please reply urgently so that I will let you know what steps to take next. Send also your private telephone, fax and mobile number for easy communication including the full details of the account to be used for the deposit. I am contacting you because of the need to involve a foreigner with foreign account. I need your full co-operation to make this work out alright.   Your assistance as foreigner is necessary because the management is ready to welcome any person, a foreigner who has correct information of this account, which I will give to you immediately, if you are interested to conclude this transaction with me. If your are capable of handling such amount in strict confidence, keeping to my instructions I need a sincere person for this venture because I don’t want to make mistake, I need your strong assurance that this money will be intact pending my arrival in your country for sharing.   You should be informed strictly that I will burn all the documents in your presence immediately after this money has been remitted to your account leaving no trace to any place.   I will apply for annual leave immediately I hear from you that you are ready to act and receive this fund in your account. This is to enable me use my position and influence to effect legal approvals for onward transfer of this money to your account with appropriate clearance forms of the ministries and foreign exchange department.   At the conclusion of this business, you will be given 20% of the total amount, 70% will be for us and 10%for any expenses incurred during the transaction.   I look forward to your earnest reply.   Yours truly,   MR. MARTINS AKU

FROM THE OFFICE OF ENGR.EMMANUEL AZIZI. FEDERAL MINISTRY OF WORKS AND HOUSING FEDERAL SECRETARIAT OFFICE COMPLEX FALOMO, IKOYI - LAGOS. ATTN: Dear sir/madam, First, I must solicit your strictest confidence in this transaction, this is by virtue of it's nature as being utterly confidential and top secret as you were introduced to us in confidence through the Nigerian Chamber of Commerce, foreign trade division. We are top officials from the Federal Ministry of Works and Housing,(FMWH),Federal Ministry of Finance and the Presidency, making up the Contract Review Panel (CRP) set up by the Federal Government of Nigeria to review contracts awarded by the pastmilitary administration. In the course of our work on the CRP, we discovered this fund which resulted from grossly over-invoiced contracts which were executed for theFMW&H during the last administration. The companies that executed the contracts have been duly paid and the contracts commissioned leaving the sum of US$17 Million floating in the escrow account of the Central Bank of Nigeria ready for payment. I have therefore been mandated as a matter of trust by my colleagues in the panel to look for an overseas partner to whom we could transfer the sum of US$17M legally subcontracting the entitlement to your company. This is bearing in mind that our civil service code of conduct forbids us from owning foreign company or running foreign account while in government service hence the need for an overseas partner. We have agreed that the funds will be shared thus after it has been paid into your account: (1) 30% of the money will go to you for acting as thebeneficiary of the fund. (2) 10% has been set aside as an abstract projection for reimbursment to both parties for incidental expences that may be incurred in the course of the transaction. (3) 60% to us the government officials (with which we wish to commence an importation business inconjunction with you ). All logistics are in place and all modalities worked out for the smooth conclusion of the transaction within ten to fourteen days of commencement after receipt of the following information: Your company name, address, company's details & activities,telephone & fax numbers. These information will enable us make the applications and lodge claims to the concerned ministries & agencies in favour of your company and it is pertinent to state here that this transaction is entirely based on trust as the solar bank draft or certified cheque drawable in any of the Central Bank of Nigeria correspondent bankers around the world is going to bemade in your name. Please acknowledge the receipt of this letter using my e-mail address, stating your tel/fax number for further details.Yours faithfully, Engr.Emmanuel Azizi. NB: Bank Account Details not necessary as preferred mode of payment is by draft or cheque. __________________________________________________________________ Get Tiscali Broadband From £15:99 http://www.tiscali.co.uk/products/broadbandhome/

Dear friend, I am Mrs.kate koroma wife to the late john koroma from Sierra Leon. I am writing you in absolute confidence prmarily to seek your assistance to transfer our cash of($12,000.000.00) now in the custody of a private Security trust firm in Europe. the money is in trunk boxesdeposited and declared as Precious stones by my late Husband as a matter of fact the company does not know the content as money, although my husband made them to under stand that the boxes belongs to his foreign partner.Source of the money: My late Husband john koroma, a native of Mende District in the Northern province of Sierra Leone, was the General Manager of Sierra Leone Mining co-operation (S.L.M.C.) Freetown . According to my Husband, this money was the income accrued from Mining Co-operation's over draft and minor sales. Before the peak of the civil war between the rebels forces and the combined forces of ECOMOG peace keeping operation that almost destroyed my country, following the forceful removal from power of the civilian elected President Ahmed Tejan Kabbah by the rebels. My Husband had already made arrangement for I and my two children to be evacuate to Ivory coast with the CERTIFICATE OF DEPOSIT he made with a security firm in Europe through the aid of U.N evacuation team. During the war in my country, and following the indiscriminate looting of Public and Government properties by the rebel forces, the Sierra Leone mining coop. Was one of the target looted and it was destroyed. My husband including other top Government functionaries were attacked and killed by the rebels in November 2000 because of his relationship with the civilian Government of Ahmed Tejan Kabbah. As a result of my husbands's death , and with the information we got that the rebels are out for us the burden became too much for me to handle coupled with the ill health of my daugther she died in the process as i could not afford her a decent medical care.Our only hope now is in you and the boxes deposited in the Security Firm To this effect, I humbly solicit your assistance in the followings ways. 1. to assist me claim this boxes from the security Firm as our beneficiary 2. to transfer this money (USD$12M) in your name to your country 3. to make a good arrangement for a joint business investment on our behalf in your country and you, our Adviser/ Manager For your assistance, I have agreed with my only surviving son that 20% of the total amount will be for your effort and another 10 % to cover all the expenses that may incur during the business transaction, and also 10% for any charity of choice the reason I am doing this is that i never new that people are passing through such hardship like this until i find myself in the same contion. Last, I urge you to keep this transaction strictly confidential as no one knows our where about. Please as you show your willingness, Forward to us your full name, address and Tel/ Fax numbers, to me via my private email address as indicated bellow, this is for security reasons as i will only be accessing my private email earnestly awaiting your response. Thanks. May God bless you as you assist us. MRS KATE KOROMA mrskatekoroma@netscape.net

From: LUCY LOKOMBOH e-mail: lokomboh@msn.com This very confidential request should not come as a surprise to you. I am LUCY LOKOMBOH, the wife of the late L.T. Col. KABONGO LOKOMBOH, who was the Chief Security Officer to the late President Laurent Kabila of Democratic Republic of Congo, with regards to your trustworthiness and reliability, I decided to seek for your assistance in transferring some money out of South Africa into your country, for onward dispatch and investment. I will reveal to you, based on the fact that I could rely on you, the height of the crisis that led to Laurent Kabila assassination, he personally mandated and instructed my husband to create and fully equip special elite force, to protect him against the rebels then, working against his government. This instruction was very discreet and highly confidential and was backed up with the sum of US$18.000, 000.00 (Eighteen million United States Dollars) in cash, for the purchase of Arms and Ammunition from an independent arms dealer in Republic of South Africa. We brought this fund to South Africa, where he was supposed to negotiate and purchase the Arms and Ammunition. This money was transported through diplomatic means, and negotiation was still in progress when the news came to me that our President has been shot. He then quickly decided to stop all negotiations and diverted the all funds to our personal use, as it was golden opportunity. He then left the children and me and went back home to attend the funeral of Laurent Kabila where he was also killed. This money is presently deposited in a Security Company here in Johannesburg, South Africa since January 2001 although the Security Company does not know the real content of the box. We deposited it as family treasure containing Gold and Diamond. I now seek your assistance in providing an overseas account to enable me transfer this money out of South Africa, to where it can be invested. I have made all the necessary arrangement on our own side to ensure smooth remittance. However, due to my refugee status I cannot operate a bank account here, neither can I invest here in South Africa. Hence my desire is to transfer and invest in your country. Please note that your account has got to be in a position to carry that amount of money. For your assistance, after the transaction, I have agreed to give you 15% of the total sum, while the balance of 85% will be for my investment. I intend to keep my presence here in South Africa low profile due to my popularity back home, so I request all information provided to be kept secret and confidential. I am obliged to provide details immediately as soon as I receive the acknowledgement of this letter from you, indicating your interest to assist me. You can contact us with the above e-mail or preferably, through e-mail: lokomboh@msn.com Best regards, LUCY LOKOMBOH Powered by Tiscali - http://www.tiscali.co.za

>From : Barrister. Kenny Martins Kindest Attention, Firstly, not to cause you embarrassment, I am Barrister. Kenny Martins, a Papua New Guinean by Nationality, a Barrister based in the United Kingdom and the personal attorney to late Mr. Mark Michelle a National of France, who used to be a private contractor with the Shell Petroleum Development Company in Saudi Arabia, herein after shall be referred to as my client. On the 21st of April 2001, he and his wife with their three children were involved in an auto crash; all occupants of the vehicle unfortunately lost their lives. Since then, I have made several enquiries with his country's embassies to locate any of my clients extended relatives, this has also proved unsuccessful. After these several unsuccessful attempts, I decided to contact you with this business partnership proposal. I have contacted you to assist in repatriating a huge amount of money left behind by my client before they get confiscated or declared unserviceable by the Bank where this huge deposit was lodged. The deceased had a deposit valued presently at GBP30 million British Pounds Sterling and the Bank has issued me a notice to provide his next of kin or Beneficiary by Will otherwise have the account confiscated within the next thirty official working days. Since I have been unsuccessful in locating the relatives for over three years now, I seek your consent to present you as the next of kin / Will Beneficiary to the deceased so that the proceeds of this account valued at GBP 30 Milliom British Pounds Sterling can be paid to you. This will be disbursed or shared in these percentages, 70% to me and 30% to you.I have all necessary legal documents that can be used to Back up any claim will be obtained From the Court of England with the Certificate Of Deposit which has been issued to me by the Bank. All I require is your honest Co-operation,Confidentiality and Trust to enable us see this project through. I guarantee you that this will be executed under a legitimate Arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. All the relevant documents that will give you the legal backing to claim the fund will be processed. Please acknowledge receipt of this message by e-mail. As I am based in the United Kingdom. And please provide me the following below; this is to enable me commence immediate preparation of all legal document that will back up our claim. 1. Full Name 2. Your Telephone Number and Fax Number 3. Your Contact Address. Your urgent response will be highly anticipated and appreciated. Best regards, Barrister. Kenny Martins.

Dear Sir, I have a profiling amount in an excess of US$183.5M, which I seek your partnership in accommodating for me. I am willing to give out 25% of this total sum to you for your quick assistance and partnership. However, I sincerely seek your confidence in this transaction, which I propose to you as a TOP SECRET. My name is Robert Bada, i am the personal assistance to the former President of Republic of Liberia (President Charles Taylor). You most be aware that Charles Taylor has been fighting serious civil war with the Liberia United for the Restoration of Democracy (LURDS) for quite some years now. And LURDS were backed all along by some foreign powerful countries. Not quite long ago, the American government ordered President Charles Taylor to leave Liberia or be forced out of power. Knowing fully well the capabilities of America and other powerful members of the United Nations, President Charles Taylor decided on the 11th of August 2003 to go into exile in a neighboring country Nigeria to seek asylum. Based on these developments, his various foreign bank accounts have been frozen and some are still under serious investigation. But in the light of all these sad happenings, President Charles Taylor was able, through the help of some loyalist succeeded to secretly move the sum of US$183.5M, on my name as the owner to a private security company vault in Nigeria where the final crediting is expected to be carried out later. All the depositing documents of the above fund were on my name and they are still in my possession YOUR ROLE: All I need from you is to stand as the beneficiary of the above quoted sum and I will arrange for the documentation which will enable the Security Company transfer / wire the fund to your bank account. I have decided to do this only with you and use this sum to relocate to European or American continent and never to be connected to any of President Charles Taylor?s conglomerates. This transaction can be concluded in 2 weeks. URGENT: Your response is needed. I want you to call me on 234 1 7755778 for more directives information and the nest required step of how we have to make immediate move. PLEASE send your REPLY to these my private email addresses: primetimes@centrum.cz and ospectra3776@netscape.net, I will also need your private and direct telephone and fax number for easy reach. Please this is a very confidential matter, you don't disclose to anybody for us to have success. As soon as I get your positive response, I will send you more details. Best regard Mr Robert Bada

I AM DR,adophilusjaja, THE ACCOUNTANT GENERAL OF UNITED BANK OF AFRICA PLC. I REQUEST YOUR CO-OPERATION IN THE TRANSFER OF A HUGE AMOUNT OF MONEY. ON SEPT. 1996, AN OIL CONSULTANT/CONTRACTOR WITH THE KUWAIT OIL MINISTRY,MR. AHMED YOUSUF MUSTAPHA, AN IRAQ NATIONAL MADE A FIXED DEPOSIT IN OUR UNITED BANK OF AFRICA PLC. (U.B.A.). ON MATURITY WE SENT A ROUTINE NOTIFICATION TO HIS FORWARDING ADDRESS BUT GOT NO REPLY. AFTER A MONTH, WE SENT A REMINDER AND FINALLY HIS EMPLOYERS WROTE TO INFORM US THAT MR. MUSTAPHA DIED IN AN AUTOMOBILE ACCIDENT, THAT HE DIED WITHOUT MAKING A WILL WHILE OUR ATTEMPT TO TRACE HIS NEXT OF KIN THROUGH IRAQ EMBASSY PROVED FRUITLESS. WHEN HE WAS MAKING DEPOSITION IN MY BANK, HE DID NOT DECLARE HIS NEXT OF KIN IN HIS DEPOSIT APPLICATION FORM, WHEN I REMINDED HIM HE SAID HE WISHED IT SO, IN THE CONSERVATIVE MANNER OF OUR BANK, I DID NOT TURN DOWN HIS REQUEST RATHER HONOR IT CONSIDERING HIS HIGH NETWORT. THE POINT IS THAT HIS EMPLOYER ARE NOT AWARE OF HIS DEPOSIT WITH US,THEREFORE I AM THE ONLY PERSON WHO KNOW ABOUT MR .MUSTAPHA,S DEPOSIT ,WHICH IS NOW LAYING IN DORMANT ACCOUNT PORTFOLIO, THE WHOLE DETAILS RELATING TO MR.MUSTAPHA'S DEPOSIT IS ALSO WITH ME.I AM LOOKING FORWARD FOR A FOREIGNER WHO WILL STAND IN AS THE NEXT OF KIN TO MR.MUSTAPHA.I HAVE WORKED OUT MODALITIES OF ACHIEVING MY AIM BY APPOINTING YOU AS THE NEXT OF KIN TO MR.MUSTAPHA AS WELL AS TRANSFER THE MONEY ABROAD FOR US TO SHARE. I WILL USE AN ATTORNEY WHO WILL REPRESENT YOU AS THE BENEFICIARY TO EXECUTE SERIES OF AFFIDAVIT IN SUPPORT OF YOUR CLAIM INCLUDING CERTIFICATE OF ORIGIN OF THE MONEY, LETTER OF ADMINISTRATION WHICH EMPOWERS YOU AS THE SOLE TRUSTEE EXECUTOR TO THE ESTATE OF MUSTAPHA. PLEASE NOTE THAT YOU WILL NOT BE REQUIRED TO SIGN ANY TRANSFER DOCUMENT AS THE APPOINTED ATTORNEY WILL DO ALL THAT. IF YOU AGREE TO ACT AS THE NEXT OF KIN/BENEFICIARY TO ENABLE ME TRANSFER/CONVERT THE MONEY TO OUR OWN BENEFIT/USE .I WILL GIVE YOU 30% OF ENTIRE SUM 60 % WILL BE FOR ME WHILE 10% WILL BE TO TAKE CARE OF ALL UNFORESEEN EXPENSES AS WE MAY INCURE IN THE COURSE OF CONCLUDING THIS TRANSACTION AND I WILL ALSO WANT YOU TO FURNISH ME WITH YOUR FULL NAME,CONTACT ADDRESS,TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBERS RESPECTIVELY. I AM URGENTLY WAITING FOR YOUR REPLY . BEST REGARDS.DR,adophilusjaja. MY PRIVATE EMAIL ADDRESS;DR,adophilusjaja@YAHOO.COM __________________________________________________________________ Get Tiscali Broadband From £15:99 http://www.tiscali.co.uk/products/broadbandhome/

Attn: President/Ceo. STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL BUSINESS PROPOSAL RE: TRANSFER OF US$21.5 MILLION (TWENTY ONE MILLION, FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND US DOLLARS ONLY). I know this email will reach you as a surprise, but need not to worry as we are using the only secured and confidential medium available to seek for foreign assistance/partnership in a business transaction, which is of mutual benefit. I am a member of the Federal Government of Nigeria Contract Award and Monitoring Committee in the Nigeria National Petroleum Corporation (NNPC). Sometime ago, a contract was awarded to a foreign firm in NNPC by my Committee. This contract was over invoiced to the tune of US$21.5M. U.S. dollars. This was done deliberately. The over-invoicing was a deal by my committee to benefit from the project. We now want to transfer this money which is in a suspense Account with NNPC into any Overseas Account which we expect you to provide for us. SHARE: - For providing the account where we shall remit the money into, you will be entitled to 30% of the money, 60% will be for me and my partners while 10% has been mapped out from the total sum to cover any expenses that maybe incurred by us during the course of this transfer, both locally and international expenses. I would require the following: - 1. Your company's names, address telephones and fax numbers. 2. The bank where the money will be remitted to. The above information would be used to make formal applications as a matter of procedure for the release of the money and onward transfer to your account. It does not matter whether or not your company does contract projects of this nature described here. The assumption is that your company won the major contract and subcontracted it out to other companies. More often than not, big trading companies or firms of unrelated fields win major contracts and subcontracts to more specialized firms for execution of such contracts. We have strong reliable connections and contacts at the Central Bank of Nigeria, as well as the Federal Ministry of Finance and we have no doubt that all the money will be released and transferred if we get the necessary foreign partner to assist us in this deal. Therefore, when the business is successfully concluded we shall through our same connections withdraw all documents used from all the concerned Government Ministries for 100% security. We are ordinary civil servants and we will not want to miss this once in a lifetime opportunity to get rich. We want this money to be transferred to the overseas Accounts for us, before the present Democratic Government starts auditing all Federal Government owned Parstatals. Please contact me immediately through my private mailbox (tobi4120a@k.ro). If you are not, it will enable me scout for another foreign partner to carry out this deal. But where you are interested, send the required documents aforementioned herein through my above mailbox, as time is of the essence in this business. I wait in anticipation of your fullest co-operation. Yours faithfully, Mr.James Tobi

Dear Sir/Madam, Good a thing to write you, we have a proposal for you. This however is not mandatory nor are we in any manner compelling you to honor it against your wish. I am Miss Frani Korona, 18 years, and my brother Abdul Korona Junior 20 years old the daughter and son of the late Dr Abdul Korona of blessed memory. My father was a highly reputable business man He was the Director General National Gold and Diamond Mining Corporation of Sierra-Leone. It is sad to say that he passed away mysteriously in Dublin during one of his business trips, though his sudden death was linked or rather suspected to have been masterminded by an uncle of his whom he traveled with at that time. But God knows the truth! My mother died when I was just 4 years old and my brother 6 years old, and since then our father took good /special care of us. Before his death he gave to us the documents of the money he has deposited with a security company oversea in two trunk Boxes as family valuables and treasures with name of my brother as the only son (Paul John Junior) as the beneficiary. He instructed I and my brother to move out of Sierra-Leone because of his uncle and with the political crisis in Sierra-Leone. The amount is US $30 million 700 hundred thousand Dollars (Thirty million seven hundred thousand United State Dollars) we managed to escape to Abidjan, the Republic of Côte d'Ivoire through the help of my father's friend. For your information, the security Company does not know the real content of the boxes and we do not wish to let them to know until the consignments are released to you, for security reasons because they were deposited and registered as family valuables and treasures. We will like to leave Cote d'Ivoire entirely after this money has been transferred to you for investment purpose in your country because of the political crisis here in this country and mostly for the future of my brother and me. My brother is presently very sick that is why I am mailing you, because he can not go to net. Now permit me to ask these few questions: - 1. Can you honestly help us as your own daughter and son? 2. Can we completely trust you? 3. What percentage of the total amount in question will be good for you after the money is in your account? Please, consider this and get back to us as soon as possible and May God be with you. (AMEN) Thank you so much. Our sincere regards, Frani Korona / Abdul Korona Junior

FROM THE DESK OF: MRS JULLIET ABRAMS AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK HEADQUARTERS COTONOU REPUBLIC OF BENIN. I am MRS JULLIET ABRAMS, credit officer of African Development Bank. I have an urgent and very confidential business proposition for you. In June, 1998, a British Oil consultant/contractor with the West African's oil and Solid Minerals Corporation, Mr. David Van Buskirk made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at US$35,000,000.00(Thirty five Million United States Dollars only) in my branch. Upon maturity,I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the West African oil and Solid Minerals Corporation that Mr.David Van Buskirk died in an air crash along with his wife on the 31st October, 1999 in an Egyptian airline 990 with other passengers on board. On further investigation,I found out that he died without making a WILL, and hitherto, all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. Mr.David Van Buskirk was residing at No 1 Rue de Avenida, G.R.A. Cotonou, Benin Republic. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr.David Van Buskirk did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$35,000,000.00 is still sitting in my Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Laws of Benin, at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will be declared frozen and forfeited to the Benin Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kin or business partner to Mr.David Van Buskirk so that the fruits of this old man's labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address,phone and fax numbers so that the attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits that will put you in place as the next of kin or business partner. We shall employ the services of an attorney for drafting and notarization of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/administration in your favor for the transfer. A bank account in any part of the world that you will provide will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 65% for me, 30% for you and 5% for expenses incurred in the course of the transaction. We could also use an ASSET MANAGEMENT COMPANY in Europe to secure this funds and transfer to your account in your country. There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done legitimately and with my position as the credit officer guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately to my email box. Please send me your confidential telephone and fax numbers for easy communication. You should observe utmost confidentiality cum secrecy, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I will require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Awaiting your urgent reply. Thanks and regards. Mrs Julliet Abrams Direct Line: 00229 07 14 19 Alternative email address: <jullietabrams@yahoo.ca>

Dear: Good Day I know that this mail might be a surpriseing to you but do consider it as an emergency. In a nut shell, My name is Miss Funke komana 18 years old from the republic of Sierria-Leone in west Africa, now seeking for refugee in Dakar -Senegal under the(UNHCR). The only child of late Dr.Solomon komana. I am looking for someone who can take me as child I promise to be obidient to you and I will bring happiness to your life, I prayed over it and selected your name amoung two names due to it's esteeming nature and the recommendations given to me, as a reputable and trustworthy person.I can do business with,and by their recommendations I must not hesitate to confide in you for this simple and sincere business.I want you to assist me in this transaction. My late father was the managing director of Rainbow Gold and Diamond Mine company in (KENEMA)Sierra-Leone.But he was poisoned to death alongside with my mother by his business associate, On one of their outing to discuss a business deal in oversea, However, after their death I managed to stay alone and when the war broke out in my country. I escape to refugee camp in senegal with every important files of my father.He has the sum of (US$15.2M)Fiften million two hundred thousand U.S Dollars only. This amount was deposited by my late father in one of the leading Banks in outside Sierria-Leone. The deposit documents indicate me as the next of kin. Presently, I am saddled with the problem of securing a trust worthy foriegn personality to help me. I will map out 15% for you. (1) you will Stand on my behalf as the beneficiary for the claim of the inheritance from the bank since the management of the bank adviced that I should solicit for an individual or corporate organization to claim the deposit for me as they cannot release it directly to me due to my refugee status in Senegal. (2) Transfer the money over to your own country and into your possession pending my arrival to meet with you. (3)Invest and manage the money for me in a good business pending my maturity. (4) Help me secure my travelling documents to meet you as soon as my money is released to you. Furthermore,you can contact the Bank for confirmation and I will issue a letter of authorisation on your name,that will enable the bank correspond with you on my behalf.I am giving you this offers as mentioned with every confidence on your acceptance to assist me or adopt me as your Child if possible and manage the money for me. Conclusively I wish you send me a reply immediately you recieve this proposal. Until then,I remain with the best Regards Miss Funke komana __________________________________________________________________ Get Tiscali Broadband From £15:99 http://www.tiscali.co.uk/products/broadbandhome/

Dear Sir/Madam At this perceived confusion or stress may have With due respect. Sorry receiving this letter Since we have not known ourselves or met before. Despite that, I am constrained to write you this letter because of the urgency of it. By way of self introduction, I am Mrs Joy Afolabi, the wife of late Dr. Sunday Afolabi Little did I know that my Late husband used his position in the present government to influence the Nigerian government to award SAGEM S.A COMPANY (FRANCE) the contract of handing the Nigerian national identification card scheme in Nigeria of, which he and his colleagues were then offered the sum of $214 million dollars by SAGEM as bribes. Since my husband was a care-free person, he was poisoned by his colleagues so that he will not get his share of the deal and later died out of shock during his treatment abroad in Germany when he Finlay realised that his case was as a result of poison, but thank God, my husband was smart enough to have kept some wealth without letting anybody knows about it. However, since after my husband death, we have suffered maltreatment and untold hardship in the hands of my late husband's family, simply because I did not bear a male child [heir apparent] for my late husband. By tradition, all that my late husband had, [wealth] belongs to his brothers/family. And myself is to be remarried by his immediate younger brother which I vehemently refused. They have taken all that I suffered with my husband to acquire including treasures, houses and his bank particular seized by them. I wanted to escape to the United States of America [USA} with my children on exile, but again they conspired and stole my International passport and other travelling document to further frustrate me. My three daughters and I are trapped in obnoxious custom and traditional norms. Thank God, two weeks ago, I received Key Text Code from a Security Company in EUROPE, that my late husband deposited U.S $15.5 Million cash in one Security company in Europe. It has therefore become very necessary and urgent to contact someone a foreigner like you to help me receive/secure these funds overseas in a reliable bank Account presumably an empty Bank Account, if available and to help invest it on our behalf as well, while we find a way of getting out to meet with you in your country. These funds are kept with one Security Company in EUROPE to avoid detection, seizure or diversion. I have had several communication with the Director of the security company in Europe, who has express willingness to help me on meeting the company's demands. This is why I have contacted you to help save my children and I By receiving these funds on our behalf. But you need to give me Sufficient assurance that you will not divert the fund if you help me. My children and I have resolved to give you 30% of the total sum. This is all my children and I have got to live on. Please, I have reposed my confidence in you and hope you will not disappoint me. I look forward to your urgent response, including your phone/ mobile No and also your fax no for easier communication. The secret codes (e.g Pin No, Secret Access Code)for this fund are safely kept with me which I can give you as soon as you express desire to help me. Thank in advance for confidentiality and I look forward to hearing from you. Mrs. Joy Afolabi. For authenticity, Please visit this site's. http://www.dailytimesofnigeria.com/DailyTimes/2003/December/4/N29bnscam.asp http://www.dailytimesofnigeria.com/SundayTimes/2003/December/14/HowAfolabi.asp http://www.vanguardngr.com/articles/2002/c2122003.htm __________________________________________________________________ Get Tiscali Broadband From £15:99 http://www.tiscali.co.uk/products/broadbandhome/

No: 24A Idrisa Road, Baghdad.Republic of Iraq. Salam Greetings to you in the name of our Allah I am Mrs Mariam Khalifa, a devoted muslim,a new muslim convert of 56 years old after being converted from a christian family by my husband.For quite a good number of years now,I have been suffering from cancer of the breast and fibroid of the womb which has for a long time now affected my health and from all indications my condition is deteriorating by day and by my doctor's prediction I have less than six months to live. My husband who is now late was killed during the US/British attack against the president of my country (Sadam Hussain).My late husband was a member of the contract award committee of the republican ministry of petroleum and resources of Iraq under the regime of Sadam Hussein. Throughout the period of my marriage with my husband,all efforts to bear children proved abortive because of my poor state of health.My husband was a very wealthy and influential man during the post war Iraq. After his death,I inherited all his wealth since he has no other next of kin. Since it is now obvious that I may not survive my poor state of health, I have deemed it necessary to leave a legacy on Earth and give a positive account and justification of the life I lived on Earth before the Almighty Allah who will punish all those unbelivers and evil doers that murderd my husband and wants to control the Iraq oil wealth in the name of war against terrorism. This I want to achieve by committing part of this wealth in all sincerlity to fund mosques, Islamic orphanages,widows and also propagating the word of ALLAH and to ensure that the society upholds the views and beliefs of the holy Quran. The holy Quran emphasized so much on ALLAH'S benevolence and this has encouraged me to take this bold step hence the reason for taking this bold decision, I know that afterdeath, i will be with ALLAH the most beneficent and the most merciful. Please, note that this sum(us$12.4 Million) was securely deposited in a security/financial company overseas in my name by my husband . I have highlighted my attorney on the said sum and all the possible assistance he wouldrender to you on the documents covering the money so as to enable you receive it as I cannot follow it up because of my ill health.Presently, my attorny is in on assylum as he is also wanted by the American/British coallision forces in Iraq. I will also issue you a letter of authorization to anable the money be paid into your account.I want you and the Muslim community where you reside to always pray for me,My happiness is that i lived a life of a true devoted muslim worthy of emulation. Lastly, I honestly pray that this money when remitted to you will be judiciously used for the said purpose and you will take 10% as a compensation for your assistance in carrying out these humanitarian services. Whoever wants to serve ALLAH must serve him in truth and in fairness. Please always be prayerful all through your life. Any delay in your reply will give me room to source for a muslim organisation or a devoted muslim for this same purpose.Until I hear from you, my dreams will rest squarely on your shoulders. May the almighty ALLAH continue to bless you. Best regards. Mrs. Mariam Khalifa,

FROM THE DESK OF MR MUSA ZONGO. BILL AND EXCHANGE MANAGER. FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPT. BANQUE DEVELOPPEMENT DU AFRICAINE-ADB ANNEXE. REPUBLIC OF BENIN-COTONOU. PHONE +229 683 625. GOOD DAY. I am MR MUSA ZONGO,the Manager in charge of BILL AND EXCHANGE DEPT UNIT of BANQUEDEVELOPPEMENT DU AFRICAINE-ADB ANNEXE. COTONOU-REPUBLIC OF BENIN with due respectand regard. I have decided to contact you on a business transaction that will be beneficialto both of us at the end of the transaction. During our investigations and Accounting auditing in this bank, my department cameacross a very huge sum of money belonging to a deceased person who died withhis entire family on FEBRUARY 14,2002 in an AUTO CRASH along BURKINA FASO/LOME-TOGOEXPRESS WAY in WEST AFRICA and the fund has been dormant in his account withthis Bank without any claim of the fund in our custody eit her from his familyor relation before our discovery to this development. Although personally, I keep this information secret within myself to enable thewhole plans and idea be Profitable and successful during the time of execution.The said amount was us$14M (Fourteen million united states dollars). As it may interest you to know, I got your contact informations through south africannetwork online programme and after i prayed for GOD'S devine mercies,i decidedto contact you over this enterpresing transcation that both of us must benefitsfrom this business of such magnitude without any problem. Meanwhile all the whole arrangements to put claim over this fund as the bonafidenext of kin to the deceased,get the required approval and transfer this moneyto a foreign account has been put in place ,futher directives and needed informationswill be relayed to you as soon as you indicate your interest and willingnessto assist me and al so benefit your self to this great business opportunity. In fact I could have done this deal alone but because of my posi tion in this countryas a civil servant, we are not allowed to operate a foreign account and wouldeventually raise an eye brow on my side during the time of transfer because Iwork in this bank. This is the actual reason why it will require a second party or fellow who willforward claims as the next of kin with affidavit of trust of oath to the Bankand also present a foreign account where he will need the money to be re-transferredinto on his request as it may be after due verification and clarification bythe correspondent branch of the bank where the whole money will be remitted fromto your own designation bank account. May I at this point emphasize that this transaction is 100% risk free as I havemade arrangements for a successful deal before contacting you. On smooth conclusion of this transaction, you will b e entitled to 25% of the totalsum as gratifications,while 5% will be set aside to take care of expenses thatmay arise during the time of transfer and also telephone bills, while 70% willbe for me . Please, you have been adviced to keep top secret as i'm still in service and intendto retire from service after we conclude this deal with you. I will be monitoring the whole situations here in this bank until you confirm themoney in your account and ask my entire family and me to come down to your countryfor subsequent sharing of the fund according to percentages previously indicatedand further investments, either in your country or any country you advice usto invest in. All other necessary informations will be sent to you when I hear from you.I suggestyou get back to me as soon as possible via telephone and also through this email,statingyour wish in this deal. Yours Faithfully. MR MUSA ZONGO. phone +229 68 3625. Alternative Email musa.zongo@caramail.com

Attention, RE: TRANSFER OF US$48.223 MILLION [Strictly confidential] I am Mr.Kemass mcdonald , the operational manager in account management section in charge of credit and foreign bills of one of the prime banks here in South Africa. I am writing in respect of a foreign customer of my bank who perished on EGYPTIAN Boeing 737 PLANE CRASH into the red sea with the whole passengers on board. He opened an account in this bank and died without a written or oral WILL attached to the account. Since his death, I personally watched to see the next of kin but all has proved abortive as no one has come to claim his funds and no other person knows about this account or anything concerning it. The account has no other beneficiary and until his death he was the manager of his company here in South Africa. The amount involved is 48, 223,000.00 USD. [Forty eight million, two hundred and twenty three thousand United States Dollar]. We will start the first transfer with $8,000,000.00[Eight million]. Upon conclusion without any disappointment from your side, we shall re-apply for the transfer of the remaining balance. THIS TRANSACTION IS 100% RISK FREE and should be treated with utmost secrecy and confidentiality. Furthermore, your area of specialization or country of origin is not a hindrance to the success of this transaction. We are presently affected by the South Africa Civil service code of conduct laws that prohibits civil servants from operating private foreign accounts. I have discussed this issue with the Bank Manager who I must involve for a smooth and successful transfer of the fund to any account, which you will provide. However, I want you to act as the next of kin to the deceased by providing your bank account where the fund will be transferred for immediate investment on any viable project. The banking ethics here does not allow such fund to stay more than 2 years without claim hence the fund will be recalled to the government treasury as unclaimed fund after this period of dormancy. I got your contact through my personal search to see if you can assist by providing your safe bank account for the transfer or find a reliable person capable of receiving such amount in his or her personal account. At the conclusion, 65% of the fund will be for me. 20% for you, 10% for charity both in Africa and in your country and the remaining 5% will be set aside for expenses both parties might incurred during the transfer process. Kindly e-mail, fax or call me as soon as you receives this email. You should also include your private fax and phone numbers for easy communication. Respectfully yours, Mr.Kemass mcdonald Most confidential contact information: private:e-mail: kemass_200md@fastermail.com Tel: 874 - 76 - 3648313 Fax: 874 - 76 - 3648315 Find local movie times and trailers on Yahoo! Movies. http://au.movies.yahoo.com

MANAGER:Mr JOHN DUF AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK.(ADB) DAKAR-SENEGAL.Branch. Email:johnduf1@post.cz Tel: +221-5124859 I know this email will reach you as a surprise, but need not to worry as i am using the only secured and confidential medium available to seekfor foreign assistance in a business.I am Mr JOHN DUF from the AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK.(ADB), DAKAR-SENEGAL.Branch. This business request may seem strange, but I crave your indulgence and pray you view it seriously as I am convinced that you would be capable to provide me with a solution to a money transfer.On June 6, 1999, an America Oil consultant/contractor with Petroleum Corporation, Mrs. Barbara .A. Bill made a numbered time (fixed) deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at US$10,500,000.00(TEN Million Five Hundred Thousand Dollars )in my branch upon maturity. I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the Petroleum Corporation that Mrs. Barbara .A. Bill and har husband and their only son. died in the plane crash On October 31, 1999, (an Egyptair Boeing 767 Flight 990) with other passengers on board as you can confirm it yourself via the website below:http://www.marsearthconnection.com/ea990.html On further investigation, I found out that she died without making a WILL and attempts to trace har next of kin were fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mrs. Barbara .A. Bill did not declare any next of kin or relations in all his official documents,including his bank deposit paperwork in my bank. This sum of US$10,500,000.00 and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it According to AFRICAN law, at the expiration of (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the SENEGAL Government if nobody applies to claim the fund.Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand as the next of kin to Mrs. Barbara .A. Bill so that the fruit of this old woman's labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt Government officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full name and address so that the Attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits which will put you in place as the next of kin.We shall employ the service of two attorneys for the drafting and notarization of the WILL and obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate administration in your favour for the transfer. Any bank account in any part of the world which you will provide will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin.The money will be paid into your account for us to share in ratio of 60% for me and 30% for you and 10 % will be set aside for expenses incured during the business . There is no risk at all; the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and my position as the Branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately via the private email address below, upon your responses, I shall provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please observe utmost confidentiality and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country.Please upon the receipt of this mail message, send to me the following to enable me start the processing of the fund transfer into your bank account(:1) The beneficiary's name(.2.) Your private / official telephone and fax number. Awaiting your Urgent Reply via my private email:johnduf1@post.cz and johnduf2320021@mail2world.com or call me on my private telephone number: +221-5124859 Thanks and God bless, Mr JOHN DUF MANAGER: AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK.(ADB) DAKAR-SENEGAL.Branch.

Dear Sir/Madam, Compliments of the season. It is indeed my pleasure to write to you this letter, which I believe you will welcome it . Mr Edward Govou, the manager,credit and foreign bills of Eco Bank du Benin-Rep. I am writing in respect of a foreign customer of my bank who perished Eygptian Air Flight with the whole passengers aboard on 31st oct 1999, Since the demise of this our customer,I personally as watched with keen interest to see the next of kin but all has proved abortive as no one has come to claim his fund of $4.250m[Four Million Two Hundred and Fifthy Thousand Dollars ]in a dormant account which has been with my branch for a very long time. You are advice to receive this fund in to your bank account since there no person to aply to receive this fund as the next of kin.this transaction is LEGAL AND LAGITIMATE.There after I and my collegues will visit your country for disbursment.All the important document in this will be send to you to proved. On this note, I decided to contact you to be the next of kin as no one has come up as his relation and the paying department has been look for theoriginal next of kin to the deceased that died. And the country law here does not allow such money to stay more than Five years, for the money will be recalled to the gvernment treasury as unclaimed after this period. Upon the receipt of the required bellow of your information response, I will send to you the application form in which you fill and aply for the release the to you,and the bank's contact information regard to this transaction. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this is 100% free and you should not entertain any fear as all modalities for fund transfer can be finalized within six banking days, after you apply to the bank as a original relation to the deceased. There after I will fly down in your country for disbursment according to the percentages in claiming of the deposits and its transfer to your position, we shall share the funds in the mutual understanding as we agreed . When you receive this letter, kindly send me an e- mail signifying your good decision TO RECEIVE THIS FUND PEACEFULY. And also forward to me the requied information as to be the original bebeficiary to transfer the fund in your name and favour . YOUR FULL NAME. YOUR ADDRESS. YOUR BANKING DETAIL INFORMATION WERE YOU WANT THIS FUND TO BE TRASFERED. YOUR DIRECT MOBILE PHONE/FAX NUMBER FOR COMMUNICATION . Upon receive all these I forward your information required to the paying department enable them recorganise you as well i will send to you a text of application inwhich you will fill and apply for the immediately realsed of this fund as original NEXT OF KIN.Also I will like you to treat this transaction with the utmost secrecy because of my position in this bank. oping for a very successful business relationship and benefit with you.urgently contact me through the above vai email or at bgovou@hotmail.com Respectfully submitted, >From Mr Edward Govou. ------------------------------------------ Use o melhor sistema de busca da Internet Radar UOL - http://www.radaruol.com.br

Hello Sir, I am Mr Ahmed Ali,a member of the Movement For Democratic Change in Zimbabwe... my party is opposed to the Zanu-PF party of the incumbent President Robert Mugabe.I went into a partnership with a white farmer and a buisness man in Zimbabwe and as we progressed in buisness,i bought his ideas and philosophy which made me join the movement for democratic change which is dominated by the whites(of which my colleague is a top member). We control a greater portion of the white-dominated farms in Zimbabwe and we are major shareholders in major companies in Zimbabwe.The Mugabe government and his political associates are not tolerant with the activities of the movement for demcratic change and he is using indirect guerilla war tactic to oppress the members. Zimbabwe war veterans invaded our farm and confiscated some of our assets and held us hostage.I managed to escape from their brutality but my buisness partner died on the struggle.He left message that i should sell off all our assets including the farms,estates and the companies ensuring that his family relocates oversea and also to invest the money propperly bearing in mined that the next step of the guerillas will be to confiscate those remaining assets. I have successfully sold off the remaining portion of our estate , companies and farms after which i managed with the help of the immigration to sneak out of zimbabwe with my friend's family to Dubai,so right now we are in Dubai(UAE).The total sum in our possession at this moment is US$14M(fourteen million) realised from the aution sales of the estate ,farms and companies.The money is secured in a security company. I got to know you from your country's buisness journal in johannesburg world trade center(WTC)and from my careful analysis i realized that you could assist in this venture.All i want u to do is to make urgent arrangement and come down to Dubai so that you could open a non-resident account which will use in transfering the money into your nominated account overseas for onward investment. I have two options for you,the first is that you could choose to have a certain agreeable percentage of the money for nominating your account for this transaction,the other is you could as well go into a joint business partnership with me for proper investment of the fund in your country. Which ever way you want it,feel free to notify me.I have also mapped out %5 of the money for all kinds of expenses incured in the process of the transaction and if you don't prefer joint partnership,i am offering you %20 of the fund while the rest %75 will be for my investment. Pls contact me immidiately so we can proceed in details. Email: aali503h@yahoo.co.uk </ym/Compose?To=aali503h@yahoo.co.uk> Thank you for your coperation. Mr. Ahmed Ali. .

Dear Madam/Sir, I greet you in the Name of GOD. I am MRS REBECCA ATKINS from South Africa. I am married to Late MR SMITH ATKINS of blessed memory who was an oil explorer in Kuwait and Brunei for fifteen years before he died in the year 2000. We were married for twelve years without a child. He died after a brief illness that lasted for only four days. Before his death we were both devoted to our God and respect other who serve him. Since his death, I too have been battling with both Cancer and fibroid problems. When my late Husband was alive he Deposited the sum of $18.5million (Eighteen Million, Five Hundred thousand U.S Dollars) with a Deposit Company in Europe.the money is deposited as Family Valuables/Treasure for security reasons. Recently, my doctor told me that I have only six months to live due to my cancer problem, and this lead to a stroke attack which bother me most though because I cannot move as I use to. Having known my condition I decided to entrust this fund to either a philanthropic organization or devoted individual that will utilize this money the way I am going to instructs herein.30% of the US$18.5million goes to you to ensure that you are prepared for the task ahead, 60% of this money will be used in all sincerity to fund philanthropic organization, orphanages, widows and 5% will go to the family Attorney who will prepare the Authorisation and the balance 5% sent to me to at least prepare for my funeral and off-set my medical bills. I am taking this decision because I don't have any child or devoted relations whose behavior has left much to be desired while I am ill and above all I don't want a situation where this money will be used in an UnGodly manner,hence this bold decision. Since my health is Retrogressing by the minute, you will have to send your POSTAL ADDRESS, CONTACT PHONE NUMBER AND FAX and a little details about yourself, because I got your address from the internet after a thorough search. As soon as I receive this information from you I will make arrangement to prepare the Authorization through the family Attorney for you to get Possession of the Deposit. As soon as I receive your reply to my confidential email address. reb_atkins01@cotas.net and the authorization is given to you by me, I will give you the name and contact of the Deposit company where the money was Deposited in Europe, for claims to the consignment. Until I hear from you, I pray that this letter bring you and your family good tiding while my dreams to help humanity rest squarely on your shoulders. May the Almighty God continue to guide and protect you. Remain Blessed, MRS REBECCA ATKINS. NOTE; All replies should be forwarded to my confidential email address: reb_atkins01@cotas.net ----------------------------------------- Internet gratis en: http://www.free.com.pe Americatel Internet Free Tu conexión Free más rápida

From: Sizu Zamba (Esq). Solicitors, Corporate & Property Consultants. South Africa. Dear Sir, I hope this meets you in good well. My name is Sizu Zamba (Esq). a legal practitioner and Attorney to late Mr. Ziya Bazhayev who died in the plane crash of Yak-40 jetliner on March 9, 2000. You may follow the Link below to read about the Plane Crash my client lost his life: http://www.amarillonet.com/stories/031500/usn_LA0703.001.shtml & http://news.1chinastar.com/ll/english/61934.shtml My late client was an influential wealthy businessman, a Russian Contractor in my Country and a Russian big time Oil dealer and the Principal owner of Oil Alliance Company and he left behind a deposit of Twelve Million, Two Hundred Thousand United States Dollar ($12,200,000.00USD) in his domiciliary bank account in a commercial bank here in South Africa. Which is one of the main reasons it has been very important to locate his next of kin. I have employed every method to locate any of my clients extended relatives but this exercise has proved unsuccessful. After the death of my client his bankers contacted me, as his Attorney to provide his next of kin who should inherit his fortune. The director of remittance of his bank adopted a resolution and I was mandated to provide his next of kin for the payment of this money or forfeit the money to the bank as an abandoned Estate. The bankers had planned to invoke a clause in the property Act, to confiscate the funds after the expiration of a period given to me. I am convinced that you may be able to act in locus for my late client as his next of kin, I therefore, decided to contact you with these facts before me. By virtue of my brief and my closeness to the deceased, I am very much aware of my client's financial standing and the bank account he operates here in my country. I have reasoned very professionally and I feel it will be legally proper to present you as the next of kin of my deceased client and the sole beneficiary of his estate, so that you are be paid the funds left in his bank account, hence I contacted you. I seek your consent to present you as the Next of Kin; the bank needs only the facts as presented legally. The rest is between you and I and with my guide we can have the money paid into your account, once this is done we shall both share the funds. 50% to me and 40% to you, while 10% should be for Expenses or Taxes as may be required. I shall assemble all the necessary Legal Documents that will be used to back up our claim. All I require is your honest cooperation to enable us see this deal through I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any Breach of law. Please get in touch with me. Best Regards, Barrister Sizu Zamba (Esq). N/B: PLEASE FORWARD YOUR RESPONSE TO MY PRIVATE EMAIL BOXT AT sizuzamba@spinfinder.com

Good day, Please permit me to contact you through this medium. My name is Dr.Hilary Colsman, solicitor to the great Yengeni family in South Africa. Recently, my client's wife Mrs. Susan Yengeni took my attention to the wide use of her husband's name by some impersonators/Scam artist to defraud foreigners, claiming to be related to the family. Incase you had received such email before now, from anyone else, please ignore the email and desist from it now. She also revealed to me about her husband's funds that is been deposited in a bank in my country. For your information: Her husband, Mr. Tony Yengeni was arrested and charged to court for a multibillion dollar arms deal fraud, which was politically motivated by his enemies as her husband was the chairman of parliament in South Africa and the former chief whip of the ruling political party. We had pleaded guilty in exchange for his acquittal on corruption charges but were later convicted on trumped-up charges. This led to his bank accounts in my bank and abroad being frozen. Now, as a matter of urgency, we need your assistance in the remittance of the discovered funds abroad. The funds are currently deposited with a bank in South Africa, which I will disclose to you upon my receipt of your favorable response and consent in this deal. The amount is US$22.5 Million United States Dollars, which was deposited by Mr. Tony Yengeni before his arrest. At the moment, the account is on Dormancy, because no one has been operating the said account since his arrest. All the account details and documents where also brought to me by his wife. I hope you understand. You can find more about her husband?s predicaments at the following websites: http://www.polity.org.za/html/govdocs/pr/2001/pr1003b.html http://www.go.za/projects/procurement/yengeni.htm http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/1577682.stm http://www.hsf.org.za/focus22/focus22ethics.html http://www.hinduonnet.com/thehindu/2001/10/06/stories/0306000k.htm http://www.armsdeal-vpo.co.za/articles00/govt_reserves.html http://www.ifp.org.za/Releases/190303apr.htm Let me assure you that this transaction is 100% risk free. From my discussion with her, she has agreed to give you a reasonable percentage of the money for your assistance, which will be negotiated and agreed on by both sides. I am obliged to assist this lady knowing that she has a limited knowledge in the business world. I will need from you a mutual understanding and then we shall make plans of how the funds would be secured into an account in your name. More so, Thanks and God bless you for your understanding. Please do not forget to email me your private telephone number so that I can give you a call to discuss this matter if you are interested in this proposal. Awaiting your reply via email. Best regards. Dr. Hilary Colsman